Chapter 1415 - One Step, One Blade, One Kill

Huang Shaotian, without a doubt, was the busiest person on the field right now.

Ye Xiu and Fang Rui’s combined offensive wasn’t something that anyone in the entire Glory scene could deal with without struggle, and Huang Shaotian also had to guard against possible attacks from other characters.

Happy’s Ghostblade One Inch Ash hadn’t made any moves since unleashing that Ice Boundary. However, this just made things more scary. With Huang Shaotian on guard, if he struck once more, then Huang Shaotian would definitely be able to lock onto his position and deal with him. However, if he refused to strike, then he could be anywhere. No matter where Huang Shaotian had his character go, he had to carefully be on guard for a ghost boundary.

There was also Wei Chen’s Windward Formation.

Where were they? Huang Shaotian had no idea. A message sent into the chat wouldn’t reveal anything about a character’s position. Warlocks were talented at CCing. In the current situation, if Troubling Rain was hit by a Warlock’s CC, then he would certainly be wiped out. Thus, these characters that weren’t in sight were also the ones that Huang Shaotian had to watch out for the most.

Two in hot pursuit, two hidden away, and they didn’t even know if the fifth character was a Launcher or a Cleric. It seemed like Happy was set on making sure Huang Shaotian failed in his reconnaissance on them, patiently stalling with him.

Twenty percent of Troubling Rain’s health had already been chipped away. Against the team of Ye Xiu and Fang Rui, no one in the Alliance could deal with them without taking any damage. Huang Shaotian ran even as he fought, but he didn’t find any sign of Happy’s three other members. Instead, he gained a far better understanding of the surrounding terrain.

Playing hide and seek with me, huh?

Huang Shaotian was certain that Happy’s other members were around here, just hidden. These ambushers would only shine when the rest of Blue Rain arrived. Huang Shaotian purposefully exposed an opening under the Ye Xiu and Fang Rui’s joint assault, taking a huge risk to try and tempt the other three into acting. However, Happy’s members managed to resist this temptation.

There was no point in continuing like this! If his attention slipped even just for a moment, he might be wiped out by these two. To stall them, Huang Shaotian had broken through the limits of his focus and was already beginning to feel himself on the verge of slipping. No one had infinite focus. Having to deal with a joint assault from two All-Star players while also keeping an eye out for attacks from hidden assailants… the fact that Troubling Rain was still alive, was already pushing past the limits of Huang Shaotian’s ability!

Unfortunately, even now, Huang Shaotian still hadn’t managed to figure out anything. He was being overwhelmed, and Happy was too well prepared.

It seemed like they wouldn’t be able to use Happy’s tactics against them anymore. It was quite a shame. However, if he tried to lure them to where Blue Rain was waiting, would they fall for it? Just these two were extremely sharp players!

Huang Shaotian kept his eyes locked on the two characters in front of him. If this continued, he would be wiped out. He had maintained a defensive stance, struggling even as he made it seem like he was trying to run. Putting on airs like this wouldn’t get him any information about how decisively these two had locked onto him. However, if he really tried to run now, would he succeed?

Huang Shaotian had been feeling rather exhausted, but now excitement once again burned within him.

He enjoyed finding those infinitesimal opportunities in the most dangerous of situations and then personally expanding on such a possibility. That sort of rush was the best kind of rush.

Then…

Formless Phantom Blade!

Troubling Rain’s wrist flicked, suddenly activating a powerful skill.

Stalling, testing, reconnaissance, but at the same time, Huang Shaotian was also making preparations. He was creating the illusion of having no way to fight back, hiding the opportunities he had in order to secure an escape route for himself. Yet, he was up against two old opponents who were very familiar with his style. It wouldn’t be easy to keep his intentions hidden from both of them at once.

Then, could he do it?

It was time for him to see.

Huang Shaotian was practically vibrating with his excitement, you could even say that this was exactly what he had been eagerly anticipating, the moment where he would break through the barrier the two had created and successfully escape.

Sword light flashed.

And this powerful skill was, in fact, activated while Troubling Rain was sprinting forwards.

This was like shooting a target while on the move, and it made the mechanics and control of the blade even more complex. Ye Xiu and Fang Rui were both experienced veterans; they wouldn’t retreat in fear of the power of a high leveled skill. They would look for openings, waiting for an opportunity to strike. So no matter how challenging the situation, their mechanics wouldn’t waver.

Wavering meant defeat.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Arc after arc of elegant sword light flashed through the air, crisscrossing and descending upon Lord Grim and Boundless Sea.

One step and how many blades?

Many were focused on this.

Executing Formless Phantom Blade while on the move wasn’t a technique unique to Huang Shaotian, and the way people judged skill with this technique was by how many blades per step.

Some people could execute three blades per step, some four and a few five, or somewhere between these numbers.

In reality, a higher number didn’t necessarily mean more skilled, because this wasn’t a competition of hand speed, but efficiency. The ideal effect of a mobile Formless Phantom Blade was one step, one kill.

That’s right.

One step, one kill, that was the true goal of this technique. The executed number of blades per step was just a way to accomplish that. If a single blade could complete this kill, then that would be the best. The less blades used, the more blades there were to continue the next step, the next kill.

One Step, One Blade, One Kill.

That was the highest realm one could reach for this technique.

Then with one of Troubling Rain’s steps, how many blades did he need to accomplish one kill? That was what everyone was focused on.

Six blades!

Troubling Rain had executed six blades on the first step! His hand speed was admirable, but using six blades wasn’t all what impressive.

It wasn’t impressive, but it was understandable.

He was fighting one against two, and against Ye Xiu and Fang Rui as well. In reality, being able to accomplish this one kill was already impressive enough.

One kill naturally didn’t mean a one-hit-KO. It simply meant to strike and successfully deal damage to an opponent with this step, or force them back. Either would count as a kill.

There was no way Ye Xiu and Fang Rui would so easily sustain damage in a two on one. Lord Grim and Boundless Sea both chose to retreat, but it was a feigned retreat!

These two tricky bastards.

Huang Shaotian saw through it immediately, so when everyone had thought Troubling Rain was executing six blades in this one step, he added another two.

One step, eight blades!

This record was rather appaling. Formless Phantom Blade was usually ten blades max for each execution of the skill, and now Troubling Rain had already executed eight blades. How could this even count as the One Step, One Blade, One Kill technique? He was just standing there and spamming DPS!

Normal players wouldn’t understand the importance of these two blades. Ye Xiu and Fang Rui were both purposefully exposing openings, trying to bait him. Yet it was with these two blades that Huang Shaotian managed to cover up his openings and fully complete his one step, eight blades.

Continue!

Troubling Rain advanced again!

One step out and two more blades after the previous two.

One step, two blades, one kill!

That step was truly impressive. Though it was two blades, there was no point nitpicking at that. Huang Shaotian was against two opponents after all! Maybe for others one step, one blade was enough, but he needed two blades. It was far too unfair to ask him to fight off two opponents with one blade.

After one step came another.

After two blades, came another two.

Twelve blades!

Many people were keeping careful count.

Currently, for Formless Phantom Blade, Liu Xiaobie held the record at fifteen blades. Normal pros could usually reach thirteen blades, which meant that after the twelve blades should come the finishing blow. However, Huang Shaotian’s situation wouldn’t give him the opportunity to execute this finishing blow.

The last blade was the strongest, but after this blade, there was a long ending lag, too long for him. Huang Shaotian wasn’t in a good position right now, so he didn’t dare do something with such a long ending lag. This final blade of Formless Phantom Blade was something he couldn’t afford to execute in his One Step, One Blade, One Kill. So that would mean that the path Troubling Rain had cut out for himself with each blade ended here. However, it didn’t seem like the two characters he was facing had retreated enough!

So, it wasn’t finished yet!

One step, two blades, one kill!

Fourteen blades!

It was only one blade away from Liu Xiaobie’s record of fifteen, but this was during movement, during One Step, One Blade, One Kill. It needed sharper judgement and more mechanics, yet Huang Shaotian had completed fourteen blades under these circumstances.

Even though it was Happy’s stadium and Happy’s fans, they couldn’t help but admire Huang Shaotian. Getting half his health smashed by a tree wasn’t enough to erase the fact that he was still a top God!

Break through!

With Formless Phantom Blade’s One Step, One Blade, One Kill technique, Huang Shaotian had managed to break through Ye Xiu and Fang Rui’s harassment. Since he didn’t execute the finishing blade, there wasn’t an ending lag. Troubling Rain’s Ice Rain swung, about to execute a Triple Slash and escape, yet that was when a message popped up in the global chat.

“You guys are worthless! You got shook off like that?”

Windward Formation, Wei Chen!

Was he going to strike?

Huang Shaotian’s heart thudded. Wei Chen’s message was timed too well; it was clear that he had been attentively watching the situation over here. That meant that Windward Formation’s attack was probably already on its way over by now, right? This Triple Slash might just be slashing right into their trap!

Huang Shaotian made this immediate judgement when the message appeared and this Triple Slash’s path was forcibly turned away from the perfect arc he had planned out, swerving and making a Z shape.

Woosh!

A dark purple light flashed by out of nowhere, curling around the air – the head of the light merging with the tail – and then vanishing.

Huang Shaotian’s heart pounded from the close call. That was the Warlock’s Binding Curse. If it wasn’t for his quick reaction, Troubling Rain would’ve been tied up by that.

“What do you mean? We purposefully gave you a shot at him, y’know?” In the chat, Fang Rui replied to Wei Chen.

“Look at what wonderful people we are, giving you a chance to show off in front of your disciple. Where’s your gratitude?” Ye Xiu added.

“Fine, thank you, you dumbasses,” Wei Chen retorted.

The audience watched on, dumbstruck. Happy’s in-team atmosphere… was quite something.

Chapter 1416 - Aid

So in the end, did Ye Xiu and Fang Rui fail to stop Huang Shaotian, or did they purposefully lead Huang Shaotian into Wei Chen’s attack range?

Pan Lin looked at Li Yibo; Li Yibo looked at the sky.

Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, and Wei Chen’s trash talking had completely disrupted his judgement. He rarely dared to make comments on Happy’s actions, and now he was even more afraid to speak up.

It wasn’t just the commentator and guest whose judgements were disrupted, but also Huang Shaotian himself.

Was it a trap?

No matter how confident someone was, they would inevitably have such uncertainties at times like this. The path he had planned out for Triple Slash immediately became foggy. If Windward Formation was hiding there, then Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash or Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain might be ready to ambush him too.

Would a ghost boundary suddenly appear in front, or would cannonfire envelop the area?

Huang Shaotian, the expert opportunist, conducted himself resolutely, but in this moment, he began to hesitate.

However, there was no other way out.

Ye Xiu and Fang Rui were closing in from behind, so no matter what was waiting for him ahead, he had to try.

In that moment, Huang Shaotian understood that he had probably really fallen into their trap, or perhaps he had made a move that forced his opponents to move their pieces. Either way, he wasn’t in a good situation at all.

It seemed like he’d have to wait and see if there was an opportunity to act!

Triple Slash continued forth, Troubling Rain’s form merging with the sword light around him. However, Huang Shaotian couldn’t solely focus on the path ahead, because the two behind him both had ranged skills, so Huang Shaotian had to make sure to guard his own back as well.

He turned around. Speak of the devil!

Boundless Sea raised his hands, forming a loose grab. This was the position for Cloud-Grasping Fist.

As a Blade Master, Huang Shaotian had no way of interrupting it, and it wasn’t going to be easy dodging Cloud-Grasping Fist at this range. The Cloud-Grasping Fist’s qi energy had yet to fully form. Everything could only be determined from the moment the skill was fired. In that moment, the Qi Master would have to use their hands to form the skill, and that was also when the direction of the Cloud-Grasping Fist would be locked.

As for Lord Grim? The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was held parallel to the ground, the umbrella tip drawn back and energy gathered at the mouth of gun that was exposed. He was using the Launcher skill set into the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella’s gun form, Laser Rifle. It was a charged shot too.

That was when Huang Shaotian noticed a change in lighting. He spared a moment to look upwards, seeing dark purple clouds gathering overhead, getting thicker and thicker. Warlock skill Chaotic Rain was prepared to fall.

Even as skilled as Huang Shaotian was, he was at a bit of a loss as to what to do in this situation.

Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, Wei Chen.

The three characters simultaneously attacked, and none of these skills were instant. One was charged, the other two cast, and they were all placed clearly in front of him.

Three skills. Which would activate first, and which would activate later?

Not even Huang Shaotian could figure that out! Preparing their attacks so openly like that… It didn’t have the abruptness of instant attacks, but it created huge psychological pressure. Even with his incredible reaction speed, their little trick had Huang Shaotian struggling.

It’s coming!

Boundless Sea’s hands suddenly slammed closed and Cloud Grasping Fist’s invisible qi energy flew out. But at the same time, the muzzle of Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella flashed, Laser Rifle roaring out. However, the moment the laser shot forth, Lord Grim shook the muzzle a little. This small detail had Huang Shaotian unable to figure out where the Laser Rifle was actually aimed.

What a bastard!!!

Huang Shaotian was so harried that he could only trash talk to himself.

Roll!

Troubling Rain rolled across the ground, but Huang Shaotian had no idea if he could really dodge all of these attacks. By now, he was acting entirely according to his instinct.

Boom!

Laser Rifle brushed by, a miss!

As for Boundless Sea’s Cloud Grasping Fist, it had been fully completed by now, and Troubling Rain’s form was still within range. Cloud Grasping Fist… missed as well!

Huang Shaotian felt his spirits soar, but then suddenly, there was a light “splash” sound that came from Troubling Rain’s shoulder. Like an omen, it was followed by a relentless downpour of rain. Cursed purple droplets of Chaotic Rain splashed onto the ground and Troubling Rain.

In the end he failed to dodge them all completely!

Huang Shaotian sighed, not bothering to rush to act.

Chaotic Rain did very little damage. The crux of the skill was the Confusion that it could inflict.

Under Confusion, the character wouldn’t go crazy under the system’s control, but the orders that the player inputted would be messed up.

Trying to make the character go left might would make it go right; trying to make it go forwards might instead have it backing up.

If it was just that, then things would be easy to deal with. With training, it wouldn’t be hard to learn how to play with reversed controls, but the problem was that it wasn’t so easy to deal with Glory’s Confusion. The reversed controls came and went at random; that was truly called confusing, and there was no way to truly master it. With the same reason, it was impossible to execute skills with precision either.

The only thing you count count on to counter a Confusion was luck.

However, was luck enough to deal with his current opponents?

In that moment, Huang Shaotian fell into despair. His plan had been completely ruined. Not only had his reconnaissance mission failed, he hadn’t been able to lure Happy into Blue Rain’s ambush either.

And he had no choice but to ask for aid from his teammates. This wasn’t a time to let pride and dignity get in the way. If he died like this, then it would be a huge and direct blow to his team. Meanwhile, there was a far better, though uncertain, chance with letting Blue Rain charge in.

Huang Shaotian chaotically controlled his character, but no matter confused or not, he had to keep his character moving. He couldn’t just stay there like a sitting duck. At the same time, he was already composing a message in the team chat. He had to explain the situation in as much detail as possible while requesting aid.

Providing aid didn’t mean that as soon as Blue Rain’s members arrived, Troubling Rain would be able to escape danger. Happy would naturally do their best to prevent him from being saved. This was a kind of pin, and Blue Rain would need a plan to counter this pin.

Hopefully they’ll get here on time…

Huang Shaotian sent the message. Uncharacteristically, there wasn’t a single unnecessary word. He briefly and clearly explained his situation.

“Isn’t it a bit late to have only just sent a message?”

Who would’ve thought that someone would reply as soon as his message appeared?

Then, a white light swirled around Troubling Rain and cleansed his Confusion.

This was the Paladin skill, Purify, and there was only one Paladin in today’s match: Soul Speaker, played by Blue Rain’s Xu Jingxi.

“I found the old captain!” Lu Hanwen’s message popped up in Blue Rain’s chat, just the sight of it eliciting joy in them.

“Kill” Yu Wenzhou’s order was curt and direct, seeming cruel and emotionless. In reality, with his hand speed, he would naturally make sure to use as few words as possible when giving orders in battle. Cruel and emotionless… that was called thinking too much.

The sound of a blade piercing the air rang out at once.

A Blade Master’s swordplay was generally very swift, but Lu Hanwen was using a greatsword. This attack of his was imposing, comparable to Berserker.

Is everyone here already? Huang Shaotian didn’t stop his controls. He knew that his teammates had probably already been preparing to give support, otherwise they wouldn’t be able to arrive so timely. However, he didn’t have the time or energy to be moved about it now. Blue Rain’s aid was probably within Happy’s expectations. If so, then what tricks had Happy prepared against Blue Rain’s full team?

“Careful, Hanwen!” Huang Shaotian could only hear the sound of sword swings; he couldn’t see what was happening over there. However, considering his understanding of his old captain Wei Chen, there was no way that cunny, slippery old fox would make dealing with him easy. It wasn’t a trap or anything, was it?

“I’m keeping watch!” That was when a single reply from Yu Wenzhou dispersed Huang Shaotian’s worries. With him keeping watch, then everything was under control, right?

“Over here, Huang Shao!” Zheng Xuan’s Spitfire Bullet Rain appeared in Huang Shaotian’s field of vision, throwing skills in the opposite direction of where Huang Shaotian was facing to help provide cover for his escape.

Blue Rain was displaying their teamwork, so what about Happy? How would they deal with this situation that they should’ve been prepared for?

All the spectators looked on awkwardly.

At such a crucial moment of time, Happy’s team members were still relentlessly trash talking Wei Chen, reminding him that it wouldn’t look good if his junior to defeated him.

“You’re twice his age!” Ye Xiu reminded.

“More than,” Fang Rui corrected.

“If you get cut down so easily then that would be quite the embarrassment,” Ye Xiu said.

“Indeed.”

This time, Wei Chen didn’t reply. Naturally, this wasn’t because he was alright with being mocked like this, but it was because he couldn’t spare any effort into arguing with these two while Lu Hanwen’s greatsword Blade Master was harassing him. Plus, he could clearly see another character standing not too far off, watching on predatorily.

Swoksaar.

The memories of his past resurfaced.

That winter over ten years ago, Glory launched. The mass promotion of the game had all those online gamers on the edges of their seats. Wei Chen, even now, could still see that winding line of people, all waiting to buy their first Glory account card.

It was on that day, standing in that line, after waiting for a full four hours, that Wei Chen successfully obtained an account card. Then, this card was given an identity: Warlock Swoksaar.

That was the very same Swoksaar in front of him.

Standing not too far, but not too close, as if watching the world below from the heavens, like a general on the field, always keeping track of everything that was happening.

The change in player seemed to have changed the character as well.

This was Swoksaar, yet it was no longer his Swoksaar. He had a marvelous successor, who had managed to gain glory far beyond what Wei Chen had accomplished.

All those years ago, he was the captain, the ace player, but against this boy who could count as his student, he had lost.

As for today? The position of captain, the ace, had all been taken by the other, while he had fallen from grace. He was late to the game, so late that he broke the record for the oldest player in the scene. However, this time, he was the challenger. From that day onwards, he knew that there would come such a day. Like an usurper, he rose to the challenge against this man who stood at the the top, who was no longer a boy.

Chapter 1417 - Comeback

Windward Formation, Swoksaar.

The two Warlocks hadn’t even exchanged blows, yet there already seemed to be sparks in the air.

As for Lu Hanwen? He was the most active player in this battle. But in comparison to Wei Chen and Yu Wenzhou, this young player was lacking a storyplayer. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were currently ignoring his plays, instead focusing on the two Warlocks.

In fact, because of their access to spectator controls, the audience had a far better understanding of the adjustments being done made by both teams than anyone on the field. Even so, they didn’t know what the result of these changes would result inbe. The fans of both teams were filled with anxiety.

When the battle was intense, the audience didn’t know where to look.

On the other hand, the viewers tuning into the broadcast had an much easier time. Wherever the broadcast picked was what they got to see. The difficult decision-making went was made by to the cameraman.

Right now, in order to coordinate with Pan Lin and Li Yibo, the camera focused on those three players.

But no matter how much hype was given to the two Warlocks of different generations, the fact that Lu Hanwen was the most active player at the moment could not be changed.

The greatsword-wielding Flowing Sword displayed a frightening aggression. How would Wei Chen respond?

“Uh… Wei Chen’s Windward Formation is… running around the rock in circles,” Pan Lin tried hard to make Wei Chen’s response seem like a brilliant play, but reality was cruel. His attempt only made his description seem flimsy.

“Very effective pathing…” Pan Lin added in a comment and then looked at Li Yibo in desperation.

Help me, senior!

Pan Lin hinted. He truly had no idea how to glamorize the situation.

“Haha,” Li Yibo laughed,” It’s very crude, but he’s dodging Lu Hanwen’s offense efficiently, no?”

“The viewers, who haven’t been playing Glory for long, might not be familiar with Wei Chen’s style. How can I describe it? His desire for victory is extremely strong. He doesn’t care about how he looks on stage. In order to win, he’ll always choose the most appropriate option,” Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin gasped with admiration.

To put it briefly, isn’t he just saying “he’ll do anything to win”? But from the way Li Yibo described it, this sort of unpleasant remark was transformed into high praise.

“Lu Hanwen is playing adorably too, haha!” Pan Lin quickly went along with Li Yibo. It was a playoffs match that could end a team’s season, yet he unexpectedly threw out the word “adorable” as a description. That was the reality of things though. Wei Chen and Lu Hanwen, one old and one young, were running around a rock as if it were a children’s game. The word “adorable” was quite a fitting adjective, no?

“Yu Wenzhou is very calm. It looks like he has no intentions of getting involved,” Li Yibo said.

“Uh, I think he’s probably considering the overall situation. Not all of Happy’s members have acted yet!” Pan Lin said.

“Let’s take a look at the situation over there…” Li Yibo said.

Watching two people run around in circles wasn’t very exciting. The hyped showdown between Blue Rain’s two Warlocks of different generations never occurred. As the scene switched to the other end of the battlefield, Pan Lin and Li Yibo were starting to lose interest in it.

“Zheng Xuan is providing cover for Huang Shaotian’s retreat,” Pan Lin started with the central theme of the battle taking place here.

Boom boom boom boom!

Although Zheng Xuan’s Spitfire wasn’t as colorful as Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms style, every Spitfire drew on it to a certain extent. Zheng Xuan provided a cover of bright light for Troubling Rain, while attacking Ye Xiu and Fang Rui to slow down their pursuit.

“You bastard, you’re so enthusiastic today!” The pressure on Huang Shaotian had lessened significantly. The usually washed out Zheng Xuan was currently very focused, which made him feel even more gratified. Sure enough, every member of Team Blue Rain was someone who could be counted on!

“HS” Zheng Xuan replied with just two letters, but those familiar with him immediately recognized it as his favorite two words.

“How stressful? Is that it? No need to be so stressed!” Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker was nearby. Troubling Rain and Bullet Rain were both inside his healing range. He had confidence that as long as he wasn’t disturbed, he could preserve their lives. If it wasn’t for them not having a full picture of Happy’s arrangements, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain could turn around and counterattack with the support from Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain and his Soul Speaker.

But without enough information, fighting a battle that could determine the winner would not be a wise decision. As a result, Blue Rain did their usual tactic: defend first and then counterattack.

Thus, with help from Zheng Xuan and Xu Jingxi, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain steadily retreated. Just when it looked like he would join up with Bullet Rain, a powerful beam of light descended from the sky.

Satellite Beam!

This attack had come out of nowhere. However, Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xian reacted quickly, promptly dodging to the side. The Satellite Beam crashed to the surface of the ground, sending up billows of sand. Four smaller beams split off and rotated, sweeping up even more sand. The sand unexpectedly gave the Satellite Beam an additional effect, sending clouds of sand into the air. Traces of the Satellite Beam’s path could be seen. The rhythm between Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan had been sent into disarray.

Satellite Beam? Launcher? Su Mucheng?

So Happy is without a healer?

That was the first thought that flashed into Huang Shaotian’s mind. Afterwards, he looked at the rooftop of a dilapidated building. Because of the attack, Dancing Rain had exposed her position.

Then, only Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash remained.

Where was he?

After the Ice Boundary, he disappeared. Was he waiting for an opportunity to mount a sneak attack, or had he run off to trade places with the healer?

No matter the case, this was a golden opportunity! The other side didn’t have a healer. Blue Rain could go on the offensive and force trades with Happy to lower their health!

Opportunity!

This was an opportunity!

Glory’s greatest opportunist began to fire up facing this opportunity. He forgot about the exhaustion from facing Happy alone, replacing it with a burning passion.

“Counterattack!” Huang Shaotian roared in the chat, directly using the word counterattack to show just how great his determination was. After typing out these words, his Troubling Rain turned around and headed towards Lord Grim and Boundless Sea.

“Zheng Xuan, follow me! Healer, provide cover!” Huang Shaotian quickly gave out orders.

On the battlefield, the captain had the highest authority, but the shotcaller couldn’t micromanage every player down to the details like marionettes. In particular, Team Blue Rain’s captain was limited by his hand speed. They had never witnessed their screens being flooded from commands given by their shotcaller like Thunderclap’s Xiao Shiqin did. What they most often saw instead was Huang Shaotian flooding the screen with trash talk.

Because of this reason, Team Blue Rain required each member to have strong tactical awareness. In situations without many orders from their captain, the team members had to coordinate and make decisions on their own to achieve Yu Wenzhou’s strategic goal.

And this time, Yu Wenzhou’s strategic goal was to provide cover for Huang Shaotian’s retreat and then reconvene with the rest of the team. But now, Huang Shaotian made a change to it and blew the horn for a counterattack.

There was no time for a discussion. Seeing that Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had already turned around, even if Zheng Xuan and Xu Jingxi had different thoughts, they had no choice but to coordinate with Huang Shaotian. Team Blue Rain was just like this. They would always choose to advance or retreat together.

The two sides crossed fire.

Zheng Xuan and Xu Jingxi immediately understood Huang Shaotian’s intentions. Happy didn’t seem to have a healer, so the two instantly became bolder. But where was Happy’s fifth player? Had he gone to switch with their healer? Or was he waiting somewhere for them to fall for a trap?

The two became aware of this issue. They paid attention to the terrain and the movements of Ye Xiu and Fang Rui.

2v2.

Ye Xiu and Fang Rui had support from Su Mucheng’s Launcher. Huang Shaotian and Zhueng Xuan had support from Xu Jingxi’s Paladin.

Happy had the stronger offense, but the defense provided by Blue Rain’s healer made up for it. In the end, the one who would deal more damage would be Blue Rain.

Yu Wenzhou still didn’t make a move. When Huang Shaotian made the call to counterattack, he continued to calmly observe the situation.

Where was Happy’s fifth player?

He was still concerned about this issue. He went over the terrain again and again in his mind, but he couldn’t think of a place where a Phantom Demon could launch an explosive ambush. This place was an ancient city, but because it was in ruins, it was all out in the open. In this environment, there wasn’t a location where a Phantom Demon could instantly lock up the place with ghost boundaries.

As a result, if a Phantom Demon were to make a move, it should have happened long ago. An ambush was not a smart decision. In this situation, a Phantom Demon wasn’t enough to make up for the loss of a healer.

The Phantom Demon should have gone to trade places with the healer. In that case, this really is a great opportunity.

Yu Wenzhou finally made his mind. He wouldn’t stay on the defense and be their final path of retreat. However, who would have thought that at this moment, Wei Chen’s Windward Formation would suddenly make his move.

Windward Formation hadn’t broken away from Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud. He had someone at his heels already, yet now he wanted to add in Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar to the fight? 1v2?

The spectators were stunned.

Was Wei Chen really that incredible? A player who could 1v2 two All-Star players?

But soon afterwards, because he had been busy attacking Swoksaar, he didn’t have time to dodge Flowing Cloud’s attack. Windward Formation crashed to the ground, tumbling away.

What’s going on?

Everyone frowned. This Wei Chen didn’t seem to have the ability to 1v2? What was he thinking?

But then, they saw Windward Formation continue rolling as if he couldn’t stop rolling, all the way until he vanished.

Lu Hanwen had been surprised because the attack had connected too easily. When he came back to his senses, he hastily gave chase.

“Watch out!!” Seeing Windward Formation roll out of sight, Yu Wenzhou immediately gave a warning.

But in the end, he was still a half beat too late.

Hexagram Prison.

Chapter 1418 - The Familiar Swoksaar

The curse runes shimmered in the air, swiftly forming a prison. Lu Hanwen had been too hasty in his chase, and by the time he saw Yu Wenzhou’s warning, it was already too late. Flowing Cloud was instantly trapped by the Hexagram Prison.

Seeing that the attack landed successfully, Wei Chen let out a sigh of relief. After all, there was a reason this player had made it to the All-Stars even at such a young age. If Wei Chen hadn’t fully taken advantage of the map surroundings, he really wouldn’t have been able to get rid of this kid.

Hexagram Prison, the number one Root skill. When maxed at Level 75, the effect lasted nine seconds, and even more frightening, there was no way to dispel this curse. It wasn’t considered a status skill, so skills like Purify, Expel, Focus, and so on all had no effect. Similarly, no matter how high a character’s Spirit stat was, no matter how good their Resistance, they had no way of breaking out of the Hexagram Prison early.

There was only one way to get out of a Hexagram Prison early: kill the caster. But right now, that didn’t look to be possible. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud would be spending the full nine seconds sitting in the Hexagram Prison.

For Wei Chen, these nine seconds were extremely precious. At last, he had nine seconds free from the youth who’d been furiously chasing and killing him all this way. But it didn’t look like he’d be able to take it easy, because Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar was already beginning to move.

Eight years.

It had already been a full eight years since the last time Wei Chen used Swoksaar.

In eight years, Swoksaar had risen from Level 55 to Level 75. New equipment, new skills. Wei Chen shouldn’t be familiar with this current Swoksaar – and yet, he was very familiar.

Because, in the end, this character was the part of Glory he cared about the most. Even though he hadn’t touched him since then, he still paid attention to Swoksaar’s growth. In every match, Wei Chen could always pick out any adjustments that had been made, no matter how small. Just like this, Wei Chen watched as the character’s new controller slowly erased the traces that he’d left behind, and replaced them with his own stamps.

“Idiot!”

Every change that Swoksaar went through would provoke another round of disdainful cursing from Wei Chen. He would often turn to the guys next to him and look down on these changes for being so noobish, for not understanding Warlocks at all.

His little followers all revolved around him, so of course they believed whatever he said.

But what about himself?

When there were many people around him, Wei Chen would curse like this. But when he was alone? He could only smile bitterly.

In his heart, he knew all too well that he was simply unhappy to watch the traces he’d left on Swoksaar slowly get wiped away.

And in the end, even the weapon in Swoksaar’s hand had been changed.

Curse of Destruction?

The name of the new scepter sounded both arrogant and cultured. With this, the final trace that Wei Chen had left on Swoksaar was erased, and he could sit still no longer. After that, Windward Formation gained the weapon Death’s Hand.

Death’s Hand. This was the Silver weapon that Swoksaar had used in the very beginning. And now, Wei Chen had revived it.

He picked up the weapon that Swoksaar had abandoned. To many people, this made his Windward Formation seem like a cheap knockoff of Swoksaar.

But Wei Chen did not care. If the character ID “Swoksaar” hadn’t been locked to the original character, he would have called his new Warlock “Swoksaar” as well.

Wei Chen didn’t completely understand why he felt the need to compete like this. He probably still just felt unfulfilled!

And now, it was time for all this to come to a close.

Wei Chen knew very well that with his current condition and skill, there was no way he could appear in all of the intense playoff matches.

Facing Blue Rain, this might be his final performance on this stage. And this battle was one in which he could show his strength to the fullest.

Because he understood Swoksaar.

Even if it wasn’t the one that had been built for him, he still understood this character, better than anyone else.

Swoksaar was casting.

It was Curse Arrows.

This low-level skill, given to Swoksaar, whose cast speed was +34, was so fast that it was practically an instant-cast.

So fast!

But this wasn’t all.

If it was just a cast, then Swoksaar’s Curse Arrows should be even faster than this.

The slight delay was because he let the skill charge for just a moment. Curse Arrows was a skill that could be charged, and the longer it charged, the balls of light would multiply, and more arrows would be fired in the end.

If the skill was used immediately, there would be thirteen arrows; if charged to the fullest, the number of arrows could reach twenty-six. And Swoksaar’s pause just now to let the skill charge would push the number of arrows to fifteen.

Wei Chen knew all of this too well. Windward Formation calmly dodged this attack from Swoksaar, and even the controller now behind Swoksaar, Yu Wenzhou, was slightly surprised.

Because the opponent had dodged too calmly.

Such a slight charge, producing two extra arrows, was normally very easily overlooked. To wait until noticing the extra arrows and then dodging would be an on-the-spot reaction and movement, whether or not they actually managed to dodge. But Windward Formation’s calm movement clearly revealed that he knew the attack would be like this from the very beginning.

He saw through it!

Just from the way in which Windward Formation had dodged the attack, Yu Wenzhou could make judgments to this extent. And at this moment, all of the members of the audience, including commentators Pan Lin and Li Yibo, hadn’t even noticed that this Curse Arrows had hidden such a trap. The two of them only praised how fast Swoksaar’s cast was, without even realizing that slight charging delay.

The attack had been unsuccessful, but Swoksaar stopped moving.

Yu Wenzhou still had doubt in his heart. He couldn’t tell what Happy’s plan was, nor could he guess Wei Chen’s intention. Was he really trying to stall two players by himself? It wasn’t that Yu Wenzhou didn’t respect Wei Chen, but the fact simply was that Wei Chen couldn’t manage that.

The Hexagram Prison trapped Lu Hanwen for nine seconds, but what did that accomplish? Without the firepower of other players to support, these precious nine seconds were slipping by without Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud suffering any damage. After these nine seconds, how would the situation change?

Yu Wenzhou decided to watch a little longer.

As expected, still so calm.

Over these eight years, Wei Chen had never stopped paying attention to Swoksaar, and so at the same time, he gained an extremely clear understanding of the player behind Swoksaar. Furthermore, he had interacted with this new controller early on. He would never forget that laughable presence in the training camp, who had, during one ordinary day of training, defeated him.

This calm youth would become the foundation of Blue Rain’s future.

From that day on, Wei Chen acknowledged this, and reality proved that he hadn’t been wrong. Even though Huang Shaotian was the top attacker of present-day Blue Rain, Blue Rain’s strategy, Blue Rain’s style and rhythm, were all decided because of Yu Wenzhou’s presence.

Perhaps it was precisely because he could maintain calm and clarity at every moment that Huang Shaotian’s opportunistic style could become so refined and exciting. Because of this foundation, Huang Shaotian could walk on the blade’s edge with complete confidence.

At this time, Huang Shaotian was already leading an assault, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was trapped in Hexagram Prison, but Yu Wenzhou was still unhurried as he continued to analyze the situation. If he couldn’t understand, then he wouldn’t make any rash movements.

Curse Arrows!

Wei Chen fired back with the same skill. His Windward Formation couldn’t cast as quickly as Swoksaar, but a low-level skill like Curse Arrows couldn’t take too much time. He didn’t let it charge, instead releasing it immediately. Death’s Hand swung outward, the purple spheres of light spun and traced an arc in the air, and just like that the Curse Arrows fanned outward.

“Wei Chen’s technique really shows off his experience!” Li Yibo exclaimed. Maybe the old generals couldn’t compete with the youths in terms of hand speed, but in terms of technical control, that was something that was truly refined over time.

Actually, reasonably speaking, Wei Chen wasn’t an old general in the typical sense, having retired for N years before returning. To return after having a large blank space in his career, calling him an old general was less accurate than calling him a rookie.

Wei Chen had to readjust to the rhythm of the Pro League matches like a rookie. But everyone knew that in the regular season, he’d appeared pathetically few times. Only until the end of the season did he appear in consecutive matches. Even though he hadn’t had many appearances, it had been enough.

Because an old general didn’t need to adjust to the rhythm. They simply needed to rediscover it.

Rediscover the rhythm, rediscover victory!

“Beautiful!” Pan Lin offered his own praise after Li Yibo’s exclamation. The Curse Arrows spread out evenly in a fan shape, like a peacock opening its tail. No Warlock player could do this any more perfectly.

But was that really the case?

In the eyes of the audience, it seemed so.

But in Yu Wenzhou’s eyes…

There’s an opening!

In practically the very instant that the orbs fired the Curse Arrows, Yu Wenzhou already saw an opening.

The Curse Arrows were evenly distributed, but the rhythm wasn’t entirely even. They were spaced evenly on the left and right, but what about in front and behind?

In front and behind, that meant before and after.

There was a difference before and after, leaving an opening that could be traveled through.

Turn, move horizontally!

Yu Wenzhou’s controls couldn’t be fast, but they would always be that accurate.

It clearly looked like he was about to be struck by the Curse Arrows, but in the end, he seemed to pass right through them. Swoksaar remained standing, and that fan arrangement of arrows maintained its shape without a single arrow going missing. Not a single one had hit.

“He dodged them?” Even Li Yibo was dumbfounded.

Yes, he dodged it, but he only dodged the Curse Arrows.

Windward Formation’s new cast was already beginning, magic energy swirling around his Death’s Hand.

Death’s Door?

Yu Wenzhou was stunned. He wanted to use Death’s Door, facing an opponent head-on like this?

Even if he had the cast speed of his Swoksaar, this bit of time wasn’t enough!

He had to interrupt it. Swoksaar tossed a Soul Slice in that direction. But Yu Wenzhou wasn’t about to sit back and relax. Wei Chen, no matter what, shouldn’t be playing like this.

Yu Wenzhou turned his camera view, and quickly discovered another Windward Formation, casting a spell.

It was Shadow Clone Technique!

Yu Wenzhou instantly understood. The one that was right in front of him was obviously a clone. Just when Swoksaar had turned his body to duck through the Curse Arrows, Windward Formation had used this Ninja skill.

The Windward Formation over there was the one he truly needed to interrupt.

But, not enough…

The range wasn’t enough!

Windward Formation’s cast range was extremely large, even larger than that of Swoksaar’s. If he wanted to interrupt it, Swoksaar would have to walk forward a bit.

But it was too late.

The distance of two body-lengths decided the success of a skill.

Chapter 1419 - Every Means Possible

Yu Wenzhou’s hands weren’t fast, but his mind was extremely so. In an instant, he analyzed many situations with great clarity.

Like Wei Chen, he couldn’t be more familiar with the Warlock class. There wasn’t much match data on Windward Formation, so reports on this character weren’t incredibly comprehensive, but things like cast speed and cast range could be judged just from one a single match. After that, even if the character improved, these stats would only increase, not decrease.

According to all these known reports, Yu Wenzhou now made an instantaneous judgment: he was too late.

He even went a step further and recognized that this was a playstyle specifically meant to counter himself and Swoksaar. If another Warlock player had been standing here, Wei Chen might not have succeeded this time. But it was him, and it was Swoksaar.

The player’s traits, the character’s stats, they had all been thoroughly studied. These few moments had been tailored to deal with Yu Wenzhou and Swoksaar. Nothing had been wasted, and just like this, the powerful attack Death’s Door was cast.

How would the situation change after nine seconds?

Yu Wenzhou had wondered this question earlier.

Now he knew, they didn’t need to wait nine seconds. Right now, with this Death’s Door, he was about to fall into a fairly disastrous position.

Far away, Windward Formation now finished casting, and curse energy gathered around his Death’s Hand. Behind the flashing light, Yu Wenzhou could see Windward Formation’s face.

This was exactly the face in his memories: still young, their first captain, Wei Chen. The Wei Chen of today, already over thirty years old, now had more than a few lines on his face from the passing years.

Yu Wenzhou watched silently, unmoving, looking as though he had given up.

Wei Chen jolted, but he had already finished summoning Death’s Door. Tendrils of darkness shot out from within the door, immediately wrapping around Swoksaar, but even now, Yu Wenzhou didn’t make any movements.

Correct. None at all.

The darkness caught Swoksaar, dragging him inside the Death’s Door, but Swoksaar didn’t resist this process at all.

And after that, the attack of Death’s Door on Swoksaar ended.

“Fuck!” Wei Chen couldn’t help but curse.

This was Yu Wenzhou’s calm, his ability to clearly anticipate all that would happen. He understood that his own hand speed wasn’t enough to deal with the Death’s Door and Wei Chen standing intently next to it. So, he didn’t try to circle around, simply allowing this powerful attack to land. He traded 15% of his health to end Wei Chen’s offensive.

Yes, it ended.

Wei Chen boasted of how well he understood Yu Wenzhou’s style, but he didn’t anticipate that this steady player would actually use this kind of sacrificial strategy. None of the follow-up attacks that he’d prepared were fit to deal with this kind of situation. Death’s Door was successfully cast, but it ended too quickly, leaving Wei Chen grasping for a next move.

Soul Slice!

Wei Chen could only use an instant-cast skill on instinct to try and continue his offensive. But the fact that Death’s Door vanished so quickly made his heart feel empty.

Soul Slice, was it?

Yu Wenzhou was watching Windward Formation’s movement, and he easily dodged this attack. He knew that Wei Chen was surprised at this moment, because he had purposely created this surprise.

He saw how well Wei Chen understood himself and Swoksaar, so in this kind of situation, any judgment and decision based on his style would definitely be within the opponent’s calculations. At a time like this, he had to take a path that he normally wouldn’t.

And so, Yu Wenzhou did this. He took an unusual action to instantly break the judgments that Wei Chen had made based on his deep understanding.

Even the highest-level experts might not have been able to notice this battle of wits.

Only Yu Wenzhou himself could deeply feel the familiarity that Wei Chen had toward himself and Swoksaar. That Death’s Door just now had truly forced him into a position where he had no other option.

But even though he managed to do something outside of Wei Chen’s predictions, he had still ultimately been unable to escape from this Death’s Door, and Swoksaar did take 15% in damage. This Death’s Door had pushed him to desperation, even if he’d used a surprising move to swiftly climb out of this desperation.

He’d disrupted Wei Chen’s rhythm. But what next?

Looking at this opponent that completely understood him, Yu Wenzhou felt a great pressure upon him.

Flaming Arrow?

Yu Wenzhou saw Windward Formation begin to use this skill.

This was another low-level Warlock skill. Even though it required a cast, for these high-end professional characters, the cast time was practically instantaneous. Windward Formation’s staff gave a slight wave, and this Flaming Arrow already formed. Black smoke burned into the shape of an arrow, and with a shake of Windward Formation’s staff, the arrow flew forward.

But, wasn’t this distance still a bit too far?

It wasn’t difficult for Yu Wenzhou to dodge. The range of the magic attacks from Elementalists or Warlocks was always be inferior to the range of a bullet. Magic attacks with only this much range weren’t suppressive enough at the pro level.

But after waving out this skill, Wei Chen didn’t pay any more attention to Yu Wenzhou and Swoksaar. Windward Formation suddenly turned, and Death’s Hand pointed toward Flowing Cloud.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had already escaped from the Hexagram Prison, and he immediately came charging toward Windward Formation.

He didn’t expect that Windward Formation would suddenly turn to face him.

Death’s Hand swirled with the light of a curse.

Lu Hanwen frantically controlled his Flowing Cloud to dodge to the side, but that black light flew right toward the direction toward which he had tried to dodge.

But Lu Hanwen was good. Even though he was walking straight into the attack, his reaction speed and control were top-tier. Flowing Cloud ducked to the side once again, and that mass of black light hit only air.

Wei Chen was helpless.

Dealing with this youngster was entirely different from dealing with Yu Wenzhou. Right now, he regretted that Death’s Door had already ended, because if Yu Wenzhou had prolonged its duration, then it would have served as a threat toward Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud as well.

Yu Wenzhou bold choice had completely disrupted Wei Chen’s original plan. 1v2, control Lu Hanwen for nine seconds, and then force Yu Wenzhou to suffer a powerful attack. To be honest, this was already an impressive performance. Most other players, if put in this position, probably would not have been able to play a more beautiful nine seconds.

But he wasn’t satisfied.

His original plan wasn’t just nine seconds.

“Hanwen, go over there.” Seeing that Lu Hanwen had escaped, he immediately sent this message in the chat.

The showdown between the old and new generation of Warlocks, this was a topic that the audience greatly enjoyed seeing, but the players weren’t obliged to cooperate. They were playing a match, not putting on a show. Yu Wenzhou directly sending Lu Hanwen away right now certainly wasn’t to cooperate with the hot topic. He simply did this because it seemed that Wei Chen’s plan had been to stall both of them by himself. Even though Yu Wenzhou still didn’t know what his end goal was, but preventing this from happening would at least hinder Happy’s plans.

Huang Shaotian’s side was relying on their healer to put pressure on Happy, and they needed a powerful attacker. Lu Hanwen fit this responsibility better than Yu Wenzhou. So, he had Lu Hanwen go and help them. His faceoff with Wei Chen was therefore only a typical, logical, strategic decision.

Wei Chen, of course, couldn’t accept this.

“Little brat where are you running!” Seeing that Flowing Cloud wanted to escape, Wei Chen refused to give up.

But he could only yell. Yu Wenzhou, of course, was covering Lu Hanwen’s retreat. Yu Wenzhou used a Flaming Arrow, returning the skill that Wei Chen had just tried to use against him.

Wei Chen wanted to stop Flowing Cloud from leaving, but he wasn’t going to have Windward Formation go and brawl it out! Of course, he would be relying on casting spells. But Swoksaar’s Flaming Arrow flew over, preventing Windward Formation from casting.

But Windward Formation actually began to rush forward, and as he dodged this Flaming Arrow, he swung his hand and tossed out an object.

Puff!

Purple smoke filled the air.

After the Shadow Clone Technique, Windward Formation demonstrated yet another low-level Ninja skill – Ninja Tool: Smoke Bomb.

The silhouettes of Windward Formation and Flowing Cloud were swiftly swallowed by the smoke. Lu Hanwen’s reaction was intelligent, with swordlight illuminating the smoke. Even as he protected himself, it allowed Flowing Cloud to continue to advance.

Chaotic Rain!

Yu Wenzhou also controlled Swoksaar to begin a high-level cast. He couldn’t lock onto Windward Formation’s position right now, but if Windward Formation didn’t come to stop him and insisted on casting a curse on Flowing Cloud, then he wouldn’t have time to jump out of range of a Chaotic Rain.

In the smoke, Flowing Cloud’s greatsword swung every which way, seeming invincible.

Puff!

Amidst the fog, drops of blood scattered. Finally, it seemed that Windward Formation was hit. But quickly after, with a “pa” sound, the swordlight stilled. It was still present, but it was no longer moving forward.

This was… Spike Trap?

Even though Yu Wenzhou hadn’t seen it, he could make a good guess.

Wei Chen had suffered a slash, but he managed to have Windward Formation use the Thief skill Spike Trap and halt Flowing Cloud’s offense.

But by this time, the Chaotic Rain was already pattering down. It didn’t look like Windward Formation, who had just suffered a slashing attack, had time to escape from the smoke.

“Wei Chen is really working hard!!” Pan Lin exclaimed, feeling moved and saddened.

Wei Chen wasn’t playing a pretty match. He seemed desperate as he did everything possible to contain Flowing Cloud.

Running circles around the boulder. Sent rolling to the side with a slash. And now he barely stole the chance to place this Spike Trap, under the cover of a Smoke Bomb, still hurting from a sword injury.

Wei Chen wasn’t fighting an easy battle. Everyone could see how he was struggling to maintain the situation.

In a direct battle against Lu Hanwen, he would almost certainly lose, but by using these endless little tricks, he worked hard to try and stall both Lu Hanwen and Yu Wenzhou here.

But his hard work would come to an end with the fall of this Chaotic Rain.

Flowing Cloud was still stuck, but Yu Wenzhou was already prepared to have Swoksaar come over to maintain control of Windward Formation.

He had Swoksaar to move forward. But then, Swoksaar rolled to the left.

“What is Yu Wenzhou doing?” Everyone was stunned. This roll seemed to be completely pointless. Had he noticed some unrecognized danger? Even the audience, with their omniscient view, hadn’t seen anything.

But Yu Wenzhou’s reaction was faster and more accurate than the audience members with omniscient view.

Confused?

Yu Wenzhou looked at Swoksaar’s status in shock.

A moment later, he already realized what had happened.

Magic Mirror. It was Magic Mirror.

The Warlock skill Magic Mirror reflected all side effects of a magic attack. Amidst the smoke, not only had Windward Formation laid down a Spike Trap for Flowing Cloud, he had also hidden a Magic Mirror, waiting for Swoksaar’s Chaotic Rain to fall upon it.

Chapter 1420 - The Value of Desperation

Swoksaar was Confused?

It had already happened, yet not a single person had noticed.

Even though the audience had their omniscient view, when zoomed out, it couldn’t clearly show every single detail. Everyone basically understood the overall rhythm of Wei Chen’s actions, but no one had detected that Windward Formation’s dirty trick just now was to hide his cast of Magic Mirror.

The Magic Mirror was controlled by the caster, and could be suspended in the air.

For a few single-target skills, if the Magic Mirror was precisely positioned, then when reflecting the skill, it could also protect the caster from taking damage. For a wide-range attack like Chaotic Rain, the Magic Mirror couldn’t completely protect the caster, but it would still serve the purpose of reflecting the skill’s side effects. So, in the end, both Swoksaar and Windward Formation entered the Confused state together.

The careful Yu Wenzhou had actually fallen to another one of Wei Chen’s tricks. Everyone was shocked, but they were still wondering about the value of this plot having succeeded.

Under the Chaotic Rain, both Windward Formation and Swoksaar became useless.

But what about Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud?

He wouldn’t be affected by a teammate’s attack, and the thing that was currently preventing him from moving, the Spike Trap, was a mere low-level Thief skill. He would definitely be the first person to escape from the control of a skill.

But after that, Windward Formation would still be Confused. Wasn’t that just asking for a beating? At a time like this, Lu Hanwen would probably hold off on going over to help Huang Shaotian, and instead take advantage of this opportunity to furiously attack Windward Formation.

Wei Chen’s response had been outside of everyone’s expectations, but that didn’t necessarily mean it was a perfect solution.

“He doesn’t have any better choice,” Li Yibo sighed. “He can only do his best and use whatever ideas he has to tie up Blue Rain’s two players.

Pan Lin was silent. This old general was working so hard; who would be heartless enough to criticize his judgement for being this or that?

If he had faster reactions or faster hand speed, perhaps there would be other, better options.

Both Pan Lin and Li Yibo understood this clearly, but the two of them reached an unspoken agreement not to discuss this.

This hypothetical was simply too cruel, especially for an old general. He’d once had these things, only to gradually lose them. The tragedy was that he would never be able to recover them again.

These scars left by the passage of time shouldn’t be considered a form of failure.

Wei Chen was already doing the absolute best he could with what he had.

As a Warlock specialist just like Yu Wenzhou, he’d managed to ensnare Yu Wenzhou twice. This was something that no Warlock player had ever accomplished before. Not once since Yu Wenzhou’s debut. And now, this old general past his prime had actually managed to do it!

Just based on this, he had the right to stand on this stage.

Just based on this, everyone should understand why Happy sent him onstage.

The smoke quickly dissipated.

Flowing Cloud was still stuck in the trap. Windward Formation and Swoksaar were unable to control their characters properly in their confusion. The three characters still displayed the symptoms of their statuses, as though they were performing a play.

But this play would eventually reach its curtain call.

Just like everyone expected, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was the first to escape from his status condition, and he immediately charged toward Windward Formation.

The greatsword Flame Shadow lifted up and then plummeted, tracing a burning scar in the air.

Windward Formation was still moving around chaotically. Compared to Swoksaar, who had just been standing quietly after discovering he was Confused, Windward Formation seemed as laughable as a monkey.

But, no one could laugh.

Even in this condition, was he still trying to pull something off?

Seeing this, many audience members felt choked up. They knew that Wei Chen couldn’t do anything, that Windward Formation would be slashed by Flowing Cloud’s greatsword. After that, with Yu Wenzhou coming into the picture, if Wei Chen didn’t receive any help, then he might meet his end right here.

The old general had only returned to this stage with much difficulty. Was he about to complete his curtain call just like this?

As the greatsword Flame Shadow descended, quite a few people couldn’t bear to watch. But at this moment, a pocket suddenly split open in the air, and from the shifting void, a black claw shot outward. Just this one extended claw snagged Flowing Cloud, who was using Collapsing Mountain, in midair.

This was…

Warlock skill: Claw of Darkness!

Everyone was stunned.

Even under Confusion, he was still able to use a skill?

And the first one to react was once again Yu Wenzhou. He suddenly understood why Windward Formation, after suffering the Chaotic Rain, had continued to move around randomly. Because Wei Chen had been constantly trying a set series of inputs, hoping he could activate this skill through sheer luck.

Claw of Darkness…

Yu Wenzhou thought about the inputs necessary for this skill. Indeed, when Confused, this skill had a higher probability than others of being successfully used.

But “higher” was only relative. Yu Wenzhou couldn’t do the calculations immediately, but he knew that it was still a very low probability.

Yet even so, Wei Chen hadn’t given up. As soon as he was hit by the status, he began tapping out the inputs. If the Confusion disrupted his movements, then he would just start over again. In this short amount of time, no one knew just how many times he had repeated these inputs. Everyone only knew that, in the end, he had succeeded. In this crucial moment, Windward Formation’s cast was successful, and he summoned forth the Claw of Darkness.

Claw of Darkness was a powerful grab skill. Even Collapsing Mountain did not out prioritize it. Just like that, Flowing Cloud was snatched in the air by the Claw of Darkness.

When viewers realized that Wei Chen had this kind of determination, to stubbornly pull off this skill even when Confused – they felt tears gathering in their eyes.

Happy’s fans all knew Wei Chen’s past. But to be honest, no one felt that this guy had the air of a powerhouse team’s captain. In their eyes, this guy was more like a boss of a casual little group in-game.

The two years that Wei Chen had spent in the Alliance were its grassroots days. After that, he’d never let go of the game. To be honest, Wei Chen didn’t have much of the air that was associated with any present-day pro player, let alone the sort of distant, lofty air shared by the powerhouse players.

Even though he was an old player that hadn’t appeared very often, Happy’s fans still loved him very much, exactly because he was so down-to-earth. It was like he had popped up in the game, casually taken down some dungeons dungeon, grabbed some equipment, and then cheerfully ran back to the professional scene to cause some chaos.

And everyone felt that Happy had invited Wei Chen because they wanted someone old in their ranks to help pass on experience and knowledge to the younger members. No one thought that he would make any significant contributions in matches. They felt that his few appearances were Happy’s way of paying respect to him. He would play around a bit, and everyone would watch and laugh, and that would be it.

But now, everyone understood.

No matter how old Wei Chen was, no matter how he lacked the air of a pro player, he still had a pro player’s heart.

A heart striving for victory. A heart of a champion.

Using his own methods, he proved this point to everyone.

Yu Wenzhou, Lu Hanwen.

Did they really think that two All-Star players could stomp him down so easily?

No!

Up to this point, Windward Formation indeed seemed very pathetic, and he had lost more health than his opponents. Every new moment made people feel that this was it, that he was done for.

But again and again, he stabilized the situation, he remained on the battlefield.

This old guy, how long would it take until he gave in?

Even Blue Rain’s players, Blue Rain’s fans, couldn’t help but feel moved.

So this was their old captain?

So this was the senior they told stories about, their extremely dirty, extremely shameless senior?

Even though he was their opponent now, in the hearts of the Blue Rain players and fans, they quietly felt a burst of pride.

Yes, Wei Chen now represented Happy. But the deepest markings on his skin were those from his time as Blue Rain’s first captain, the person who had laid down the foundation for Blue Rain!

Applause.

The entire stadium burst into applause.

From every corner of the stadium, from every corner of everyone’s hearts, came forth applause.

Flowing Cloud fell to the side as a result of the Claw of Darkness, and the Confusion on Windward Formation and Swoksaar ended at the same time. And Wei Chen continued his tenacious struggle.

Not good. Something was wrong.

Yu Wenzhou wasn’t someone who relied on his intuition. He made all of his judgments based on the opponent’s movements and behavior.

Wei Chen was desperately keeping the two of them tied down here, but there was no way that victory would be decided here. What would determine the final victory would still be that 3v3 battle!

3v3. Blue Rain had made such a confident assault, and their confidence had stemmed from the fact that Happy didn’t have their healer. They could attack unrestrained, trading blood for blood, until they defeated the opponent with the greatest speed possible. But because he and Lu Hanwen had been delayed all this time, the two of them hadn’t been able to enter the battle over there. So, this offensive of theirs became somewhat inefficient.

And over there, Happy had three attackers. In terms of damage output, they had the advantage over Blue Rain. 3v2, blood for blood, Blue Rain was bound to take more damage. Even if they had a healer to support them, because there were only two attackers, the explosiveness of their attacks was underwhelming, which would only drag on the battle longer.

The longer this dragged on, the more health they would lose and need the healer to restore. Then, that turned this into a trade of health for mana, the healer’s mana.

If Happy’s healer successfully joined the battle at this time, and the two sides entered a prolonged conflict…

Not good. It would be extremely unfavorable toward Blue Rain.

The healer didn’t have enough mana, so they needed to fight and end this battle quickly. But Blue Rain wasn’t a team that was good at a speedy attack. They were good at defensive counterattacks, waiting for the opponent to move first before striking. For this, the importance of defending the healer was obvious. Happy’s goal truly was to target Blue Rain’s healer. Trade their own health for the healer’s mana, wear down Blue Rain’s healer until he was useless, so that Blue Rain had no way of fighting at their usual rhythm.

Target the healer.

From the professional circle to the in-game Arena, the most common strategy in team battles.

It was no surprise at all. And yet, it was always effective.

Chapter 1421 - Understood by Everyone

We can’t keep it up!

Right when Yu Wenzhou realized what Happy’s true strategy was, Huang Shaotian also started to feel pressured.

3v3. Team Blue Rain’s side had a healer. If it was a direct confrontation, their side should have the advantage. The problem was that this 3v3 wasn’t the only fight taking place. From an overall perspective, their slight advantage was not nearly enough. They needed speed, explosiveness, DPS, and time to eliminate their opponents.

Happy’s fifth player still hadn’t appeared, and it wasn’t just out of patience. Huang Shaotian had deduced a certain possibility: Qiao Yifan’s Phantom Demon had gone to switch with Happy’s healer.

Blue Rain held the advantage during this period of time. However, lowering Happy’s health bars wasn’t enough. They needed to kill a player from Happy before their Cleric arrived.

Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan were clearly far from achieving this goal. From time to time, the two would look towards the other battle, hoping Yu Wenzhou and Lu Hanwen would hurry and come. However, help never arrived.

The two didn’t try to urge their teammates to hurry up. None of them, including their healer Xu Jingxi, typed a single word.

There was no need to say anything. When Huang Shaotian had called out to Zheng Xuan and Xu Jingxi to counterattack, the other side should have gotten the message and made the appropriate decision. If they hadn’t come yet, it could only mean that their situation didn’t permit them to.

Huang Shaotian’s side could not see the other battle. How could they know that their old captain Wei Chen was struggling with all his might to keep Yu Wenzhou and Lu Hanwen from leaving?

As a famed opportunist, Huang Shaotian had an excellent read of the match.

Even though he didn’t know the reason, without either Yu Wenzhou or Lu Hanwen, he understood that just his and Zheng Xuan’s attacks weren’t enough. They had dealt quite a bit of damage to Lord Grim and Boundless Sea, but they had taken even more damage. Happy’s side had three attackers, after all.

Boom boom boom!

Artillery fire came from both Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain and Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain. Ye Xiu and Fang Rui were dodging, but Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan? They had their characters rush through the gunfire to attack.

This was because of the difference in team compositions. Team Blue Rain had a healer, and that enabled them to be recklessly aggressive.

Their health was guaranteed to be above a safe level at the cost of the mana from Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker. White light constantly flashed, protecting Troubling Rain’s and Bullet Rain’s health.

Huang Shaotian felt that the situation wasn’t good, so he constantly checked on Soul Speaker’s situation.

The constant flashes of white light were somewhat glaring to look at. During intense team fights, the healers would often look like this. However, it was only a 3v3, yet Soul Speaker was already this busy.

It was because of their current tactics.

But strangely, Happy made no attempts to stop them.

How could Ye Xiu and others in Happy not understand their intentions? Of course they would, but they seemed to be fine with it. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain stood farther away, so Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan didn’t target her. Xu Jingxi had his Soul Speaker stand in a position, where Su Mucheng couldn’t reach him, so that his spells would not be interrupted. With him dodging around, Su Mucheng simply gave up and stopped targeting him.

Happy was going along with Blue Rain’s plans. They were practically setting up the conditions for Blue Riain’s plans to work, as if they were luring Blue Rain to do it.

Yu Wenzhou and Lu Hanwen still hadn’t arrived. Was this all part of Happy’s plans?

Huang Shaotian felt like something wasn’t right. Troubling Rain began attacking more carefully, no longer as reliant on their healer.

Zheng Xuan felt a change from Huang Shaotian. Without asking about it, he immediately matched his Bullet Rain with Huang Shaotian’s rhythm. It wasn’t that this guy couldn’t figure out the problem, rather, he was just too lazy to think. As a result, he rarely thought deeply during a match. He always played lazily, for example, like how he was just going along with what his teammate did.

Boom!

Huang Shaotian was hesitating, when he suddenly heard a muffled sound.

To their side, on top of a long wall of medium height, a head suddenly poked out from a crack. The head was covered with ash and blood and in a utterly pathetic state.

Who?

For a moment, Huang Shaotian wasn’t sure who the character was, and had to check the name by sliding his cursor over him.

Windward Formation.

It was Wei Chen’s Windward Formation?

Has it finally been settled?

Just when Huang Shaotian thought this, that bloody head suddenly retracted.

It looks like it’s about over.

Huang Shaotian continued to think. If Windward Formation was eliminated, the two on that side could come over and help them. Then, they could strengthen their offense. Even if Happy’s healer arrived, it would still be a 5v4. Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan had already lowered Happy’s health significantly, thus the match would certainly end in Blue Rain’s victory.

Continue to attack!

Huang Shaotian was about to shift gears back, when an order came from their captain Yu Wenzhou: slow.

It was just one word. It wasn’t clear who Yu Wenzhou was referring to, but Huang Shaotian immediately slowed down.

Zheng Xuan and Xu Jingxi also saw the order, and made the same decision. Their offense suddenly slowed.

“Woah, have they figured it out already?” There was no way Ye Xiu wouldn’t notice such a change.

“Old Wei, you dead yet?” Ye Xiu said.

There was no reply. Wei Chen saw it, but he could only curse inwardly. How could he have any time to chat?

“Keep them nervous!” Ye Xiu also sent out an order. His Lord Grim and Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea suddenly went aggressive.

What?

Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan were startled.

Ye Xiu and Fang Rui had tried their hardest to stay on the defensive. Happy had no healer, so they needed to carefully preserve their health. They could not afford to be as reckless as Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had some healing capabilities, but in such an intense battle, his healing was like trying to put out a burning cart with a cup of water.

Now, the two suddenly bared their fangs. That was a fierceness only Troubling Rain and Bullet Rain previously had!

Happy’s healer has arrived?

That was the first thought from Blue Rain’s team members. Sure enough, An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands appeared from behind a stone pillar. His cross, Holy Contract, glowed with white light, a spell ready to cast.

Shua!

Holy light surrounded Lord Grim. In that instant, the holy light seemed to converge and then blossom into a wave of resplendence.

Critical heal!

It was similar to a critical hit from an attack. A critical heal would heal 50% more, just like a how a critical hit dealt 50% more damage.

Lord Grim’s health instantly shot up a chunk. Little Cold Hands had cast the Cleric’s strongest heal, Holy Words. Lord Grim’s sudden increase in health made Huang Shaotian’s heart hurt.

“Fuck, you bastard. You’re not afraid of overhealing?” Huang Shaotian started his trash talking again.

“I’m not afraid at all!” Ye Xiu replied. Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella shined with white light as well. He had healed himself. The amount healed was tiny, but nevertheless, he would always heal himself from time to time.

“Because we have more than enough mana!” Ye Xiu said. There was no need to hide it at this point. He believed that Blue Rain had certainly figured out their intentions by now, but what could they do? They had already accomplished their goal. Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker had consumed a substantial amount of mana. Even if they knew, they had no way of changing it. And soon, he would still need to consume more mana, because it was no Happy’s turn to attack.

Rush them!

Lord Grim, Boundless Sea, and Dancing Rain attacked together. An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands also went into the open, becoming their pillar. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain no longer let Blue Rain do as they pleased. Dancing Rain leaped into the air, and found her target, Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker.

She knew that Soul Speaker was here, and had thought about how to quickly reach him. However, she hadn’t attacked. Happy’s intentions were truly too obvious.

And this was only for Blue Rain.

The viewers had figured it out far earlier than Blue Rain.

Because when Blue Rain had guessed that Happy’s Cleric was on his way there and had seized that opportunity to attack, they had seen that An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands had gone into position even earlier. But because of Ye Xiu’s orders, he had carefully stayed hidden and waited.

The unskilled players might not understand why, but if Pan Lin and Li Yibo couldn’t understand why given these circumstances, then they would simply be too clueless.

Happy’s plans were obvious, and they watched as Blue Rain fell for it. When Pan Lin and Li Yibo discussed it, they believed that Yu Wenzhou, Lu Hanwen, and Wei Chen’s battle would be key.

As it turned out, Wei Chen was miraculously able to hold on. He stalled two players simultaneously, even if it was such an embarrassing manner…

“Wei Chen is this match’s MVP!” Li Yibo said, “I’ve never seen anyone that could make Yu Wenzhou look so helpless.”

“But it looks like he’s reached his limit!” Pan Lin said. He gave his respects to the old general. Windward Formation had fallen. Wei Chen had done his all, exhausting the entirety of his character’s life.

“Happy’s healer is almost there! Perhaps this will be a new turning point!” Pan Lin said.

“There seems to be a trap!” Li Yibo saw Yu Wenzhou’s and Lu Hanwen’s movements, and suddenly sniffed something out.

Chapter 1422 - Reversal

Hurry up and heal him!

The health on Wei Chen’s Windward Formation was about to hit zero. The viewers focused their eyes onto An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands, hoping he would go over and rescue Windward Formation.

Many of the viewers had felt touched, seeing Wei Chen’s tenacity. They hadn’t cared before, but now, they held their hopes for Happy. They didn’t want to see Wei Chen, who worked so hard and ended up in such a sorry state, to fall just like that.

If Windward Formation died here, wouldn’t all of the preparation that Happy had laid out be pointless?

Hurry!

Everyone stared at Little Cold Hands attentively. Among them was Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou.

Hurry and come!

He had the same thoughts. Swoksaar continued to attack Windward Formation, but his gaze was in a different direction. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud followed suit.

He isn’t able to get there!

With the help from an omniscient view, the more skilled spectators could feel it.

“It’s a trap!” Li Yibo saw through it.

“He truly is Yu Wenzhou. To think he could still come up with a scheme in this situation. He’s using Windward Formation as bait to lure Happy’s Little Cold Hands over. He wanted to pick him off!” Li Yibo said.

The camera quickly pulled out a bird’s eye view of the battle. The indicators on Little Cold Hands, Swoksaar, Flowing Cloud, and Windward Formation suddenly became brighter. Swoksaar and Flowing Cloud looked to be readying for the final killing blow on Windward Formation through a pincer attack, but at the same time, their pincer attack had locked onto Little Cold Hands. If Little Cold Hands went over to heal Windward Formation, he would be intercepted midway and trapped.

With the enemy healer under their control, killing off Windward Formation would only take an instant. Afterwards, Happy would not only be down one person, but their healer would be in the enemy’s hands as well. Happy would fall into a disadvantageous situation.

All of this happened in a flash. Happy did not have a single second to spare, if they wanted to rescue Wei Chen’s Windward Formation,

The battle seemed to have frozen in this instant. What Blue Rain had predicted would happen, didn’t happen.

As a result, the slight pause from intentionally slowing their attacks became extremely obvious.

Wei Chen was surprised at first, but after carefully paying attention to Swoksaar’s and Flowing Cloud’s movements, he quickly figured it out.

“Haha,” He laughed in the chat.

Yu Wenzhou knew that once this moment had passed, his plan would be ruined. Their cunning old captain would certainly realize it. A warning’s probably been sent out already?

Who was to blame?

Yu Wenzhou looked at Happy’s motionless Cleric. He knew that Happy’s Cleric was a rookie, and not a particularly talented one like Happy’s other rookies. An Wenyi was oftentimes viewed as Happy’s weak point.

But then again, Happy used their weak point as bait, and came up with several traps. This was Ye Xiu’s speciality. Using one’s own weakness and turning it around to become the opponent’s downfall.

What about now?

Could it be because this rookie Cleric was too slow to react and failed to notice Windward Formation’s situation, ruining Yu Wenzhou’s carefully thought out plan?

If that was truly the reason, Yu Wenzhou could only sigh at his bad luck. A hole had appeared in his plans because his opponent’s skill was too poor. What could he do?

Knowing that this plan had failed, Yu Wenzhou had Swoksaar attack. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud also rushed forward and swung down, taking down the last bit of Windward Formation’s health. Windward Formation became the first player to be eliminated from the team competition. While stalling Blue Rain’s two players, he had truly exhausted everything, including his character’s life.

Even now, there were still no signs of any sort of response from Happy’s side.

“How could a healer be this bad??” Countless viewers slammed their tables in anger and cursed. Many of the crowd members were extremely dissatisfied with An Wenyi as well. They had forgiven this rookie healer the whole way through and believed in him just like the rest of Team Happy. But now, he just did nothing as Wei Chen’s efforts were wasted. Who could endure such an injustice?

“Is he stupid?”

“Get down!”

“Quit!”

An Wenyi clearly didn’t have any braindead fans who defended him no matter what. The fans loved or hated him depending on his performance.

It was fine if you weren’t skilled enough. No one disregarded the fact that he was a rookie. What they cared about more was his attitude, a proactive attitude.

It wasn’t even important if An Wenyi could save Windward Formation or not. They were angry that he just sat there staring into space, as if he didn’t know what was happening on the other side of the battle.

It was okay if you failed, but you can’t just do nothing.

To the spectators, An Wenyi was a person who did nothing. Curses instantly filled the stadium. However, the match still went on.

After killing Windward Formation, Swoksaar and Flowing Cloud quickly rushed to join with the rest of the team. The two hadn’t taken much damage.

On the other side of the battle, it was now Happy’s turn to be reckless.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain took the high grounds and tunneled onto Soul Speaker. Zheng Xuan wanted to protect his healer, so he started firing at Su Mucheng. At this distance, his Spitfire Bullet Rain could reach her. The force from a Burst Grenade threw Dancing Rain off from the high grounds. However, Su Mucheng quickly adjusted, landing Dancing Rain at another attack point.

The home game advantage!

In this exchange against Zheng Xuan, Su Mucheng fully displayed her familiarity with this region. She didn’t even need to look around to find a suitable attacking position.

In the group arena, Zheng Xuan had beaten Su Mucheng in the 1v1. He didn’t lack the confidence in contesting against Su Mucheng. However, in this team competition, while his target was Dancing Rain, Su Mucheng’s target was Soul Speaker. As a result, Zheng Xuan needed to consider both sides. It was just too much to think about. For a lazy person like Zheng Xuan, it was truly torture.

He couldn’t hold down Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain. In the end, all of the misfortune fell onto Xu Jingxi.

Soul Speaker ran around, but Su Mucheng was always able to quickly catch him. If it was as simple as you-chase-I-run, then Xu Jingxi could lure the opponents into the area, where Blue Rain had originally planned on fighting Happy in. But the problem was that he could not leave because he had to heal his allies on Blue Rain.

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain was being pincered by Ye Xiu and Fang Rui. While Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker dodged Dancing Rain’s attacks, he had to think of every possible way to keep Troubling Rain healthy.

If this situation continued, Blue Rain’s three players had no chances of winning. But now, this period had passed. Yu Wenzhou and Lu Hanwen joined the battle. The tides shifted once again. A Curse Arrow shot towards the high-up Dancing Rain. The greatsword, Flame Shadow, cut into battle and danced alongside Ice Rain.

“You guys are finally here!” Huang Shaotian let out a sigh of relief. Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker had been baited and then forced to heal afterwards, causing him to constantly consume mana. Now, Blue Rain had the 5v4, relieving him of some pressure! They could not let this opportunity go.

“Attack!” Yu Wenzhou ordered. All of Blue Rain went on the offensive.

“Focus on restraining, avoid trading, increase their mana consumption,” Yu Wenzhou pointed out the overall strategic direction. They had the numbers advantage, but Happy had used up much of their healer’s mana. They needed to fight carefully. If their healer went out of mana too early, their advantage would instantly crumble.

Usually, teams would utilize their numbers advantage to launch an all-out attack and hopefully kill a target to widen the advantage, before the other side’s sixth player arrived. In the Glory team competition, most victories were obtained in this way.

However, it wasn’t suitable for the current Blue Rain to launch an all-out attack because their healer did not have the mana to support such an endeavor. As a result, Yu Wenzhou emphasized that they wouldn’t be going all out to kill an enemy player. They couldn’t waste their numbers advantage though, so they needed to carefully go about it. While killing an enemy player was the main objective, it could not be forced.

Calm.

Besides calmness, there was only calmness.

Yu Wenzhou was always calm. Whether Team Blue Rain had the lead, was falling behind, or was in a difficult spot, he would never lose his cool. He would always search for the most reliable method to deal with the situation. It was through this foundation that allowed Huang Shaotian to find an opportunity to wreck havoc on the battlefield.

But soon afterwards, when Blue Rain attacked, they encountered an unexpected response.

Attack!

Yes, they went on the offensive, but Happy also went on the offensive.

It was a 4v5, yet Happy was still attacking.

It was a standard team competition situation, yet both teams responded in unconventional ways.

The side with the numbers advantage played conservatively. The side with the numbers disadvantaged played aggressively.

The viewers were all dumbstruck. They had no idea how such a strange situation had come about.

Only the pro-level players who were watching the match could feel the balance shifting, when they saw this scene.

“Happy is the one in control!”

Wang Jiexi, Xiao Shiqin, Zhang Xinjie… all of the top experts had the same thought.

Because this reversed situation had resulted from Blue Rain’s healer using up too much mana.

And everything had been set up by Happy.

This current situation should be within Happy’s plans.

Wei Chen’s Windward Formation hadn’t been ignored by Happy’s healer. Happy hadn’t planned on saving Windward Formation in the first place.

Wei Chen obtaining victory no matter the means included coldly sacrificing himself.

Blue Rain’s two generations of captains, a confrontation between the original owner and the successor of Swoksaar?

In the end, it was just a topic to talk about.

This was a team competition, and what Wei Chen pursued was the team’s victory and nothing more.

Chapter 1423 - Competing for First

Attack!

Both teams attacked.

Blue Rain, with the numbers advantage, played defensively. Happy, with the numbers disadvantage, played aggressively.

Is that fine? Is Happy looking to kill themselves?

Quite a few people had their doubts. But when they looked at the situation more closely, they discovered that it might not be the case.

Because of Blue Rain’s tactical goal, Blue Rain looked increasingly uncomfortable facing Happy’s aggression. Even if they had an extra player, Happy’s reckless fighting negated the advantage. An extra player simply meant another target to attack, and wouldn’t that mean more overall damage? In the meantime, Happy was relying on their healer to hold on!

Trying to suppress Happy’s offense through attacks would be even more difficult. Happy’s team composition needed to be taken into consideration.

Fang Rui, the master of playing dirty.

Su Mucheng, the long ranged Launcher.

Ye Xiu, the all-class expert. He wasn’t famous for his dirtiness, but his dirtiness wasn’t to be underestimated. Did you think he didn’t have a part in creating the dirty playstyle?

Suppressing these three truly wouldn’t an easy task.

Their reckless fighting was a huge a burden on their healer. It required excellent judgement, fast reactions, and exceptional timing to keep up with them.

An Wenyi had talents but also weaknesses in these areas. Little Cold Hand’s new equipment helped make up for it to a certain extent, but having him take control of such a chaotic battlefield would be worrying for Happy.

However, the current situation was rather favorable for him.

Happy had a total of four players.

Su Mucheng’s Launcher was a long-ranged Launcher. She wandered around the edges of the battlefield and didn’t come into contact with the center of it, so she received very little damage.

As a result, An Wenyi only needed to take care of Lord Grim and Boundless Sea. Those two may be fighting recklessly, but since he didn’t need to take care of the usual four players like in a typical team fight, the burden on him was drastically reduced. For An Wenyi, looking after four players was worrying, but he was plenty confident in taking care of just two players.

“What a wonderful detail!” Li Yibo discovered this point and immediately gave praise.

A team like Happy’s was a blessing to the players. Even if you had weaknesses, the team could still make up for it and create a stage for you to perform brilliantly.

“Speaking of which, this was originally Team Blue Rain’s specialty!” Li Yibo thought of this point.

Yes, Team Blue Rain was a very player-inclusive team, a trait that gave them great flexibility. For most teams, when their important player left, they hoped to find a similar player with the same class and playstyle to fill in the gap, as to prevent the team’s tactical system from breaking apart. But Blue Rain? Blue Rain didn’t cling onto this idea.

After Yu Feng left, everyone was wondering what Berserker player Blue Rain would find as a replacement. Instead, Blue Rain picked out a little Blade Master demon and announced that this kid was their most important transfer of the season. In the following seasons, Blue Rain remained as the mighty Blue Rain.

Many players performed well in Blue Rain, but after leaving the team, they appeared mediocre. Lin Feng, who left Blue Rain for Wind Howl, was one such example.

As a rather peculiar battle Thief, Lin Feng was a unique existence with quite a bit of fame in the Glory community. When discussing Thieves, after Fang Rui was Lin Feng.

Fang Rui had boldly chosen to change classes this season. Then, Lin Feng took his place in Wind Howl, inheriting the number one Thief character, Doubtful Demon. Many people thought that he would reach new heights, and the title of Number One Thief would easily be his. They believed that interest in the the battle Thief playstyle would soar due to Lin Feng’s new status.

And the result?

Despite having an All-Star level character, Lin Feng’s days in Wind Howl weren’t as prosperous as many had expected.

Let alone his performance on stage, just the numbers showed a considerable decrease compared to his time in Team Blue Rain, despite having a more powerful character. In the past, Lin Feng had drawn quite a bit of attention. After leaving Team Blue Rain, he took control of a more powerful character, yet instead of a meteoric rise, he sunk into mediocrity.

Team Blue Rain was a team that could give each player a stage to shine on. But from the looks of it, Happy could do the same. Even a lesser skilled player like An Wenyi could become Happy’s pillar of support.

Perhaps in the beginning, Happy had been a newly formed grassroots team, so they had no other choice.

But in the winter transfer season, Happy had the opportunity to find a better healer. At that time, Happy had an extraordinary win record, better than many teams not just by a little bit. Happy had such a glaring weakness too. Numerous healers from mid-tier and low-tier teams raised their heads, hoping Happy would recruit them and let them join this rising dark horse.

But Happy chose not to!

From the start of the winter transfer window to the end, Happy showed no intentions of doing so. After the winter break, Happy presented a full set of new equipment for Little Cold Hands, showing their trust in their rookie healer. Afterwards, this rookie healer proved that Happy’s trust in him was not unfounded. His performances gradually became steadier, and his role in the team gradually became clearer. The doubt towards him lessened day by day.

In today’s match, when Windward Formation fell without any sort of help from his healer, even the home team fans felt dissatisfied with him. But soon afterwards, as the battle progressed, everyone realized that all of this had been part of Happy’s plan.

When they saw An Wenyi, whose ability was often called into question, perfectly support Ye Xiu and Fang Rui, they began to understand the reasoning behind Happy’s arrangements.

Perhaps it was somewhat cruel.

If Windward Formation was still here, An Wenyi would have to split more of his attention to take care of him, and things might not go as smoothly for Happy.

If the healer couldn’t keep up, the healer’s team would definitely be suppressed in a chaotic battle.

This was an important note in this match.

Blue Rain clearly had the numbers advantage, yet why were they feeling constrained? It was simple. It was because their healer could not keep up. Blue Rain’s Paladin, Soul Speaker, needed to conserve mana and could not support a full-on aggression.

But under Happy’s threat, it would not be good if Soul Speaker didn’t take up more of a burden.

“Attack their healer!” Yu Wenzhou finally ordered, adjusting Blue Rain’s strategy.

Happy’s healer might not be the best, but he was more than good enough to support two characters.An Wenyi’s mastery of timing and Little Cold Hand’s critical heals were a big blow to Blue Rain’s strategy.

Zheng Xuan wasn’t a spirited player in the first place. After shooting a few bullets, a holy light would shine and his target’s health would go up instead of down. It was truly disheartening.

This sort of trade isn’t favorable for us!

Because of Su Mucheng’s long range and the craftiness of Ye Xiu and Fang Rui, Blue Rain’s numbers advantage was stifled. At this moment, their only point of breakthrough was Happy’s healer. He was the one supporting Happy. Directly attacking him would be more effective usage of Blue Rain’s numbers advantage.

Triple Slash!

Huang Shaotian, the opportunist, had been ready to attack Happy’s healer. When Yu Wenzhou gave the order, he just happened to have found a good opportunity. He Triple Slashed to open up a path, and Troubling Rain immediately made his way over.

Crash!

Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella instantly opened up in front of him, blocking his way.

Troubling Rain’s sword did not fall. The second slash flashed out, moving horizontally across the umbrella. The half step gave him a new angle, and he went for it with the Triple Slash!

Dong!

Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella moved across again, ready to block the Triple Slash. But Troubling Rain had already switched moves to guard against it. Wasn’t that also an attack? Troubling Rain used Guard, blocking the attack. The self-knockback from Guard sent Troubling Rain outwards.

Turn around, Colliding Stab!

It was a Berserker low-level skill, so Troubling Rain could obviously learn it. The damage wasn’t important. It was a movement skill, so every player regarded it as an important skill to learn. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had also learned this skill. It was a frequently used movement skill in his arsenal.

In a trail of smoke, Troubling Rain dashed towards Little Cold Hands. The other members of Blue Rain had also seen Yu Wenzhou’s order and coordinated with Huang Shaotian. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud moved in front of Lord Grim, stopping Lord Grim from pursuing Troubling Rain.

However, Ye Xiu ignored the intercept. Lord Grim leaped backwards and instantly rushed out with three movement skills. His target, Soul Speaker!

Trade?

Ye Xiu’s intentions once again surprised everyone.

“Is Happy planning on trading their healer for Blue Rain’s?” Pan Lin cried out.

“This… I really don’t understand!” A rare moment from Li Yibo, who hadn’t made any mistakes yet for this match. He directly acknowledged that he didn’t understand Happy’s intentions.

Yes, who could understand it?

Happy held the advantage despite the numbers disadvantage, and it was all because of their healer.

Their healer had an abundance of mana, while their opponent’s healer had used up a lot of mana. This difference had come from Happy’s many set-ups, obtained from sacrificing Wei Chen’s Windward Formation. This should have been their key to victory

On the other hand, Blue Rain had their hands tied because of their healer. But with Happy having their healer as well, Blue Rain could not abandon their own healer. This situation was good for them though. Happy was unexpectedly not going to rescue their healer and instead attacking Blue Rain’s. Wasn’t this trade beneficial to Blue Rain?

By sacrificing Wei Chen, Happy gained the upper hand. It was a beautiful play from Happy.

But this time, supposing that Happy completed this trade, it would be a beautiful win for Blue Rain.

And this beautiful win for Blue Rain would come from Happy’s own hands.

Li Yibo wasn’t the only one who couldn’t understand it. Blue Rain didn’t either.

Chapter 1424 - The Healers of the Two Sides

Wipe out Little Cold Hands. How would Happy respond to that? Yu Wenzhou had considered all sorts of possibilities, but the decision to give up on the healer had only surfaced for a mere moment.

Under these circumstances, how could Happy abandon their healer?

But that was exactly what happened; Happy didn’t bother making any moves to protect Little Cold Hands. Ye Xiu started it and Fang Rui followed suit, then, Su Mucheng who had been continuously harassing Soul Speaker, began to focus her cannonfire as well.

Blue Rain’s members were all rather stunned. For a moment, they didn’t know what to do.

In the current situation, Happy shouldn’t choose to abandon their healer. Everyone knew that, so how would Blue Rain not? They were the ones who could feel the pressure brought by the difference between the two healers.

So when their captain told them to wipe out Happy’s healer, they knew all too well the reasoning behind this.

However, Happy instead chose to focus on Blue Rain’s healer. They couldn’t understand this decision at all.

What was Happy scheming?

Not just Blue Rain, but all the spectators couldn’t help but think that way.

After all, everyone was like as Li Yibo had said; they couldn’t figure out what Happy was up to.

There must be a deeper reason, right? If it was just a trade, then that was unreasonable.

The spectators didn’t understand; they could just joke around about it. Li Yibo didn’t understand; he could yell about it in the broadcast. However, what about Yu Wenzhou? As Blue Rain’s captain and their commander on the field, he couldn’t make a decision blindly.

However, right now, he had to, because there was no time for him to consider the situation slowly. Hesitation was already surfacing amongst Blue Rain’s ranks. Without a clear command to direct them, if they wanted to save their Soul Speaker, but also wanted to take down Little Cold Hands, they might end up with nothing accomplished and their efforts wasted. Then, they really would be on the track to losing.

Was this hesitation something Happy purposefully tried to elicited?

That was all Yu Wenzhou could come up with in the time he was given. His mind moved fast, but at a time like this he wanted nothing more than a skill that could stop time, pause the entire battlefield and let him contemplate their situation properly.

But now, he had to take decisive action.

Thus, Yu Wenzhou used his actions to direct his teammates. Swoksaar raised his arm and pointed Curse of Destruction at Little Cold Hands, unleashing a curse.

Understood!

Blue Rain’s members immediately understood, so no matter how hesitant they felt, they all went directly after Little Cold Hands. If they killed the Cleric quick enough, then they might even be able to go back and rescue their Soul Speaker. Considering endurance, Paladins had the advantage over Clerics. After all, this was a class that could act as an MT. With their plate armor, plus their Holy Shield Technique, Halo Smash, Life Activation, Extreme Survival, etc, or defensive skills, or skills that could help them endure. Otherwise, why would people say that Paladins were more defensive?

Xu Jingxi was also keeping watch for Yu Wenzhou’s decision.

Their opponents were probably aiming for a trade, and what they wanted, naturally, was to see their opponent’s healer wiped out while theirs was fine.

So, this decision wasn’t abandoning him, and Xu Jingxi naturally couldn’t just sit and watch. He had to be the most focused member on the field, because he would be facing off against three of Happy’s members, and his goal was to survive through this attack, as long as he could.

A Holy Shield Technique first!

Xu Jingxi decided. Since healers weren’t very good at movement, he didn’t bother trying to avoid Happy’s members and play hide and seek with them. He planned to play to the Paladin’s talents and take every chance he could get to survive.

However, after he made the actions to activate the technique, but Holy Shield Technique didn’t appear!

He was silenced?

Xu Jingxi startled. This silence came from… Little Cold Hand’s Sacred Fire…

An Wenyi, against an assault even more intense than the one Xu Jingxi was facing was still supporting Happy’s offensive at a time like this?

This time, it was a Sacred Fire. Next, was he going to send over a Holy Commandment or something?

Blue Rain naturally wouldn’t let An Wenyi have it so easy. Letting a Sacred Fire through was careless. No matter what the next skill was, they would interrupt it at once.

Just this Sacred Fire was enough to prove Happy’s determination. They didn’t seem to be trying to play a trick or anything. They seemed to be completely focused on this trade between healers.

At this point, even if they had made a mistake, even if they had missed something, they could only continue charging down the path they had chosen!

Seeing Happy’s determination, Yu Wenzhou didn’t waver, instead hardening his resolve.

All out offense. Both sides were putting everything they had into DPS.

Neither team’s healer bothered with trying to dodge, both doing their best to endure the assault head on.

Happy’s Little Cold Hands had low defense, but An Wenyi was a master at grabbing opportunities. Even under this siege, he still managed to time a few instant cast heals for himself. Powerful, high crit rate heals instantly restored Little Cold Hands’ health, almost like bringing himself back from the brink of death.

As for Blue Rain’s Soul Speaker, he had high defense and more health than Little Cold Hands. Though his self protection methods had been interrupted by Little Cold Hands’ Sacred Fire at first, messing up his rhythm, he still seemed more likely to survive than Little Cold Hands.

But reality proved otherwise.

Though Soul Speaker had more health than Little Cold Hands, he wasn’t at 100 percent, only 71.

This was the effect of Su Mucheng’s harassment just now.

In an all out battle, no character would stay at 100 percent. For a good healer, keeping each character’s health at a safe level within their control, that was enough. In addition, Xu Jingxi has fell into an awkward position where his mana might not be enough, so he spent as little of it as possible. Thus, Blue Rain’s entire team was at a slightly lower health, including himself.

However, in the blink of an eye, he had fallen into a situation where he had to use his health to endure. Xu Jingxi regretted not casting a few more skills on himself.

Who would win in this trade?

Right now, no one was sure. Little Cold Hands had a weaker defense, and Blue Rain had a strong offense. Soul Speaker had less health, and while Happy might be down one player, they had more ways to provide buffs and debuffs.

Lord Grim’s Sword Boundary increased all of Happy’s Strength and Intelligence.

Boundless Sea’s Pulse Break lowered Soul Speaker’s Strength and Intelligence.

Dancing Rain’s Armor Piercing Missile could destroy Soul Speaker’s Defense.

What made things even more depressing for Xu Jingxi was that just when he had found an opportunity to use Life Activation, Lord Grim waved his hands and sprinkled some Disperse Powder onto him, removing the healing.

“It looks like the two sides are evenly matched,” After a certain point, Li Yibo got a rough idea and carefully made a note.

“Yes, but I feel like Happy’s attacks are more complete. Blue Rain’s offense isn’t perfect,” Pan Lin said.

“They have some doubts in their heart! If it wasn’t for these doubts, they wouldn’t have let Little Cold Hands send out that Sacred Fire,” Li Yibo said.

“They’re still wondering why Happy did what they did!” Pan Lin said.

“Yes, even though they slowly strengthened their resolve, it still delayed them,” Li Yibo said.

“Which side will be faster?” Pan Lin raised the most concerning issue.

“No one will know until the end,” Li Yibo said. This time, it wasn’t that he didn’t dare to guess, it was that he was certain this race wouldn’t be as simple as just a contest of DPS. At the end, just before the final blow, the two sides would certainly try to stop the other.

A trade was just something said.

Any team would hope to kill the other side, while preserving their own. As a result, in the final moment, the two sides would definitely make one last ditch effort to protect their side’s healer. Li Yibo believed this with absolute certainty.

“It’s almost time!” Seeing that Little Cold Hands and Soul Speaker were about to hit 10% health, Li Yibo suddenly spoke out.

“Almost time?” Pan Lin was confused.

“Pay attention to the final moments,” Li Yibo said.

“The deciding moment!” Pan Lin raised his voice to hype up the crowd.

Sure enough, as Li Yibo predicted, a change occurred in the final moments.

A grenade was suddenly thrown from Bullet Rain towards Happy’s space.

Boom!

However, the grenade only flew halfway before exploding. There was no light, only a powerful pressure that appeared even stronger because of the sand. In an instant, a sandstorm formed.

“Burst Grenade!” Pan Lin shouted.

If Zheng Xuan’s sneaky Burst Grenade had landed in Happy’s space, the entirety of Team Happy would be sent flying away, collapsing their encirclement on Soul Speaker.

But Happy had been wary. Lord Grim shot the grenade out of the air, successfully blocking it.

“He truly is Ye Xiu!” Li Yibo praised from the bottom of his heart. Whether it was technique or situational awareness, he deserved praised for all of them.

At this moment, Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar was chanting a curse. Suddenly, a star seemed to twinkle in the cloud of sand stirred up by the Burst Grenade.

It really was a star!

Star Refraction!

A ray of light shot out. No one in Blue Rain had any methods to block it. The bonus skills attached to Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella seemed endless. He had never used this Star Refraction before.

Star Refraction hit all four members of Blue Rain. Although the level one Star Refraction dealt little damage and had no attack effects, Swoksaar’s casting had been interrupted. At the same time, a grenade rolled over.

Star Refraction was just to use up Blue Rain’s methods. The true killing blow was this grenade.

“Burst Grenade!!” Zheng Xuan instantly recognized the grenade, but it was too late for him to block it.

Boom!

Happy returned the favor with a Burst Grenade of their own. But because of this skill’s low level, it wasn’t as powerful as Bullet Rain’s Burst Grenade. Even so, everyone in Blue Rain had been forced flying.

Immortal Guides the Way!

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain was able to squeeze out this skill.

Little Cold Hands was suddenly blown back together with Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud.

Chapter 1425 - Time Difference

“Beautiful!” Pan Lin shouted.

Burst Grenade was undoubtedly a tool to forcefully break encirclements. Blue Rain had intended on using this skill to do so, but before they could act, Happy threw out their own Burst Grenade.

Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella only had one gunner form, and in this match, it had been shown that Laser Beam had been added on as the bonus skill. It was not possible for him to have access to any other high-leveled gunner skill. This Burst Grenade must have come from Dancing Rain’s Devouring Sun.

This grenade successfully invaded Blue Rain’s space and exploded. Everyone thought Blue Rain’s control over the situation had been destroyed, and Happy would be able to rescue their healer. However, in that instant, Huang Shaotian was able to complete an Immortal Guides the Way and borrow the blow-away effect of the skill to send Little Cold Hands flying.

This move was like a gift from the heavens. The fans of Team Blue Rain had experienced several ups and downs in just a split second. Just as they thought that they had lost, Huang Shaotian pulled them back.

Lu Hanwen was careful. He didn’t dare waste Huang Shaotian’s save. The airborne Flowing Cloud swung his greatsword towards Little Cold Hands. On the other end, Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain fired a Stun Bullet and an Ice Bullet towards this side while in the air. They would not let Little Cold Hands escape so easily.

The knockback from a level one Burst Grenade was limited. Compared to the Burst Grenade from Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain, the sand and dust lifted from the explosion only covered a small area. Blue Rain’s unity of will was an impregnable stronghold, forcefully keeping the situation under control. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud stuck close to Little Cold Hands, and Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain immediately dashed over as soon as he landed back onto the ground.

But inside this small-scale cloud of dust, Huang Shaotian noticed a bright flame swaying down.

“Fuck!”

Huang Shaotian immediately realized what it was.

Heat-Seeking Missile!

This skill possessed both a large AoE and strong knockback. It had to be blocked no matter what.

But was where enough time?

Troubling Rain swung his sword with a Sword Draw, the sword light splitting the yellow sand in half. But it wasn’t enough!

It was just off by a bit, but the sword light wasn’t able to reach the Heat-Seeking Missile’s signal in time.

It’s over!

Huang Shaotian felt helpless. This time, there was nothing he could do. But the instant his sword light missed, a black light suddenly flew out. With a shua, the signal was cut out of the air.

Soul Slice!

Huang Shaotian was delighted. He turned his head and saw Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar. Swoksaar had sent out a precise attack at a crucial moment, bringing Blue Rain back once again.

“Steady!” Yu Wenzhou reminded everyone in the chat. The signal, knocked away by the Soul Slice, did not land in Team Blue Rain’s space, but the Heat-Seeking Missile that followed soon afterwards dropped down in a column of flames. An enormous explosion erupted, sending yellow sand everywhere like a volcano. The sand flew into the air and then dropped down like heavy rain. Blue Rain felt a lingering fear, seeing this scene. This attack was far more terrifying than Burst Grenade.

Bang bang bang bang.

Amidst the turbid cloud of yellow sand, sounds of gunfire could be heard. Several black shadows dropped down towards where Blue Rain had trapped Little Cold Hands.

FIM-92 Stinger!

Using the yellow sand as cover, the Stinger had burst apart into multiple missiles before falling down. With the number of missiles there, Blue Rain could not deal with them one by one. Their only choice was to do their best and avoid them. But right at this moment, An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands had struggled out and was heading towards the center of Stinger’s AoE. Seeing that there was no hopes of him being rescued, An Wenyi decided that he would drag them down and make both sides suffer.

But what could Blue Rain do? If they didn’t give chase, An Wenyi might actually be able to escape. Fortunately, Stinger didn’t have a strong knockback like the previous two skills. It wouldn’t be able to break apart the situation, but it would still deal some damage.

In this final exchange, Happy had the upper hand. They were fully utilizing their home game advantage. Taking advantage of the yellow sand as cover, Happy was able to sneak in attack after attack. Blue Rain had just narrowly escaped twice, but there was nothing they could do about the final Stinger.

Happy wasn’t done yet with their harassment. After the Stinger and yellow sand baptism, a crack suddenly appeared in the air. With a rumbling sound, a Death’s Door opened wide.

Everyone in Blue Rain went white.

Wei Chen was no longer there, which meant only Lord Grim could have used this skill.

A level one Death’s Door had lower range and dealt less damage. Even so, its main threat laid in its ability to disrupt the situation. As a result, quite a few Warlocks wouldn’t bother leveling Death’s Door too much. A few points in it was good enough.

A level one Death’s Door had a short range, but Ye Xiu had timed it perfectly. An Wenyi seemed to have received a signal. His Little Cold Hands was running for his life towards there. It looked as if he wanted to jump through the door.

“Go away!”

Immortal Guides the Way!

Huang Shaotian shouted. This time, it was Lu Hanwen that used the skill, forcefully blowing Little Cold Hands away. Blue Rain gave chase as the black tendrils from Death’s Door reached out for them.

Luckily, it’s only level one!

After escaping from Death’s Door’s range, Blue Rain felt incredibly relieved. But soon afterwards, the worst thing that could happen happened.Happy’s three attackers were rushing over, behind them was the corpse of Blue Rain’s healer, Soul Speaker.

In the end, Happy was able to eliminate Blue Rain’s healer first, while Little Cold Hands still had 5% of his health left. The harassment from Happy had completely disrupted Blue Rain’s attacks.

However, one combo was enough to take out 5%.

Blue Rain’s four characters quickly chased after Little Cold Hands, ready to kill him regardless of anything else.

An attack fell!

A holy light suddenly surrounded Little Cold Hands.

Holy Cure! A powerful instant heal. It had a very long cooldown, and Little Cold Hands had already used it not too long ago, so it couldn’t have been ready yet. It was undoubtedly another annoyance by Lord Grim. This time, he had added a heal to his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. It was only level one, but it could not be ignored.

Boom!

Lord Grim was healing, but Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea were attacking. Launchers and Qi Masters did not lack AoE, and the AoEs were coming. Yu Wenzhou and Zheng Xuan were fine. As long-ranged classes, they didn’t need to stick close to Little Cold Hands. But Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen needed to stay close to Little Cold Hands to do anything. Su Mucheng and Fang Rui knew this and took advantage of it, forcing the two to take damage.

Even so, Little Cold Hands didn’t have much health left. Ye Xiu’s heal wasn’t enough for one combo from Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain. All it did was delay the inevitable. Finally, Little Cold Hands fell, and Blue Rain’s players let out a sigh of relief.

4v3 without healers.

It looked to be time for Blue Rain to launch a counterattack, but Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had quietly appeared from behind Blue Rain. With a chant, a ghost boundary was laid down, and without any pause or hesitation, One Inch Ash was like a phantom demon as he ferociously tore into Blue Rain. Ye Xiu, Fang Rui, and Su Mucheng immediately followed suit.

4v3?

The 4v3 never happened.

“What perfect timing!” Pan Lin exclaimed.

Li Yibo was silent. Was it really a coincidence? Li Yibo was hesitant, but Yu Wenzhou was certain that it was.

This was Happy’s map. They had a clear understanding of the distance between this location and the support zone. They knew exactly how long it would take to complete a character trade, or for the sixth player to sub in after a death.

It was a difference in timing. By the time Happy’s sixth player arrived, Blue Rain’s sixth player would have only just started. Blue Rain may have the numbers advantage, but if one of their characters wasn’t there yet, the advantage was negated until he arrived.

4v4. It was a 4v4. And Happy had a fierce warrior in their midsts. He seemed to have no regard for his own character’s health. He rushed straight into the enemy lines and cut off Blue Rain’s retreat.

Then, a pincer!

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui fought crazily too, completely disregarding their own characters, trading blow for blow.

Blue Rain didn’t want this sort of fight, but Happy had cut off their retreat and then focused them, giving Blue Rain no chance to maneuver around. If I’m going to die, then you might as well die with me.

Steady?

We can’t!

Defending required a healer to rely upon. If not, if one player met the focus of four enemies, run? Block? None of those could completely deal with the situation. To do so required support from other players, which was the current situation. Blue Rain was now deeply entangled with Happy.

If this continued, Happy might not have the upper hand though. A team competition wasn’t like an individual competition, where whoever was attacking had the upper hand. In 4v4s, who was attacking and who was defending constantly fluctuated. Right now, it was a chaotic mess. No one was able to easily escape. But Happy had nothing after this, while Blue Rain had their sixth player coming. Happy had the step up the entire time, but was this going to be the end result? Both sides were suffering, but once Blue Rain’s sixth player came, it would be a 5v4. He would just need to wave his hands, and wouldn’t this match be over?

No, this wasn’t the case.

At the final moment, Yu Wenzhou finally understood.

Happy’s plan for the team competition relied on their two point advantage from the group arena!

Chapter 1426 - Giving Out Candy

Yu Wenzhou didn’t neglect their loss in group arena. It was just that from the start, Happy’s arrangements never seemed to take advantage of this point. Even now, Yu Wenzhou wasn’t sure whether Happy had planned this from the beginning, or if it had been an adjustment based on the flow the team competition.

Throughout the course of team competition, he had been trying to guess what Happy’s goals were, but whenever he made a realization, he was always a half beat too slow.

This delay was fatal for him and Blue Rain.

Blue Rain played reactively. A reactive playstyle required one to pinpoint the opponent’s lifeline and then target it. It was through this style that Yu Wenzhou became a Master Tactician. He reacted quickly and thought through issues meticulously, allowing him to swiftly read the situation. Then, he would grasp the opponent’s goals and search out a way to destroy the opponent’s strategy.

However, Happy had carefully concealed their goals from the start. For a period of time, Blue Rain didn’t even have knowledge of Happy’s team composition.

Huang Shaotian had been sent out to investigate, but he ended up trapped by Happy. The rest of Team Blue Rain was forced to be drawn out. This was their first mistake.

However, Blue Rain had no choice but to make the mistake. At the time, the enemy plans weren’t clear, and Yu Wenzhou had no plans to launch a counterattack. As a result, Blue Rain prepared to rescue Huang Shaotian and would make adjustments after doing so.

But then, Happy started giving out candy.

Wei Chen went in for a 1v2. This sort of ace player reliant strategy was commonly used to create a balance on the ace player’s end, while the other side of the battle established a numbers advantage. However, in this match, Wei Chen was at an absolute disadvantage in the 1v2, while the other side of the battle was still just a 3v3. Moreover, for Happy, it was a 3v3 without a healer.

Happy was at a disadvantage in both sides of the battle. If Blue Rain couldn’t grasp this opportunity, they would not be Blue Rain.

Wei Chen’s tenacity was unexpected though. He had successfully stalled two players, causing Blue Rain’s healer to overuse his mana to support Blue Rain’s offense.

In the end, Wei Chen’s Windward Formation died. From this point, Blue Rain seemed to have grasped onto another opportunity, happily gaining a numbers advantage.

They had also used this advantage. When Happy started relying on their healer in the 4v5, Blue Rain decisively targeted Happy’s healer.

At this moment, Happy gave Blue Rain another piece of candy.

They actually abandoned their main pillar of support in the 4v5: their healer.

Happy made a trade with Blue Rain. Both healers ended up as sacrifices. Although Happy had taken out Blue Rain’s healer first, making it more difficult for Blue Rain to finish off their healer, no one would say that Happy had the upper hand.

Up until Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash arrived at the perfect time.

It was beautiful usage of the difference in distance between the two team’s support zones. Blue Rain had less health overall too. If that was all, Happy still wouldn’t have the advantage. However, once their group arena two point lead was taken into account, everything made sense.

Why did Happy work so hard to establish an advantage for their healer and then abandon it all so quickly?

Because their advantage didn’t come from having more mana or having more players on their side.

Yu Wenzhou understood everything now. Happy didn’t want a direct confrontation, especially a 5v5 battle.

The reason?

Just like many of their matches in the regular season, they protected their healer.

Yes, abandoning their healer was a form of protection. An Wenyi may have improved considerably, and his character may have been built just for him, but his capabilities still couldn’t match the capabilities of the healers from powerhouse teams.

The more complex the battle, the more unfavorable it was for An Wenyi and Team Happy. As a result, they simply avoided it. They had no intentions of relying on their healer to win because their healer had never been their strength.

They utilized this so-called advantage, constructing their plans around it. All of these plans came together to take advantage of their true strengths.

No healer.

Team Happy: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Qiao Yifan.

Team Blue Rain: Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian, Lu Hanwen, Zheng Xuan.

From the names, Happy’s player roster stood shoulder to shoulder with Blue Rain’s.

As for characters, Lord Grim’s class itself was an advantage, let alone his full set of Level 80 Silver equipment.

Dancing Rain and Boundless Sea were All-Star characters. Their foundation was there. In terms of upgrading Level 70 Silver equipment to Level 75, the powerhouse teams were no better than Happy. Happy took an even higher-end route. The amount of Level 75 materials in their possession was no fewer than the amount of Level 75 materials that the other teams had. In addition, these two also had Level 80 Silver equipment.

Blue Rain’s biggest advantage was their extra player.

But Song Xiao’s Receding Tides was still heading over, so this advantage didn’t exist right now!

Hurry! Hurry!

The cameraman would focus on Receding Tides from time to time. He wasn’t in the fight at the moment, but everyone knew that he was this match’s deciding factor, especially for Blue Rain.

Blue Rain was trying to stall until Song Xiao arrived.

But Happy understood their intentions. Happy wasn’t going to play tactics with them. Their only goal was to attack regardless of anything else.

Holy light would flash from time to time in this chaotic battle. Ye Xiu was still having his Lord Grim heal. But in this battle without healers, his bit of healing became all the more precious. It was especially loathsome to Blue Rain.

The health on both sides could be depicted as downward slopes.

Who would be the first to fall?

Seeing where Receding Tides was located, everyone was certain of this point. Before he arrived, someone would certainly die. But who?

From the remaining health on each character, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had the lowest. Ever since he started his investigation at the beginning of the match, Huang Shaotian had never rested. He had constantly been in high-intensity fights. His Troubling Rain’s health had never gone up. When Soul Speaker died, he had the lowest health on the team. And he was someone who needed to fight in close range, which naturally made him a target for Happy.

No way to retreat.

If Blue Rain could retreat, they would have certainly done so. Then, they would convene with Song Xiao.

But Happy bit at them too tightly. If they tried to force a retreat and let Happy chase, they would only lose health needlessly. If things went poorly, their corpses might all that be left.

All they could do was try to move the battle towards Song Xiao.

Persist!

Everyone understood. They grit their teeth and bore the pain. The countless people in the crowd stood up anxiously. Happy looked to have the advantage in health, but it wasn’t to the point of having no worries. A single mistake could turn everything around.

Come on!

None of the players on either team could sit still as they stood up and stared at the match screen.

Troubling Rain, 6%!

Who would be the first to fall?

Huang Shaotian had pulled off several miracles this round. Could we see another one with just 6% of his health left?

No one regarded Huang Shaotian as a dead man. As long as he stood on the field, he would always be the greatest threat.

Sword’s Divine Judgement!

Troubling Rain suddenly activated his awakening skill. Huang Shaotian had waited a long time before using this skill. It was a skill that could open up the current situation. As long as there was an opportunity, Blue Rain would still choose to retreat to get closer to Song Xiao.

But..

Qi Guard!

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea raised both arms, forming a Qi Guard, shielding Lord Grim, Boundless Sea, and One Inch Ash all at once. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was outside of the attack’s range and wouldn’t be affected by the wave of sword qi.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim took advantage of the Qi Guard to complete a cast.

Devil World Flower!

A Summoner skill was used, a level one Devil World Flower. It had low health and light attacks, but its functionality was comprehensive.

Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain immediately fired a Blazing Bullet.

Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella suddenly opened.

Bang!

The flames spread out from the impact between Blazing Bullet and the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. The Devil World Flower was unaffected, its vines extending out.

Blue Rain was annoyed! It was such a critical moment, and now they had another target to worry about.

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain leaped into the air, dodging the curling vines. His sword fell. With the buff from Sword’s Divine Judgement, the swing was faster and more ferocious. Before he even landed, the Devil World Flower was cut into pieces.

But Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was waiting for him!

Circle Swing!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a spear and struck towards the sky. Troubling Rain hastily swung his sword to try and block it, but he was too late. The spear stabbed into Troubling Rain and instantly flung him down.

Blue Rain’s other team members immediately tried to save him, but Troubling Rain only had so much health left. How could Happy let him go? Kill!

Troubling Rain became the first to fall. Happy’s fans cheered, while Blue Rain’s fans grit their teeth.

“Sigh… what a pity…” Pan Lin sighed. He had high hopes for Huang Shaotian. He had expected him to perform one final explosive display, but in the end, all he ended up doing was trading his life for a Devil World Flower.

“From the numbers, Huang Shaotian’s hand speed seemed to have fallen,” Li Yibo looked at player hand speed stats and said.

“Ah?”

“He was in a very tense situation throughout the entire match!” Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin let out a sigh. Although it was somewhat unfortunate, no one was a machine. Huang Shaotian hadn’t had a single moment of rest. He had exhausted the most energy out of anyone else in the match.

“But Blue Rain seized this opportunity and took out quite a bit of Boundless Sea’s health,” Li Yibo said.

“Boundless Sea still has 11% health left. Happy has the 4v3 for a short period of time! Ah! Boundless Sea doesn’t care about himself at all. Happy’s focusing on Flowing Cloud!” Pan Lin said.

Chapter 1427 - Countdown

Dazzling light engulfed the battlefield, but soon afterwards, a shadow flashed out.

Lord Grim! Target, Bullet Rain.

“A change in target?” Pan Lin asked.

“No, it’s over,” Li Yibo could see it clearer.

Under the intensive focus fire from the enemies, a character without a retreat path and a healer had no way to survive too long. Life and death was only a matter of seconds. Fan Rui’s Boundless Sea became the next player after Troubling Rain to depart from the battlefield. But Flowing Cloud was also on the verge of death. Ye Xiu didn’t bother with this final blow, instead rushing out into the yellow sand towards Bullet Rain.

Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain and Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar were long ranged. Stalling for time was much easier for them. Team Blue Rain clearly planned on taking advantage of this point. After Troubling Rain and Flowing Cloud fell, the two had no reason to continue fighting. With a turn, they went to convene with Song Xiao.

But Ye Xiu’s pursuit was extremely fast. He had predicted ahead of time that the two would have an easier time running away once their close-ranged allies fell, so he chased after them before the time came.

In the blink of an eye, a considerable distance between the two sides was erased. Zheng Xuan knew he had no chances of winning a footrace against Ye Xiu. His only choice was to kite. Bullet Rain fired a Flash Bullet, but Lord Grim responded with an open of his umbrella and dashed forward with a Charge. Neither his movement speed nor his eyesight was affected.

Zheng Xuan wanted to cry. That bastard was too annoying. He always made people feel helpless.

Boom boom boom, Bullet Rain fired all sorts of bullets. At this point, conserving his mana was pointless. The final outcome would be decided here. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was more of a close-ranged fighter. After Troubling Rain, Boundless Sea, and Flowing Cloud fell, he had the lowest amount of health.

19%.

Fuck, 20%!

Lord Grim healed himself. With a blink, his health jumped to 20%.

So fucking annoying!

For someone like Zheng Xuan who had no fighting spirit, this was no better than torture.

After Boundless Sea, Flowing Cloud finally fell at the hands of Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash. He and Su Mucheng did not immediately follow Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. Dancing Rain instead fired at Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar.

In reality, Su Mucheng had paid particularly close attention to Yu Wenzhou. A Warlock’s set of skills such as Chaotic Rain, Death’s Door, Hexagram Prison, Binding Curse were all control skills that could bring about destruction to this delicate situation. Su Mucheng gave up on a few opportunities to deal damage so that she could keep Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar under control.

Yu Wenzhou played intelligently too. Even if he could not find opportunities to use these disruptive skills, he used his very existence to attract a considerable amount of attention from Happy. Were it not for the threat of a Warlock’s control skills, the pace of the battle would have gone much faster.

Right now, Su Mucheng was entirely focused on Swoksaar. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash also rushed towards him. In this 3v2, Happy no longer focused on a single target, instead splitting up.

But there’s not enough time, is there?

The long-ranged characters had started this battle with relatively more health than the close-ranged characters, and Song Xiao’s Receding Tides was nearly there. The broadcast even put down a countdown to his arrival.

20 seconds!

Blue Rain still had almost half their health left. It didn’t seem possible to kill them all in this amount of time. There were less players on both sides, so their overall damage output was lower than before.

19, 18, 17…

The countdown continued to tick. It no longer seemed possible to kill either of the two Blue Rain members at this point. What mattered now was how much health they would have left by the time Receding Tides arrived. If they only had a sliver of health, Happy could just ignore Receding Tides and finish off Bullet Rain and Swoksaar for the win.

16, 15, 14…

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim finally caught up to Bullet Rain, dodging the two attacks towards him. He grabbed Bullet Rain with a Fling.

Throw!

The landing point was One Inch Ash’s double overlapping ghost boundaries.

Weakened, Frozen, Bullet Rain received two negative status effects as soon as he landed. Soon afterwards, a third ghost boundary appeared, Blind!

Bullet Rain was in trouble. Everyone could see it. The Happy fans cheered excitedly.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim dashed towards Bullet Rain. As he moved, his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella fired towards Yu Wenzhou, forming a pincer with Su Mucheng.

They were originally Best Partners with a spear and cannon combo, but their dual gun synergy was no worse. The attacks from both sides multiplied the pressure on Yu Wenzhou.

Bang!

Swoksaar was hit by Lord Grim’s Stun Bullet.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain completed a movement at just the right time. Electricity crackled into a ball and shot out. The X-1 Extruder sucked in Swoksaar towards One Inch Ash’s ghost boundary.

10, 9, 8, 7…

Only ten second were left. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was struggling to keep Bullet Rain locked into the formation. Fortunately, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim arrived just in time to give him a helping hand.

6, 5, 4, 3…

Song Xiao’s Receding Tides could already be seen, his figure getting closer and closer.

There was no need to count down to zero! Receding Tides was a Qi Master, and Qi Masters didn’t need to get close to attack.

Sky Piercing Strike!

Receding Tides sent out an attack. Rippling qi fired from his two palms, lifting up yellow sand into the air. Like a yellow dragon, it crashed into the battlefield.

The characters in Happy within its attack range hastily moved aside, but at this moment, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash burst apart his ghost boundaries.

Ghost Feast!

The power of the ghost gods were like demonic shadows. Along with the yellow sand scattered by the Sky Piercing Strike and the desolate atmosphere of the ancient ruins, a sense of eeriness could be felt.

Ghost Feast dealt enormous damage, but because of the limited amount of time Qiao Yifan had, there weren’t a lot of ghost boundaries placed down yet. Song Xiao’s Receding Tides invaded like a storm. At full health, he didn’t care about what damage he took. He could quickly break open the situation through force. As a result, Qiao Yifan’ didn’t dare delay and immediately used the skill while he still had the chance.

Boom!

Dancing Rain started aiming at Receding Tides, but Song Xiao ignored the damage and continued his charge forward. His character leaped into the air, Landmine Quake! Another AoE rumbled over.

Yellow sand rose again.

Void Sand Sea had no wind, but the skills from the characters lifted up the sand like a strong storm. Everything always seemed to be wrapped up in sand.

Kill!

Happy did not choose to retreat. They surrounded Swoksaar and Bullet Rain and attacked ferociously. The Landmine Quake knocked Lord Grim into the air, but with a Quick Recover, Lord Grim immediately got up and continued attacking.

Lord Grim’s health: 6%!

The hearts of Happy’s fans tightened.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was extremely important. The stickiness of melee characters were a characteristic that long-ranged classes could not replace. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was a Phantom Demon and didn’t count as a true melee class. If Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim fell, Blue Rain would have three mid- to long-ranged classes. Blue Rain could just pull apart, and Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan would have a difficult time grabbing onto them.

Blue Rain understood this point. Whenever they had a chance, they would focus on Lord Grim.

6% health. A single combo from any of them would be enough to send him off!

Spiral Qi Kill!

Claw of Darkness!

Electric Grenade!

Blue Rain’s three players launched attacks towards Lord Grim from three angles.

But…

All of them missed!

Lord Grim was like a demon. He switched between several movement skills, switching directions three times within a small gap. All three skills hit nothing but air. Then, he turned around and counterattacked!

Everyone in the stadium went crazy.

What was a God? What was a core player? This was the embodiment of one!

Had there been an opening in Blue Rain’s attacks? There didn’t seem to be one, but through extraordinary intuition and control, he dodged a series of attacks that shouldn’t be able to be dodged.

Yu Wenzhou and Zheng Xuan wanted to pull away, but Lord Grim was right besides them. They had no way of escaping.

One Inch Ash’s ghost boundary fell again.

Not only did their attacks fail to land on Lord Grim, they gave One Inch Ash an opportunity to cast a ghost boundary.

This was the value behind a top player. The openings that they could create weren’t ones just anyone could achieve.

Ghost fire blazed inside the Flame Boundary as if trying to refine Swoksaar and Bullet Rain. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain provided assistance with her artillery fire.

Song Xiao was in a difficult situation. He was the healthy general leading the charge, yet he still hadn’t broken open the situation. He was also extremely nervous.

Lord Grim!

Lord Grim was key.

Only 6% health left!

A Flash Burst or a Qigong Blast was enough. Focusing on a single target was to prevent any mistakes. However, their attempt to prevent mistakes backfired. Lord Grim slipped out, and Happy was able to latch onto Blue Rain’s two long-ranged classes.

Flash Burst!

Song Xiao didn’t think too much. Even if he couldn’t kill Lord Grim, he had to at least force him away! That would give his two allies some space to maneuver.

Receding Tides threw everything aside and stepped into One Inch Ash’s Flame Boundary. He took the damage from ghost fire and fired an attack at Lord Grim.

Lord Grim dodged to the side. Yu Wenzhou and Zheng Xuan seized this opportunity and pulled apart, one to the left, the other to the right. But Lord Grim waved his sleeves.

Shadow Cloak!

Swoksaar and Bullet Rain were suddenly grabbed back.

However, Qi Burst!

Receding Tides followed up with another attack, seizing the opening that appeared when Lord Grim used his skill.

Lord Grim’s health instantly turned to zero, but then, a Satellite Beam descended.

Lord Grim’s final move had bound Swoksaar and Bullet Rain together. This Satellite Beam had hit both characters.

Is it over?

Amidst the shining light, the health on both characters rapidly fell, stopping at single digit percentages. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash sent out several slashes, successfully killing Swoksaar. Although he wasn’t able to take down Receding Tides, at this point, victory was already there’s.

With the little health Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain had left, Happy’s remaining two characters ignored Song Xiao and finished him off. No matter how much damage they took, they didn’t care. Song Xiao could be completely disregarded. It didn’t matter how perfect of a condition Receding Tides was in…

Chapter 1428 - Victory

“Victory has already been decided. In the first round of the playoffs, Happy takes their home game win,” The match wasn’t truly over yet, but Pan Lin gave the announcement anyways.

Happy had won five points in the group arena and had won five points in the team competition so far, for a total of ten points.

As for Blue Rain? They had only won three points in the group arena. To win or tie the first round, they would have needed to not only win the team competition, but win it with at least two players left. Unfortunately, they failed to achieve this goal. With Bullet Rain down, Blue Rain had lost five players. Even if Song Xiao took down Su Mucheng and Qiao Yifan, it was impossible for Team Blue Rain to win this round’s team competition.

“Coach Li, how about you give a rundown of this match?” Pan Lin asked.

“This match… how can I say it…” Li Yibo pondered, “Team Happy had completely grasped Team Blue Rain’s tactical traits, limiting Team Blue Rain’s performance by a considerable degree. We can see that the two opportunities seized by Team Blue Rain had actually been intentionally prepared by Team Happy. But you can’t say it was entirely a trap. Those opportunities were indeed good opportunities for Team Blue Rain. It was just that they were met with hindrance during their execution and could not reach the desired outcome.”

“Such as Wei Chen stalling Yu Wenzhou and Lu Hanwen?” Pan Lin said.

“Yes. Happy’s strategy was actually very ambitious. It required an old general, who had left the pro scene seven years ago and only just returned, to contend with Lu Hanwen and Yu Wenzhou, two All-Stars. Let’s think about it for a moment. If Wei Chen’s Windward Formation had been killed earlier, or if he failed to stall both players, the match may have ended completely differently,” Li Yibo said.

“If those imaginary situations really had happened, perhaps Happy might have countermeasures in place?” Pan Lin said.

“This we don’t know. If I had to guess, I’d say probably? After all, it was a rather risky strategy,” Li Yibo said.

“Oh, the match is now officially over. As expected, even though Song Xiao was in a 1v2, he came into the fight much much healthier than Happy’s two players. In the end, he was able to win the 1v2, but it no longer has any effect on the final outcome of today’s match,” Pan Lin said.

“From the data we have on the team competition, Blue Rain had the advantage. After all, the team competition was their win. Unfortunately, if you look at the round as a whole, they lost,” Li Yibo said.

The two teams walked out of their player booths.

The two teams met in the center and shook hands.

Compared to the start of the match, the mood on both teams were now two extremes.

“You played very well. Thanks for the match,” Yu Wenzhou maintained his calm.

“You played so-so,” Ye Xiu wasn’t polite at all.

“We’ll see you next round,” Yu Wenzhou said. If he were anyone else, it might sound like there was a hint of vengeance in his words. But coming from Yu Wenzhou, these words just sounded like he was stating a fact.

Next, Huang Shaotian.

“Hahahaha,” Ye Xiu only laughed.

“What are you so happy about? You just barely won,” Huang Shaotian remarked disdainfully.

“The championships are won by just a narrow margin,” Ye Xiu said.

“Leave it for after you beat us!” Huang Shaotian said.

“That’s next round’s business,” Ye Xiu expressed dully.

The teams passed by each other one player at a time. The two sides had simple exchanges. The winners weren’t arrogant, and the losers weren’t downcast. Happy’s last player as their sixth player, Wei Chen. He shined the brightest in the team competition, doing what people considered impossible.

“Are you convinced?” Wei Chen shook Yu Wenzhou’s hands.

“I’ve always been convinced,” Yu Wenzhou smiled.

“Are you scared?” Wei Chen asked Huang Shaotian.

“What’s there to be scared of,” Huang Shaotian rolled his eyes. He had respect and gratitude towards Wei Chen from the bottom of his heart, but in terms of their interactions, there was no way he could be serious with him.

“Little demon, now you know the might of your senior!” Lu Hanwen was third in line. He was still going through puberty, and his voice hadn’t deepened yet. He was shorter than the other players by a head. Wei Chen rubbed his head instead of shaking his hands.

“Amazing,” Lu Hanwen nodded his head, “Let’s see who’ll win next time, senior!”

“Little bastard!” Wei Chen cursed inwardly. He obviously knew that if he had to fight Lu Hanwen several times, he would definitely lose more than he won. In today’s match, from a PvP perspective, he had been killed by Yu Wenzhou and Lu Hanwen. He had done what he had hoped to accomplish. He had achieved his goal, so he had succeeded, but in terms of winning… let alone him, the team competition had been won by Team Blue Rain.

The final outcome was a difficult problem for the Alliance. They weren’t sure who to give the MVP award to.

Team Blue Rain had won the team competition, but Team Happy had won the overall round. From the overall flow of the team competition, it could be seen that Happy had no intentions of winning. Their goal was to win as many points as possible in the team competition. From this perspective, Happy had been more successful in the team competition. They had achieved what they wanted. However… how could they ignore the actual outcome?

From pure numbers, Huang Shaotian was excellent in the team competition. Whether it was the damage he took or the damage he dealt, he was number one in both categories. His contribution in the team competition was obvious. However, the first problem was that Happy had reached their goal in the team competition, and the second problem was that Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had half his health knocked away by a tree in the group arena. No matter how it was spun, that should be considered a big mistake.

As for Happy’s players? Wei Chen’s performance in the team competition had been astonishing, being the decisive factor there. However, he had died early in the match. There were many other deciding factors later that he wasn’t a part of. He also didn’t appear in the group arena.

For the group arena, Happy’s Mo Fan performed spectacularly, but he didn’t participate in the more important team competition.

As a result, the two sides had their pros and cons. In the end, the MVP award was given to Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu had completed a 1v2 in the group arena too. It was just that Mo Fan being a rookie beating Huang Shaotian to complete a 1v2 made his performance more eyecatching.

In the team competition, Ye Xiu wasn’t as stunning as Wei Chen, but he had been the deciding factor in multiple crucial moments.

“Maybe we’re just too used to Ye Xiu’s amazing performances, so we always forget about him?” In one of the reports for this match, Ye Xiu had been described as the MVP who won the award without batting an eye.

This round’s performance didn’t garner Happy too much praise. In the next day’s Esports Weekly, Happy’s victory was described as “a successful exploitation of the new competitive format”.

This comment came about mostly because Happy had exposed their intentions in the team competition, revealing that they would win the overall match through points. The team competition had always been the most important part of a match. Happy had lost the team competition, yet still won the overall round, which was quite unusual to many people. The new competitive format had been used in Season 9’s playoffs as well, but it was the first time this sort of situation had occurred.

“In the home game, they took advantage of their group arena fluke to win the overall round, but in the following two away games, does Happy have enough courage and enough confidence to face them?”

Another report commented in this way.

The group arena win was regarded as a fluke, obviously because of Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain losing half his health from a tree. This sort of situation would obviously be treated as an accident. Happy’s win had been built upon this fluke.

Next, two away games…

This seemingly normal statement was actually filled with malice. As long as Happy won the next match, this first round would be over. But the report stated two away games, indicating that Happy would certainly lose the following one.

The Happy haters found quite a bit to talk about because of this match. But before Happy’s next round began, the next day’s first round fourth match came knocking down.

In the fourth match, Tiny Herb played against Thunderclap, winning 10 to 9. In addition, the point distribution for this match was identical to the point distribution for the Happy vs Blue Rain match. Tiny Herb won the group arena 5 to 3, but lost the team competition 5 to 6. However, the total points tallied to 10 to 9, Tiny Herb’s win.

Was it on purpose?

Was it by luck?

No one knew.

The discussion point was the same for two matches. The results were the same, but the responses were different. It was easy to think that the evaluations were unfair. In the numerous reports, Happy’s match against Blue Rain was pulled out, comparing the differences between the two matches to explain that despite the same outcome, Happy’s had been intentional, while Tiny Herb’s had not been.

“In the group arena, Tiny Herb earned a tremendous win, and it was not through luck.”

“In the team competition, the home game Thunderclap played powerfully, but Tiny Herb didn’t rely on their group arena advantage. Instead, an intense confrontation between the two teams unfolded. In the end, the 5 points obtained was a result of their intent to win.”

“The goals and attitudes that the two teams displayed are conclusive.”

The evaluation of Tiny Herb and Thunderclap became a comparison between Happy and Tiny Herb. The reports were scared that if they didn’t explain their thoughts clearly enough, their reputation would be damaged.

Chapter 1429 - Two Teams Eliminated

Whether or not it was intentional was a topic that could be discussed for an entire week, if the match had occurred during the regular season. But the tempo of the playoffs didn’t give anyone a break to consider such topics.

With the high frequency of one match being played each day, it was almost too much for the spectators to take in, with each match leaving a different impression on them. Whether or not winning through the group arena was intentional was already an outdated topic. At this point, it was already the first match of the second round. In their home stadium, Team Samsara would face off against Team Hundred Blossoms.

Having already lost one home game, Hundred Blossoms already had no path of retreat. But even facing off against Samsara, the most dominant team in the season, the team aiming for three consecutive championships; Hundred Blossoms didn’t show any sign of fear. Under Yu Feng’s command, Hundred Blossoms took the initiative to go on the offensive against Samsara in their away game. In the group arena, both teams fought fiercely, going back and forth, with each side eliminating the opposing players quickly. Neither side was able to secure a significant lead, but in the end, Samsara still won the group arena with a score of 5 to 4.

Just like this, Team Hundred Blossoms entered the life-or-death team competition with a one point disadvantage.

They didn’t play conservatively, only taking the necessary precautions when playing an away game. Even in their position, one step away from elimination, Hundred Blossoms continued to take the initiative to the best of their abilities.

In the last round of the regular season, Hundred Blossoms had also faced off against Samsara. It had also been their away game, and they had also been on the precipice of elimination, but relying on their tenacious determination, they played to the best of their abilities, seizing one point after another. At the end of the day, it was a one point advantage that had secured them a spot in the playoffs.

But even in that round, in the team competition that followed afterwards, Hundred Blossoms had also tried their very best, but ultimately lost. In the first round of the playoffs, Hundred Blossoms had personally experienced Samsara’s different temperament when it came to the playoffs.

Winning two championships had given them a great deal of self-confidence. This allowed them to put on a steady and calm performance in the playoffs. In this manner, they unflinchingly withstood the great waves from Hundred Blossoms in their home game, defeating them and letting Team Hundred Blossoms clearly understand the difference in strength between the two teams.

Faced with this steady and stable playstyle, Hundred Blossoms had little chance of winning. Samsara’s stability meant that everyone could hardly imagine them making any fatal mistakes that would lead to their defeat.

That night, the players of Hundred Blossoms felt somewhat depressed. Facing off against what seemed to be an unbeatable opponent had dampened their spirits. But after one night, everyone from Hundred Blossoms had re-adjusted their state of mind.

If they already felt as if victory was nigh unachievable, what else was there to fear? They would throw caution to the wind, play an exciting match, and that would be it!

Yu Feng could feel this kind of an atmosphere throughout the team. So, in this crucial away game, they simply put aside their reservations, allowing everyone to put their all into this battle.

Victory? Defeat? Forget about such matters for the time being!

On the most cut-throat stage of the playoffs, against the strongest team, let’s see what we can achieve! The team competition showcased an even more brilliant back and forth than the group arena. Every single member of Hundred Blossoms put on their best performance, with each player having their own outstanding moments. Nevertheless, the team that achieved victory at the end of the day was still Team Samsara.

Team Hundred Blossoms had been eliminated, but after this loss, Yu Feng could see unwillingness and vexation on the faces of all the members of Hundred Blossoms.

“If only my deployment of the Devil World Flowers hadn’t been disrupted!” The Summoner, Zhu Xiaoping, slapped his leg as he lamented, unresigned.

“It’s my fault, if only I had given you the proper covering fire at that time, then…” Zou Yuan said.

“If only that sneak attack of mine had succeeded, then…” Zhou Guangyi, their Assassin, said.

One match had left them with too many “if only”s.

At this time, these hypothetical scenarios actually symbolized hope for Team Hundred Blossoms. Because they would have opportunities and circumstances to turn those hypotheticals into reality.

“Next year, we will return once more!” Yu Feng said.

“Once more!” Zhu Xiaoping didn’t slap his leg, instead clenching his fists tightly.

“Once more!” Everyone in Hundred Blossoms solemnly nodded their heads.

After desperately killing their way into the playoffs, two matches in the first round had spelt the end of their journey through the playoffs. They were regretful, they were unresigned. But Yu Feng felt that these were exactly what they had gained. Because they were regretful, because they were unresigned, they would have more motivation. If the only thing they felt was despair from losing against a strong opponent, how would this team ever have the courage or confidence to fight once more?

Having such a competition, having such a group of teammates, it was really too great!

Yu Feng thought of this, feeling that he would definitely have incomparably bright prospects in the near future.

Team Samsara advanced into the top four, taking a solid step towards their goal of winning three consecutive championships.

In the various reports the next day, they naturally still sang the praises of the victor. Two rounds, two group arenas, two team competitions, and Samsara had won them all, indisputably seizing victory in their opening round. For them, aside from words of flattery and praise, there really wasn’t much else to say.

“Samsara’s greatest enemy may only be a feeling called ‘arrogance’,” one report said.

Immediately, the question of which team could possibly snipe Samsara’s three consecutive championships became a topic of discussion. Just like the question of who could stop their consecutive victories in the regular season, it quickly became a hot topic of discussion amongst everyone.

The team that had put an end to Samsara’s record of consecutive victories, Hundred Blossoms, had already been personally sent out of the playoffs by Samsara. Then, would there be another team that would say goodbye to the playoffs next?

In the first round of the playoffs, in their second game, Team Tyranny would face off in their home stadium against Team 301.

In their previous home game, Team 301 had lost miserably. Everyone could see that in the more cautious environment of the playoffs, Team 301’s help from abroad, who had only been part of the team for half a season, was increasingly unable to create opportunities for his team. What’s more, their opponents were Team Tyranny, home to a number of old generals who had incomparable levels of experience. On top of that, they had an extremely cautious tactician, Zhang Xinjie, along with the fact that Team Tyranny’s current playstyle was no longer their old, hyper-aggressive style, instead focusing on defence. All these factors greatly restricted Team 301’s ability to execute their gameplan. What was originally a dark horse that countless people had thought highly of was now the team with the most disappointing performance in the playoffs. In the first match, it had been as such, and in this match, it was the same.

Compared to their first match, 301’s only improvement was taking one more point for themselves.

“Your tactics aren’t bad, go back and keep working hard!” When the players were shaking hands after the match, Zhang Xinjie said this to Team 301’s foreign help, Bai Shu.

Ridicule? Contempt?

Bai Shu obviously didn’t have a sufficient understanding of Zhang Xinjie, completely misunderstanding the intention behind Zhang Xinjie’s words. Actually, it had to be understood that Zhang Xinjie’s words were always very simple, so what he had meant was just the most simple and direct interpretation of those words. On the other hand, Bai Shu’s thought process wasn’t as uncomplicated. Because they had suffered defeat, because the tactics that he had brought weren’t able to be fully put to use, Zhang Xinjie’s praise, saying that his tactics “weren’t bad” after the match sounded exceedingly ear-piercing to him.

Bai Shu wasn’t too happy, preparing to retort sarcastically. Trash talk was, after all, a global language.

“Thank you for your advice.” Before he could open his mouth, the person standing in front of him, Team 301’s captain, Yang Cong, had cut in, replying to Zhang Xinjie in his place.

Obviously, Yang Cong clearly understood Zhang Xinjie’s personality, and at the same time, he also foresaw that Bai Shu, who didn’t really understand Zhang Xinjie, might have a negative reaction to his words, so he had quickly intervened.

Bai Shu was stunned for a moment, but he didn’t say anything, deferring to Yang Cong’s attitude, and quietly finishing the post-match formalities. It was only when they had returned to their club that Yang Cong explained to Bai Shu that Zhang Xinjie’s words were utterly devoid of ridicule; instead, he was simply stating the facts.

“Continue to work hard!” Yang Cong patted Bai Shu on the shoulder.

Bai Shu lowered his head, spending some time in deep contemplation, but he also realized that with only half a year to fit into the team, his tactics were indeed lacking in many aspects. After using them for half the regular season, they were no longer surprising to the rest of the teams in the Alliance, and in the cut-throat environment of the playoffs, it was inevitable that he would hit a wall.

“Continue to work hard!” Bai Shu raised his head, replying to Yang Cong, his eyes filled with determination.

Yang Cong laughed. As a player who had debuted in the third season, he didn’t have much time left in his professional career. Being the core, or the main force, such roles would gradually leave him. If he stubbornly refused to budge, it would instead burden his entire team.

Yang Cong would no longer be able to build 301’s future. The person in front of him, Bai Shu, he was the one who would have to shoulder the burden of 301’s future. In Yang Cong’s eyes, Bai Shu was a talented player, worthy of being entrusted with such a role. He was quite happy that his team was able to dig out such an outstanding player from the pro scene overseas.

Outside of the Glory Alliance, how many Glory experts were there that they had never seen, and never played against? Yang Cong couldn’t help thinking about this.

If he had the chance, he really wanted to experience it first-hand! As Yang Cong thought about this, he felt a sense of melancholy. Whether or not he would still have such a chance was something that he couldn’t be sure about.

Team 301 became the second team to be eliminated from the playoffs. And Team Tyranny, who had been underestimated throughout the regular season, now looked like they had gathered themselves once more in the playoffs. In front of Tyranny, 301, who had been a headache for countless teams in the second half of the regular season, had instead been battered and bruised.

This was Team Tyranny’s real strength! Many articles ran such a tagline.

“Real strength”, these two words would always make people feel deeply moved. After the end of the first round, Team Tyranny’s popularity rating increased by an incredible amount. Many people had already begun to predict that the two teams vying for the championship in the end would still be Tyranny and Samsara. In the news, aside from discussion of the match between Tyranny and 301 from the night before, there were also predictions and opinions on the match that would happen that night.

Happy’s away game against Blue Rain!

Three days after their first match, these two teams would face off once again. The Happy haters flocked out of their holes, wanting to see if Happy, who had fought such an arduous and utilitarian battle in the first match in order to win, would be able to make any waves in their away game.

“In Blue Rain’s home game, there shouldn’t be any big tree blessing Happy anymore, right?”

The tree falling on Troubling Rain still remained as the most eye-catching moment of the first match. Happy’s haters especially liked to use this as an example to explain that Happy’s victory had been a fluke, something purely based on luck. It was a pity that no matter how many times they brought it up, Happy didn’t feel anything much, but instead, Huang Shaotian was gnashing his teeth, viciously cursing this group of Happy haters hundreds of times.

“That smelly brat, it’s best that he doesn’t run into me!” Huang Shaotian repeated many times over these three days. The “smelly brat” naturally was referring to Mo Fan, but “not running into him”, meant quite the opposite. Huang Shaotian couldn’t wait to run into Mo Fan again.

Chapter 1430 - Blue Rain’s Starting Player

With the second match, it was Happy’s turn to play the away game. The day before, they flew over to Blue Rain’s home city, City G. A night of rest allowed them to recover from the fatigue of travel. That morning, they warmed up in the temporary training room specifically for away teams. In the afternoon, there weren’t any group activities, so everyone found their own ways to get into condition. When it was about time, they would go over to the stadium together to familiarize themselves with the surroundings, and soon after that, tonight’s match would be upon them.

After lunch, everyone returned to their own rooms to take a break. Wei Chen, smoking, stood by the hotel room window and absently stared outside.

“Isn’t this already your second time here? And the second time you’ve stayed here? What’s with the sad face?” Ye Xiu said from the side. Like their place in Upper Forest Park, he and Wei Chen were rooming together.

“Last time we came, I don’t think I went to visit the team,” Wei Chen said.

“You want to visit?” Ye Xiu asked. He knew that by “team,” Wei Chen was referring to Team Blue Rain.

“Before, not really, but after last match, I suddenly kind of want to,” said Wei Chen.

“I understand,” Ye Xiu said, nodding.

“You understand?” Surprised, Wei Chen turned to look at him.

“Last match was a struggle for you, so now you need to go in front of those guys and aggressively show off,” said Ye Xiu, with a face of sympathy.

“Oh, fuck off!” Wei Chen said snappily.

“If you want to go then just go. Do you really need to waver over something as small as this?” After that, Ye Xiu didn’t pay him any more mind. He went to go take a nap to rest up. Wei Chen stood by the window and continued to waver for quite a while. In the end, he made up his mind, firmly finished and extinguished his cigarette, and left.

Ye Xiu slept for the entire afternoon. By the time he woke up, Chen Guo was already calling everyone to head over to the stadium together to familiarize themselves with it. By this time, Wei Chen had already returned, and was acting as though nothing was up. Had he gone? Ye Xiu didn’t ask, nor did he say anything about it. After Happy assembled, everyone left the hotel together and arrived at Blue Rain’s stadium, Xiaochuan Stadium.

Last time it had been somewhat unfamiliar, but this was now their second time here. Following the workers, Happy filed into the stadium. All of the facilities needed for the match were already prepared, and Happy’s members were simply wandering around, imagining the atmosphere that this place would have in a few hours. They would often do this during the regular season as well, so everyone was used to it. No one could say for sure whether it was useful, but because everyone did this, there wouldn’t be any downside.

“You’re here!” As Happy was aimlessly hanging around, they suddenly heard someone greeting them. When they turned, they saw Blue Rain’s Captain Yu Wenzhou. He was just by himself, calmly standing to the side and looking at the entire Team Happy. The greeting had sounded less like an opponent, and more like a host welcoming some guests.

“Yeah, we’re here.” Ye Xiu answered for Happy.

“Good luck with your preparations.” Yu Wenzhou dipped his head and didn’t bother them any further, leaving them to their devices.

“What was that for?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu. The home team players generally wouldn’t come to familiarize themselves with the stadium beforehand. Of course, a few players had their own unique habits, but it didn’t seem that Yu Wenzhou had been exposed for having any such special habits.

“Who knows,” said Ye Xiu, watching Yu Wenzhou depart. “Just casually wandering around, probably!”

The next time they saw Blue Rain’s current captain, it was already nighttime, right before the match’s start. The two teams were lined up in the player passageway, waiting to enter.

“Work hard.”

“Good luck.”

The two captains at the front of the two lines represented their teams as they encouraged each other. The air actually seemed quite harmonious. After that, the teams entered the stadium as normal, nothing out of the ordinary. But because Blue Rain had lost the previous match, they had to win today’s match no matter what. As soon as the players entered, Blue Rain’s home fans erupted.

In order to cheer on their team today, special preparations had been made on Blue Rain’s side. Guild Leader Changing Spring had specifically recruited helpers and arranged everyone in all corners of the stadium. This let the devoted fans act like a train, driving up the spirits of the whole stadium.

And Changing Spring himself was sitting in the east seating section, directly across from the west.

On the west side was the section reserved for the away team fans, while the east side had Blue Rain’s diehard fans. Over here, they were directly opposite the away team fans, and could easily engage in contests with them.

With the explosion from the Blue Rain fans, the Happy fans on the west section weren’t about to be outdone. Even though there was no way for them to get the upper hand due to their inferior numbers, they would certainly let the opponent recognize their presence. The fan squad following Happy for the playoffs had been personally organized by Wu Chen. Right now, the west seating area included Thousand Creations, Horse Shooter, Seven Fields, Sleeping Moon, these players who were the backbone of Guild Happy. Everyone had made thorough preparations with sophisticated equipment, all sorts of eye-catching noisemakers that swiftly began to disrupt the home crowd’s cheering.

“Wow, the players have only just entered the stadium, and the fans on both sides are already going at each other! It looks like today’s match is going to be exceptionally exciting!” said the broadcast commentator Pan Lin, feeling the atmosphere in the stadium.

“Blue Rain has no more path of retreat. They’re going to have to give their all in this match,” said Li Yibo.

“But Happy won their last match by only a narrow margin. Blue Rain isn’t under too much pressure, right?” Pan Lin said.

“Well, a team should never let themselves feel too much pressure. But if they let down their guard because Happy only won narrowly, then that attitude would be very bad for them. I trust that Blue Rain would not do such a thing. Whether a narrow or a big victory, Blue Rain’s situation right now would be the same,” said Li Yibo.

“You’re right. Right now, the players from both teams have already arrived at their own competitor booths, and the match will start soon. For the group arena, Happy will probably send Ye Xiu up first again, right? Then on the home side, who will Blue Rain send up to deal with Ye Xiu? The win or loss of this first point can have a big impact on the morale of both sides!” said Pan Lin.

“But they also have to be careful, what if Happy doesn’t send Ye Xiu first? Then whatever plans Blue Rain makes to deal with him might come to nothing, and it’ll hurt their own rhythm,” said Li Yibo.

“Then what should Blue Rain do?” Pan Lin said.

“There isn’t a perfect way to deal with this, so let’s just see what they do. This is the pressure exerted by a top-tier player!” said Li Yibo.

“Alright, let us wait and see. Will Happy continue to send Ye Xiu onstage first? And what kind of response will Blue Rain make? Right now, there are still five minutes until the match officially begins,” said Pan Lin.

The five minutes passed in the blink of an eye. The judge came to call for them, and the two teams began to send their players onstage.

“Ye Xiu! As it turns out, it’s still Ye Xiu!” Pan Lin shouted. On Happy’s side, Ye Xiu had already stood up.

“What about Blue Rain? Who will Blue Rain send up to battle?” Pan Lin looked at Blue Rain’s side, but still didn’t find his answer. But at this moment, the digital screen in the stadium displayed the names.

Happy, Ye Xiu, Lord Grim.

Blue Rain, Yu Wenzhou, Swoksaar.

It was as though the broadcast froze, entering five seconds of dead silence.

Pan Lin’s mouth had fallen open. For a long time, he was unable to say anything. In the stadium, too, when the names came out, it went completely quiet.

“Yu… Yu Wenzhou?” Pan Lin double-checked the words on the screen, and then took another look at Blue Rain’s player area, where Yu Wenzhou was already walking toward the stage.

Yes, it was Yu Wenzhou.

In reality, when Ye Xiu had stood up, Yu Wenzhou had also already stood up on Blue Rain’s side, and when Pan Lin had checked the screen, he had seen that. But… he never would have thought that Yu Wenzhou was the player that Blue Rain was sending out. He had subconsciously thought that he’d stood up to let another player pass by, or maybe as the captain he was giving some last reminder to the player about to go onstage. Who would’ve thought that this was Yu Wenzhou himself about to head onstage?

Yu Wenzhou… was about to 1v1?

Five seconds of silence, a stammered announcement of Yu Wenzhou’s name, and then another five seconds of silence. Finally, Pan Lin recovered for good, and began yelling with disbelief in his voice.

“Yu Wenzhou! It’s actually Yu Wenzhou! Blue Rain’s first player in the group arena, the player facing off against Ye Xiu, is actually Yu Wenzhou?! Coach Li!” At the end, Pan Lin called for Li Yibo. Such a big thing happening, you hurry up and say a few words!

“This is indeed an extremely unexpected arrangement.” Li Yibo forced himself to remain calm. He couldn’t allow himself to be as passionate or volatile as Pan Lin, he had to display how much more of a refined person he was.

“Yu Wenzhou… I don’t even remember the last time he appeared in a 1v1,” said Li Yibo.

“Today he’s suddenly going onstage, this is probably a tactic specifically targeted toward Happy sending Ye Xiu first?” said Pan Lin.

“I would think so…”

“Has Yu Wenzhou found the secret to dealing with the unspecialized Lord Grim?” said Pan Lin.

“This… There probably isn’t any such secret, right?” said Li Yibo.

“Then what’s he thinking?” said Pan Lin.

Li Yibo couldn’t answer that question, and so he didn’t. Yu Wenzhou, who hadn’t played an individual match in who knows how long, today wanted to challenge Ye Xiu, challenge this season’s King of Dueling, the unspecialized Lord Grim who had been an incomparable headache for countless players…

They hadn’t even finished processing this reality by the time the two characters had already finished loading in, and the round officially began.

“The battle’s starting, right now the battle’s starting, Happy’s Ye Xiu, against Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou. This is a matchup in a group arena, I don’t think I need to describe just how unusual this confrontation is?” Pan Lin shouted.

“Hey!”

At this time, the two players entering the battle had already begun conversation in the chat. The first one to speak was Ye Xiu.

“You’re really too bold, aren’t you!” Ye Xiu said.

“I’m giving it a try,” said Yu Wenzhou.

“If you end up winning this, no one in the pro circle will have any face left! This season’s King of Dueling finally taken down, and it’s by you?” Ye Xiu said.

“Don’t rule out that possibility,” said Yu Wenzhou.

“How’s your hand speed right now? Can you reach 200?” Ye Xiu said.

“So-so!” Yu Wenzhou answered.

Chapter 1431 - Misty Thicket

Yu Wenzhou had been in the scene for all these years, and his hand speed was on record. His hand speed wasn’t a secret any longer, everyone knew. As a rival, there was no way he wouldn’t have checked these statistics, so Ye Xiu’s question was clearly a taunt.

A hand speed of 200 was, in general, seen as the boundary between pros and casual players. Of course, this two hundred referred to effective APM, not button mashing.

Yu Wenzhou’s status as a hand cripple was judged according to pro player standards. Pro players nowadays could easily reach 300-400 on average. Yu Wenzhou could only get past 200 with great effort, and usually averaged below 200. It was no wonder no one thought he could last in the beginning. He was completely different from the pros around him with their terrifying hand speed.

However, normal players didn’t have any right to mock him for it.

Normal players’ effective APM generally drifted around 100. Those that went above 120, aiming for 200, were experts. Glory was a very complex game. There were plenty of fast people, but those who were able to fully utilize this speed ingame were rare.

Yu Wenzhou’s effective hand speed was usually approaching 200. In other words, his hand speed was the same as the experts among casual players. Yet, he managed to become a pro player with this speed, a member of the Golden Generation, an All-Star Player, Master Tactician, the captain of a powerhouse team like Blue Rain…

Yu Wenzhou was very inspirational. His achievements became proof for many players without much talent in hand speed that they could achieve as well. Unfortunately, it had to be said that they were sorely mistaken. They had been delighted, finding a common point between them and this God, but that point was a flaw. The flaw itself didn’t mean anything. Yu Wenzhou’s current heights was in no way related to his flaw, but instead because of the efforts he had placed into and the talents he had in other areas to make up for this flaw.

There were plenty of Glory players with this hand speed.

But amongst all these players, only Yu Wenzhou had made it here.

And now, Yu Wenzhou was doing something he hadn’t done in a long time.

He was playing in a 1v1 match, and in the playoffs, too, against the best 1v1 duelist of the season.

“Huh… This map…” It was only after chatting for all this time that Ye Xiu placed his attention on Blue Rain’s choice of map.

Misty Thicket.

A forest map, with little variation in terrain. It was long and narrow, stretching from north to south. The trait that differentiated this forest from normal forest was in its name, the forest was filled with mist.

With dense forestry and layers of evening mist, this map limited character vision greatly. It was good for ambushes, and hindered ranged fighters. Pan Lin and Li Yibo as well as countless spectators had all already started discussing this back while Ye Xiu was still mocking Yu Wenzhou’s hand speed.

Everyone was shocked that Yu Wenzhou was fighting a 1v1 match. However, they all instantly realized that Yu Wenzhou wouldn’t fight his opponent upfront and compete with mechanics, but used the terrain to execute tactics and tricks. But, Misty Thicket? Li Yibo had already pointed out in the TV broadcast that this map put ranged fighters at a disadvantage, and Warlocks were a ranged class.

What was Yu Wenzhou planning? After seeing Blue Rain’s map choice, everyone was even more confused. That was when everyone saw that Ye Xiu seemed to be about to comment on the map.

But all they got was, “Huh… this map…” and then, then nothing!

Both sides had started to move already. Ye Xiu was very direct and went straight down the middle, but in this map, even heading straight forward could result in an ambush attack. Since visibility was low, the two sides would pretty much be within range of each other when they could see the other. Lord Grim looked like he couldn’t be bothered to waste the brainpower on figuring out a roundabout route.

Yu Wenzhou, on the other hand, seemed to be treating this much more seriously. Swoksaar had spawned in the north corner of the map, and he had began heading south from the west while Ye Xiu was still talking. However, Swoksaar didn’t go too far west. On this map, if you went too far from your target, you wouldn’t even be able to find them when ambushing them.

However, this was only the current situation. The further south Swoksaar went, the more he swerved west. Slowly, his distance from the central axis of the map grew and he drew almost completely out of the visible areas of the map.

“This positioning… doesn’t this make Yu Wenzhou incapable of finding Lord Grim as well? Or did he predict that Ye Xiu would make Lord Grim come west as well?” Pan Lin wondered aloud.

“The problem is, Ye Xiu didn’t…” Li Yibo added.

Not long afterwards, the two characters approached the center of the map, slowing down. Then, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim suddenly began to fire shots.

Bang bang!

Bang bang!

The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella’s gun form was a rifle, so his normal attack consisted of two consecutive shots. Ye Xiu was currently just using normal attacks. It didn’t cost any mana. He fired shot after shot, randomly shooting into the air.

“He’s purposefully exposing his own position!” Pan Lin exclaimed. From Yu Wenzhou’s view, he couldn’t see Lord Grim, but every time a gunshot rang out, the gunfire could be seen through the layers of mist.

“Does he intend to draw Yu Wenzhou into attacking and then use that to figure out where Yu Wenzhou is?” Li Yibo said, “But…”

He wanted to say that Warlock skills were hard to see through this sort of of mist. The lighting caused by Warlock skills were relatively dark, not nearly as eye-catching as an explosion elemental light. For Warlock skills, if there was any elemental damage, it would be dark element.

However, Li Yibo was terrified that with Ye Xiu’s experience and observation skills, he would be able to easily catch the light of Warlock skills even under the current circumstances, so he didn’t dare continue.

What about Yu Wenzhou? Perhaps he had the same thought as Li Yibo, since he didn’t attack when he saw Ye Xiu expose Lord Grim’s position, having Swoksaar approach slowly instead.

Lord Grim continued to shoot randomly, two shots at a time, switching up his directions. A few bullets were sent west, brushing past Swoksaar’s shoulder. The spectator’s with their omniscient view felt their heart leap into their throats with every shot, but Swoksaar stayed immobile.

“What precise judgement,” Li Yibo exclaimed.

It was because Yu Wenzhou’s judgement was so precise that he had Swoksaar stay immobile, otherwise, if one couldn’t be certain, then they would have their character dodge.

“From this angle, how far can he see?” Pan Lin mumbled, but there was no data on something like that, and there was no way of figuring out with their omniscient view.

Bang bang, bang bang.

Lord Grim continued to shoot and Swoksaar had stopped in his tracks. Yu Wenzhou was carefully observing the shots that Lord Grim was firing.

The audience had a much clearer view of this than Swoksaar, and seeing Lord Grim’s actions, everyone only had one thought: what a tricky bastard!

Lord Grim, holding up the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in gun form, had the muzzle directed behind him, which meant that all his shots were aimed behind him…

Yu Wenzhou was currently carefully observing. If he wouldn’t figure this out and waited for the line of fire to turn, then launched a sneak attack while Lord Grim “had his back turned”, then unfortunately, he’d be charging right into Lord Grim’s line of sight.

How sly! How despicable!

The spectating Blue Rain fans all cursed, led by those dead loyal high ranking members of the Blue Brook Guild. These guys had gone up against Ye Xiu in game and they had plenty of personal experience with his tricks and schemes, leaving unimaginable pain in their hearts.

However, this commotion wouldn’t have any influence on the match itself. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim continued to cunningly shoot behind him.

Yu Wenzhou stayed motionless, carefully observing for a full half a minute.

Ye Xiu continued to turn and shoot for a full half a minute.

On the thirty-fifth second, Yu Wenzhou finally acted.

Swoksaar began to cast, directly going for a Chaotic Rain.

There was a roar of applause.

Since this skill summoned acidic clouds in the sky to create rain, it didn’t matter where the character was casting from, the attack would still come from above. It would be impossible to figure out the character’s position using this.

And so, thick, dark clouds began to gather above Lord Grim’s head.

The applause grew in volume, everyone eager to see Lord Grim being splashed! But that was when, with a whoosh, Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up above his head.

“Fuck!” Quite a few people cursed aloud at this.

If this was actually a Knight’s shield, then it might not be possible for it to block all the Chaotic Rain by holding it above a character’s head like that. However, this Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was an umbrella when opened. It was the best at blocking the rain.

“Drift inside! Drift inside!” Someone suddenly started to yell and others soon followed suit. They were hoping that there would be some wind that would blow the rain off course and under the umbrella.

But it was like Ye Xiu had heard the Blue Rain fans’ words. Lord Grim suddenly squatted down.

Squatting with an umbrella over his head really covered all his bases. Now even wind wouldn’t be able to do anything.

Blue Rain’s fans all blew up in rage. Fuck, can’t you play seriously!? You pretending to be a mushroom or something, squatting there?

But it was then that above Lord Grim’s head, amidst the dark clouds, light flashed. There seemed to be six spots of light…

Hexagram Prison!

The players who were familiar with the Warlock class recognized it immediately.

“Brilliant!” Those who managed to react fastest yelled.

This Hexagram Prison was a flawless sneak attack!

Yu Wenzhou had predicted that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim would open up the umbrella to block Chaotic Rain. No other method was safe enough. After all, he hadn’t seen it being casted. By the time he noticed, the clouds were already gathering and ready to spill.

Then, with the umbrella open, Ye Xiu had completely blocked off his own view of the sky above. Thus, when a Hexagram Prison fell silently from the heavens, he wouldn’t notice it.

“Die!” Blue Rain’s fans n the stands cheered in excitement.

As expected of their captain. This technique was absolutely brilliant, absolutely spectacular!

Hexagram Prison descended!

Chapter 1432 - Battle of Connotations

The battle was already occurring, and the spectators could see everything clearly with their omniscient view. However, the scene was more shocking, watching from the player’s view.

This was because for both players, apart from mist and trees, they couldn’t see anything else.

Yu Wenzhou’s attack had been launched while he was completely incapable of seeing his opponent. He had deduced Lord Grim’s location purely through the shots the other had fired, yet his attacks were so precise.

The Hexagram Prison descended, and a shield’s protection couldn’t defend against everything. Hexagram Prison’s effect wasn’t something that could be negated by a shield.

But, hand seals!

In the close up shot, everyone could clearly see Lord Grim suddenly let go of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, his hands rapidly forming seals. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had yet to fall when he was done with the seals.

There was only one Ninja skill under level twenty that required hand seals.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Would he make it?

Everyone was sweating like crazy. In the end, this Shadow Clone ended up activating before the Hexagram Prison landed.

The Lord Grim caught by Hexagram Prison, in the end, was a mere shadow clone.

“Did he notice it?” Pan Lin cried out.

“No. He definitely couldn’t see or hear this attack coming… It should be a judgement made through Ye Xiu’s experience and awareness,” Li Yibo estimated. “Did you notice? If it wasn’t for Lord Grim squatting, then this Shadow Clone Technique might be a little too late.”

Pan Lin startled and the shot was switched to a slow motion replay. The beams of light from the Hexagram Prison were mere millimeters away from the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in Lord Grim’s hands when the latter’s Shadow Clone Technique activated. However, if this skill had been activated while standing, then the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella would have certainly been caught by the beams of light already.

“As expected of the all-class Glory Textbook!” Pan Lin’s awed voice rang out. This sort of reaction speed and awareness was a perfect display of Ye Xiu’s familiarity and understanding with the Warlock class, which was what allowed him to predict the sneak attack via Hexagram Prison.

Thus, the home spectators who had been excited, immediately began to worry for their captain.

This was because Swoksaar’s casted curse had already shot forwards. This time, the skill was no longer one that descended from above, so Ye Xiu could already deduce Swoksaar’s position. His Lord Grim was waiting, watching, at one side.

A ghostly shadow arrived, darting through the Chaotic Rain and into the Hexagram Prison, into Lord Grim’s Shadow Clone.

The audience was heartbroken!

Captain, you fell for a trick!

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim immediately charged in the direction the ghostly shadow had flown in from, careful to not make any noise.

Hurry and run! That was the inner voice of the audience members. This time, it was almost as if their captain had heard.

“Yu Wenzhou hasn’t neglected to consider this possibility either!” Li Yibo announced.

Swoksaar was already leaving his original position under Yu Wenzhou’s control.

“But if he attacks after leaving, he would still be locked onto by Ye Xiu, no? Considering Lord Grim’s movement speed, he should be able to close in quickly!” Pan Lin said.

“He won’t move elsewhere and attack,” Li Yibo said with surprising confidence.

“Huh? Has he noticed Lord Grim’s actions?” Pan Lin was confused.

“He’ll notice soon enough enough,” Li Yibo corrected with a smile, “Think. What skill did he use just now?”

“Grasping Ghosts?” Pan Lin was saying when the ghostly shadow that Swoksaar had sent out just now suddenly flew back.

“Ah! This…” Pan Lin cried out in surprise. Didn’t… didn’t this expose Swoksaar’s position again?

“So, he now knows that the Lord Grim he trapped was nothing more than a shadow clone,” Li Yibo laughed.

Pan Lin froze for a moment before realizing what had happened.

Grasping Ghosts would latch onto a target and deal damage for a period of time. After the skill finished, the ghostly shadow would fly back to the user and restore the Warlock’s health by 33 percent of the damage it had dealt.

Shadow clones were very fragile, so Swoksaar’s Grasping Ghosts had only latched on for a moment before destroying the shadow clone. After that, the ghostly shadow would naturally come back. No matter if it was from the time the skill had been active or the recovery statistics, Yu Wenzhou could easily determine that Grasping Ghosts had only latched onto a shadow clone.

So this skill wasn’t just an attack, but also reconnaissance!

Pan Lin’s heart was struck by surprise after surprise. This match was way too deep for him.

However, the ghostly shadow which flew back to its owner was like a guiding light. Ye Xiu seemed to have noticed this as well and immediately adjusted Lord Grim’s direction upon seeing the ghostly shadow.

Grasping Ghosts moved extremely fast, but Lord Grim was also putting on as much speed as possible. He no longer thought about executing a sneak attack. Lord Grim’s figure seemed like a ghostly shadow as it darted through the forestry as well. Soon enough, Swoksaar’s form appeared in his view.

“So fast! He’s too fast! How will Yu Wenzhou shake him off now?!” Pan Lin cried out.

Yet that was when, with a boom, a sandstorm arrived on the forest map, enveloping Lord Grim inside.

The stadium was filled with shock, and as for Lord Grim’s current status? He was losing health, and had a blind.

“Sandstorm Trap!” Pan Lin exclaimed, stunned.

This was a high level Thief’s trap skill that dealt damage and inflicted a blind. Yu Wenzhou had set this Thief skill into Swoksaar’s Curse of Destruction.

Now, everyone had a much better understanding of how annoying it was when the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was set with all sorts of different skills in its many forms. This sort of variation wasn’t something one could easily guard against. See, even Ye Xiu himself fell for it here. No matter how familiar he was with the system of skills Warlocks used, it would be too hard to guess what Nightwalker skill was set into the opponent’s weapon. If you really took all the possible skills into consideration and stayed on guard for any of them, then you probably wouldn’t even be able to play properly.

However, Swoksaar’s Sandstorm Trap was only rank one. It didn’t do much damage, and the blind lasted for three seconds.

These three seconds allowed Yu Wenzhou to leave a Curse Arrows for Ye Xiu and flee.

“Hey, why doesn’t Yu Wenzhou take this chance to try and bring Lord Grim under his control?”

Pan Lin wondered with some disappointment.

However, the Curse Arrows soon gave him his answer.

Though Lord Grim was blinded, he hadn’t been otherwise affected. Suddenly, he activated Slide Kick, not only dodging the Curse Arrows, but also closing the distance between him and Swoksaar.

Li Yibo glanced at Pan Lin, knowing that the other had gotten his answer already from his expression.

Yu Wenzhou wasn’t careless at all. This was Ye Xiu. Three seconds of blindness was too risky a chance and Yu Wenzhou clearly didn’t want to take risks. After quickly casting a Curse Arrows, he chose to flee.

By the time Lord Grim’s blind wore off, Swoksaar was out of sight. Ye Xiu hurriedly used what he had last seen and the possible distance Swoksaar could’ve run in three seconds to deduce the other’s approximate direction and whereabouts, but didn’t manage to find the other after searching.

The two’s first clash ended just like that. Lord Grim hadn’t managed to deal any real damage to Swoksaar, but at this stage, it was Swoksaar that people were more worried about.

“He has such an overwhelming and threatening presence!” Li Yibo exclaimed, referring to Ye Xiu.

“However, Yu Wenzhou has managed to deal some damage to Lord Grim, though it’s not much,” Pan Lin said.

Then they saw Lord Grim cast a Recovery on himself. Li Yibo gazed at Pan Lin without speaking.

“Seems like you plan on dragging things out!” Seeing as he couldn’t find his target, Ye Xiu started chatting.

“You can heal. Dragging things out will benefit you,” Yu Wenzhou replied.

“Continuing to drag things out like this is just a waste of effort. How about we roll die to decide who wins? Whoever loses can GG*,” Ye Xiu suggested.

The audience exploded.

What was even more shocking was that Swoksaar’s dice roll soon followed, and then came a “97”!

“Wow!” Blue Rain’s home stadium erupted in applause.

Then, in the chat.

“The hell are you doing? Be serious. This is the playoffs,” Ye Xiu said.

The audience exploded again.

“Hahaha….” Pan Lin didn’t even know what to say anymore.

“It’s just a joke. There’s no way the referee would allow the two to use die to decide the victor,” Li Yibo laughed.

This might be a game, but this was also a professional match!

Imagine in a soccer match where the two teams flipped a coin, and then, heads, you guessed it, ok, you win I guess, and then they just leave?

That was unacceptable. The Glory Pro League matches wouldn’t allow such a thing either. Even when people went GG and surrendered, the Alliance would deliberate on the validity of the GG after the match.

Although the two were trashtalking each other on the chat, they hadn’t stopped moving.

Yu Wenzhou had shaken Ye Xiu off, but he had also lost Lord Grim’s position as well. Right now, the two were carefully searching through the mist, trying to find the other.

This was something they couldn’t use logic to figure out. They were pretty much searching blindly, and the visual hindrances made the map seem even bigger.

One minute, two minutes…

The two didn’t meet, wandering around in the mist. The audience, with their omniscient view, sometimes couldn’t even feel any tension. The two were careful and cautious, but in reality, they were already on practically opposite sides of the map.

The broadcasters were pretty stressed out, too! Glory matches weren’t like soccer matches which finished when time was up, so the broadcasters couldn’t control the time for their programme. If it finished beforehand, that was alright, but if it took too long, then it would mess up the schedule for the programmes following.

However, what choice did they have? The match couldn’t be moved just because they wanted it to be.

“There’s no helping it! We can’t continue like this!” Ye Xiu spoke up again, and the broadcasters immediately began to adore him.

“What do you suggest we do then?” Yu Wenzhou replied.

“Let’s meet up somewhere and end this!” Ye Xiu said.

“Where?” Yu Wenzhou asked.

Ye Xiu sent some coordinates.

Thirty seconds later, no one appeared at the coordinates agreed upon. Both characters carefully hid themselves nearby.

Neither of them successfully tricked the other. The broadcasters were weeping.

Chapter 1433 - That’s All You’re Showing Us?

Five minutes.

A one on one battle that lasted five minutes wasn’t uncommon in the pro circle. However, the problem right now wasn’t that this battle had been five minutes long, but that five minutes in and both characters were at full health. That miniscule amount of damage dealt by Swoksaar’s Chaotic Rain and Sandstorm Trap had long since been healed by Recovery.

Right now, both characters appeared near the coordinates Ye Xiu had given, but neither of them showed themselves.

“Where are ya? Come out!” Ye Xiu yelled.

“I’m here, but I don’t see you,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Last time I came out first. It’s your turn,” Ye Xiu said.

“Which time?”

“Stop pretending you don’t know. Did you forget when I was shooting and let you hit me?” Ye Xiu raged, as if he hadn’t been trying to trap his opponent before and had revealed his position out of the goodness of his heart. Though it had already been five minutes, the audience hadn’t forgotten Ye Xiu’s little trick of shooting behind him. Was that something someone who was generously giving themselves away would do?

“Oh.” Yu Wenzhou acknowledged his words, then sent another message, “Did you see the curse I just sent?”

“I! Didn’t! See! It! Yu Wenzhou you had better not try anything!!!” Ye Xiu warned his opponent.

Finally, the referee couldn’t take it anymore. “Less useless talk from the two of you! Focus on the match!”

The messages sent by the referee were in the form of system messages. Just like how, in game, no matter how powerful a player was, they couldn’t beat the system, in pro matches, no matter how talented a trash talker, no one dared trash talk the referee. With the referee’s words, the two captains both fell silence. Their team members offstage looked at one another. For Happy, they weren’t caught too off guard because Ye Xiu had led them charging through the online game, so his unprofessionalism wasn’t anything foreign. But for Blue Rain… When had they ever seen their captain talk so much in a match? Because of his hand speed problem, their captain never had any time to chat, but using today’s map choice, he had managed to make up for that.

In reality, these two had never paused in their current actions while they chatted. No one made to actually stand into the area of the coordinates Ye Xiu gave. Both of them were a distance away, and maintained this distance as they circled around the area. The audience could see that one of them was moving clockwise and the other anti-clockwise. They were bound to meet eventually. It all depended on who would spot the other first amidst this dense mist.

Neither side was moving very quickly, careful to make no noise as they stepped forth.

Like that, they approached each other, bit by bit, little by little.

All the audience felt their hearts rising further and further into their throats.

Commentators Pan Lin and Li Yibo were silent now as well. The entire world of Glory had sunk into silence in that moment, as if the slightest sound would affect the two players onstage.

The big screen provided the two player’s views as they turned constantly. Then, at practically the exact same moment, they both stopped.

Charge!

Lord Grim immediately charged out, shockingly accurate, straight towards Swoksaar’s location/ As for Swoksaar, he wasn’t nearly as aggressive. The moment Lord Grim stepped out, he turned and darted behind a tree. The audience had known from before with their omniscient view that Swoksaar had paid careful attention to his pathing, prepared for this sort of sudden meeting.

Gunshots!

After using Charge, Lord Grim began shooting as he ran, the bullets striking the tree Swoksaar had hid behind. However, Swoksaar was no longer behind the tree. Lord Grim stepped two steps to the side, but still didn’t see Swoksaar. Lord Grim didn’t stop moving, continuing to charge as he threw a grenade out.

Boom!

The explosion created by a grenade was relatively more intense. In this mist, it could also light up the area, making it easier to see the silhouettes of other characters. However, Swoksaar still remained hidden to Ye Xiu.

The Blue Rain fans all let out a breath of relief, because these coordinates that Ye Xiu had suggested weren’t random. That guy had wandered about, carefully cataloguing the terrain in this area, familiarizing himself with the environment.

Seeing him call Yu Wenzhou over, everyone had cursed that crafty bastard Ye Xiu, yet Yu Wenzhou hadn’t refused, continuing onwards. Everyone was worried that Yu Wenzhou would fall into Ye Xiu’s trap, but now it seemed…

“Heh. This is Blue Rain’s map, after all! Ye Xiu’s few minutes of research can’t beat Yu Wenzhou’s understanding of this map!” Li Yibo laughed.

Yu Wenzhou’s response to their sudden meeting was confident and decisive. Swoksaar didn’t pause for the slightest moment, his movements making everyone’s hearts skip a beat in anxiety. Yet Ye Xiu, in the end, never noticed him even once. This result was too puzzling. It took a while before the system managed to come up with a simplified video displaying Lord Grim’s movements and changes in view, and then Swoksaar’s movement patterns and the obstacles he used for cover. From this video, the audience could clearly see that Yu Wenzhou’s choice of pathing was in Lord Grim’s blind spot. Yu Wenzhou’s familiarity with this map truly did far exceed Ye Xiu’s. Ye Xiu was skilled enough to have managed to find many useful aspects to the terrain with what little time he was given, he probably wouldn’t be able to improvise such a successful response like Yu Wenzhou could.

“Spectacular! No wonder Yu Wenzhou dared to fight Ye Xiu one on one,” Li Yibo praised.

“But if this continues, how does he plan on beating Ye Xiu?” Pan Lin asked.

Although Yu Wenzhou was good at avoiding the other, he didn’t dare to face Ye Xiu head on. From this perspective, one couldn’t say that he had the advantage. If all you did upon seeing your opponent was avoid him, then there was no way you could beat them. You had to launch some sort of assault!

“Let’s keep watching!” Li Yibo said.

After this, Ye Xiu still lost Swoksaar. He had no choice but to have Lord Grim stop.

“Hey, all you do is hide and run. How are we going battle like this?” Ye Xiu yelled into the chat self-righteously.

The stadium was instantly filled with booing. They couldn’t believe this guy. He couldn’t find Captain Yu so he started going after the referee, implying that Yu Wenzhou’s behavior wasn’t acceptable?

“This is strategy.” That was how Yu Wenzhou ended up replying, also sounding like he was giving the referee an explanation.

“What an annoying guy,” Ye Xiu said as Lord Grim began shoot randomly again.

“I’m right here! Come at me!” Ye Xiu hollered.

“No rush.” Was Yu Wenzhou’s reply. He never stopped inputting commands, but there was no hurry to his actions. From Swoksaar shaking Lord Grim off to now where he was turning back to find an opportunity to attack, his actions were steady and unrushed.

Not long later…

“Hey!” Ye Xiu expressed his displeasure. Another Chaotic Rain? Didn’t he have any new tricks? However, he didn’t use any new tricks to counter this. Again, he opened the umbrella, squatted, then Shadow Clone Techiqued out of there. It was just that this time, Yu Wenzhou didn’t follow up with another Hexagram Prison, the Chaotic Rain steadily falling upon the Misty Thicket.

One couldn’t deduce the caster’s position from these sorts of skills. At most, a range, so there was no way to do anything about it. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim blankly stood amidst the forestry, watching the rain fall.

And then… there was no more and thens…

Blue Rain’s home stadium was filled with booing. This was Yu Wenzhou fighting, the much adored captain of Blue Rain, and in a one on one match, too, something he hadn’t done in ages. Yet there was booing.

The audience couldn’t help it.

Here we are, our hearts in our throats, and that’s all you’re showing us?

The two on the stage remained unmoved.

Chaotic Rain stopped. The forest sunk back into silence.

Lord Grim suddenly darted out, moving with a Charge skill.

But the direction…

With the audience’s omniscient point of view, they knew immediately that this was the wrong direction, but Ye Xiu’s movements didn’t stop. After Charge, Lord Grim immediately changed directions and used a Colliding Stab. Another high speed movement skill. This time, the direction was far more accurate, but it wasn’t enough!

After witnessing the two exchanges just now, many of the more careful audience members had noted down the distances between the characters back then. Though they probably weren’t as observant as the two players, they knew that the distance was probably the upper limit to the players’ views in the Misty thicket. Lord Grim’s charge was in the right direction, but the distance you travelled with this technique wasn’t enough to bring Swoksaar into view…

Continue forwards! Many people prayed, yet after that Colliding Stab, Lord Grim switched directions again and used a Shining Cut…

You went in the wrong direction!

Many people cried in their heads.

However, those that realized what Ye Xiu was trying perked up.

“There!” Li Yibo yelled.

“Ah?”

With an “ah” from Pan Lin, Lord Grim’s Shining Cut had ended. It wasn’t towards Swoksaar’s direction, but it flashed through Swoksaar’s view. That meant that he also had a moments chance to see Swoksaar’s position.

“He’s using high speed movement to increase the range of his view!” Li Yibo explained to the audience.

“Did he see?” Pan Lin asked loudly.

Lord Grim’s reaction gave him the best answer. Shining Cut swept out, but it was already just a shadow clone. Lord Grim’s real body was near Swoksaar.

Boom boom boom!

Anti-Tank Missiles’s three shells flew out with tongues of flame. The three missiles were very spread out, not aiming to strike their target, but using light to lock onto Swoksaar’s form.

Yu Wenzhou repeated his previous action. Having stood, prepared, he turned and darted behind a tree, but this time, Ye Xiu was prepared as well. Lord Grim stopped to cast and a Goblin appeared beside the tree.

Lord Grim lunged forth. Swoksaar had disappeared from view once more. Yu Wenzhou’s use of his environment was truly ingenious. However, the Goblin was still in Lord Grim’s view. Lord Grim, sprinting forwards, rapidly headed towards the direction the Goblin was unsteadily charging towards.

Chapter 1434 - There’s a Trap

Ye Xiu’s trick had Pan Lin and Li Yibo exchanging a look in the broadcasting room.

“I don’t know why but I suddenly thought of the phrase ‘close the door and release the dogs’,” Pan Lin suddenly sighed.

“Haha, I don’t know if the door closed or not, but he really did release a dog,” Li Yibo laughed.

“And this dog is practically biting at the heels,” Pan Lin noted, watching the screen.

Currently, Ye Xiu still couldn’t see Swoksaar, but the Goblin continued to move, confident in where to go. Even novices knew that summons would only move when under the control of the player or on auto. Otherwise, they would just stand in place dumbly. So, Pan Lin and Li Yibo made a few comments but didn’t discuss it in detail, since it was so simple. However, before Ye Xiu, how many people would think to use the most low leveled summons to hunt down Yu Wenzhou whose understanding of the map was unparallelled?

With a clear direction, Lord Grim’s pursuit was swift. If it wasn’t for the fact that he had used three movement skills in succession to increase the range of his view, then Lord Grim would’ve caught up a while ago. Unfortunately, those three skills were on cooldown, meaning that Lord Grim wasn’t at his fastest. Even so, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim close the distance rapidly with what he had. At the very least, he could see Swoksaar’s form now.

The Goblin was small, with short legs. It wasn’t very fast at all. Normal players could easily shake them off as well. However, these few moments had given Ye Xiu a chance.

Bang bang!

As he moved, Lord Grim shot twice to disrupt Swoksaar’s movement. But Yu Wenzhou didn’t react to it at all. Swoksaar didn’t even bother to dodge.

Ye Xiu knew that something was wrong. There was no way you could escape just by ignoring these attacks. That wasn’t a thing!

Gatling Gun!

Ye Xiu resolutely activated this skill. Bullets shot out like a flood. It didn’t take many shots before Swoksaar turned into a puff of smoke and disappeared in the mist.

“Hahahahaha!” The audience was delighted, because they had known about this from the moment it happened!

You might have your cunning tricks, but I’m no less crafty!

Ye Xiu’s use of summons to track his target had fully utilized the characteristics of this basic skill, but Yu Wenzhou soon countered, tooth for a tooth.

Shadow Clone Technique!

It was also a low level skill, which was generally used as a teleportation skill by Nightwalkers. But right now, Yu Wenzhou was using it the way it was originally intended: to confuse the opponent.

An experienced player like Ye Xiu definitely wouldn’t be tricked by a Shadow Clone Technique. It was just unfortunate that a dumb little summons was easily tricked by a technique like this.

As soon as the Goblin began to chase, Yu Wenzhou had Swoksaar quickly form hand seals. Afterwards, the one the Goblin and Lord Grim were pursuing was Swoksaar’s shadow clone.

Then where was the real Swoksaar?

Rumble…

A rumbling erupted, the air split open, and the pitch black Death’s Door rose from behind Lord Grim.

Under these circumstances, if Swoksaar didn’t successfully take the chance to launch a powerful attack, then Yu Wenzhou wouldn’t be worthy of being Blue Rain’s captain!

If he could, he would probably have the Death’s Door cast on top of Lord Grim. Yu Wenzhou didn’t seem to intend to use Death’s Door’s CC at all. With a Death’s Door so close, he was clearly aiming to deal damage as fast as possible.

“That’s a wise choice!” Li Yibo praised. “Using Death’s Door’s control to launch an attack to eliminate Death’s Door’s ending lag would maximize damage, against a skilled and experienced expert like Ye Xiu, Yu Wenzhou might end up failing to deal any damage and exposing himself instead. Usually, this usage of Death’s Door wouldn’t pose much of a threat to Ye Xiu. Lord Grim’s movement methods and speed vastly lowered the difficulty of escaping from Death’s Door. That’s why it was better to just set Death’s Door right next to him and aim for a quick round of damage.”

Li Yibo’s analysis was very reasonable this time, and he was also correct. That was, indeed, what Yu Wenzhou was thinking. He didn’t ask for too much, because he knew that it was best to not give his current opponent any chances. His ability to grasp opportunities was on par with Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian. Against this sort of person, you would have to be ready to improvise and counter what he did. If you planned and schemed, then he was sure to trick you into falling into the very trap you set.

Boom!

A Death’s Door activated next to its target: the miasma immediately latched onto the character, directly skipping over the part where it dragged its target back and exploding!

Damn cool!

Applause filled the stadium.

This strike struck bone. The damage from the Chaotic Rain and Sandstorm Trap from before was nothing.

Nineteen percent!

That was how much of Lord Grim’s health this attack had taken.

Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar was centered around powerful control and high bursts. His personal style was similar to the cooldown style. Yu Wenzhou was unsuited to chaining long combos to stack damage.

He grasped a chance and unleashed a powerful skill to take out almost one fifth of his opponent’s health, swift and resolute. More importantly, Yu Wenzhou didn’t expose Swoksaar’s position with this attack. Currently, he was hidden to the side, already casting a second skill.

Hexagram Prison!

Just through the distance between Lord Grim and the Death’s Door and their relative positions, Yu Wenzhou had managed to calculate exactly where Lord Grim would be thrown to by the Death’s Door’s explosion. Hexagram Prison was executed so precisely that there was no way to stop it. Ye Xiu was trying to have Lord Grim quick recover to roll back onto his feet when the Hexagram Prison trapped him.

Hexagram Prison didn’t do any damage on its own. Damage was only dealt with other skills while the target was trapped. Yu Wenzhou wouldn’t miss such an opportunity either, no longer caring if Swoksaar would be exposed or not anymore.

Curse Arrows, Burning Arrows, two low level skills that Swoksaar rarely ever used. Then, a Shadow Flames and Grasping Ghosts, two damage over time skills.

Lord Grim’s Myriad manifestations Umbrella had such a large surface area for defense, it made his opponents depressed, but now that he was caught by Yu Wenzhou’s Hexagram Prison, it was Ye Xiu who felt depressed.

Since it was too big, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella couldn’t open up into its shield form in the Hexagram Prison. Lord Grim could do nothing but take the damage from the four skills.

Swoksaar’s position was completely exposed now, but after these four skills, Yu Wenzhou didn’t have Swoksaar flee. Swoksaar waved his Curse of Destruction, continuing to cast…

This skill had a visibly longer cast time, and at practically the same time the Hexagram Prison disappeared, Curse of Destruction was jabbed at Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu seemed to have realized something as well, and had Lord Grim raise the Myriad manifestations Umbrella at almost the same time, wanting to use Rotor Wings, but it was too late…

There were no flashes of light, but the ground under Lord Grim’s feet had been changed through a curse.

Lord Grim, attempting to use Rotor Wings to escape, was about to jump into the air, but the moment his feet left the ground, he sunk.

Dense forestry, denser mist…

This scenery was creepy enough, but when Ye Xiu looked downwards, he saw that the area under Lord Grim had already been cursed. Strange runes crawled over the ground like squirming maggots, and the area seemed to have a layer of fog over it, making the ground look wet and sticky. The howling of the damned filled his ears as his body sunk. Withered grey hands burst out of the soil, the hem of Lord Grim’s pants clenched in their fists. Later on, some heads even appeared, teeth snapping, and others rose up to catch Lord Grim in an iron embrace, all holding on for dear life, tugging at him, as if they wanted to pull him into this curse as well.

Just the special effects alone made it worthy of being a high level skill…

Death Entanglement!

The new level 75 Warlock skill. A skill above even Death’s Door.

Before the skill ended or before a target walked out of the affected zone, the skill would deal damage over time to the characters enmeshed. In addition, a powerful slow would be inflicted, and even better, skills like Teleportation, Shadow Clone Technique, even Rotor Wings couldn’t be used in the affected area. They would all be interrupted, and the character would be grabbed by the wraiths.

There was no instantly escaping the area cursed by Death Entanglement, unless you were very lucky and started on the edge of the skill’s area of effect, able to step out in one step. However, Yu Wenzhou had set the skill so that Lord Grim was in the center. No matter which way he walked, the skill would probably end before he could walk out.

“It seems like you really did manage to trap me…” Ye Xiu was still in the mood to chat at a time like this! After Death’s Door and the four consecutive skills, then this level 75 skill… this combo of Swoksaar’s was the highest damage he could do in this period of time.

31%!

That was the total damage these skills had dealt to Lord Grim. Death Entanglement was a level 75 skill, but it’s damage was nothing compared to Death’s Door. However, that didn’t mean it was at all a weak skill. It’s CC far overpowered Death’s Door.

31%, added to the 19% from Death’s Door, meant that Yu Wenzhou had taken half of Lord Grim’s health in one go. This was truly a display of his power.

“Unfortunately, it isn’t enough,” Yu Wenzhou replied. This was true disappointment. Of course, he hoped that he could skill Lord Grim here and now. However, under the current circumstances, he didn’t have any confidence that he would be able to trap Lord Grim so well after the Death Entanglement ended. Exposing his position was an extremely risky move, so he had no choice but to stop his assault and have Swoksaar find a new, better place to hide.

“This performance of yours is more than enough for you to brag about. You can even tell your kids about it after you grow old,” Ye Xiu replied.

“I still hope that the story can become a little more spectacular,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Impossible! You’re nowhere near good enough!” Ye Xiu said.

“That’s no secret,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“I planted a fatal trap for you,” Ye Xiu informed the other.

“Oh? What is it?” Just as the message sent, Yu Wenzhou paled. Swoksaar really did step into a trap.

Then, Lord Grim appeared right in front of him, face to face, practically no space between them.

“A Shadow Trap. Scared yet?” Ye Xiu asked.

Chapter 1435 - An Incomprehensible, Godly Turnaround

After Shadow Trap triggered, the user would immediately appear at the trap’s position.

If one were to ask what use this skill had, the short answer would be just one word: Ambush.

This was because the skill allowed the player to abruptly engage in close-quarters combat with his opponent, and at the same time, it also referred to the skill that Thieves most commonly used along with it: Ambush. If the skill Ambush connected, it would deal double the damage to the target while stunning them for three seconds. It had considerable benefits when paired with the Thief’s Stealth, or with Shadow Trap.

But to Ye Xiu, he didn’t he didn’t need Ambush at all, all he needed was an opportunity to latch on to his opponent.

What latching on to his opponent meant was something that everyone was very clear about.

The moment Shadow Trap appeared, the jubilant atmosphere in Blue Rain’s home stadium immediately died down. It was as if someone had hit the mute button on the whole stadium, sending it into absolute silence.

But very quickly, the jumping and cheering and laughing began again. In the West wing of the stadium, the Happy fans suddenly became spirited again!

“Godly turnaround!” They shouted loudly.

Indeed, it was really a godly turnaround.

But how this godly turnaround was created was something that no one understood.

How was the Shadow Trap placed? How did he know that Yu Wenzhou would step on it at that precise moment?

Pan Lin stared at Li Yibo, Li Yibo stared at Pan Lin, and the commentators fell into an embarrassing situation. Even if they wanted to escape, this question was something that they couldn’t run away from.

It was fortunate that Lord Grim was engaging in an intense offensive, so Pan Lin put on an act and commentated on the current situation, while Li Yibo hurriedly reviewed the replay.

By staring unblinkingly at the replay, he really did manage to find the moment that Lord Grim placed the Shadow Trap. The problem was, finding it was finding it, but Li Yibo couldn’t figure out the reason why the Shadow Trap was placed at that location.

Li Yibo was so frantic that he began sweating. The television directors had sent word that the hotline for the broadcast even had many viewers calling in to ask what on earth had actually happened.

Li Yibo’s cheeks streamed with tears. He really wished that he too could make a call to find out what had happened.

In the past, even after being made a laughing stock for his wrong predictions, Li Yibo was still able to come up with roughly the right answer after looking closely at the situation afterwards. This time, however, he was wracking his brains but couldn’t come up with an answer. How could he explain it? He couldn’t just say it was all luck, right?

Swoksaar fell.

This result came as no surprise. In a close-quarters fight, Yu Wenzhou’s disadvantages were obvious. Even though he had the awareness, the experience, and the judgements, Ye Xiu wasn’t lacking in any of these aspects either. On top of that, the Unspecialized Blitz had an extremely fast tempo, amplifying Yu Wenzhou’s shortcomings even more. Towards the end, everyone had clearly seen his struggles. The die-hard fans in Blue Rain’s home stadium almost couldn’t bear to watch it any longer, but Ye Xiu had no such qualms. From start to finish, the Unspecialized Blitz had an even tighter tempo than usual.

In the first battle, Happy emerged victorious. Nonetheless, when this result became clear, the mood in the stadium had actually become more stable. After all, when that Shadow Trap had been triggered, everyone had already prepared themselves for the worst. The fans of Blue Rain knew that no matter how it appeared, their captain would definitely be fighting an arduous battle. If he could easily take away half the health from Ye Xiu’s character, would their captain really be avoiding the individual competitions?

Applause.

When Yu Wenzhou left the stage, he still received applause. Sure, he had lost, but the fans of Blue Rain were already more than satisfied by what he had managed to achieve. “Fight on!” they shouted, hoping that the players from Blue Rain wouldn’t be discouraged by this loss.

Indeed, Blue Rain’s players weren’t discouraged. They stood up, welcoming their team captain.

“You played well!” Everyone said in succession.

“Being swept away by a single combo is still considered playing well?” Yu Wenzhou laughed bitterly.

“It was nearly you sweeping him away with a single combo,” Huang Shaotian replied.

Yu Wenzhou shook his head. The actual circumstances were something that he understood more clearly than anyone else.

“When was that Shadow Trap placed?” Yu Wenzhou asked Huang Shaotian.

“When he summoned that Goblin to chase you,” Huang Shaotian said.

“It was at that moment?” Yu Wenzhou thought pensively. In his heart, he already had a general idea of what had happened. Nevertheless, this wasn’t the time for careful thinking. Blue Rain’s second player had already prepared to leave and was looking at him, waiting for his command!

“It’s a shame, I fell into his trap too quickly. Do your best!” Yu Wenzhou said to the second player who was about to go onstage.

Song Xiao, the key player who would always shine during the playoffs.

In the end, in the last round’s group arena, he had been firmly suppressed by Ye Xiu. The team competition was an even sadder affair. Despite his confidence, he didn’t have any time to put on a good performance before being killed by a slash.

“Watch me!” Song Xiao roused his spirits and entered the stage.

In the group arena, the map didn’t change, so it was still Misty Thicket. In the time that it took to change players, Pan Lin and Li Yibo thoroughly discussed the map, going back and forth as if they had an inexhaustible amount of things to say. This chatter was actually a sign of their lack of confidence. In the end, the two of them still weren’t able to explain how Ye Xiu knew where to place that Shadow Trap from the last round. At this time, discussing the map was a way for the two of them to embarrassedly change the topic!

The second round of the group arena soon began.

In the previous round, Lord Grim had half his life taken out in one wave of attacks, and when he forcefully killed off Swoksaar, he had suffered a little more damage, putting his total health at thirty-nine percent. As such, when the round began, Ye Xiu first had Lord Grim cast a few healing skills, bringing his total health to fifty percent and causing the entire stadium to begin cursing at him. Only after this did he unhurriedly have Lord Grim set out.

Similarly to the last round, Lord Grim directly took the middle road. What about Receding Tides, who had set out first? Song Xiao had chosen to take a roundabout route to the east. When Lord Grim reached the center of the map, Ye Xiu stopped moving, but he couldn’t find any trace of his opponent. Had he taken a tactical route?

Ye Xiu was simple and straightforward. He stopped guessing, instead directly asking in the public channel, “You want to ambush me again?”

“If not to ambush, then what’s the point of choosing this map?” Song Xiao was self-righteous and confident. As an important core player, Song Xiao’s resistance against trash talk was outstanding, not needing to avoid chatting here and there with others.

“You have a point! I’m at 24, 58, come and ambush me!” Ye Xiu sent simply.

“Please wait a moment, I’ll be there soon,” Song Xiao replied.

“The left side or the right side?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Both the left and right side,” Song Xiao replied.

“Alright!” Ye Xiu replied. Afterwards, under everyone’s watchful eyes, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim leave the spot where 24, 58 was.

Walking straight, towards Blue Rain’s respawn point. After charging out for a distance, Lord Grim turned right.

All of a sudden, the crowd was sent into an uproar. With this one turn, Lord Grim had looped behind Receding Tides!

“This… this…” Pan Lin said “this” twice. What he really wanted to ask was “How did he do this,” but after failing to figure out the godly turnaround from earlier, Pan Lin forcefully swallowed his question.

How had he managed to make such a precise decision? At this moment, Li Yibo was similarly flabbergasted.

Was it from their conversation earlier? Pan Lin carefully pored over every single one of Ye Xiu’s lines. Was there some kind of probing nature to them?

“He guessed it.” From Blue Rain’s player seats, Yu Wenzhou’s conclusion was extremely simple.

“Guessed it?” Some of his teammates were doubtful.

“If not left, then right. A fifty-fifty, just like taking a penalty kick. If he made the shot, then it would be a great success, if not… even if he missed, he wouldn’t lose anything. Of course it was worth a shot,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“Then his luck is just too good!” Blue Rian’s players were depressed, as if they’d just missed a penalty kick.

As they spoke, Song Xiao had already reached those coordinates, but he didn’t walk out of the mist to expose himself. Instead, he stopped moving, taking the initiative to call out to Ye Xiu.

“I’ve arrived,” Song Xiao said.

“Liar, I don’t see you,” Ye Xiu replied.

“I also don’t see you, why don’t you shoot once or twice and let me find you,” Song Xiao said.

“That won’t do. That’s a privilege reserved for team captains, I can’t simply break the rules,” Ye Xiu said.

“Then there’s nothing to be done, the two of us can just slowly drag things out!” Song Xiao said.

“By selecting this map today, it really seems as if Blue Rain’s intentions are to drag things out!” Li Yibo suddenly said.

“With this map, if they don’t drag things out, there aren’t many other things they can do…” Pan Lin said.

“If they wanted to fight head-on, there’s still the option of going directly to the center of the map. But both of Blue Rain’s players have been playing tactically, purposefully making use of this map’s special features, dragging the tempo of the battle until it annoys everyone, this…” Li Yibo felt as if he had grasped some important point, wanting to organize his thoughts before speaking again, when Pan Lin suddenly shouted from beside him, “He’s got it!”

In Ye Xiu’s field of view, a faint silhouette of a person had appeared. After wrapping around, he had finally found Receding Tides.

In the end, it was as if Song Xiao had also heard Pan Lin’s loud shout, because that faint silhouette disappeared in the blink of an eye. With a Charge, Lord Grim rushed forwards by several body units, but he still couldn’t find a trace of Song Xiao. With an omniscient point-of-view, the crowd could clearly see that when Lord Grim had quietly appeared, it unfortunately wasn’t a wraparound, but instead, he had circled around Receding Tide’s front, and both players had seen each other.

Afterwards, as if he had no intention of fighting whatsoever, Receding Tides hid behind a tree.

Lord Grim charged out, but Receding Tides took a long detour behind the tree, running far away from Lord Grim.

“This…” Pan Lin didn’t quite understand. Song Xiao hadn’t been ambushed, the two players had noticed each other at the same time. If you were to say that Yu Wenzhou immediately ran after being discovered, everyone would be able to understand that. But Song Xiao? He had indeed been suppressed to death by Ye Xiu in the previous round, but when all was said and done, he didn’t draw as short a stick as Yu Wenzhou, he could still put up a fight! If he still wanted to run under these circumstances, then what did he plan to do? Do the same as Yu Wenzhou, and wait for an opportunity when he had complete control over his opponent before making a move?

But Swoksaar was a Warlock, with many controlling abilities, allowing Yu Wenzhou’s plan to come to fruition. Song Xiao was a Qi Master, so wouldn’t it be difficult for him to create such a beautiful opportunity for himself? Could it be that this guy was planning to play dirty and launch ambushes non-stop?

Just as Pan Lin thought this, Song Xiao really did have Receding Tides move up for an ambush again.

Ye Xiu had a rich amount of experience, so even after charging over and not seeing Receding Tides, he still remembered where his silhouette had been, and after taking a look at the position, he already had some inferences about where Song Xiao might be hiding, so Lord Grim had already begun striding in that direction. In the end, just as everyone thought that Song Xiao was ready to run, he suddenly had his character strike a sudden blow.

Sky Piercing Strike!

Just as Ye Xiu had Lord Grim wrap around that tree, trying to guess where Song Xiao had run off to, Receding Tides sent out a Sky Piercing Strike towards him.

Chapter 1436 - Wearing Down

The attacks made from the ethereal qi from a Qi Master were actually more visible than usual on this map, where any movement disturbed the thick fog. Even though Song Xiao had launched this Sky Piercing Strike very quickly, it didn’t pose any difficulty for Ye Xiu.

Charge!

Even though he clearly saw the attack coming for him, Ye Xiu chose not to hide behind a tree, but to ferociously charge forward.

Boom!

Part of the qi from the Sky Piercing Strike slammed into the tree, giving off a muffled sound, followed by the rustling of the tree’s leaves and branches. Ye Xiu hadn’t chosen the safer method of dodging the attack – he seemed almost in a rush as he chased after Song Xiao.

“It looks like Ye Xiu has lost some of his cool?” Pan Lin shouted, his voice full of surprise. He’d been commentating Glory matches for a number of years now, so he’d commentated for the old Battle God One Autumn Leaf Ye Xiu as well as the current unspecialized Lord Grim Ye Xiu. For Pan Lin to become so distinguished in the Glory commentary circle, he was at a solid level. He had always felt that this new Ye Xiu, after returning to the professional scene this season, was somewhat different from before.

Pan Lin hadn’t experienced the years when Excellent Era had swept the Alliance, but from the seasons afterward, in the matches where Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng built their reputation as Best Partners, he could imagine just how ferocious that dominating Battle God had been. Even though Excellent Era’s scores had been in a steady decline in the following years, Pan Lin could still tell that all of the powerful teams in the Alliance still viewed Excellent Era as a difficult enemy. And Ye Xiu had always been the target that all of the Gods and experts had aimed to defeat.

Ye Xiu had always been this pinnacle existence.

All the way until he departed in Season 8. Just like that, a God had fallen. In the days of his absence, though, the Alliance continued to develop. The king of the new generation, Zhou Zekai, lived up to expectations as he won two championships and continued to charge toward Excellent Era’s record of three consecutive championships.

The times had changed, and in the eyes of many younger viewers, Zhou Zekai was the one who was worthy of being called Glory’s number one. The returned Ye Xiu was no longer the pinnacle presence of before, no longer that lofty goal that everyone wanted to challenge and defeat. This time, he had become a challenger. Those people who had once looked up to him now all had beautifully powerful teams behind them. And this Team Happy that Ye Xiu now led could only look up to them.

No longer was he the one being challenged. Now, he was the challenger!

From the beginning, Pan Lin had felt that looking at Ye Xiu and Happy from this angle would be very interesting. But… Ye Xiu hadn’t cooperated at all! Right after they’d barely managed to defeat Excellent Era, they were already hollering about winning the championship. Where was the attitude of being the challenger?

But Pan Lin understood. This was probably the principle of not letting yourself be intimidated by the opponent’s identity, while still being cautious of the opponent’s abilities and tactics.

Season 10, 38 rounds. The television broadcast wouldn’t choose Happy’s matches every week, but Pan Lin still watched every single one of Happy’s matches.

As a commentator, he couldn’t demonstrate emotional bias. He could only praise those that performed well, or express regret for those that didn’t. Even though he would also sometimes forget himself while a particularly thrilling performance onstage, on the whole, the emotions of a commentator had to be almost mechanical. Their emotional expression was trained, or in other words, it was… a performance.

In reality, Pan Lin had paid very close attention to Happy this season. Like many others, he was very curious about that weapon in Lord Grim’s hand, and he was very curious about how this team, a team that had come from who-knows-where but had miraculously defeated Excellent Era in the Challenger League, would ultimately perform in the professional circle.

The people who had paid this kind of attention to Happy had reaped quite some satisfaction this season.

Happy, this patchwork team, had done extremely well.

And those who had been paying attention to Happy were, of course, paying attention to Ye Xiu as well.

Thirty-seven consecutive wins! To be able to watch this record built from start to finish, this was an incredible reward for those paying attention to Ye Xiu over the course of this year.

But in the process of watching these consecutive victories, Pan Lin felt a few other things.

Thirty-seven consecutive wins. Even in Ye Xiu’s pinnacle years, he had never had such a perfect performance before. Part of this was of course because Lord Grim was unspecialized, but separating the character from the player, Pan Lin felt that Ye Xiu was different as well.

The Ye Xiu of the past, who had led his account to earn the title of Battle God, was domineering on the battlefield, invincible.

But today’s Ye Xiu? He’d won thirty-seven consecutive battles, which still seemed invincible. But Pan Lin felt that, even though his results were incredible, the returned Ye Xiu didn’t seem to have that same brash, dominating air that he’d had as a Battle Mage.

Was his temperament different because his class was different?

At the beginning, Pan Lin had thought this was the case. But after seeing many matches, it didn’t seem quite right.

It wasn’t until the end of the season, and he saw the adjustments and changes that Team Tyranny had made, that Pan Lin finally understood.

Ye Xiu, like those three old generals of Tyranny, wasn’t young anymore! That brash and sharp air of the Battle God had slowly bled away with the flow of time. Before, because Ye Xiu had always been present and everyone was always watching his matches, they hadn’t noticed the feeling very clearly. But after leaving and then returning after a year and a half, the scars left by the passage of time were suddenly in stark clarity.

He hadn’t wantonly squandered his youth, nor had he willfully tried to compete with the years. He had simply been continuously adjusting and perfecting his own technique, using whatever style best suited him at the time to engage in battle.

Calm, elegant, and then old. From the very start, he had never planned to lament this inevitable fact of life. Just like how he faced the championship, he faced this saddening situation with vigor.

This season, quite a few people discussed the pressure that Ye Xiu faced, leading a team like this. They discussed just how exhausting it was for him, all for the sake of victory.

But Pan Lin didn’t agree.

Ye Xiu had indeed been working very hard. Without him, this Team Happy definitely wouldn’t be what it was today. But over Happy’s thirty-eight matches, whether they won or lost, Pan Lin had always seen an air of joy.

Yes, joy!

The sort of joy that came from playing from the heart.

Glory was, after all, a game. Pan Lin wondered whether many people had forgotten this point. After last round, many commentators criticized Happy’s brutally utilitarian style of play. After reading them, Pan Lin found them laughable.

Utilitarian?

Had they not realized that the Glory Alliance itself was the most utilitarian?

The implementation of all sorts of rules, the requirement that the battles be splendid, this and that, all of it revealed the utilitarianism.

In comparison, Pan Lin felt that Happy’s performance wasn’t utilitarian at all. It was purely a pursuit of victory. Pan Lin had always thought that those who wanted both victory and a beautiful battle were the real utilitarians!

Victory and loss. A very straightforward thing, and yet so many details had to be bickered over. The utilitarianism revealed a sort of hypocrisy.

The battle wasn’t pretty?

But the thing was, who was going to contribute a pretty battle for you? The players were on the battlefield, they cared about victory, and certainly not appearance. You thought the battle was ugly, but didn’t you know just how happy the players were while playing?

In Pan Lin’s eyes, Ye Xiu was undoubtedly this kind of person. He never cared about the opinions of those around him. Using the best method to obtain victory, this was what he had always done. This was one thing that had never changed about him, from age 17 to age 27.

So now, Ye Xiu’s decision had caught him somewhat off-guard. This sort of action, eager to show a certain attitude, didn’t suit Ye Xiu’s character!

“He does seem a bit rushed…” Li Yibo hadn’t thought as much as Pan Lin. Just from technique, Ye Xiu’s forced charge was a bit impatient. Even if he was anxious to lock onto Receding Tides’ position, the risk was a bit too much. Song Xiao, after all, wasn’t Yu Wenzhou. Coming into close range wasn’t an immediate guarantee of victory.

Right now, Lord Grim rushed into close range and the two began to fight. But could he really take him down with this?

No one thought he had a good chance. The only reason Li Yibo didn’t dare say so was for fear of getting slapped in the face.

Lord Grim’s charge earlier had really been a bit of a struggle, but an arrow once fired couldn’t be recalled. He had charged forward, so he had to see this through. But Lord Grim’s rhythm never managed to stabilize, and in his exchange with Song Xiao’s Receding Tides, he failed to gain the upper hand. Instead, he presented an opening to Song Xiao.

But Song Xiao didn’t have Receding Tides pursue this opening. He actually chose to retreat, and instantly hid himself once again within this foggy forest. It appeared that Blue Rain had made thorough preparations on this map. Song Xiao’s control when controlling the path of Receding Tides was no inferior to Yu Wenzhou’s.

“They really are planning on dragging this out!” Pan Lin was stunned.

“They’re playing an endurance battle!” Seeing this, Li Yibo’s tone became much more confident than before.

“What are they wearing down? Lord Grim’s health? Mana?” Pan Lin said.

“And Ye Xiu’s energy,” said Li Yibo.

Pan Lin paused, and then looked at the time. Indeed, today’s group arena had been dragging on for quite a while. Normally, by this time, the group arena would already be on the third or fourth battle. Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou had been defeated and replaced by Song Xiao, but Happy’s first player Ye Xiu still hadn’t gone down! Blue Rain wasn’t giving him the chance to end a match quickly. Even when there was a chance to counterattack, Song Xiao had chosen to back off. The intention was all too clear: they wanted to play a long endurance match.

And this Song Xiao wasn’t like Yu Wenzhou, he didn’t have to worry so much about the opponent closing in. Just after escaping, he was able to come back and harass him again as if it were nothing.

Once, twice, three times…

Song Xiao’s steadiness and ability to perform under pressure was, in this match, used entirely on running around. Every time he’d come to harass Ye Xiu for a bit, and as soon as the situation became slightly unfavorable, he’d instantly run away. Again and again, he actually succeeded in getting away every time. This struggle continued on for another five minutes, and in that time, the health of both players had dropped less than ten percent. This rhythm was almost disastrously slow.

“How will this match turn out?” Pan Lin said weakly. The first or second time when Song Xiao had rushed back, he had gotten excited and shouted a bit, but after that he wasn’t fooled again. From Song Xiao’s current attitude, it seemed that the only way Song Xiao would relax would be if Lord Grim completely stripped off all of his equipment and just stood there waiting to be attacked.

Clutch player? Pan Lin didn’t feel it. The feeling that Song Xiao gave him now was more like that of a frightened songbird.

Chapter 1437 - Can't Follow You

Everyone in the stadium was starting to feel sleepy.

This was Blue Rain’s home game, but Blue Rain was entirely at fault for this boredom. It was their players who were waging guerrilla warfare. It was their players who were refusing to confront Ye Xiu directly. It was their players who were dragging this game out.

This was practically a test to see whether the fans truly supported them…

Scattered all around the stadium, the loyal Blue Rain fans responsible for hyping up the crowd had encountered the greatest obstacle for a cheerleading squad: the game was dragging out for so long that even they were having trouble keeping themselves motivated.

“This is our team’s strategy!” They could only inform everyone sincerely. Trying to get everyone to cheer loudly for this sort of game would be too forced. Then, as if Song Xiao had caught on to the crowd’s feelings, his Receding Tides rushed forward. Everyone was excited. They waited, saving their energy for the explosive confrontation to come, only to be met with Song Xiao’s Receding Tides running away.

This was too hurtful to them!

The crowd in the stadium were doing the same as Pan Lin. After crying out twice for false alarms, Pan Lin wouldn’t fall for it again. Everyone could only pray that the match would end! Was there really any point in doing all of this?

“What’s the point?” Ye Xiu represented the thoughts of Blue Rain’s fans and questioned Blue Rain’s strategy in the chat.

Song Xiao used actions to reply back. Receding Tides rushed out again.

“How many times has he done it?” The audience members whispered to each other. This was already the only topic they could think of.

“The fifth?”

“I think it’s the sixth.”

“Isn’t it the sixth?”

“If I’m remembering it correctly.”

“Alright, it’s the sixth then!” The audience members clearly didn’t care much about this topic.

Sky Piercing Cannon!

Even a skill used to initiate battles wasn’t anything exciting anymore. Everyone was completely numb to it at this point.

“Song Xiao’s Receding Tides has rushed out once again. Let’s see what he’ll do this time,” Pan Lin forced himself to sound energetic. But because the same scene had repeated itself over and over again, he couldn’t bother to think of new ways to word it.

“Sky Piercing Cannon, Landmine Earthquake… Oh, he has Qi Flowing Cloud activated… Spiral Qi Kill missed. It hit a tree. He’s starting to retreat. Lord Grim is chasing after him, ” Pan Lin calmly described the scene. It was as if he wasn’t talking about a battle.

“Receding Tides has turned around behind the tree. He’s turning again…” The commentary stopped. Ye Xiu had lost sight of Receding Tides. It looked like the chase stopped here again.

But then, Lord Grim suddenly retraced his steps, and Receding Tide appeared in his sights again.

“Ah!” Pan Lin wasn’t prepared for such a sudden change and couldn’t find the right words. Fortunately, Li Yibo had been quietly thinking during the seemingly endless loop. When Lord Grim retraced his steps, his eyes immediately lit up.

“He’s caught on!”

“Yes, Song Xiao had escaped from Ye Xiu in the same way the last few times. This time, Ye Xiu has caught onto him,” Pan Lin clarified.

Anti-Tank Missiles!

Boom boom boom, three missiles flew out.

“Ah, why’d he attack so hastily! Get closer!” Pan Lin felt that it was a pity for Ye Xiu. In his eyes, Ye Xiu had seized a rare opportunity. From his omniscient view of the match, he could see that Song Xiao wasn’t aware that Lord Grim had retraced his steps to a different angle. Ye Xiu could have sneaked closer. But instead, as soon as he found a new angle, he had Lord Grim attack.

Song Xiao was startled by the artillery fire. He was just about to dodge out of reflex, but he stopped himself at the last moment.

This was bait! A sudden attack to bait him into jumping up and exposing himself.

The thought had flashed through his mind, but then he realized that the direction wasn’t correct.

By the time he realized it, it was too late.

Boom boom boom!

Three Anti-Tank Missiles exploded, all of them hitting Receding Tides. Song Xiao immediately rolled to reduce the knockback from the explosions, while also adjusting his line of sight to see Lord Grim.

“It hit! It actually hit!” Pan Lin cried out.

Although it was a sneak attack, Launcher skills made noise. At this distance, Song Xiao could have reacted in time to dodge it, but he was still unexpectedly hit.

“He probably thought the attack was a trap,” Li Yibo said.

“He misjudged the situation.”

“It’s not just that,” Li Yibo said.

“What else is there?”

“Ye Xiu has started taking advantage of the terrain,” Li Yibo sucked in a deep breath of air.

“Oh, these past few minutes…”

“He’s been running around this place in circles the entire time. Not only was Ye Xiu familiarizing himself with the terrain, he’s been familiarizing himself with Song Xiao’s thoughts,” Li Yibo said.

“So he’s already grasped Song Xiao’s escape route!” Pan Lin was pleasantly surprised. This surprise wasn’t from his bias towards Happy, but rather, there was hope that this battle would finally end!

Collapsing Mountain!

After the Anti-Tank Missiles, Ye Xiu didn’t conserve his skills. Lord Grim sprinted over and then crashed down with a Collapsing Mountain.

Song Xiao had suddenly been hit by a strike and now his opponent was in front of him. However, he didn’t panic and saw through this Collapsing Mountain’s momentum. Receding Tides took a step forward and then let out a palm.

Qi Break!

A powerful high-level skill, yet it looked so gentle. There was no ear-piercing sound or flashy visual effects. All of the surging power was contained within the character. Until the final moment, no one would know what would happen. Qi Masters were filled with hidden meaning.

“See! Qi Masters are meant to be played dirty!” When one looked at things from a different perspective, what one concluded would be different. Happy’s Fang Rui didn’t think about the hidden meaning behind this powerful skill. Instead, he thought about sneak attacks and playing dirty…

His palm pushed against the side of the descending Lord Grim. Song Xiao had calculated the distance and direction. Even if Ye Xiu adjusted the angle of this attack, he wouldn’t be able to hit him. It was too late for Ye Xiu to switch to a different attack. Every skill attacked at a certain angle. At this point, there weren’t any possibilities left, were there?

Shing!

A sword light slashed through Receding Tides.

Sword Draw?!

Song Xiao was shocked.

You can do that?

Amidst the spray of blood, Receding Tides was knocked back. His Qi Burst had been interrupted. The Sword Light seemed to splash onto Receding Tides as Ye Xiu continued his onslaught.

“What’s going on? What just happened?” Pan Lin cried out.

“If I’m not mistaken… that Sword Draw was from his left hand,” Li Yibo said.

The battle was still ongoing. It wasn’t convenient to put out a replay. As a result, the cameraman played the previous clip on a smaller screen in slow motion. From the smaller screen, everyone finally saw that it was a Sword Draw from the left hand!

Lord Grim’s Collapsing Mountain had been executed using his right hand. While in the air, he switched hands and used Sword Draw. For a normal player, they would have to cancel Collapsing Mountain and then position the sword to the correct angle. But Lord Grim? They didn’t know if he cancelled Collapsing Mountain or not, but in that instant, Lord Grim’s left hand grabbed the end of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and performed a Sword Draw…

“This… Collapsing Mountain should have been cancelled, but because of Lord Grim’s umbrella, he doesn’t need to waste time adjusting the angle of his weapon. At that instant, he probably positioned his weapon for the left hand… letting him use his left hand to perform the move,” Li Yibo analyzed.

“A surprise attack! No wonder Song Xiao was caught off guard!” Pan Lin shouted.

At this moment, Song Xiao had been grabbed by Ye Xiu and caught in an onslaught of attacks. But the so-called Mister Clutch wouldn’t panic so easily. Song Xiao remained calm and defended, while looking for an opening.

Finally, an opportunity came!

Receding Tides seized this opening and tried to escape using the terrain. But when he made a turn around the tree ahead, Lord Grim cut him off.

“You’ve done this same move so many times. Aren’t you bored yet?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Sure enough, Song Xiao’s been completely seen through!” Pan Lin shouted.

“Even in this terrain, there are very few ways to completely escape Ye Xiu’s pursuit. Song Xiao had scurried around so many times, yet still wanted to keep doing the same thing. It’s as if he’s regarding Ye Xiu as a dead person,” Li Yibo said.

“It looks like I can’t run,” Song Xiao defended and answered Ye Xiu.

“Feel free to try again if an opening appears,” Ye Xiu said.

“No need. Let’s fight!” Song Xiao said. He switched up his fighting style. He was no longer as careful as before, always looking for an opportunity to escape. Receding Tides had gotten into a fighting posture, ready to confront Lord Grim.

“You should have just done this a long time ago,” Ye Xiu said.

“Do you even have enough health left to fight me?” Song Xiao was quite arrogant in front of God Ye Xiu.

“More than enough. I’ve been healing myself,” Ye Xiu typed.

While playing hide-and-seek with Song Xiao, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim heal himself every now and then. He couldn’t completely use up his mana just to keep his health up, after all, Lord Grim needed mana to fight! He hadn’t used Wish Prayer, which meant that he had most likely added a different skill onto his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

“Come!” Song Xiao shouted.

“I’m coming!” Ye Xiu replied. Lord Grim turned around and vanished.

“This is…” Pan Lin was speechless. The entire Glory world was speechless.

“What is the meaning of this!” Song Xiao stamped his feet.

“Did you think I’d fight just because you wanted to fight? I need to save my strength for the team competition!” Ye Xiu replied in the chat. Lord Grim traversed through the forest as if he were extremely familiar with it. Ye Xiu had already played on this map for dozens of minutes.

“I’m coming!” Ye Xiu suddenly shouted. Song Xiao wasn’t disturbed, but Lord Grim really did come.

Shua shua shua, several fast attacks; Song Xiao raised his spirits. Shua shua shua, several movement skills. Lord Grim was gone.

Lord Grim was matchless in terms of speed. Appearing and disappearing like a ghost was too easy in this sort of map.

“He’s playing… the cooldown style…” Li Yibo said as he saw Lord Grim search for an opportunity to attack.

Chapter 1438 - Professional Sandbagging

Song Xiao finally stopped conducting guerilla warfare and prepared to engage in a direct confrontation. However, it was Ye Xiu who refused to cooperate. Ye Xiu started conducting guerrilla warfare instead, continuing the tedious pace of the match.

“Shouldn’t Ye Xiu be trying to hurry and end it. Why’s he dragging things…” Pan Lin said.

“He holds the initiative by being the one dragging the match. In terms of energy, it’s more relaxing for him. If he fought with Song Xiao directly, it would be a contest of reaction speed and mechanics. For Ye Xiu, who’s already played for ten or so minutes, keeping up the speed and precision required for the overwhelming blitz of an unspecialized is difficult and tiresome. Blue Rain’s intention to tire out Ye Xiu in the group arena is already very obvious. Ye Xiu isn’t going to let them have their way…” Li Yibo said.

“But if he plays conservatively, it’ll be rather hard for him to beat Song Xiao…” Pan Lin said.

“That’s what it seems like…” Li Yibo had noticed Ye Xiu’s sneak attack attempts. He was playing just like how Song Xiao did. He never went in too deep. As soon as the situation seemed slightly unfavorable, he would immediately retreat. He wouldn’t brute force it. As a result, the damage dealt by both sides was extremely low. When Song Xiao held the initiative, he two sides had fought for 5 minutes, yet had only taken down 10% of each other’s health. Ye Xiu held the initiative now, but it was no better than the previous game of hide-and-seek.

“Even if he keeps this up, he’ll still get tired!” Pan Lin said. This playstyle put less of a burden on Ye Xiu, but if the match went on long enough, exhaustion would still slowly build up.

“Yes… Song Xiao is aware of this point too,” Li Yibo said.

Song Xiao had been surprised by Ye Xiu’s sudden retreat from a direct confrontation, but after realizing Ye Xiu’s intentions, he calmed down. He had no intentions of reversing the situation. He calmly put on a defensive posture and carefully dealt with Ye Xiu’s attacks. If Ye Xiu wanted to run, he would let him. He was in no hurry to chase after him. However, he couldn’t let him run around too freely, so he would occasionally put some pressure on him. The intensity of the match needed to be maintained to a certain extent. If not, Ye Xiu could just find a spot to sleep, and Song Xiao wouldn’t know. How would that tire out Ye Xiu?

“Coach Li, this is attacking by defending!” Pan Lin said.

Song Xiao’s sturdy defense made it so that Ye Xiu wasn’t getting much from his multiple sneak attacks. If this scenario repeated enough times, Ye Xiu would still get tired.

“Ye Xiu still holds the initiative though. I presume he probably has a plan in mind,” Li Yibo said.

Time passed minute by minute. The stalemate continued for another ten minutes. The second round of the group arena had already taken over ten minutes. Including the first round against Yu Wenzhou, Ye Xiu had been playing for nearly twenty minutes…

“Ye Xiu is… picking up a rock and smashing his own foot with it!” Pan Lin sighed. From his perspective, Ye Xiu’s decision was incorrect. Did he not think Song Xiao could be so tenacious? But Song Xiao is famous for being clutch! He never dropped the ball in the playoffs. Ye Xiu was waiting for him to make a mistake, yet ten minutes had passed, and he had nothing to show for it. His repeated attacks had only grinded down 20% of Receding Tide’s health. On the other hand, under Song Xiao’s persistent pressure, Lord Grim had lost 15% of his health.

Song Xiao was very satisfied with this outcome. Not only had he achieved the original strategic goal, if these trades continued, this match would easily be his.

17 minutes…

Song Xiao looked at the time. This 1v1 had unexpectedly gone on for so long. And at this pace, playing until 20 minutes wouldn’t be a problem. 20 minutes! Song Xiao almost felt that it was inconceivable. Before today, he had never thought it was possible for a 1v1 to last 20 minutes.

For such a long match, no matter if it was an intense match or not, just playing a competitive match for this long must be tiring, no? He was just defending, and he was feeling somewhat tired. And Ye Xiu? How long was he planning on continuing this stalemate? He was probably riding a tiger that he couldn’t get off. He probably didn’t think that he could defend for this long without exposing any openings.

Mr. Clutch. The nickname hadn’t come about for no reason. No matter how important of a responsibility he was given, he never dropped the ball.

It didn’t matter if it became 20 minutes, 25 minutes, or even 30 minutes! As long as Ye Xiu could still play, then Song Xiao could as well!

Song Xiao didn’t relax and focused even harder. But by concentrating, he suddenly realized that he had missed something.

This isn’t right… why would I need to suddenly focus even harder? I’ve always been focused! There’s no reason to step it up a notch. Could it be that just before, he had become lax?

“Hey, how long are you going to keep this up?” At this moment, a message from Ye Xiu suddenly popped up.

“As long as you want!” Song Xiao replied.

“Really? But unfortunately, I can’t accompany you the entire way through,” Ye Xiu said.

What? Song Xiao was startled. Had Ye Xiu given up? Was he going to type GG?

“One last time! I’m coming!”

The moment the message came out, Lord Grim rushed out. Song Xiao reacted fast, and Receding Tides immediately moved to receive him.

Is he planning on putting up one last fight? The likelihood of Ye Xiu directly going GG was small. From Ye Xiu’s actions, it seemed that he had finally realized he couldn’t continue dragging things, so he was planning on ending it as soon as possible?

A pity! You only made this decision now. Even so, I won’t let you have your way so easily!

Song Xiao had a plan in mind long ago. When he had prepared to fight Ye Xiu directly, he had no intentions of ending it quickly. His ultimate reason for standing here in this match was to drag things. Whether it was through hit-and-runs or through direct fights, he would do his best to drag this match. Right now, Ye Xiu wanted to settle it, but Song Xiao wasn’t going to let him end it so easily. He would continue defending tenaciously for as long as he could.

Come!

Song Xiao prepared himself. Suddenly, a light appeared in his sights. Sword light!

This fast?

Song Xiao was startled. He hadn’t been mentally prepared for an attack this fast.

Roll!

Song Xiao instinctively rolled. Receding Tides immediately rolled backwards, but soon afterwards, Receding Tides spun around into the air.

What happened?

Song Xiao was dumbstruck.

The attack had come out faster than he had expected. He had planned on making a counterattack after the roll, but before he could even finish the roll, he was launched into the air.

“Ye Xiu has suddenly launched an all-out offensive! Only two attacks, and he’s broken through Song Xiao’s defenses! What’s going on?” Pan Lin was dumbfounded. He almost couldn’t believe what was happening in front of his eyes.

Eleven minutes. An entire eleven minutes.

During these eleven minutes, Ye Xiu had launched who knew how many of these attacks, but every time he did so, Song Xiao would block them all. Then, Ye Xiu would retreat. The scenario would repeat itself, and it just looked like Ye Xiu was helpless.

But this time… how did he suddenly break through Song Xiao’s defenses?

“Take a look at this,” Li Yibo suddenly said. A smaller screen appeared on the broadcast. This smaller screen didn’t show a replay, but rather a graph. The curve went from high to low and then stayed low for a long time before a sudden spike.

“This was Ye Xiu’s APM during these 11 minutes,” Li Yibo said.

“How low!” Pan Lin noticed the long length of time. It was a valley that lasted seven minutes. And before hitting this valley, there was a gradual downward drop.

40!

An APM of 40 appeared in a pro match. And this APM had lasted for 7 minutes.

No matter how effective each action was, 40 APM was nowhere near enough in a pro match. Someone with such a low hand speed should have been eliminated long ago, yet he had unexpectedly lasted 7 minutes with an APM of 40.

What was his opponent doing in these 7 minutes?

Everyone knew the answer. During these 7 minutes, Song Xiao had been defending earnestly, defending against an opponent with an APM of 40.

“How did it turn out like this?” Despite seeing the data, Pan Lin couldn’t believe it. They had been watching from an omniscient view, how come they hadn’t noticed Ye Xiu sandbagging to such a degree?

“Song Xiao’s been completely tricked,” Li Yibo said.

“In the first four minutes, it could be said that Ye Xiu had injected an anaesthesia into him. Using these four minutes, he had gradually lowered the intensity of his attacks, making small but careful adjustments to his pace such that Song Xiao wouldn’t notice. After these four minutes, Lord Grim’s attacks became much more terse than before. However, Song Xiao had been maintaining his 100% to defend the entire time… He had assumed he had been tiring out Ye Xiu, but he hadn’t noticed that Ye Xiu had actually been sandbagging the entire time. He was the one tiring himself out…” Li Yibo said.

“You can do that?” Even though Li Yibo explained it clearly, Pan Lin felt that it was inconceivable. However, when he thought about it again more closely, Ye Xiu hadn’t tricked just Song Xiao, but the viewers watching as well.

Sandbagging…

To think this phrase could be used to describe a pro match. And in a 1v1 too, a sandbagging that lasted 7 minutes.

Pan Lin didn’t know what to say. He watched as the match proceeded. Lord Grim’s onslaught had sent Receding Tides into a complete mess. When the first attack had struck, Pan Lin had initially thought that Song Xiao had reacted a bit slow and believed it was because Ye Xiu had distracted him with his message. He thought that Song Xiao would quickly recover. But now he knew, the reason Song Xiao had reacted slowly was because Ye Xiu had been conditioning Song Xiao for the past seven minutes. The sudden acceleration was too abrupt for Song Xiao to react in time. Song Xiao hadn’t been sandbagging those eleven minutes. He had been focusing the entire time; he was tired…

“But I don’t think Ye Xiu can win,” Li Yibo suddenly said.

“Why not?”

“His mana. Lord Grim doesn’t have enough mana, “Li Yibo said, “But Ye Xiu’s already done everything he could. He didn’t let Blue Rain’s strategy tire him out and dealt as much damage as he could to Receding Tides. Afterwards, he’ll be leaving an exhausted Song Xiao for his team’s next player… Ye Xiu is truly terrifying.”

Chapter 1439 - Not Easy

The second round of the group arena finally ended. As Li Yibo had predicted, Song Xiao had won.

Ye Xiu had been limited by his mana. After sandbagging for seven minutes, he leaped out and gave Song Xiao’s Receding Tides a fierce beating. He used up all of his mana, though, and lost in the end.

Song Xiao won, but even so, Team Blue Rain’s braindead fans weren’t excited. If this were an individual competition, the outcome would have been worthy of celebration. But this was only a part of the group arena. Ye Xiu had not only defeated Yu Wenzhou, Song Xiao’s Receding Tides only had 28% of his health left. How could they be excited?

When Ye Xiu walked off from the stage, the Blue Rain fans didn’t know what sort of attitude they should display. Applause? Not possible. Boo? They couldn’t do it. The reason the match had turned out this way was because of Blue Rain’s own strategic arrangements. Not only did they fail to accomplish their goals, Ye Xiu had sandbagged and fooled them. If they booed Ye Xiu, Team Blue Rain would be the ones losing face.

“This match went on for 19 minutes and 21 seconds, which is probably a new record for a 1v1 on the competitive stage,” Pan Lin said.

“Probably,” Li Yibo nodded his head.

They just mentioned this record in the passing. They didn’t actually care too much about it because it wasn’t a record worthy of being proud of. In a 1v1, the faster the match ended, the more impressive it was. Only those sorts of records were worthy of being remembered.

“Ye Xiu had the dominant position in the last parts of the match. I feel like if he had conserved his mana a bit better, he might have been able to beat Song Xiao,” Pan Lin said.

“Uh… I think he probably held back intentionally, so he wouldn’t waste too much energy in this match!” Li Yibo said.

“He was that in control?” Pan Lin muttered in disbelief.

“Nice job.” The members of Team Happy got up to welcome back Ye Xiu.

“Sit, sit. That must have been exhausting?” Chen Guo was worried. Blue Rain’s intentions had been obvious. Even though Ye Xiu had been able to relax for 7 minutes, the two 1v1s he played had lasted nearly half an hour. He had played for a long time.

“I’m good,” Ye Xiu smiled.

“No need to be worried. He’s definitely fine,” Wei Chen said.

“How do you know?” Chen Guo said.

“He’d played the online game day and night for a year, yet he was still able to maintain his skill level. How he could he not know how to conserve his energy? To think those youngsters at Blue Rain would actually employ this sort of strategy! They definitely messed up. If they wanted to tire him out, they should be fighting him directly,” Wei Chen said.

“That… seems to make sense!” Chen Guo thought about it for a second. In the regular season, in their second match against Wind Howl, Tang Hao had fought a 1v1 against Ye Xiu in the individual competition. The two sides had fought each other in a direct confrontation. That 1v1 hadn’t lasted long, but Ye Xiu had clearly looked exhausted after winning the match against Tang Hao. Using a direct method was a better way of tiring out Ye Xiu.

“If we knew those guys would make this sort of arrangement, I should have gone up to play too,” Wei Chen joked.

Everyone laughed. After knowing that Ye Xiu wasn’t too tired, everyone felt more relaxed. Happy’s second player was Mo Fan. This map was clearly suitable for him. After seeing this map, everyone already had high hopes for Mo Fan. It was just that no one could see any sort of enthusiasm or excitement from him. Mo Fan mumbled a “mm” and then went up on stage.

When the third round of the group arena began, Pan Lin and Li Yibo could tell that this map was rather suitable for Mo Fan. As expected, Mo Fan didn’t hesitate to take a roundabout route. However, he went along the west path, while Song Xiao’s Receding Tides went along the east path. Thus, the two characters passed by each other. When Song Xiao approached the central path but didn’t see Mo Fan, he said a few words in the chat. Mo Fan did not respond though. When he didn’t see Receding Tides on the west path, he directly cut to the east path.

Song Xiao’s Receding Tides only had 28% of his health left. He didn’t dare be as bold as Mo Fan. Receding Tides went in a circle and cut across the center. When the viewers saw their movements, Song Xiao running around randomly might really end up with him circling behind Mo Fan.

“Ah, this… I’m not sure if I should say that Song Xiao’s luck is rather good, or if Mo Fan is being too careless!” Pan Lin said.

“Careless? If you look closely, Mo Fan is being very careful,” Li Yibo chuckled.

“Oh?” Pan Lin took a closer look after Li Yibo’s reminder and soon noticed the hints. Mo Fan’s Deception wasn’t just rushing forward mindlessly. When he made the horizontal cut across, he borrowed the dense forest as a cover.

“Mo Fan’s this familiar with the map?” Pan Lin was surprised.

“I remember you saying that Ye Xiu had picked up a rock and smashed his own foot with it?” Li Yibo joked, “I think those words are more suitable for Blue Rain!”

“What? Oh…” Pan Lin suddenly remembered, “Blue Rain wanted to tire out Ye Xiu, but after playing for so long, not only did they fail to do so, by dragging on the match, Happy had a lot of time to familiarize themselves with the map through the spectator omniscient view.”

“Correct. Mo Fan is only a first-year rookie. How could he coincidentally be familiar with the map Blue Rain chose? His understanding of the map is because of the nearly thirty minutes of time Blue Rain had gifted him!” Li Yibo said.

“Today, Blue Rain has truly… miscalculated,” Pan Lin sighed.

“It looks like Ye Xiu might have had a method to finish the match quickly, but he intentionally went along with Blue Rain’s pace to give his teammates time to understand the map,” Li Yibo said.

“This… is that true?” Pan Lin was astonished.

“Beating them at their own game, isn’t that his usual style?” Li Yibo said.

“But it didn’t feel that excessive during his time with One Autumn Leaf!” Pan Lin said.

“Probably because he didn’t have as much pressure on him before!” Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin stared blankly and realized that it was true. Ye Xiu wasn’t as young as before to the extent that Blue Rain would intentionally try to exhaust him. The current him probably couldn’t charge forward fearlessly like before. He needed to use his brain more in these matches. In addition, Team Happy was not a powerhouse like Team Excellent Era. Although the sudden appearance of a bunch of Level 80 Silver equipment in the first round had given everyone a fright, after observing them in real combat, the pro teams could see that Happy’s Level 80 Silver equipment seemed rather superficial. The equipment didn’t reach their theoretical might.

They were at best as good as Level 75 equipment.

The R&D departments of the participating playoffs team all had talented people. Before the first round of Happy versus Blue Rain had ended, there were already people who had reached this conclusion.

Happy was trying to catch up to everyone else. The level that their equipment could reach could only approach the level of these powerhouses. Level 80 Silver equipment weren’t miracles. They were tricks. They could only approach but not exceed.

For Happy to reach this stage was already impressive. People were perhaps no longer surprised by Happy’s outstanding performance to the extent that they had forgotten how Happy had achieved such incredible results under such disadvantageous conditions.

And how much effort had Ye Xiu put in during these hardships?

Leading a powerhouse and leading a new team, there was no need to explain which one was more difficult, no?

Leading this new team, Ye Xiu had beaten Team Excellent Era in the Challenger League. He had won 37 1v1s in the regular season. Team Happy finished sixth in the regular season and entered the playoffs and had the lead right now against Team Blue Rain.

Was Ye Xiu truly not as good as he used to be?

None of that could be seen!

The current Ye Xiu might be the best Ye Xiu.

He was able to utilize all of his talents in Glory to lead Team Happy to such heights! Many people should open their eyes and look again more clearly.

Li Yibo’s nonchalant remark made Pan Lin suddenly feel emotional. Ye Xiu had built Happy up from nothing, starting from that Internet cafe all the way to the playoffs stage, step by step, difficult yet brilliant.

“He really has gotten behind him!” At this moment, Li Yibo shouted, bringing Pan Lin back to the match. Pan Lin saw that Song Xiao’s Receding Tides had taken a roundabout path, making an arc behind Deception’s horizontal cut across. But…

“He doesn’t know!”

Song Xiao repeatedly looked in all directions, but he didn’t seem to notice Deception.

“How unfortunate,” Pan Lin said. His heart had swayed towards Happy, but he had to maintain a professional attitude.

At this moment, Mo Fan’s Deception suddenly stopped.

“Has Mo Fan sensed something? What keen intuition!” Pan Lin shouted.

“It’s probably because while he cut across, he had traversed quite a bit of distance yet still didn’t meet his opponent. From this, he was able to deduce that his opponent had chosen a different route. What do you think he deduced from that?” Li Yibo said.

“Turn around and retrace his steps!” Pan Lin said excitedly.

“If Song Xiao doesn’t make any large adjustments, they’ll soon run into each other,” Li Yibo said.

“But Song Xiao needs to pay attention to where he looks! If he doesn’t focus and misses it, he’ll be on the defensive,” Pan Lin said.

“That will depend on what he thinks Mo Fan is doing,” Li Yibo said.

The two had started talking faster, matching the increasing tension in this life and death match.

“They’re getting closer, closer, closer!” Pan Lin shouted non-stop.

“Song Xiao… ah!” Li Yibo sighed. Because Song Xiao wasn’t looking at where Deception was coming from. And after Mo Fan discovered Receding Tides, he had Deception hide behind a tree. By the time Song Xiao turned towards his location, all Song Xiao could see was dense fog.

Chapter 1440 - Sixteen Leaves

Where had Deception gone?

Of course, with their omniscient view, the audience couldn’t be clearer about this. The Blue Rain fans present were more concerned about whether or not Song Xiao knew the answer to this question.

But it seemed that… he didn’t. Song Xiao’s pace didn’t change in the slightest, Receding Tides still cautiously walked along the thicket, while continually adjusting his field of vision. The moment that Deception’s silhouette had appeared happened to be when he was looking away, a stroke of bad luck for him.

Nonetheless, by continually adjusting his field of vision, it meant that Mo Fan couldn’t easily find a position from which he could mount a sneak attack. After Deception had concealed himself, he very carefully and very patiently followed Receding Tides, gradually closing the distance between the two. With the environment of Misty Thicket, being able to see the opponent meant that the two players were in fact already very close to each other. Even so, this was still a very long process. Sometimes, because he wasn’t able to find a suitable route to approach, the distance between Deception and Receding Tides even increased.

But no matter what, Deception still hid behind Receding Tides, not being discovered from start to finish.

One minute, two minutes……

Normally, this was a distance that could be crossed in an instant, but Mo Fan had unexpectedly used more than two minutes to close the distance. The extreme caution that he showed was purely to avoid Song Xiao discovering him.

With one player at full health, while the other only at 28%, to most people, the opportunity earlier when he had first encountered Song Xiao was already more than enough. If he had just charged up and forcefully fought him head-on, he could perhaps have already concluded the battle, but unexpectedly, Mo Fan still cautiously prepared a sneak attack.

The broadcasting department was practically crying already. If this went on, would today’s group arena be fought for two hours? Unexpectedly, the rounds were actually being played in such a dragged-out manner.

After using two minutes and forty-one seconds, Mo Fan seemed to have finally reached a distance that he was satisfied with. When Song Xiao turned around again to look in another direction, Deception put the Ninjutsu · Disappearing Body Technique to full use, forming seals with both hands at a rapid pace.

Ninjutsu · Shadow Dance.

More than ten Shadow Clones of Deception had already surrounded Receding Tides in the blink of an eye, raising their Ninjatos, which gently fell towards Receding Tides like leaves.

Ninjato, Silver Weapon: Sixteen Leaves (十六叶 shí liù yè).

The moment that this Silver weapon was revealed to the world, everyone was startled. The Silver Weapon of the number one Ninja in the professional circle, Team Misty Rain’s Dark Forest, was called Sixteen Nights (十六夜 shí liù yè), only differing by one word from Deception’s weapon, but overall, it sounded the same.

The names for all Silver equipment was system-generated, but as a way of generating publicity, clubs would often ascribe their own meaning to the name of a piece of Silver equipment. For instance, Dark Forest’s Ninjato, Sixteen Nights, had a chance of inflicting Blind as an additional effect, so this could be the origin of the word “Night” in the equipment’s name. But then, what about Sixteen Leaves?

Unlike the bigger clubs, Happy didn’t have established systems in place. As a result, since they focused purely on training well, playing well, and achieving good results, other aspects such as publicity weren’t particularly well-honed. Even if they had some sponsors to help with publicity, they wouldn’t sponsor the likes of Deception, a character who hadn’t appeared many times in Happy’s games.

Since Mo Fan hadn’t appeared very much, the various teams didn’t have a clear idea of what properties Sixteen Leaves possessed.

At this moment, after Ninjutsu · Disappearing Body Technique was quietly used, Shadow Dance immediately surrounded and attacked Receding Tides. As they attacked, more than ten Ninjatos gently floated down, fluttering like long leaves that had been curled up by the wind.

Sixteen Leaves? Was this what it was named after?

The audience may not have thought of so much in an instant, but the broadcast’s explanation had to be more acute. In that instant, they had immediately been given a speaking point for Happy’s Deception.

“Sixteen Leaves!” Pan Lin shouted loudly. As he shouted, he saw Deception’s Ninjato floating like leaves, and then he saw the fresh, red blood that had instantly filled everyone’s field of view……

“Everything hit!” Pan Lin shouted again.

Truth be told, whether or not everything connected was impossible for anyone to determine in that instant, but it was just that the blade’s edge spraying fresh flowers of blood in that instant was far too dazzling a sight. Even in the online circle, there might not be many Shadow Dances in which every single Shadow Clone managed to hit their mark at the same time. This wasn’t something that could be achieved by the opponent simply being unable to guard against it. Even using a wooden dummy, having a player control that many Shadow Clones to find the appropriate angles to attack at the same time was a difficult feat. In Glory, it wasn’t possible for characters to physically overlap with one another. Even though teammates couldn’t damage each other, they would definitely still block each other’s paths. Of course, the Shadow Clones from Shadow Dance were no different. In this instant, for Shadow Dance to completely connect in such a spectacular fashion, it wasn’t just because Song Xiao couldn’t defend well enough. It was also a matter of Mo Fan’s skillful character control.

“Beautiful!” Li Yibo matched Pan Lin praise and shouted. However, in this moment, the television broadcasters were actually somewhat conflicted. It was indeed an exhilarating moment, but when directly observed, it was a little bit too bloody.

But that bloody moment passed by in an instant. Just as the television directors were distractedly considering whether or not to quickly cut out that scene, the bloody moment had already passed. Those eye-catching flowers of blood fluttered and scattered on the ground, like the shedding of dead leaves, creating a poignant scene.

In the end, just as everyone was shouting and praising Mo Fan’s brilliant ambush, Receding Tides, with countless blades in his body, suddenly raised both his arms and started to spin. A skill that shouldn’t have even appeared in a Qi Master’s arsenal was used, and as both his arms rotated, the surrounding trees and leaves had already started to spin in the air from the centrifugal force. The Deceptions that had closely surrounded Receding Tides also started to sway.

Spinning Cyclone Kill!

Some people immediately recognized the skill. This wasn’t a Qi Master’s ability, instead, it was from another Fighter subclass. It was a Grappler skill! Using centrifugal force, the Grappler would attract and then crush everything in his surroundings using his two hands, a powerful Level 70 skill!

Of the ten Shadow Clones of Deception, no matter which one was the heart, none of them were able to escape from Receding Tide’s control. The priority of grab skills had always been the highest in all of Glory.

In the whirlwind, Receding Tides quickly rose up, and his arms continued to spin wildly in the air. As a result, the qi from the attack also gradually brought those ten immobile Deceptions away from the ground……

Boom……

A deep explosion rang out from within the thicket. Spinning Cyclone Kill didn’t originally have this sort of audio effect, but at this moment, the effect of the Spinning Cyclone Kill that had been added onto Receding Tide’s weapon was really too shocking. He had managed to completely grab all ten characters at once……

If there was only one target, the Grappler would entangle the target, jump up, flip, and fall, creating huge amounts of damage. But at this moment, there were simply too many targets, so this one Spinning Cyclone Kill seemed to falter. As he jumped, he was already teetering on the verge of collapse, and the targets weren’t entangled within his hands, instead, he was using qi to gather his targets. Of course, when he flipped over, there was no flip, and when Receding Tides had barely jumped up, he had already started to fall, and those Deceptions that had been forcefully gathered by his ability also immediately started to fall.

Nonetheless, this one move had the priority of a grab skill. The Deceptions hadn’t been launched high, and they hadn’t been been flipped, meaning that the damage output from the skill would be somewhat lower, but even so, a hit was a hit.

Boom boom boom… boom!

The ten Deceptions fell to the ground first. Receding Tides brought the qi from Spinning Cyclone Kill to the ground last, sending out a final heavy sound. The resulting shockwaves spread out and immediately collided against the pile of Deceptions on the floor from all directions.

The whole stadium had been silent for a long time, and in that moment, it finally exploded in enthusiastic cheering and applause.

“Song Xiao wasn’t completely defenceless!” Li Yibo sighed, deeply moved.

“Song Xiao really focused his attention. Even though Mo Fan’s ambush succeeded initially, it was quickly defused by him,” Pan Lin said.

“Exactly!” Li Yibo immediately added, “Spinning Cyclone Kill’s startup isn’t fast, but Receding Tides still managed to use it in that instant, meaning that he must have made that decision ahead of time. In the first instant that Shadow Dance was used, Song Xiao immediately made a precise judgement and controlled his character accurately. But under the suppression of Shadow Dance, he had no way of escaping, so he straightforwardly took the attack, but quickly responded with a Spinning Cyclone Kill!”

“And even though Spinning Cyclone Kill is slow, it has high priority. Even though so many Shadow Clones of Deception were attacking Receding Tides, it still didn’t manage to interrupt the usage of this skill!” Pan Lin added.

“Exactly, so after forcefully taking this blow, the offensive that Mo Fan launched was broken by Song Xiao,” Li Yibo said.

“The defensive capabilities of Team Blue Rain’s players are indeed impressive…” Pan Lin said.

The two of them went back-and-forth, clearly analyzing the present situation, but this wasn’t because the two players had reacted slowly afterwards. On the contrary, Mo Fan’s next reactions were extremely fast. The moment Spinning Cyclone Kill hit the ground, a pile of Deceptions staggered unsteadily, but amongst them, several took advantage of the opportunity, got up, and scattered in all directions.

Song Xiao had no way of figuring out which of those fleeing Deceptions was the heart of the Shadow Dance, and even if he knew, there was no use. The heart of the Shadow Dance could be transferred.

At the end of the day, it was because his Spinning Cyclone Kill was only level one, so the strength of the centrifugal force was insufficient. There was no way it could fully control that many characters, and in the last instants of the skills, there were still some gaps left.

Mo Fan was extremely agile, and using these small gaps, he immediately controlled Deception to dodge the attack.

Poof poof poof poof……

As the Deception with the heart of the Shadow Dance escaped, the Shadow Clones immediately turned into a cloud of smoke.

Mo Fan’s Deception escaped, immediately escaping into the dense thicket. With that many escaping figures, Song Xiao had no way of knowing which was real.

Deception had escaped, but he was still behind Receding Tides, and he immediately charged out once more!

Chapter 1441 - Fireworks Style

Mo Fan had previously been playing extremely slow, taking nearly three minutes to close the distance. But suddenly, he sped up. Step back and turn around in one fluid motion. A new offense had begun practically the instant the several shadow clones disappeared.

As for Song Xiao?

Song Xiao was still whirling around looking for traces of Deception. By the time he turned backwards, Deception had reached him.

Flame Slash!

The dense fog seemed to boil as flames leapt into the air. The fiery attack was incomparably fast, slashing Receding Tides directly in the face.

Boom!

The flames clung onto Receding Tides and burned him.

One, two, three, four, five…

Five consecutive hits and then Deception vanished into the fog.

The excitement had just reached a peak, but all of it just collapsed in an instant…

This again! Those familiar with Mo Fan’s style collectively gave out a sigh. The fast-paced burst had revealed his skillfulness, but the display always went away immediately afterwards. Beautiful but brief like fireworks.

“Fireworks Style,” Pan Lin said. He wasn’t the one who came up with this name, but rather a nickname people in the forums had given Mo Fan’s weird playstyle. When Pan Lin found it, he felt that it was a very suitable name, and so when Mo Fan showed it off, he called it out.

“Oh, I’ve heard of this name before, too. It paints a pretty picture,” Li Yibo chuckled.

Two consecutive offensives. The first Shadow Dance had been beautiful, but Song Xiao’s timely response to deal with it had been outstanding as well. But Mo Fan’s sudden change in pace had caught Song Xiao off guard. The five-hit combo performed from five skills had been perfect. By the time Song Xiao readjusted himself, Mo Fan’s Deception went into hiding.

Song Xiao wasn’t going to sit and wait for his death to come. He had Receding Tides chase in the direction that Deception had disappeared into.

Mo Fan simply hid behind a tree and went in a circle around Song Xiao. Deception was behind Receding Tides again. This time, Mo Fan didn’t wait too long before launching his next wave of attacks. The sudden sneak attack from behind had caught Song Xiao in a fluster. But this time, Mo Fan’s combo had been stopped. Receding Tides was able to escape the third wave of attacks from Mo Fan.

Not waiting for the counterattack, Mo Fan had Deception immediately retreat after seeing the attack miss.

“Speaking of which, Mo Fan is much more familiar with this playstyle than Song Xiao is…” Pan Lin said.

“I think it’s quite clear who’s going to win this round. I’m a bit worried for Song Xiao though. He had fought against Ye Xiu for a long time, and he must be quite tired. Now, he’s against Mo Fan, who’s playing this sort of grind game that won’t let him ease up. Song Xiao… will he have spent too much energy in today’s group arena?” Li Yibo said.

“Ah… this is truly…” Pan Lin wasn’t able to find the right words. Blue Rain had tried to tire out Happy’s Ye Xiu. Not only did they fail, Song Xiao had a rough time while trying to exhaust Ye Xiu. And now, he was up against another tiresome opponent, Mo Fan. Not only did it look like he was going to lose, he would most likely be affected in the following team competition by the fatigue from his group arena matches.

“Perhaps Song Xiao should give up,” Pan Lin said.

“But do you think he will, with his personality?” Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin fell silent.

Although Song Xiao wasn’t a God, with the nickname Mr. Clutch, he would often shine in important matches. As such, Song Xiao’s pride was no lesser than that of a God’s.

Facing against a rookie, Mo Fan, and against a grind strategy that Happy was using against them, Song Xiao shrinking back would be admitting that Blue Rain’s strategy today was an utter failure. It would mean that he had given up to a certain extent.

Song Xiao would not give up. It was because he never gave up that he made plays at critical moments and became known as Mr. Clutch.

Shrink back, give up? Never!

Receding Tides traversed through the thicket. After experiencing such a long battle, Song Xiao could still muster up another burst of energy. Receding Tides looked to be even nimbler than before.

Poof! Bang!

Deception launched another sneak attack, which brought upon a powerful counter from Song Xiao. On this fourth wave of attacks from Mo Fan, Receding Tides surged with qi. With a Flash Burst, he completely toppled Mo Fan’s wave of attacks.

“Where are you running!”

Song Xiao would not let this opportunity go and had Receding Tides chase after him. As long as he could stick close to him, he would have the chance to stop Mo Fan from disappearing and attempting another sneak attack.

Despite only having 3% health, he wouldn’t cower. He would continue forward!

This Mo Fan player didn’t seem to like trades. With only 3% health left, Song Xiao felt like he could take advantage of this habit. He couldn’t miss this final opportunity. He had to stick close!

Spiral Qi Kill!

Receding Tides whirled his arms, spinning qi in the air. Because of this map’s dense fog, the traces left behind from this skill was very clear. A spiralling white dragon flew forward.

Boom!

The qi exploded, but it was just a straw dummy that was torn to pieces.

Substitution Technique!

Song Xiao immediately looked around, trying to find Deception. But he didn’t think that it would come from below…

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Deception tunneled out of the ground. The ninjato in his hands, Sixteen Leaves, looked like tree leaves again. But this time, the leaves weren’t floating down. Rather, they seemed to dance with the wind, sending a ribbon of blood into the dense fog.

Dead!

Receding Tide’s health finally hit zero. Song Xiao hadn’t been able to bite at Mo Fan one last time.

Scrap picker…

Song Xiao thought of Mo Fan’s background. In terms of running for his life, Mo Fan was a master. Song Xiao couldn’t help but think of their match against Happy during the regular season. Team Happy’s defeat had been certain, yet Ye Xiu and Mo Fan had frantically played hide-and-seek with them**.

What a troublesome kid!

Song Xiao shook his head. He stood up and then left the player booth.

Right now, only the Happy fans on the west platform were cheering excitedly. The rest of the stadium filled with Blue Rain fans had worry and gloominess written all over their faces.

The home team had the advantage of picking the map and should be trying to take the initiative. But this match? Blue Rain’s plans for this map completely failed. Instead, Happy’s Mo Fan was like a fish in the water as he handled Song Xiao like a worm.

84%.

Deception still had this much health left. Would Blue Rain’s next player be able to deal with him?

It was just a rookie, bur Team Blue Rain’s fans were worried for their team. Mo Fan’s skill was unquestionable, perhaps even feared.

“Who is Blue Rain sending up next?” Pan Lin said.

Song Xiao went back to Blue Rain’s player bench with his head down. Mr. Clutch wasn’t able to clutch it out today.

“You did well. Take a rest!” Yu Wenzhou did not scold him. Instead, he took the initiative to console him.

The Blue Rain fans watching with an omniscient view could grasp the true situation faster than the players playing on the stage.

Song Xiao had fallen for Ye Xiu’s trap. While Ye Xiu was sandbagging, he had been completely focused on defending and tiring out Ye Xiu. During that time, he was no longer tiring out Ye Xiu, but rather, it was Ye Xiu tiring out him.

Afterwards, he was stuck in Mo Fan’s slow and dragged out pace. Song Xiao was truly exhausted. But he could not relax. The more crucial team competition still needed him. He could only follow his captain’s words. He hurried to the sidelines to rest as much as possible before the team competition began.

“Go!” At this moment, Yu Wenzhou called out to Blue Rain’s third player.

Li Yuan, Summoner Eight Notes.

Last round, he had encountered Mo Fan in the group arena, but had lost miserably. He met him again in their game. Li Yuan was pleased. He needed to take revenge for last time.

“Good luck, Li Yuan!” The entire stadium stood up and cheered for him. Their opening wasn’t good, making everyone nervous and worried.

“Watch me,” Li Yuan waved his hands to his teammates and to the crowd as he walked onto the stage.

The match soon began.

Li Yuan finally switched up Blue Rain’s initial strategy and went along the central path.

Mo Fan still took the roundabout route, but he took a rather strange path. He first had Deception move west. Once he moved far enough, he took a path north and slightly to the east.

“What is Mo Fan thinking?” Pan Lin wondered.

“This… it looks like he’s planning on cutting off Li Yuan after calculating his movement speed,” Li Yibo said.

“Cut off?”

“The choices at the start of the match are the central path, the path slightly to the west, and the path slightly to the east. Because of the dense fog, you can’t deviate too far east or west from the central path, otherwise it’s pointless. That’s why Mo Fan is having his character move tangentially. If the opponent takes the central path, the opponent will be moving towards the southern end. If the opponent takes the west or east path, the opponent will move slower south than if the opponent took the central path. If Mo Fan continues along his current route, he’ll come across two intersections on either the central or eastern path. Three possibilities. He’s covering three possibilities before he tries anything else,” Li Yibo said.

“In that case, he’s already succeeded! Will they meet on the central path?” Pan Lin looked at their movements.

“That’ll depend on what Li Yuan does,” Li Yibo said.

Li Yuan’s Eight Notes quickly reached the center of the map. He had Eight Notes stop and look at his surroundings.

“If Eight Notes doesn’t move, Deception might not run into him,” Pan Lin said.

“He’ll probably move!” Li Yibo said.

“Not only does he need to move, he needs to move forward,” Pan Lin said.

Just as he said this, Li Yuan’s Eight Notes continued forward towards the south. In Pan Lin’s eyes, Eight Notes was already doomed.

Chapter 1442 - Summoner Formation

Would Deception be able to cut off Eight Notes?

After listening to Pan Lin’s and Li Yibo’s analysis, the viewers began to ponder over this question. Through their observations, they calculated their speed and pathing to deduce whether the two would meet.

However, Li Yuan didn’t push forward mindlessly like Pan Lin and Li Yibo said he was. As Eight Notes moved, he would summon creatures from time to time, preparing for a fight preemptively.

“Li Yuan has started summoning… but in this map, if Mo Fan plays slow, it’ll be unfavorable for Li Yuan! All of us know that Summoners are very mana-hungry, and summons only stay on the field for a limited duration. Li Yuan is putting out summons, but if he doesn’t encounter his opponent within their summon duration, wouldn’t that mean he’s just wasting his mana?” Pan Lin said.

“But what can he do… it’s far too easy to get ambushed in this map. If Li Yuan doesn’t summon creatures in advance, would he have the time to summon them when the fight begins?” Li Yibo added.

“In that case, Happy’s side can just not do anything and run around in circles. If Li Yuan has no choice but to keep a few summons around, then in theory, couldn’t MO Fan just wait for him to run out of mana?” Pan Lin said.

“Haha, Li Yuan will summon, but he certainly won’t summon a lot of them!” Li Yibo laughed.

Eight Notes was a Spirit Summoner. If he mobilized his entire army, the scale would be massive. Sure enough, Li Yuan only had Eight Notes summon two Little Spirits. The two Little Spirits didn’t stick close to him. Insteady, they spread out to Eight Note’s left and right side.

“Hm? The positioning of these spirits!” Pan Lin suddenly called out when he saw this scene.

“It’s very similar to what Ye Xiu had done with his Goblins!” Li Yibo laughed.

“Yes!” Pan Lin nodded his head.

Li Yuan had the two Little Spirits on his left and right side move around freely, extending the range of his vision to the sides. Although he wouldn’t be able to directly see what the spirits saw, Li Yuan’s effective vision had increased considerably.

“In this case, wouldn’t this…” Pan Lin was just about to criticize Li Yuan, when Eight Notes drew another two summoning circles and called out two more Little Spirits. One of these two spirits moved to the front, while the other moved behind him. Li Yuan had now expanded his effective vision in every direction.

“Beautiful! I don’t know if Li Yuan thought of it himself, or if got inspiration from Ye Xiu,” Pan Lin praised. He saw that the four Little Spirits were positioned neatly to the front, back, left, and right of Eight Notes. All of them were moving at the same speed too.

“However, this method has dead angles. Li Yuan’s vision is in fact in a cross shape. His vision at the corners is a bit lacking. But if he wants to make up for those corners, he’d have to summon four more Little Spirits, which would be too wasteful. He could have his spirits rotate in a clockwise or counterclockwise direction, but it would slow him down and would also place an extra burden on his mana,” Li Yibo said.

“Li Yuan should be aware of this weakness!” Pan Lin said.

“Of course he knows. Take a look at his line of sight. He’s focused on those four corners,” Li Yibo said.

“In that case, even if Deception comes in from one of those four corners, he’ll still be discovered,” Pan Lin said.

“Not just that… if he comes in from one of the four corners, he won’t be seen by the Little Spirits. That also means that Mo Fan won’t know about the existence of the Little Spirits. If that moment comes, the two Spirits on that side can circle around and ambush him from behind,” Li Yibo said.

“Oh! If you say it like that…”

“This is an interesting and well-thought-out formation. We originally thought that this map was rather disadvantageous for Summoners, but Li Yuan unexpectedly answered back with this brilliant formation,” Li Yibo said.

“Ha, if the map really was disadvantageous for Summoners, I doubt Blue Rain would have sent Li Yuan up for the group arena!” Pan Lin said.

“True. The two players are approaching,” Li Yibo said.

“Yes! Mo Fan’s Deception is cutting in diagonally. At this speed, Deception will come in from the southwest corner of Eight Note’s summon formation!” Pan Lin began speaking louder. He hadn’t expected this match’s high point to come so quickly. They had seen through Li Yuan’s formation in theory, but how would it work in practice?

The camera shifted to Mo Fan’s point of view. Would he notice the two Little Spirits?

Step by step, he approached.

The two moved quite fast, especially Mo Fan’s Deception. As he moved, he would borrow his surroundings as cover from time to time. This map clearly hadn’t been chosen by Happy, but he seemed to know this map inside and out. You could reach a certain level of understanding from looking at the map through an omniscient view, but to adeptly utilize the map required real practice. Mo Fan was able to quickly maneuver through the map stealthily as soon as he loaded into the map. It had to be said that he had quite the talent in this area.

Deception’s footsteps gradually slowed down and became more and more careful.

Almost there…

Mo Fan had been calculating. If Eight Notes had taken the central path, it should be about time for the two to come across each other. As a result, when it was about time for them to meet, Mo Fan had Deception slow down.

Hm? What’s that over there!

At this moment, a glimmer of light suddenly appeared in his view. Mo Fan turned to take a closer look and saw an Water Spirit charging towards him.

“They’ve found each other! But…” Pan Lin shouted. Everyone knew what he meant by ‘but’: Mo Fan had noticed the Little Spirits.

Li Yuan’s cross-shaped formation had been very balanced. If one wanted to pass through the formation diagonally without being noticed by Spirits, one would have to take an extremely precise route. Mo Fan’s path clearly wasn’t precise enough. He came in from angle just slightly off from the center, resulting in him being discovered by the Little Spirits at the front.

Mo Fan was quite calm. He didn’t hurry to attack and instead tried escaping from this Little Spirit.

After watching Ye Xiu’s and Yu Wenzhou’s match, Mo Fan knew what these summons could do. The summon’s movements could warn the owner of his position, but at the same time, he could use them bait the opponent to a position which he could ambush from.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Deception immediately formed a hand seal. His shadow clone remained there and continued to run forward as the Water Spirit chased after it. As for his real body, he moved to the side and ran forward along with the shadow clone.

“This…” Pan Lin was stunned.

Wasn’t this a replay of the Yu Wenzhou versus Ye Xiu match?

At that time, Yu Wenzhou had used Shadow Clone Technique to trick Lord Grim’s Goblin. Right now, Mo Fan was using Shadow Clone Technique to trick Eight Note’s Little Spirit.

“This… both sides are doing what their opponents did in the first round of the group arena…” Pan Lin remarked. But just when he finished saying these words, he realized his mistake.

Mo Fan was doing the exact same as Yu Wenzhou, but Li Yuan? Li Yuan wasn’t Ye Xiu. Eight Notes wasn’t an unspecialized, so his following reaction would be very different from Ye Xiu’s.

After noticing the abnormal movements of his LIttle Water Spirit, Li Yuan knew Deception’s general location despite not being able to see Deception, so he had the other LittleWater Spirit on Eight Note’s left to draw closer. The movements of the two Little Dark Spirits on his right and back were also adjusted.

Why did he choose to group the same-element Spirits together? There was naturally a reason behind it. Because Big Spirits required two Little Spirits to fuse together. Li Yuan had arranged it in preparation to create a higher-staged Big Spirit.

The other difference with Ye Xiu… When Ye Xiu found Swoksaar, Lord Grim chased after him relentlessly. But when Li Yuan ascertained Deception’s position, Eight Notes slowed down, only making sure his summons were within his line of sight. Afterwards, he summoned more Little Spirits. They didn’t all move in the same direction. Rather, the Little Spirits spread out like chess pieces. The viewers had an omniscient view, and from the bird’s eye view from the broadcast, they could clearly see Li Yuan’s current formation.

As for Deception, his real body and his clone were trapped inside the net. The ambush Mo Fan had been waiting for never came because Li Yuan didn’t seem to have any plans of getting near him. Eight Notes stayed outside of his vision.

The situation seemed poor for Mo Fan, but many people were feeling doubtful.

Because in the last confrontation between Li Yuan and Mo Fan, Mo Fan had displayed masterful skill at escaping. Last time, despite being searched for by an army of summons, Deception hadn’t been caught and was actually able to slowly approach Eight Notes.

“What will happen this time?” Pan Lin spoke out everyone’s thoughts.

“I’m afraid, it’s unlikely…” Li Yibo replied.

“Oh? What are your thoughts, Coach Li?”

“This time… Mo Fan doesn’t even know where Eight Notes is!” Li Yibo said.

“Indeed!” Pan Lin suddenly realized the issue.

“But if it’s just escaping, I’m quite confident he can do it,” Li Yibo followed up.

“If it’s just escaping?” Pan Lin looked at the match, “He’s already escaped, no?”

Deception’s Shadow Clone had dissipated, while the real Deception was carefully hidden. After the Little Spirits lost their target, they didn’t know what to do and immediately stopped moving. But the viewers soon discovered that apart from the Little Spirits that had lost their target, the rest were following Li Yuan’s orders and heading towards a predetermined location.

Chapter 1443 - Patience

Deception was hiding inside a bush. Let alone with this fog, even without the fog, he was completely hidden. The camera zoomed in on Deception’s hiding spot, but it still took a lot of effort for the viewers to find him inside the bush.

This type of hiding spot was somewhat deceiving. If you didn’t look carefully at that exact spot, it would be easy to miss it. However, the system summons could not be deceived in this way. If even a single strand of Deception’s clothing stuck out from the bush, the summons would find him.

Last time, Mo Fan was able to escape from a map-wide search by an army of summons. He clearly understood that the system AI was far better than real players in this aspect. He had intended to sneak attack Eight Notes by hiding in this bush, but seeing that Eight Notes still wasn’t here yet, he knew that for the summons, his current hiding spot was the same as no hiding spot. As a result, he immediately came out from the bush.

To avoid summons, he needed to be 100% outside of their vision. Escaping the notice of summoned spirits was more troublesome than escaping the notice of summoned beasts. The Big and Little Spirits were balls of elemental energy, thus the structure of their bodies were uniform on all sides. In comparison, summoned beasts had eyes and noses, so their line of vision was much easier to figure out. When running from other players, you could run, while peeking your head out from a corner once in a while. A player in pursuit might not notice such a small detail like half a head sticking out, but summons definitely would not. It could still be done with summoned beasts, if you knew that their back was to you. But it was best not to try it against summoned spirits because it was hard to tell where the spirits were facing. If you snuck a glance at them, it likely that the spirits would notice.

Shaking off the pursuit of summoned spirits required fast and decisive movements. Hiding one’s movements as best as possible was far better than trying to observe their movements and then coming up with a plan.

After Deception came out from the bush, his movements weren’t fast, but they were well hidden. He spent 80% of his time either crouching or lying flat on the ground while moving.

“I should really record this part. It’s a master class on how to move around covertly!” Li Yibo was full of praise after seeing Deception’s movements.

As for Li Yuan?

Li Yuan was in no hurry.

After Deception’s Shadow Clone Technique ended, he had lost his target. However, his summons had reached their designated positions, so he didn’t make any more unnecessary commands. Eight Notes seemed to just be heading carefreely towards a direction.

The spirits quickly stopped moving. The elemental light emitted from the spirits pulsed amidst the dense fog. They no longer seemed to be chasing after a target. Instead, they were more like landmines or traps patiently waiting for their prey to run into them.

“Smart!” Li Yibo suddenly yelled out.

“Ah?”

“Li Yuan’s current plan is much more effective than an automatic search. In a hard-to-see map like this one, a player’s eyes can’t compare to the system AI of summoned spirits. The immobilized spirits can react faster than Mo Fan. Mo Fan’s method of dodging the spirits greatly reduces his vision,” Li Yibo explained.

“He’s been found!” At this moment, Pan Lin discovered a change in the battle.

When Deception passed between two trees, a Little Light Spirit hiding in the fog suddenly started moving extremely accurately towards Deception.

“Mo Fan’s been found, but he hasn’t seemed to notice it yet!” Pan Lin yelled.

Deception continued to move stealthily, but he seemed to be unaware of the Little Spirit chasing behind him.

“But the Little Spirit is slower than him. If Li Yuan doesn’t do anything, he’ll probably lose sight of Deception again,” Li Yibo said.

Would Li Yuan not do anything?

Of course not!

The spirits that he had positioned were under his control. As soon as a sudden movement came about, he immediately knew that he had found a target. And in this map, there were no other targets besides Deception.

And from his Little Light Spirit’s movements, Li Yuan was able to deduce Deception’s pathing and immediately gave all of his spirits new commands.

These commands weren’t just to charge over. Depending on their current positions, each spirit received a different coordinate to move to. As for the spirits far away, Li Yuan gave up on them. Eight Notes summoned new spirits to replace the ones far away and then commanded those spirits to rush over.

The Light Little Spirit that had first found Deception really had been shaken off by Deception, but two new Little Spirits had taken its place.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo believed that Mo Fan had become aware of that Light Little Spirit chasing him, which was why he had suddenly sped up to escape from its pursuit.

He had escaped from it, but two new Little Spirits were biting at his heels now.

“What great patience**!” Li Yibo had a high evaluation of this match.

Li Yuan had been quite patient. Eight Notes had mobilized quite a few spirits. He had the max limit of eight Little Spirits, as well as an Ice and Fire Big Spirit, scattered around the map.

Had he taken inspiration from how Ye Xiu dealt with Yu Wenzhou in the first round?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo took back their words.

This was Blue Rain’s home game, and Li Yuan deserved to be part of Blue Rain’s main roster. This map seemed to be unfavorable for Summoners, but he was able to fully utilize it. The spirits scattered around became traps. Did it matter if Mo Fan was an expert at escaping? The spirits weren’t chasing after him. All of them stood at their designated positions and then waited for Mo Fan’s Deception to run into them.

If this were a normal map, after encountering a spirit, Mo Fan would have plenty of room to run. But the visibility in this map was low. By the time he noticed a spirit, the distance between them would be close, making it much more difficult to escape.

Li Yuan fully utilized this point. Blue Rain’s reason for choosing this map in the group arena was becoming more clear.

Yu Wenzhou and Song Xiao had tried to tire out Ye Xiu. Blue Rain failed to achieve this goal, but that wasn’t their only strategy in mind. They had no plans of banking all of their hopes on crushing the team competition.

Li Yuan’ performance on this map illustrated this point. After Yu Wenzhou and Song Xiao, Blue Rain planned on winning as many points in the group arena. From the way Li Yuan was playing in this dense fog, Eight Notes appeared extremely powerful. Mo Fan didn’t even know where Li Yuan was, yet he was already running for his life.

After escaping one spirit, two more came. Before he could shrug off these two spirits, a third and a fourth one came…

Li Yuan had not ordered any of these spirits to give chase. He just had them stay at a certain position. But because of the terrain in this map, Mo Fan’s Deception kept running into more and more of them, and now, he could no longer move about freely.

Substitution Technique, Shadow Clone Technique…

Smoke Bomb, Caltrops…

All sorts of escape skills were used, but he just wasn’t able to cleanly escape from all of them.

Eight Notes seemed to have an endless number of spirits. As soon as Mo Fan shook off one spirit, another would take its place.

Compared to Mo Fan’s frantic actions, Li Yuan’s actions were methodical. Whether it was summoning replacement spirits or moving them around, he appeared calm and collected. He didn’t waste the spirits he would replace either. Four Big Spirits were in position now. The spirit army that Mo Fan would face was becoming increasingly large.

“If this continues, it won’t be good for Mo Fan!” Li Yibo expressed his opinion.

“Yes, if this continues, he’ll be harassed to death…” Pan Lin said. Deception had taken quite a bit of damage while trying to escape. There were moments when the spirits caught up to him. What’s more, the Big Ice Spirit and Big Light Spirits had long-ranged attacks.

Suddenly, Deception stopped moving.

Shuriken!

Deception attacked, throwing a shuriken towards the Big Light Spirit. Then, he charged forward, not in the direction he had been running in, but backwards.

Empty Cicada Double Kill!

With his ninja blade in one hand and the sheath in the other, Deception let out two attacks simultaneously.

Zi zi…

The two attacks hit two Little Spirits, letting out a sound like lightning. Spirits consisted of elemental energy, not flesh and blood. After being hit by attacks, they would make strange noises.

Empty Cicada Double Kill was a powerful attack, and Little Spirits were extremely frail. Although it was just a single attack, their health bars dropped to nearly zero.

Flame Slash!

The Dark Little Spirit didn’t have a high fire resistance like Fire Spirits. The Little Ice Spirit had a negative resistance against fire.

Boom!

Without fire resistance, neither of them could withstand the blow. A wave of fire descended, damaging the two Little Spirits’ elemental energy. The fire burned for a few moments before the two spirits dissipated.

“Mo Fan isn’t running away anymore. He’s started fighting the two Spirits directly,” Pan Lin said.

“He’s trying to force Eight Notes to come out! The spirits alone aren’t enough to contest against a pro player. Eight Notes will need to personally come out and take command, which would mean Deception will be able to see him…” Li Yibo said.

“So it’s like that… Sure enough, Li Yuan’s Eight Notes is heading over,” Pan Lin shouted.

The two players were finally in each other’s line of sight for the first time in this match.

“Will Mo Fan directly rush towards him?” Pan Lin yelled.

“Ah, he’s rushing over. He’s charging towards Li Yuan!”

Chapter 1444 - Break Out

Mo Fan had always been careful. There were often times where everyone thought that he could definitely continue his offense, but he would always run away and then look for another opportunity to launch a sneak attack on his opponent. Right now, his opponent was directly in front of him and spirits were all around him, yet he didn’t hesitate to rush him.

“Direct combat? But this time, the situation’s completely different,” Pan Lin said.

Last time was referring to the first Happy versus Blue Rain playoffs round. Li Yuan let out all of his summons to scout the surroundings and only left a Devil World Flower near him. Mo Fan’s Deception beautifully dodged around the spirits and cut straight to Eight Notes’ side. He instantly killed the Devil World Flower and then attacked Eight Notes.

But this time? Deception had only killed two Little Spirits. He hadn’t escaped from the predicament. Moreover, when Li Yuan’s Eight Notes prepared to personally take command of his summons, he had ordered all of his spirits to gather towards this place.

“He has no choice.” Li Yibo had no time to give a thorough analysis and simply gave out the main reason for Mo Fan’s actions.

Attack!

Deception rushed forward. Mo Fan may be silent and taciturn, but once he made a decision, he would take it all the way through. As a master of escape, he had a much clearer understanding of his predicament than others. If he didn’t have this sort of perception, there was no way he could have been able to pick up whatever he wanted on the chaotic PK fields and then escape.

He had grasped his opponent’s strategy. In this map, it was indeed flawless. A person’s observational abilities were far less precise than the system AI under these conditions. That was what he kept on bumping into spirits. What’s more, by the time he noticed it, the spirit would already be fairly close, making escape extremely difficult.

As a result, he started attacking the spirits. He recognized that today, there was no way to avoid these obstacles. If he couldn’t avoid them, then his only choice was to destroy them.

But after killing just two spirits, their owner appeared.

Mo Fan wasn’t too surprised. The spirits were this easy to kill because the system AI controlled them. Mo Fan wasn’t so naive to think that Li Yuan would just let him slaughter his way out. Li Yuan would certainly come out and take command of the spirits.

Fight the summons and the Summoner together? That was Tang Rou’s style.

The scrap-picker-borne Mo Fan had a clear goal: lock onto Eight Notes. That was all he wanted to do. Anything else was a waste of time.

Thus, as soon as Eight Notes appeared, Deception charged at him.

Mo Fan’s actions seemed incongruous with his usual playstyle, but it actually coincided perfectly with his usual decision making.

Storm Shuriken!

Deception lifted his hand and threw out several shurikens. As he dashed at him, Eight Notes, who had been in a blurry silhouette in the dense fog, became easier to see. Mo Fan saw as Eight Notes waved his magic staff and finish a cast. A summoning circle appeared in front of him. The soil under the summoning circle turned into a different color. The earth split apart, and vines from a Devil World Flower extended out.

Pu pu pu pu pu!

The shurikens were swatted down by the Devil World Flower. The Devil World Flower trembled and a vine drilled out from the ground.

Shua!

Deception leapt into the air. The vine tried to wrap around his ankle, but he threw out another shuriken, pinning the vine to the ground.

“Beautiful!” Pan Lin shouted. These precise and fluid movements showed just how skilled Mo Fan was. Pan Lin just didn’t understand. If Mo Fan possessed such technical skill, why was he insistent on his Fireworks Style?

Seal!

Deception quickly formed several hand seals. His two hands were like a blur to the eyes. The average viewer had no way of telling what seals he was forming. However, from the complexity of it, they could tell that it was a powerful skill.

What is it?

Ninjutsu – Exploding Flame Dragon!

Mo Fan had used this Level 75 skill last time to instantly kill off Li Yuan’s Devil World Flower. This time, the Devil World Flower had already been hit by Storm Shurikens. An instant kill was certain. Eight Notes was behind the Devil World Flower. The Exploding Flame Dragon had a large AoE and would swallow Eight Notes along with the Devil World Flower.

Boom!

A whirling fire dragon flew out from the triangle formed from Deception’s hands. However, at this moment, a wall of fire erupted, blocking the fire dragon.

These flames weren’t as overbearing as the dragon’s flames, but they were just as restless.

Big Fire Spirit!

The Big Fire Spirit acted as shield for the Devil World Flower, and facing the Exploding Flame Dragon, it rushed out to defend against it.

Using a Big Fire Spirit to take the attack was perfect. Fire elemental attacks had no effect on a Big Fire Spirit. Not only did it have no effect, the Big Fire Spirit seemed to expand; its flames danced even more wildly.

Fire Blade!

The Big Fire Spirit seemed to form an arm made up entirely of flames. The arm slashed downwards towards Deception.

Boom!

Deception suddenly went ablaze, instantly vanishing into smoke.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Mo Fan relied on this quick skill to avoid the Fire Blade and to instantly move to Eight Note’s back.

“He’s behind him!!” Pan Lin cried out.

The fast exchange between the two sides was too brilliant. Deception was able to successfully get to Eight Note’s back. Although it was hard to say how much he would be able to do with so many spirits surrounding him, he at least had the initiative during this short period of time, no?

But there was nothing!

The instant Deception moved behind Eight Notes, a sharp thorn shot from the ground. Mo Fan had no time to react. Deception was launched into the sky as if he had been pricked in the butt by it.

Thorn!

The Summoner knock-up skill was completed using summoning as well. Eight Notes had predicted that Deception would move behind him. Li Yuan knew that the Big Fire Spirit’s Fire Blade wouldn’t be enough to stop Deception’s advance.

Pa!

A crisp sound.

Eight Notes turned around. The magic staff in his hands seemed to have turned into a creature. It struck Deception, launching him even higher into the air.

Lash.

The skill was intended to be used on summons to increase their combat ability, but it could also be used as an attack against enemies.

Deception had used Substitution Technique previously to escape from the spirits. Right now, it was still on cooldown, so he had no way of escaping.

Boom boom boom!

The Big Light Spirit’s attack also arrived. A bolt of lightning crackled, crashing down onto Deception. Amidst the dense fog, spirit after spirit emerged, gathering together. Eight Notes retreated to the side, calmly commanding the army of spirits to attack Deception.

He hadn’t summoned a Spirit King yet. It required four Big Spirits to fuse together. It was more effective to use numbers to trap Deception. If he fused together four Spirits, Mo Fan might just be able to escape.

Li Yuan was calm, very calm. Blue Rain’s previous plans had failed to achieve their goal. Blue Rain’s situation wasn’t looking good either. He wasn’t a senior member of Team Blue Rain, only having one more year of experience than Lu Hanwen, yet he seemed to have the strength of a core member, keeping the battle under his control.

Deception’s health rapidly fell as the spirits swarmed him. And Eight Notes hadn’t taken any damage. If this situation continued at this pace, this round could be considered a perfect win for Li Yuan.

In an individual competition, apart from praise and a boost of morale, a perfect win was no different than a narrow win. But in the group arena, a perfect win was truly a perfect outcome.

“Is this going to be a perfect win?” Pan Lin started having his doubts. Deception only had 42% of his health left, while Eight Notes had an army of spirits at his command. The spirits had Deception completely surrounded. Under Li Yuan’s personal command, the spirits circled around Deception, attacking him.

Everything seemed to be going perfect for Li Yuan. Suddenly, Li Yibo’s eyes lit up: “Chance!”

“Chance?” Pan Lin didn’t understand, but Mo Fan’s Deception suddenly moved.

Substitution Technique!

While taking hits, Deception used an escape skill. A straw dummy lay in the center of the encirclement and fell apart, while Deceptin’s real body flashed to a different position.

This abrupt movement had sent Li Yuan’s army of summons into a fluster. Then, Ninjutsu – Shadow Dance!

Multiple Deceptions appeared.

Zi zi zi zi…

Several Little Spirits were killed instantly. Mo Fan’s observational skills were truly frightening. There were so many spirits, yet he was able to identify which ones had low health. These discerning eyes had been trained through years of scrap picking.

“Is he going to counterattack!” Pan Lin yelled excitedly. If Li Yuan completed a perfect win, true, it would be incredible. But a match with ups and downs was more fun to watch!

“He’s probably going to try to escape!” Li Yibo said. He had seen the opportunity previously and had a clearer idea of Mo Fan’s intentions. But the situation was tense, so there was no time for a more detailed analysis. The multitude of Deceptions incited chaos into the field. Suddenly, one of the Deceptions retreated.

The heart of Shadow Dance!

Everyone thought of this term. Li Yuan had no way of reforming the encirclement. If he tried to surround one of the Deceptions, the heart of Shadow Dance would quickly switch to a different clone.

After one clone ran away, a second one took off. Deception after Deception retreated in different directions, and Li Yuan had no way of stopping them.

“He’s going to run!” Just as Pan Lin said this, the first Deception that tried to escape went “shing” and turned into a block of ice.

Chapter 1445 - Near Perfect

“Frozen? How? Is it Falling Ice?” Pan Lin cried out in surprise. Falling Ice was the skill Big Ice Spirits used to attack with. Currently, the camera was on the Deception which had ran the furthest. His form was enveloped in mist, blurry from Eight Note’s point of view. Falling Ice? There was no hint of any Big Ice Spirit using that attack from the audience’s omniscient view. The freeze effect from Falling Ice wasn’t certain either. What sort of luck would you have to have in order to make sure that each hit was a freeze at such a crucial time?

What was it? As everyone mired in their bewilderment, the second Deception that charged turned into a block of ice with a pop!

Two? Everyone remained dumbstruck, and Mo Fan began to hesitate as well. The remaining Deceptions became uncertain. After spreading out, they weren’t strong and were quickly destroyed by the spirits. Mo Fan paused, but knowing that there was no other choice, he had all the Deception clones make a run for it.

Pop pop pop pop….

Miraculously, all the escaping Deceptions were turned into blocks of ice.

At the same time, three clones, clearly having left the range of Shadow Dance, shattered with the ice encasing them.

The shattered ice, along with the other two frozen Deceptions formed a circle. This circle wasn’t some random circle. It had blocked Deception’s escape and pulled away the heart of the Shadow Dance, causing the three clones to disappear at once.

“Ice Line!!!” Li Yibo suddenly realized, crying out his discovery.

Everyone who heard this immediately understood.

Ice Line, the Elementalist’s Ice Line skill.

An Ice Line would be left wherever the ice elemental power touched. The Ice Line would form an enchanted area within one second, and afterwards, whoever touched the Ice Line would be frozen with a 100 percent chance…

The skill that Li Yuan had set into his Eight Note’s staff was no longer Teleportation, but Ice Line. It was an Elementalist skill, but right now, Ice Line had turned into the key skill that would turn the tides. A skill set into the weapon having such a crucial effect was definitely more than worth its while!

With only two frozen Deceptions left, Eight Note’s spirit army would easily surround them. Li Yuan clearly had a masterful grasp of the freeze time, replenishing his summons as he had the two Deceptions surrounded.

He didn’t use this chance to summon any Spirit Kings. Perhaps it was because he didn’t see the need, or maybe he thought that the opening created by summoning Spirit Kings would be too big for this situation.

When the two ice blocks cracked open and the two Deceptions charged out, the spirits immediately swarmed over.

The broadcast director, thinking that nothing significant would occur, had already switched the shot to a replay of Li Yuan’s Eight Note using Ice Line. When Deception used the Substitution Technique to try and escape, his Eight Notes began to cast Ice Line. Everyone, including Mo Fan, had been focused on the army of spirits, not Eight Notes. This Summoner, that seemed useless in a direct battle, had become the key.

“Switch back! Switch back!!” But not two seconds into the replay, one of his colleagues cried wildly for him to switch back to the shot of the ongoing match.

“What?” The program director fumbled, realizing that they were probably missing a spectacular play from the other side.

Two seconds was enough for everything to change.

The camera switched back to the match.

Of the two Deceptions that came out of the ice, one had already disappeared while the other was on his way to disappearing…

Shadow Clone Technique!

Deception, who had just escaped from the ice, immediately used Shadow Clone Technique. This real body was, naturally, the one that attempted to escape, so the two clones were left behind. One immediately disappeared because it left the range of Shadow Dance. The other was instantly blasted into smithereens by the siege of spirits.

Deception’s real body didn’t escape so successfully.

After that false alarm, Li Yuan didn’t relax from relief, instead raising his guard, watching out for such a possibility. This time, he had considered the Ninja’s escaping ability when he swarmed the other with spirits.

The shadow clone was instantly destroyed, but his real body didn’t manage to escape immediately either.

Lightning!

Falling Ice!

Under Li Yuan’s personal direction, the light and ice element spirits immediately struck with their long ranged skills. The two attacks were both priority attacks, blocking Deception’s escape route, especially the light element large spirits’ Lightning. A row of Lightning striking down at once formed a wall of electricity.

Break through forcibly!

Mo Fan, with no other choice, made his choice resolutely. Without hesitation, Deception charged out straight through the Lightning. The Lightning struck, but Mo Fan was pretty lucky; the stun didn’t activate. However, right after, a row of Falling Ice descended. His attack came right after the Lightning. Since Deception had charged right through the Lightning, he wouldn’t be able to dodge this one….

A chill enveloped him from head to toe. A 100 percent freeze? It didn’t have that, but this strike had activated the 50 percent freeze. Deception could still move, but he had been slowed by 50 percent…

This dangerous situation wouldn’t let him take his leaving. The swarm of spirits encircled Deception completely. It wasn’t that there was no way out, but there was no chance given for escape. The escape skills of Ninjas had been considered when Li Yuan made these arrangements.

“I guess… that’s it…”

Deception’s health was about to hit zero, and Li Yibo finally made this conclusion.

Even under Li Yuan’s careful, meticulously planned encirclement and direction, everyone watched with their hearts in their throats as Deception’s health dwindled.

He didn’t give up. He didn’t give up until the end.

In the encirclement of spirits, Deception darted this way and that, trying to break out. He used all the tricks he had up his sleeve. Dart for an opening, killing his way through, open feints, sounding the east while heading west… As expected of an escape artist like Mo Fan, he had a plethora of tricks and schemes. Several times, he had charged out of the encirclement, but because he was unable to fully shake off the spirits, he didn’t manage to fully escape.

Deception fell, but this match wasn’t perfect. While he was over here trying to escape with everything he had, he had taken the time to suddenly throw a shuriken over at Eight Notes.

At that time, it was very crucial that he focused on blocking Deception’s way with spirits. Li Yuan’s judgement was very precise. If he had Eight Notes dodge and relaxed his grasp over the spirits, then Mo Fan would’ve gotten a chance. Thus, he didn’t dodge the shuriken, and had Eight Notes take the damage. The damage wasn’t much at all, and it was quite a shame, since it meant that this match wouldn’t be a perfect. However, Li Yuan didn’t bother pursuing this perfection, only wanting to continue the match steadily, and gaining a compliment from Pan Lin and Li Yibo.

This strike became the only damage Eight Notes had taken in the entire match, losing him 2 percent of his health.

The system didn’t judge it as a perfect victory, but a loss of 2 percent of his health was probably equal to a perfect in the eyes of the audience. The value and advantage a perfect gave wouldn’t be impacted any by this loss of 2 percent health.

The crowd erupted into cheering. Blue Rain had brilliantly made up a match after the two losses prior.

“Unfortunately, Mo Fan has lost this match, falling behind by a huge amount,” Pan Lin said.

“This gap is only the result. If we really consider the actual progress of the match, then, while he hadn’t managed to deal much damage, what sort of atmosphere surrounded this match? It was tense! Very tense. From this, it’s clear that the two opponents were evenly-matched. Though the result is very one-sided, but against a Summoner, one successful ambush from Mo Fan could mean his victory,” Li Yibo commented.

“That’s true. Though Mo Fan lost, he performed well this match,” Pan Lin agreed.

“Yes, and in a match of equal strength, what would become the deciding factor? The home game advantage! Li Yuan’s victory was built primarily on his brilliant grasp and usage of his terrain. His playstyle and strategy was founded on this map, and his actually performance was flawless. A very spectacular battle indeed,” Li Yibo said.

However, the audience in the venue clearly wouldn’t be able to analyze things as objectively as those two.

Last round, Mo Fan had used a tree to squash their God Huang Shaotian, and then narrowly won against Li Yuan as well. A rookie accomplishing a 1v2, especially when one of the opponents was Huang Shaotian, was a huge blow to Blue Rain’s morale. Today, his victory against Song Xiao had Blue Rain’ fans even more displeased. Seeing such a brilliant counterattack from Li Yuan, it would be a waste if they didn’t take the chance to unleash a wave of mockery.

Li Yuan was still in the player booth, so he couldn’t hear the applause, so the Blue Rain fans’ cheering didn’t last too long. When Mo Fan walked out of the player booth and came offstage, mocking applause and jeers also arrived like a tidal wave.

A rookie player generally would have a hard time facing such a situation, especially when they lost an almost perfect match to their opponent in the group arena. That was burden for the entire team and put great pressure on them. However, Mo Fan remained emotionless, as if none of this had anything to do with him, as if he were a bystander, walking right back the way he came. His reaction, or lack thereof, had the audience soon losing interest.

To Mo Fan, the jeers weren’t just because of the match. The ones guiding the fans in the audience stands were Blue Brook’s higher ups, and scrap picker Deception had been a huge trouble to them. Some of them had even been scrap picked by Mo Fan before and never managed to get revenge.

Now that they had a chance for revenge, they would naturally put their all into guiding these jeers. Yet Mo Fan’s reaction had them losing interest.

“Not bad,” The jeers that filled the stadium didn’t bother Happy’s members. Ye Xiu stood and spoke to the returning Mo Fan. “You might not have dealt much damage, but you’ve at least depleted a lot of his mana!”

“Yeah,” Mo Fan nodded and returned to his seat.

Chapter 1446 - Calculating Position

Mo Fan was still expressionless, and he didn’t have any interaction with the others. But in the few minutes that had just passed, Ye Xiu was able to determine what Mo Fan’s plan had been on the battlefield.

After being restricted by Eight Notes’ Ice Line, Mo Fan was still working hard and persevering.

And behind this perseverance wasn’t just his searching for a chance to escape. With Mo Fan’s skill in this area, he probably already recognized that so long as the opponent didn’t make a mistake, his Deception would have a very difficult time breaking through that encirclement of spirits.

His perseverance was his refusal to give in, but at the same time, it was prolonging the battle. And the goal of prolonging this battle was the same goal that Blue Rain had at the very beginning.

Wearing down.

Mo Fan wasn’t able to wear down the opponent’s health much, but through his perseverance, through the prolonging of the battle, he was able to wear down a significant portion of Eight Notes’ mana.

The Summoner class was a mana-hungry class. Even in this seemingly perfect match, because of Mo Fan’s unflagging perseverance, he was still able to leave a hidden scar.

Mo Fan couldn’t take advantage of this hidden scar. In a 1v1, under conditions like that, it was fairly unlikely that he could drag the battle out until Eight Notes ran out of mana and he could counterattack. But he still held on, all in order to help his next teammate.

The solitary Mo Fan had always been alone; he had been at Happy for almost two years without really becoming anyone’s friend. But now in this match, in the group arena, in a situation where his own chances of success were already unlikely, he understood how to fulfill his greatest potential – for his upcoming teammates, achieve the greatest chance of victory.

Ye Xiu couldn’t help but think of that one team match they had against Blue Rain, where he covered for Mo Fan’s retreat, but that guy turned around and came back to save him.

By that point in that team battle, there wasn’t much suspense. No action would have had a major effect on the battle’s outcome. But for Happy, for Mo Fan himself, it had unusual meaning. His actions that day allowed Ye Xiu to see that Mo Fan was steadily growing to become a competent pro player, a pro player who was beginning to recognize the importance of teammates and teamwork. Mo Fan’s actions that day didn’t affect the battle’s outcome, but the fact that he now had this recognition would definitely prove valuable on the battlefield one day.

And that day had arrived, the opponent once again Blue Rain. In this group arena, Mo Fan’s realization of the importance of team allowed him to finally move away from someone who was always pursuing individual endurance and victory. In a situation where he didn’t have much chance of winning on his own, he thought of how to best ensure the team’s overall victory.

Lose the battle, win the war.

This phrase was perhaps an excellent annotation for this match and Mo Fan’s future professional career.

“Now it’s up to me!” Fang Rui stood up, holding out his fist toward Mo Fan. Mo Fan looked at him without reacting.

“No passion at all!” Fang Rui grumbled, heading toward the stage. The stadium screen was already displaying Happy’s next player and character, and in the broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo could discuss how they thought Fang Rui would perform in this next match.

“Even though Li Yuan won beautifully, he’s exhausted himself quite a bit.” Li Yibo had also noticed that Eight Notes had used up a significant amount of mana.

“Now, let’s see how Fang Rui will take advantage of that point,” Pan Lin said.

Group arena, both sides were on their third player. Soon, the match began. Before either player moved, messages were exchanged.

“Always guessing around is such a pain. Name a place and let’s meet up!” Fang Rui said.

“How about the central path!” Li Yuan said.

“Alright,” Fang Rui answered, and Boundless Sea immediately turned toward the left path.

The crowd instantly booed.

This was why it was very difficult for a player like Fang Rui to become the ace player of a team. This kind of action was sometimes shameful even for his own team’s fans, so there was really no way he could become the symbol of a team.

Li Yuan’s Eight Notes had very honestly taken the central path. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea, under the booing that he couldn’t hear, was very calmly taking the roundabout route.

Li Yuan had also clearly realized that Eight Notes was rather low on mana, so he took a while before summoning a creature. He only released his first summon when he was right near the central path, letting it walk at the front before summoning two more to bolster the left and right. Evidently, he wasn’t naive enough to believe that Fang Rui would actually take the central path after saying he would.

Finally, Li Yuan arrived at the very center of the map, where the two had agreed to meet.

But where was Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea? The display screen switched point of view, and the entire Glory world was speechless.

“Left… The upper left corner? Why is Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea heading over here?” Pan Lin exclaimed, shocked.

Fang Rui’s roundabout travel here was roundabout to the very extreme. Boundless Sea was directly charging toward the very upper left corner of the map, and his current distance from Li Yuan’s Eight Notes was only growing.

“This… Maybe he just wants to be a bit farther from the opponent, so they don’t meet too quickly…” Li Yibo said.

“…” Pan Lin instantly became speechless as well. Just during the last battle, he and Li Yibo had analyzed the disadvantages this map had for a Summoner.

Because the field of view on this map wasn’t very large, if a Summoner waited until discovering the opponent to summon a creature, it might already be too late. So, a Summoner had to always have summons on hand, whether to protect or to investigate. Therefore, under these conditions, even though the two sides hadn’t met yet, the Summoner would continue to use up mana.

So right now, Fang Rui was using the simplest and crudest method. Just hide far, far, away! You can’t find me, so just continue to waste your mana!

This method capitalized upon the awkwardness a Summoner faced on this map. But for him to play dirty to this extent, it was really quite ugly to watch. The booing of the crowd now became much louder now than they had been with Fang Rui’s initial deception.

“Where you at?” Li Yuan now asked in the chat.

“Ready to ambush you at any moment,” Fang Rui said boldly, who was currently over half the map length away from Eight Notes.

“Hiding away to waste my mana?” Li Yuan actually directly called out Fang Rui’s intention.

“Haha, how could I.” Fang Rui refused to admit it.

But even though he’d completely guessed Fang Rui’s intention, Li Yuan didn’t hesitate. He began summoning one after another, and instantly eight small summons were released, scattering outward in all directions.

It was all very fast, very resolute, as though in a race against time. And when these summons spread out, everyone immediately realized that on the west side, the left side where Fang Rui had gone, there was a summon directly heading toward Boundless Sea’s position.

“Based on the character’s movement speed, he predicted the most likely path. For this kind of decision, the faster it’s made, the better. If too much time passes, then there’s no way at all of judging where the opponent might have gone,” Li Yibo said.

“Then based on that, maybe it would have been better if Fang Rui hadn’t moved at all at the start,” Pan Lin said.

“It seems that way, but he did move, and the distance he moved is within Li Yuan’s calculations,” Li Yibo said.

On an overhead view of the map, a line was drawn between Boundless Sea and that light-aligned summon, marking the place where they were likely to meet. Right now, both were steadily heading toward that point.

“Li Yuan has made ample preparations on this map,” Li Yibo exclaimed.

“There!” Pan Lin shouted. Boundless Sea and the Light Spirit weren’t battling yet, but the two had entered into each other’s sights.

At this distance, Li Yuan himself could no longer see his own summon, but he could check its movements. If he received notification that his summon was attacking, then he knew without question that that was Boundless Sea.

But at this moment, the signal he received was stronger than that. This Little Light Spirit directly vanished.

The summon’s time hadn’t expired. For it to simply vanish, that meant it was killed. Again, it could only be Boundless Sea.

Li Yuan immediately had Eight Notes to rush toward that direction, at the same time restarting his summoning. He replaced the four spirits that had headed toward the east, combining these four into two Big Spirits, and then adding four more Little Spirits, spreading out in a fan toward that direction.

This dense forest map was rectangular in shape, longer in the north-south direction, narrow in the east-west. Searching horizontally already increased the chance of encounter, and with the current formation of Li Yuan’s summons, everyone could see that Boundless Sea’s position was restricted to a very small area.

Watching this, Blue Rain’s audience felt very satisfied!

You wanted to play around, so think you can play your way out of this?

Seeing the opponent’s dirty play end bloodily was always fun to watch.

But at this moment, Fang Rui suddenly stopped playing dirty. Boundless Sea was no longer continuing toward the upper left corner, and as though he was leading an army of a million soldiers, he charged straight toward the encirclement of summons.

“Is he trying to forcefully attack his way through?” Pan Lin shouted.

But Li Yibo furrowed his brow. The rhythms of the battles on this map so far had all been fairly slow, which gave him more time to observe and analyze. Because of that, he had been commenting at a fairly high level today. At this time, carefully studying the movements of both sides, Li Yibo once again felt that something was off.

They met!

Boundless Sea, who had voluntarily made his way toward the encirclement of summons, finally met them. But because the formation of his summons was so spread out, Eight Notes couldn’t have all of them in his view. That was to say, Li Yuan couldn’t personally control every single one of the summons in the encircling formation. And the summon that Boundless Sea crashed into now was one of the independently moving summons.

Cloud Pushing Palm, Qi Bullet, Countercurrent…

Boundless Sea never stopped moving, and with a series of booms, low-level skills came out one after another. This small summon was acting like an innocent bystander passing through, and was easily taken care of.

“He broke through! And very easily, it looks like!” Pan Lin shouted.

“Yes… Li Yuan wasn’t the only one calculating the opponent’s position. Fang Rui was also anticipating, and then he guessed the surrounding formation he would use. Encirclements always surround a large area before shrinking to a smaller one. When the area’s large, the encircling members don’t have very close contact with each other, especially on a map like this. Fang Rui took advantage of this point and actively attacked, breaking through Li Yuan’s plan before the encirclement became an effective containment!” Li Yibo calmly explained what happened, but this time, he still overlooked a point.

Boundless Sea hadn’t simply escaped out of the encirclement. After killing the Little Spirit, he suddenly dashed in a slanting path.

Chapter 1447 - Genius Fang Rui

Pan Lin and Li Yibo stared blankly. The audience members misled by the commentators were stared blankly.

Break out from an encirclement? That didn’t seem to be the right direction! If he goes in that direction, won’t he crash into a spirit?

Li Yibo started thinking. But this time, the development came too fast. Before he could think it through, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea ran into a Little Spirit.

Boom!

It was another low-level skill into a normal attack, extinguishing the Little Spirit. Then, he continued.

Li Yibo finally understood: “He’s going around the circle, killing them one by one!”

Li Yuan didn’t have an omniscient view like the spectators. When the Little Spirit was killed, he could deduce the general area where Boundless Sea was located from the pathing of the Little Spirit. He didn’t have a precise grasp of Boundless Sea’s position. The spirits that he had placed far away weren’t within his command range, so he could only make adjustments for the spirits within range.

Fang Rui was targeting this point through forceful attacks. Even though his initial actions were rather dirty, Fang Rui was now attacking like thunder and moving like the wind. After killing two Little Spirits, he finally encountered a Big Spirit.

Hua!

Ice Fall. This Big Water Spirit threw a cube of ice at Boundless Sea. Boundless Sea rolled to avoid it and then shot out a Qi Bullet.

The Big Water Spirit unexpectedly moved to the side, dodging the Qi Bullet. Fang Rui realized that this Water Spirit was under Li Yuan’s control. Although he couldn’t see Eight Notes, this Big Water Spirit just happened to be within both players’ field of vision.

The situation immediately became tense. Should he continue forward, or retreat temporarily?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo had just brought this point up, when Boundless Sea rushed forward decisively.

Spiral Qi Kill!

With a wave of his hands, spiralling qi tore through the dense fog, making it increasingly more visible. The Big Water Spirit wanted to run, but this Spiral Qi Kill chased after it. In the end, a Summoner couldn’t control its summons as well as his own character, and the attack landed.

Gelala…

The Spiral Qi Kill struck the Big Water Spirit, giving off a strange sound. The Big Water Spirit shot backwards along with the rotating qi.

Spiral Qi Kill didn’t have a blow away effect. Li Yuan had decided to retreat, controlling the Big Water Spirit to move backwards borrowing the knockback from Spiral Qi Kill to reach such fast speeds.

Qi Flowing Cloud!

Boundless Sea activated Qi Flowing Cloud, buffing his movement speed. His steps quickened like moving clouds. In the blink of an eye, caught up to the Big Water Spirit and slammed into it.

Qi Break!

Qi poured into the Big Water Spirit. The qi circulating inside the Big Water Spirit could be seen due to its transparent body. Then, with a “bo”, a crack appeared inside the Big Water Spirit. The crack spread until it spread throughout the entire surface of its body. Finally, with a shatter, the Big Water Spirit crumbled into several pieces.

At this moment, Li Yuan’s Eight Notes and his countless spirits were now inside Fang Rui’s line of sight. After Fang Rui killed the two Little Spirits, Li Yuan immediately had Eight Notes replenish and send them out again. He had also recalled the wave of spirits he had spread out previously. Eight Notes had summoned a Big Fire Spirit too with numerous Little Spirits beside it.

Seeing that Boundless Sea was nearly within reach, Eight Notes commanded the spirits to form a line.

Spirit Style combat relied on numbers and cooperation between spirits. Besides a Spirit King, a single big spirit couldn’t even compare to a Death Knight or one of the Four Beasts.

LI Yuan’s attempts to surround Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea with spirits had failed. At this distance, trying to surround him would require even greater precision.

But Boundless Sea unexpectedly stopped there. As soon as he saw the line of spirits formed by Eight Notes, Fang Rui typed out a smiley face in the chat and then ran away into the dense fog.

Li Yuan wasn’t going to let him go so easily, sending out several spirits to give chase.

The spectators had a clearer grasp of the battlefield because of their omniscient view. Boundless Sea’s retreat was a fake one. After retreating, he circled back. Fang Rui had played boldly for a bit, but then switched back to playing dirty.

Not long afterwards, a Little Spirit found Boundless Sea. Fang Rui didn’t hesitate to kill it.

He continued to wander.

Fang Rui seemed to be doing what Mo Fan had done, but in fact, there was a difference in purpose. Mo Fan had been trying his hardest to escape from the notice of the spirits. However, Fang Rui was actively seeking to kill the spirits. As soon as he found one, he would quickly destroy it and then continue on with his hunt.

Li Yuan’s army of spirits started to dwindle in numbers. Seeing this scene, Pan Lin couldn’t help but sigh: “Couldn’t Mo Fan have done the same?”

“It’s different,” Li Yibo said.

“Ah?”

“Fang Rui is able to do it, but Mo Fan could not have.”

“Why?”

“Because of Eight Note’s mana. If you take a closer look at the situation, you’ll notice that Li Yuan’s spirit formation doesn’t have the same compactness as when he had deployed it against Mo Fan. Fang Rui is able to play in this way because of the foundation that Mo Fan had built. Because of the mana Li Yuan had used up in the previous round, he cannot play as boldly as he did before. If he did, his mana wouldn’t be able to last this fight.”

“But if this continues…”

“He has no way of catching Fang Rui right now. I think he should give up on beating him and instead try to take out as much of Fang Rui’s health as possible…” Li Yibo said.

Li Yibo was correct. Li Yuan currently faced a difficult situation. Those who played dirty were masters at digging into wounds. They’d take your weak spot and then mercilessly stab at it again and again. Whether it was playing boldly or playing dirty, Fang Rui had always been targeting Li Yuan’s weak point.

Whether it was the unfavorable terrain for Summoners or the mana issue created by Mo Fan’s efforts, Fang Rui took advantage of both.

“He’s not wasting the foundation that Mo Fan lay down for him. What a reliable guy!” Ye Xiu sighed. Everyone looked at Mo Fan. They wanted to see if he would put on a face of gratitude after seeing the advantage that he had built up being used. But all they was him continue staring at the screen.

“There shouldn’t be any problems with this round, right?” Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu.

“No problems,” Ye Xiu said with certainty. Li Yuan’s Eight Notes had almost no mana left, “At this point, Li Yuan will most likely try for one final all-out burst. We’ll see how Fang Rui deals with it.”

Ye Xiu analyzed it deeper than Li Yibo.

None of Li Yuan’s attacks could reach his opponent. He knew that he couldn’t let his time on the battlefield go to waste, and if this continued, it would be a waste. As a result, he decided to make use of all his remaining mana. He didn’t think too much and immediately sped up the pace, increasing the density of summons, forming new spirits to make up for the missing ones.

Fang Rui immediately noticed the change in pace. He knew Li Yuan had no choice but to bet his all to win as much as possible for his following teammate.

“Come! Let’s decide it!” Fang Rui shouted in the chat. Boundless Sea rushed forward, not towards Eight Notes, but towards the outer perimeter…

“It’s match point! What is Fang Rui planning?” Pan Lin yelled excitedly.

“He’s… running away?” Li Yibo said weakly.

“Fu…” Pan Lin nearly cursed but caught himself in the end. When he checked the map, Boundless Sea was heading straight for a direction away from all of the spirits. Wasn’t he running away?

“Mo Fan’s skill at escaping is truly outstanding. But Fang Rui is more experienced in comparison. He immediately noticed the sudden change in pace from Li Yuan…” Li Yibo said.

“Then, he ran…”

“Yeah…”

Their voices gradually became gloomier as if they felt embarrassed about reporting this reality.

At the deciding point, Fang Rui ran, quite successfully too. Because at that time, Li Yuan had just readied himself to go all out. Just when he sped up the pace, before he could spread out his new summons, his opponent smelled the air and ran.

Yes, smelled the air and then ran. It was an unglamorous description, but it fit Fang Rui’s style. The outcome was even more infuriating. Li Yuan’s Eight Notes was now out of mana. A bunch of spirits roared as they chased after him. Then, as time went by, spirit after spirit crumbled. Finally, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea showed up majestically.

“Are you going to GG, or do I need to help you out?” Fang Rui typed out arrogantly.

The entire stadium was filled with boos!

“His way of doing things is too ugly to look at. But from a practical standpoint, his plan was extremely effective… for such a dirty plan, even if you had the capability to think of it, you might not be able to do it,” Li Yibo tried his hardest to justify Fang Rui’s actions.

“Yes, for example, if Fang Rui didn’t have an extremely acute sense of awareness, he might not have succeeded in the final escape, right Coach Li?” Pan Lin said.

“Yeah…” Li Yibo said.

“Then… I guess that’s it?” Pan Lin said.

“Yeah…”

A Summoner with no mana had practically zero combat ability. What’s worse was that he still had 18% of his health left. Apart from the Shuriken thrown by Mo Fan last round, he hadn’t taken any damage. Now, he had no mana, and attacks would certainly come his way.

“Watch me destroy you!” Fang Rui became bold, facing this manaless Summoner.

“Fang Rui’s history is quite rich…” Pan Lin tried to look at things from a different perspective as he explained the origins of this master of playing dirty.

“Yes… when he first started playing competitively, he had created a random team with a few friends and participated in the Challenger League…” Li Yibo said.

“A bunch of very dirty-playing friends and a team that played very dirty,” Pan Lin said.

“Their win record wasn’t anything amazing, but Fang Rui had caught Team Blue Rain’s eyes…”

“Blue Rain has always been good at digging out people with personalities.”

“Then, Fang Rui joined Blue Rain’s training camp…”

“Afterwards, he was dug out by Wind Howl.”

“Now, he’s gone to Happy…”

“And he’s changed classes several times during this time.”

“Truly a genius.”

Chapter 1448 - I've Got Good Eyesight

Li Yuan’s Eight Notes fell without any suspense.

For a Summoner without mana, no one would blame Li Yuan for surrendering. But Li Yuan still had Eight Notes run around left and right. He had no way of resisting, but he dodged around to drag the fight.

Dragging the battle would tire out Fang Rui a bit more. This seemed to be the name of the game for this round’s group arena. However, Li Yuan had trouble dragging the fight out, and the effects were poor too. Even so, he didn’t give up until the end. He didn’t give up until Boundless Sea took away the last drop of life from Eight Notes.

Li Yuan went down from the stage.

The entire stadium roared with applause in praise of his outstanding performance last round and his perseverance this round.

Trying to drag the fight without any mana seemed like he was just haggling over pennies, lacking the air of a powerhouse. However, in this group arena, neither side was giving in, so no one was bothered by Li Yuan’s methods.

“Good job.” Li Yuan received praise from his teammates, but he himself looked dispirited. He was very unhappy with his match against Fang Rui.

Next, Team Blue Rain’s fourth player went up: Lu Hanwen, Flowing Cloud.

The crowd went into an uproar. If Lu Hanwen was fourth, then Team Blue Rain’s final fifth player was most likely Huang Shaotian. Placing the ace player as the anchor was a very conservative arrangement for this competitive format. By universal agreement, winning the group arena was only meaningful if you won by more than two points. As a result, teams usually placed their ace player as their fourth member to end the group arena then and there.

But despite this being Blue Rain’s home game, they had Huang Shaotian as their last player. Was such a conservative arrangement an indicator of their lack of confidence?

Whispers spread throughout the stadium. Blue Rain’s unusual arrangement made their fans feel uneasy.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo discussed this issue quite a bit. In the end, Li Yibo summarized it by stating a reality: “Given the circumstances, Blue Rain is temporarily on the backfoot.”

Blue Rain was on their fourth player, yet Happy was on their third. What’s more, Fang Rui had only lost 26% of his health last round against Li Yuan. He still had 74% health left and nearly full mana. It was hard to say who would win this next round. If Fang Rui won, Happy would have an overwhelming advantage.

Who will win?

Everyone in the stadium wondered as they watched Lu Hanwen go onto the stage.

He was still a young teen who hadn’t fully grown, yet his footsteps were firm. Step by step, he walked onto the stage.

The sixth round of the group arena began.

“Little demon, where do you want to meet?” Words immediately popped up into the chat as soon as the match started. Fang Rui spoke as if he was a villain in a drama.

“The center!” Lu Hanwen replied.

“Okay. You’d better not go back on your word!” Fang Rui said.

The boos were ear-deafening. Quite a few Blue Rain fans started throwing curses at Fang Rui. Last round, Fang Rui had went back on his words, yet now he was telling the other side not to go back on his words. How could they not be infuriated?

On Team Happy’s side, Chen Guo felt like she couldn’t lift her head. It was true that she was happy about winning, but she was far from agreeing with the phrase, the end justifies the means. When she looked at Wei Chen, she saw him react with a big grin at Fang Rui’s shameless display.

“Senior, I don’t think you’re in a position to warn me.” Lu Hanwen said what everyone wanted to say to Fang Rui.

“Haha, do you want to guess if I’m going to go or not?” Fang Rui said.

Shameless! Everyone cursed.

“Senior, I don’t know if you’re going to go, but I definitely will be,” Lu Hanwen replied.

“Little Lu, what a good kid!!” The crowd cheered. They didn’t know who would win this round, but at least in terms of morals, Lu Hanwen had already won a hundred fold.

Sure enough, Lu Hanwen went straight along the central path like he said he would.

“What an honest kid!” Wei Chen sighed.

“What, you disapprove?” Chen Guo said.

“I don’t disapprove. As long as you win, then I don’t care,” Wei Chen replied dully.

As for Fang Rui? He lived up to expectations. After telling his opponent to meet in the center, Fang Rui went back on his word and took the roundabout route to the right.

A short moment later…

“Senior, I’m here.” Flowing Cloud raised his greatsword and stood at the very center of the map.

“Okay, I’m almost there,” Fang Rui replied. Boundless Sea continued along the path to the right.

“I’m guessing that senior won’t be showing up from the front!” Lu Hanwen said.

“Smart.”

“Then from where?”

“Keep guessing!” Fang Rui said.

“The left or the right!” Lu Hanwen said.

“I could come from the back!” Fang Rui said.

“Right!” Lu Hanwen seemed to have been enlightened.

“So you’ve got to be careful.” Fang Rui said. His Boundless Sea was already positioned by Flowing Cloud’s right side. If he wanted to ambush Lu Hanwen, he needed to find a good hiding spot first. He couldn’t use the dense fog as cover. If he did, while it was true that the other side wouldn’t be able to see him, he wouldn’t be able to see the other side either.

Like a thief, Boundless Sea rolled around forest.

“I wonder if Zhao Yang’s watching this match,” Pan Lin suddenly said.

“Haha,” Li Yibo laughed. He immediately understood Pan Lin’s joke. He wanted to know what Zhao Yang was feeling, seeing his Boundless Sea become a dirty Qi Master rolling around in the dirt.

Fang Rui finally found a position. Boundless Sea let out a peek from behind a tree. After checking his surroundings, he immediately went back into hiding.

He could see Flowing Cloud. The other side was just standing there as if he were waiting for him. Was Lu Hanwen planning on reacting to his moves instead of taking the initiative? Because of the visibility issue, the distance between the two sides was closer to each other, and there might not be enough space to react.

While Fang Rui was pondering over how he should mount his sneak attack, a message suddenly popped up in the chat: “Senior, I see you.”

“Oh?” Fang Rui laughed. How could someone as experienced as Fang Rui be tricked by these words. He simply laughed inwardly at his opponent’s naivety.

“Yeah, I’ve got good eyesight,” Lu Hanwen said.

“Really? Ah, how terrible! You’re going to rush over and attack, so I’d better run!” Fang Rui chatted, while thinking how he should open the fight. However, the crowd outside had started growing excited.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was quietly moving ahead straight for Boundless Sea’s hiding spot.

“He really saw him!” Everyone was astonished.

“Put on a replay from Lu Hanwen’s perspective.” The broadcast immediately displayed a replay. Lu Hanwen had constantly been checking his surroundings, looking left and right.

“Slow it down.” No one noticed anything, so the call to slow it down was made.

1/2 speed.

1/4 speed.

1/8 speed.

Everyone finally saw it. It was just an instant, but Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea could be seen taking a peek from behind a tree.

Even under 1/8 speed, it had just been an instant. Fang Rui had moved extremely fast. He had only exposed his head for a short moment.

A normal player might not have caught it, but Lu Hanwen had.

I’ve got good eyesight. That wasn’t a joke!

Lu Hanwen wasn’t as naive as Fang Rui had thought. As he continued chatting with Fang Rui, Flowing Cloud closed in quietly, step by step.

“That idiot!” Wei Chen cursed, obviously referring to Fang Rui.

“That kid really has incredible eyes.” A replay of the moment was displayed on the big screen. The broadcast even put a red indicator on Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea to make it easier for people to see. When Ye Xiu saw the replay, he had been astonished by Lu Hanwen too.

Fang Rui still had no idea. However, he had finally thought of how he should start his offense. Before doing so, he needed to confirm his opponent’s position.

Boundless Sea quickly peeked his head out.

Sword light!

All Fang Rui could see was sword light. Right when his head peeked out, sword light had cut his way. Fang Rui hastily moved his mouse back, and Boundless Sea retracted his head. The sword light flew past the tree.

“How fast!!” Pan Lin cried out. As for whether he was talking about Flowing Cloud’s attack or Boundless Sea’s head, no one knew. Both were correct though.

“It’s a pity he’s using a greatsword,” Li Yibo noted.

Greatswords were far slower than lightsabers and tachis. The attack speed limited how fast a player could attack. Pro players could rely on their hand speed to attack faster than normal players, but when the hand speeds were equal, a greatsword would certainly lose out to a lightsaber or tachi.

Flowing Cloud’s Sword Draw had missed by just a hair. If he had used a tachi or a lightsaber, it would not have missed.

After almost being hit, how could Fang Rui not realize the situation. He completely abandoned his previous plan to ambush Lu Hanwen. Boundless Sea had peeked his head out from the right side. After pulling back his head, he didn’t hesitate and prepared to attack from the left.

But then…

A heavy wind blew by. Flowing Cloud’s greatsword once again swept over.

Boundless Sea could only go back into hiding behind the tree. Fang Rui finally understood that the little demon truly had demonic reaction speed and eyes. Those traits were being put to full use in this terrain.

It became even more clear why Blue Rain had chosen this map.

Chapter 1449 - Preventing Sneak Attacks

Underneath a giant locust tree, Flowing Cloud held the greatsword Flame Shadow in his hands and stood motionless, directly facing the trunk of the locust tree. Boundless Sea had his back against the locust tree and stood motionless too.

The battle seemed to have frozen. No one knew what would come next.

The two players were very close to each other. If either character breathed, the opponent might be able to hear in this silent forest.

Boundless Sea, with his back against the locust tree, quietly crouched down.

Let alone sneak attacks, just trying to circle around the tree to the left or right would be difficult. Lu Hanwen had fast reaction speeds and played quickly too. He was on guard against these two directions. See head, chop head. See hand, chop hand. See foot, chop foot.

The battle had frozen, but the two players were thinking non-stop.

Fang Rui was constantly looking around, observing everything in front of him. He was searching for a tree to use as cover to escape.

A bit difficult. Fang Rui thought. He didn’t have a better choice though. It would be easier to run than approach from the left or right. If he tried that approach, Lu Hanwen would definitely steal away the initiative.

Fang Rui began to move.

First, Boundless Sea crouched down.

Then, he gently turned 180 degrees and started to retreat one step at a time.

Fang Rui didn’t choose to roll. He didn’t dare let his line of sight leave the tree in front of him.

No signs of movement from the left or right.

What is he waiting for?

Fang Rui didn’t know, but he had made his decision and he would stick with it. Boundless Sea continued to retreat.

Suddenly, several figures flickered from behind the tree.

Six Flowing Clouds rushed out.

Shadow Step!

It could only be Shadow Step!

Six shadows. Lu Hanwen controlled them adeptly such that Fang Rui wasn’t able to tell which one was real.

Unable to continue retreating, he could only fight. Fortunately, Fang Rui had Boundless Sea retreat backwards, so his line of sight had been fixed in this direction. In the end, he wasn’t caught off guard.

Landmine Quake!

Boundless Sea slammed the ground. The shockwave would reach all six shadows. He wanted to fish out the real one.

But all six shadows leaped up at the same time, dodging the qi attack.

Falling Light Blade!

Six swords crashed down with a silver light as if forming a sword formation.

Boundless Sea didn’t dodge and crashed into one of the light blades.

“Did he see through it?” Pan Lin cried out.

“Probably not!” Li Yibo replied. He wanted to say more, but he didn’t have time. The six swords and six Flowing Clouds all moved towards Boundless Sea.

Six swords, five fake. But if Boundless Sea continued to brashly charge through the attacks, all six swords would hit, which would mean the real one would hit.

Falling Light Blade guaranteed a knockdown. Although the knockdown could be Quick Recovered, Lu Hanwen could react to it and continue with follow ups.

Qi Wave Shield!

Boundless Sea waved his hands and a wave of qi condensed into a shield.

“This…” Pan Lin didn’t understand. Qi Wave Shield wasn’t Qi Guard. It couldn’t block attacks from every direction. If he used Qi Wave Shield to block, it would at most block two swords.

“Genius!” Li Yibo saw through it and shouted out.

He didn’t have time to explain though. Hit!

Shockwaves from six Falling Light Blades spread out. Even if five of the Falling Light Blades were from fake shadows, the visual effect would still remain. Boundless Sea tumbled out in a direction. In the end, he had been hit by the real sword.

But Boundless Sea immediately let out a palm.

A Qi Bullet shot towards one of the Flowing Clouds.

Was that the real body?

It was!

After Boundless Sea took the hit, he immediately figured out which of the six sword shadows was real from the direction he was hit in.

“If he just randomly chose a sword shadow to run into, the chances of getting hit by the real one is rather low. However, Lu Hanwen had all of the sword shadows switch directions. It can be seen that the one Boundless Sea chose before wasn’t the real one.”

“After that, although Qi Wave Shield could only block two, those two swords were the most difficult to deal with if they were real.”

“In reality, neither of these two swords was the real one. The real one was among the remaining three. Fang Rui had eliminated three of them, allowing him to deal with the other three with more focus. He was eliminating each choice one by one.”

Li Yibo spoke quickly to explain Fang Rui’s thought process in the short amount of time he had.

“Amazing!” Pan Lin sighed. Fang Rui had considered so many things in just an instant. That was what it meant to be a top Glory expert.

Fang Rui was able to reset the situation with his series of reactions.

Qi Blade!

Boundless Sea slashed out a Qi Blade.

But in this dense fog, the skill’s trajectory was extremely obvious, which was quite annoying for Fang Rui.

“Senior, I’ve said it before, but I’ve got good eyesight.” Lu Hanwen saw it clearly. Flowing Cloud easily dodged it and continued his attack.

“Okay, I’ll make sure to remember it,” Fang Rui replied as Boundless Sea retreated back a few more steps.

In the past, Fang Rui would have definitely tried to use the surrounding trees to hide in and then try for an ambush.

However, Lu Hanwen’s eyes and reaction speed were impressive. Fang Rui had experienced just how bad hiding behind a tree could be. He didn’t plan on challenging Lu Hanwen in those two aspects.

The current situation was unfavorable for him. Fang Rui understood this well.

In this map, Lu Hanwen’s eyes and reaction speed were powerful weapons and just happened to be the most effective against sneak attacks.

It was extremely rare for the opponent to become aware of a sneak attack after the sneak attack landed. Usually, the sneak attack caught the opponent off guard. Glory wasn’t army against army. In 1v1s, each player had complete control of their character. If you could react in time to a sneak attack, then the sneak attack would be meaningless.

At the moment, thinking of a sneak attack was too early. Lu Hanwen was too close to him. The two sides looked to be falling into the pace for a direct battle. This wasn’t Fang Rui’s style as a master of playing dirty. In other words, a direct battle wasn’t a style he was proficient in.

As for Lu Hanwen, don’t look at how he was still young. He was the attacker in Team Blue Rain and a first-class expert in face to face combat. In addition to his personality and energy, face to face combat was one of his biggest strengths.

“Senior, watch my sword!”

When Lu Hanwen slashed downwards, he also typed out a challenge in the chat. In the beginning, people were worried. If this continued, would this kid become like Huang Shaotian and talk non-stop while fighting?

But after two years, everyone understood. Lu Hanwen sometimes talked because he had so much energy that he needed somewhere to direct it to. His hands felt uncomfortable not moving fast, so he typed to make up for it.

It seemed like he was wasting his efforts, but this kid had endless energy. A bit of wasted energy wasn’t a problem, so no one criticized it.

An oppressive wind blew from Flame Shadow. The dense fog rumbled as the sword moved, and the flow of the game began to change.

Fang Rui was gradually being suppressed. He didn’t hold the advantage in this sort of fight. He was used to taking advantage of the terrain, but because of Lu Hanwen’s eyes and reaction speed, he couldn’t do that.

“Little demon, don’t be too arrogant!” Fang Rui spoke.

“Senior, please advise me,” Lu Hanwen said. Who knew if he was being sincere or being sarcastic.

“Okay, little kid, I’ll teach you a lesson,” Fang Rui said. Boundless Sea suddenly leand to the side and let out a palm.

Spiral Qi Kill!

Boom!

The distance was too close. Lu Hanwen wasn’t able to dodge it. However, in order to land this attack, his Boundless Sea was hit by a Downwind Sword Slash.

Boundless Sea was covered in blood. Flowing Cloud was covered in violent qi.

The audience was dumbstruck.

This was the lesson Fang Rui was giving to Lu Hanwen?

What was this?

Wasn’t he just brute-force trading?

Trades happened all the time in pro matches, but everyone always did it cautiously, calculating who would come out on top. These trades weren’t just for health, but more importantly, to create opportunities for follow ups.

But Boundless Sea’s trade?

That was just purely you-hit-I-hit. There was no change in the flow of the battle. Whatever it was before was the same after.

How stupid! Fang Rui really was dirty. The crowd booed.

After Flowing Cloud was hit by Spiral Qi Kill, he quickly rushed back. As for Boundless Sea? Because of the Downwind Sword Slash, he was stunned for a certain amount of time and couldn’t immediately react.

This was the reason why everyone thought the trade was stupid. If the trade had allowed Fang Rui to push Lu Hanwen away, then Fang Rui could have created more room for him to maneuver around dirtily. That would be a meaningful trade. But because he was hit by Downwind Sword Slash, this trade was completely pointless.

Triple Slash!

Flowing Cloud used this skill to approach.

The greatsword Triple Slash was ferocious and threatening. By the time Flowing Cloud reached Boundless Sea, Boundless Sea had just gotten out of the stun.

Roll!

Boundless Sea immediately rolled to dodge the third Triple Slash.

Falling Blossom Form!

Lu Hanwen’s offense was extremely fast. Flowing Cloud pressed down on the rolling Boundless Sea.

Knockdown!

Falling Blossom Form forced the knockdown. Boundless Sea was now lying flat on the ground.

Falling Phoenix Slash!

Usually, a Rising Dragon Slash would follow. Lu Hanwen used it on the ground. Flowing Cloud twisted his body. His sword drew an arc across the ground, rising in the air, and then falling down…

Boom!

A powerful surging qi appeared in front of Flowing Cloud.

Dragon Wave!

The surging qi pushed Flowing Cloud, sending him flying into a tree.

How?

Lu Hanwen was surprised. Falling Blossom Form forced a knockdown and could not be Quick Recovered, so Boundless Sea shouldn’t have had the time to cast the skill. Could it be…

The Falling Blossom Form had missed?

Lu Hanwen recalled that instant, calculating how much health Boundless Sea should have…

However, Pan Lin and Li Yibo saw it more clearly through their spectator view.

“Fuck, how despicable… he pretended to get hit. I’ve never seen that before…” The commentary criticized him.

Chapter 1450 - A Dirty Attitude

Pretending to get hit… everyone was taken aback. There were only things people couldn’t think of. There was nothing Fang Rui couldn’t do. His genius went below everyone’s bottom line.

But then again, successfully tricking someone in a pro match was not an easy task.

When an attack missed, pro players could feel it intuitively. Health loss was also not something that could be faked.

Lu Hanwen must have overlooked both of these points for Fang Rui’s trick to succeed.

Lu Hanwen had two years of experience as a main roster player. He had far more experience than most second-year rookies, yet Fang Rui dared to cheat the kid. It succeeded too, and not without reason.

Lu Hanwen had been focused on Boundless Sea’s movements. He hadn’t been paying attention to Boundless Sea’s health. It had been a tense moment, and his offense had been quick. Falling Blossom Form had extremely high priority too. Just getting grazed was enough to knock the opponent down, so the feeling of landing the hit was difficult to notice. Lu Hanwen had been trying to speed up the tempo and had indeed been a bit negligent.

These reasons showed that Fang Rui wasn’t just playing dirty for the sake of playing dirty. He was using his brain when making decisions.

The damage dealt by Dragon Wave wasn’t low. Everyone thought that given this opening, Fang Rui would have Boundless Sea run away. But to their surprise, Fang Rui had Boundless Sea follow up with another attack.

“Is Fang Rui really planning on fighting Lu Hanwen face to face?” Pan Lin cried out. No one dared to guess what Fang Rui was thinking.

Spiral Qi Rush!

Boundless Sea appeared to be ready for a fight. Qi spiraled out of his hands as his character rushed forward fiercely towards Flowing Cloud.

Flowing Cloud could use a skill like Falling Light Blade to change directions in the air, but Spiral Qi Rush had a wide AoE range. All possible paths using Falling Light Blade were blocked by it. Falling Phoenix Slash covered a longer distance, but Flowing Cloud had just used it and it was still on cooldown.

Without any moment for delay, Lu Hanwen displayed his extraordinary reaction speed. Flowing Cloud stepped on the tree behind him and raised his greatsword up.

Rising Dragon Slash!

Flowing Cloud borrowed the height of the tree to leap up instead of fall down.

Boom!

Boundless Sea’s Spiral Qi Rush crashed into the tree. Leaves fluttered down as the entire tree shook violently.

Boundless Sea had turned around. His hands were pressed together, accumulating qi. He waited until Flowing Cloud started descending after the Rising Dragon Slash before pushing his hands outward.

Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

The dense qi coming out from his two palms formed a bridge as it flew towards Flowing Cloud.

Lu Hanwen knew that after dodging Spiral Qi Rush with Rising Dragon Slash, getting back to the ground wouldn’t be so easy. As soon as he finished executing Rising Dragon Slash, Flowing Cloud swung his greatsword down.

Falling Light Blade!

In the end, Flowing Cloud used this move to rapidly descend from the sky. Fang Rui had predicted Lu Hanwen’s reaction. He moved his mouse rapidly, causing the Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow to curve downwards towards where Flowing Could would land.

But…

Flowing Cloud dropped down and disappeared.

Boom!

The giant tree struck by Spiral Qi Rush had been shaking violently when it was hit again by the Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow.

When Flowing Cloud had used Falling Light Blade, he had controlled it to position him behind the tree. Although Fang Rui had adjusted his Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, he had no way of looping the qi around the tree. Before the attack could strike Flowing Cloud, it hit the tree.

Crash!

After being struck twice, the tree swayed even more violently, the sound of rustling leaves seemed to never stop.

Fang Rui wasn’t discouraged. He had Boundless Sea step to the side, ready to catch the falling Flowing Cloud. But when he looked from this new angle, he didn’t see Flowing Cloud.

How?

Fang Rui was stunned. Flowing Cloud had landed behind the tree. How could he have disappeared? Was it magic?

The audience members were able to see it. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were praising Lu Hanwen’s cleverness.

“The Rising Dragon Slash was a set-up for the Falling Light Blade,” Li Yibo said.

“The angle of the Falling Light Blade was very precise. After hiding behind the tree, he cancelled the skill and pushed off the tree to change angles again.”

Blue Rain’s playoffs seemed to be interconnected with trees. Last round, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had lost half his health due to a tree. This round, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud used the tree to escape from Fang Rui’s follow-up. His move was clever and unexpected. Fang Rui didn’t know how he had escaped. He was carefully exploring the terrain to try and figure out the secret behind Flowing Cloud’s disappearance. When Boundless Sea took his next step, he was met with a sword! Meteor Form!

The sword came towards Fang Rui extremely fast, and he wasn’t able to react in time. Blood blossomed in the air.

“Go go go go!” The crowd cheered.

Fang Rui, the master of playing dirty, an expert at ambushes, had been ambushed by their own player. It was too exhilarating!

Fang Rui had no way of dodging the attack, but he had time to respond after getting hit . Borrowing the force of the blow, Boundless Sea slid back, but sword light was already in pursuit!

Sword Draw!

After the maxed Meteor Form, a low-level Sword Draw followed. Both these attacks were extremely fast. The two sword lights intertwined, almost as if the two attacks were a single skill.

“He’s using a greatsword too…” Li Yibo liked to remind everyone that Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud wielded a greatsword. If he was using a tachi or a lightsaber instead, just how fast would it be?

Fang Rui couldn’t dodge this follow-up either. A streak of blood flew into the air when the sword light hit. Boundless Sea stumbled backwards.

Had he lost his balance?

No!

He was faking it!

This time, the director saw through it. The moment Boundless Sea began to stumble backwards, qi had begun to circulate around his hands, which then quietly swung outwards.

Qi Blade!

He used a Qi Blade at this distance.

Lu Hanwen had been chasing after Fang Rui, when he saw the dense fog bundle together and fly towards him. He immediately rolled to the side.

Downwards Qi Flow!

The stumbling Boundless Sea suddenly jumped into the air. With his palms directed towards the ground, qi crashed towards Flowing Cloud like a waterfall.

Flowing Cloud, who was mid-roll, slashed across with his sword.

Sky-Plunging Blade!

The skill came out as Flowing Cloud stood back up.

Boom!

The turbulent qi slammed into Flowing Cloud, but at the same time, his bright sword light tore through the sky and struck Boundless Sea.

Flowing Cloud wasn’t able to stay standing after getting struck by the force of Downwards Qi Flow. On the other hand, Boundless Sea was knocked down by the Sky-Plunging Blade and rolled twice to negate the momentum.

The two characters were both injured, but after taking each other’s attacks, they stood back up and continued to fight.

“Fang Rui didn’t run, but his playstyle…” Pan Lin said.

“Playing dirty doesn’t just mean scurrying around and guerrilla warfare!” Li Yibo said.

“Yes,” Pan Lin nodded his head.

The dirty playstyle encompassed many styles. It was similar to direct fights, there were many ways of going about it. The dirty playstyle had many paths branching off from it.

Fang Rui and Lu Hanwen fought. Pretending to be hit, pretending to lose balance and then retaliating were undoubtedly extremely dirty moves.

Playing dirty wasn’t a a technique, but a mindset.

And for Fang Rui, as the representative of the style, it didn’t matter if he fought face-to-face or indirectly, all of them contained an air of dirtiness.

In this map, Lu Hanwen’s acute perception and reaction speed were effective against the usual dirty playstyle. As a result, Fang Rui fought directly against Lu Hanwen, showing off his creativity in this battle…

Pretending to fall down, pretending to be off-balance… no one knew what other surprising tricks this guy had in store.

“Fang Rui isn’t really utilizing the features of this map, making it so that Lu Hanwen’s exceptional eyesight and reaction speed aren’t as useful,” Pan Lin said.

“But by not using the terrain, Fang Rui’s capabilities are also restricted,” Li Yibo said.

“It’s evenly matched!” Pan Lin sighed.

Yes, evenly matched.

Both sides had found their own rhythm and were in their peak competitive states. Both sides were going all out, using all the tricks they had at their disposal.

The two went back and forth, trading blow after blow. The only outcome was damage dealt by both sides, with neither side gaining an advantage. When Lu Hanwen found an opportunity to attack, Fang Rui might retaliate with a weird trick. When Fang Rui tried to combo, Lu Hanwen would often neutralize it forcefully.

Under these circumstances, Fang Rui’s 74% starting health became a disadvantage that could not be erased.

In the end, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was able to win with 23% of his health left. Blue Rain had taken back a point. It was now an even 3-3.

However, of the two Blue Rain characters remaining, Flowing Cloud only had 23% of his health left, while Happy had two characters at full health.

Chapter 1451 - No Tactics

Fang Rui had barely exited the player booth when Tang Rou stood from her seat at Happy’s bench.

They had finally gotten to the playoffs stage, but Tang Rou didn’t get a chance to fight at all in the first round. She was, naturally, extremely disappointed.

She hadn’t been a member of the team competition last round, but she was the anchor for the group arena. But Happy ended the group arena with their fourth player last round. Tang Rou had been eagerly anticipating a fight that night, yet had been no more than a spectator.

Logically speaking, it would be better for Happy if Tang Rou, as the anchor, didn’t get a chance to fight. That was something Happy would be happy about.

Tang Rou naturally wasn’t hoping that Happy did badly, she just wanted to fight.

This round, Tang Rou was positioned fourth and finally got her chance. Without waiting for Fang Rui to come down, she was already charging up onto the stage.

“Little Tang is pretty much the antonym of Blue Rain’s Zheng Xuan!” Ye Xiu exclaimed.

Chen Guo paused for a moment in surprise before considering it again. That was… true.

Zheng Xuan’s lack of motivation was infamous, always ready with a “how stressful” on his tongue. As for Tang Rou? Tang Rou had the most motivation for competition. She loved a challenge and being under pressure.

“You think they’ll go up against each other?” Chen Guo was suddenly very interested in watching the two antonyms face off.

“Probably not?” Ye Xiu said.

“There’s still another player on Blue Rain’s side!” Chen Guo exclaimed.

“Huang Shaotian,” Ye Xiu reminded her.

“Oh yeah!” Chen Guo slapped a hand on her forehead. She had forgotten; Blue Rain’s Huang Shaotian hadn’t fought yet, today! She was so used to Zheng Xuan having a set spot in the 1v1 matches, but today Blue Rain decided to try something new and gave Yu Wenzhou a spot in the group arena, and thus Zheng Xuan managed to get out of playing today. As for Blue Rain’s anchor, that was definitely Huang Shaotian. He was the core and ace, after all!

Happy’s two, one heading onstage, the other coming offstage, met halfway.

“You’re eager, aren’t you?” Fang Rui grinned.

Tang Rou just smiled, not saying anything.

“That brat’s a straightforward sort of guy, just close in directly and overwhelm him!” Fang Rui said.

“Alright.” Tang Rou nodded.

“Good luck.” Fang Rui returned to Happy’s player bench after giving his blessings.

Though it was Blue Rain who had won, it was Happy’s player coming back, so the applause was restrained. The wildest applause came from the west stands. That was where the Happy fans congregated, offering thunderous applause for Happy when they came on and off stage, no matter if they won or lost. Though Blue Rain had won a round just now, the Blue Rain fans were pretty solemn due to the overall situation not being in their favour.

“Young people nowadays sure are something!” Fang Rui exclaimed, having returned to Happy’s bench. When discussing Lu Hanwen, he obviously did have the right to act the veteran.

“Did you think you could defeat him easily?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Actually, I really did think so at first. I’ve fought the brat a few times in these past two years,” Fang Rui admitted.

“He’s improving really fast, isn’t he?” Ye Xiu said.

“He has a limitless future ahead of him.” Fang Rui’s expression was uncharacteristically serious.

Chen Guo was listening in on the side, and after a good while, she turned her head to look at Fang Rui. “So you mean to say your loss was reasonable?”

“Ah, boss, you really know how to start a conversation!” Fang Rui slapped his leg excitedly.

Chen Guo rolled her eyes. She had thought it was weird that these two were suddenly feeling generous and nice enough to complement their juniors. She should’ve expected that they were just shamelessly setting up a scenario to make this loss seem reasonable! Seems like Fang Rui was rather embarrassed at losing to this second year rookie.

“Haha.” Ye Xiu laughed, sitting to the side, but afterwards, he said seriously, “Boss, I think we should keep an eye on him. He’ll become a powerful rival that Happy won’t be able to shake off for ten years.”

“Like Han Wenqing!” Chen Guo blurted out. Rivals of ten years, Chen Guo, used to seeing things with One Autumn Leaf in mind, immediately thought of Han Wenqing and his Desert Dust.

“How?” Ye Xiu didn’t agree. “I destroyed him ages ago. It’s him who can’t avoid me.”

“Hey, hold your horses! In season four, he destroyed you.” Wei Chen couldn’t help but interrupt.

“Haha, everyone who walks by the river will get their shoes wet some time,” Ye Xiu replied.

This analogy… how come it sounded no less arrogant? Chen Guo was speechless.

The reason why Happy’s players had the energy to chat was because the match had yet to start. Although Tang Rou went up early, the break between each round was set. Tang Rou had already gotten up there, but now she still had to wait.

After about half a minute, the battle between the fourth position players on each side began.

Tang Rou, having accumulated her aggression for so long, had full health. Soft Mist charged right out. Lu Hanwen, with Flowing Clouds only at 23 percent health, resolutely choose to play tactically after the match began.

“Lu Hanwen is planning on being tactical!” From Pan Lin’s tone, it was clear that this choice was rather surprising.

With what Lu Hanwen had shown so far in terms of personality and play style, he was definitely not a tactical player. Plus, as a second year rookie, could he really do tactics well?

“His opponent is Tang Rou, after all!” Li Yibo’s words cut through everyone’s doubt.

Although Lu Hanwen only had two years of experience, that was more than Tang Rou, who had only played one regular season and was in her first playoffs.

Lu Hanwen wasn’t a tactical player, but Tang Rou… wasn’t one either, no?

Hoping for a battle of wits like what Yu Wenzhou and Ye Xiu had from two brute force style players wasn’t realistic. Lu Hanwen’s tactics might not be very methodical or deep, but Tang Rou was the same. His not-so-good tactics might just be enough here. They were both at the same level, so who knew.

“Speaking of, this is Tang Rou’s first playoffs battle!” Pan Lin brought up.

“You’re right. She didn’t get a chance to play last round,” Li Yibo said.

“She doesn’t seem nervous at all! She was so impatient, coming up,” Pan Lin laughed.

“Nervous? Think about it. She’s the player who said she would 1v3, then faced all those accusations, yet could still still play normally onstage. Think of what sort of mental fortitude she has,” Li Yibo reminded the other.

“That’s true. It seems like the usual problems that newbies would face won’t be an issue here,” Pan Lin said.

“Indeed. The problems Tang Rou faced never came from the environment. They were mostly self-focused, like her grasp of rhythm, her defensive ability, etc. which we discussed in the regular season,” Li Yibo added.

“That’s right, we did discuss some of her problems in the regular season, but with each battle until now, I can see a clear improvement,” Pan Lin commented.

“Now it’s time to test these improvements,” Li Yibo said.

These two talked with a hint of pride, like it was they who had guided Tang Rou to where she stood now.

“Tang Rou has gone directly for the middle while Lu Hanwen’s decided to head to his right, and thus circling to the map’s west side.” Pan Lin focused on the match and began to commentate.

Tang Rou had charged quickly and Soft Mist soon arrived at the center of the map. She carefully looked around, but didn’t see her opponent.

“Have you yet to arrive or are you circling around?” Tang Rou asked in the chat.

As expected of someone from Happy, who spent all her time with Ye Xiu and the others. Tang Rou asked this question so reasonably and straightforwardly, as if she hadn’t considered this to be a crucial match of the playoffs. There was no reason for an opponent to give you a straight answer to that sort of question!

Lu Hanwen, that poor child, answered ever so honestly, “I’m circling around.”

“Which side?” Tang Rou asked.

The entire stadium was filled with whispering. Why did none of Happy’s member care for these courtesies? They were all wondering.

“Guess.” Lu Hanwen sent an emote with its tongue out, finally not being so honest anymore.

“Alright then, I’ll wait for you,” Tang Rou replied and then Soft Mist just stopped there, turning her head back and forth and observing her surroundings.

Lu Hanwen was, naturally, very familiar with this map. Flowing Cloud soon circled around to the central route’s west flank before starting to carefully approach, using the forestry as cover. Finally, when he peeked out from behind a tree, he found Soft Mist.

How should he strike?

Seeing Soft Mist who was turning her head back and forth, Lu Hanwen scratched his head. This really wasn’t his forte!

After thinking for about five seconds, Lu Hanwen made a decision.

He’ll ambush from behind!

He thought to himself. So, he carefully watched Soft Mist turn her head around, and when she was facing away from his direction, Flowing Cloud darted out!

“…” Pan Lin was rendered speechless for a moment. After being given a top tier dirty performance, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud charging out like that just seemed so lacking. Pan Lin was too embarrassed to call it an ambush.

“Flowing Cloud circles around to the west side and strikes!” In the end, he summarized it with that.

Offstage, Fang Rui was rolling on the ground with laughter as he gestured wildly towards Blue Rain’s other players. Over on Blue Rain’s side, Yu Wenzhou also changed the topic immediately when it was brought up. He didn’t want to talk about Lu Hanwen’s attempt at being tactical because there was nothing to talk about.

Such a simple and direct ambush from behind… those who would be caught off guard by that would only be the newest of newbies.

Tang Rou wasn’t that new anymore, and her mental fortitude was far greater than many veterans.

Lu Hanwen’s very, very simple sneak attack didn’t do anything a sneak attack was meant to.

Soft Mist immediately rolled to avoid it, and when she got up, she already had a counterattack at the ready.

Lu Hanwen’s tactics ended there.

Clang clang clang!

Their weapons slammed against one another.

Everyone immediately felt much less awkward.

This was how the juniors should be fighting! Direct and intense. Leave those sneaky, crafty tactics to those old men!

Clang clang clang!

The clash of weapons, the collision of skills. The terrain was nonexistent and the map no longer had any effect. For two players like them, just them a small space and they could turn the world upside down with their battles.

This was a battle purely of mechanics and skill.

Chapter 1452 - One Step Above

The atmosphere in the stadium livened up.

The previous rounds had reflected Blue Rain’s reasons for their map choice. There was layer upon layer of hidden intent. In the last round, Fang Rui and Lu Hanwen had fought face to face. However, everyone was wary of Fang Rui, afraid he would suddenly slip away. And when Fang Rui fought, he still played dirty. The greatest strength of playing dirty was that it not only struck at your character, but at your heart too. Lu Hanwen had won quite handily, but Blue Rain’s fans had been worried the entire time.

It was fine now.

A matchup that everyone could enjoy had finally arrived.

Spear vs sword.

The two weapons clashed and collided, immensely satisfying. Even so, Blue Rain’s fans couldn’t be entirely happy because their Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud only had 23% health left! It wasn’t suitable for him to fight head on. Blue Rain’s fans were conflicted. They wanted to watch this sort of battle, but they were worried about how it was disadvantageous for their team.

23%. Let’s hope for a miracle!

Their hearts were gripped with anxiety. They didn’t dare to look down on Tang Rou.

Her reputation had hit rock bottom as soon as her pro career began, but the Alliance still gave her the title of Best Rookie despite the controversy. It could be seen just how convincing her performance in the regular season was.

A player who won Best Rookie could not be treated like a normal rookie.

Could he do it with 23% health?

Blue Rain’s fans were so worried that they were too scared to look at Flowing Cloud’s health.

But whether they looked at it or not, his health would still fall in this unyielding battle.

47 seconds!

After Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud rushed out from behind a tree and launched a sneak attack, the battle had lasted for 47 seconds. In the end, Flowing Cloud fell.

Lu Hanwen had done his best.

He knew that with Flowing Cloud’s health, he could not trade hitpoint for hitpoint. He had done his best to avoid forced trades with Tang Rou and played more flexibly.

Nonetheless, the fight only lasted 47 seconds.

Flowing Cloud had no more health left.

Soft Mist had lost 31% of her health.

From the numbers, Soft Mist had lost more health than Flowing Cloud in this battle. It appeared as if Tang Rou hadn’t played as well as Lu Hanwen.

But wins couldn’t be looked at from statistics alone. After all, a player played differently depending on their circumstances. Lu Hanwen needed to play flexibly and focus on defending. Tang Rou could be more aggressive and forceful. It was only by utilizing an advantage that it could be called an advantage.

Lu Hanwen came down from the stage.

23% for 31%. It wasn’t an impressive trade. Blue Rain’s fans had higher expectations.

It wasn’t a bad trade though. When Lu Hanwen came down from the stage, the crowd applauded fervently.

As for Lu Hanwen himself? He was somewhat unhappy with the result. He had performed to the best of his ability though. Though he was disappointed, there weren’t any moments which he had felt upset about. It simply meant that he wasn’t good enough!

I need to continue working harder!

Lu Hanwen returned to his team with this resolution. Their last player in the group arena appeared on the big screen. To no one’s surprise, Blue Rain’s anchor was their number one player: Huang Shaotian.

The cheers from the crowd reached a peak.

He was Blue Rain’s last hope for the group arena and their ace player.

Last round…

Blue Rain’s fans didn’t want to think about what happened in the last group arena. They just hoped that Huang Shaotian could hold on to Blue Rain’s last point at this crucial moment.

Huang Shaotian went onto the stage and entered the player booth. The crowd instantly quieted down.

Everyone stared at the big screen, at the loading screen, at Troubling Rain’s spawn point shown by the holographic projection technology.

The match began.

“Where are we meeting,” Tang Rou said bluntly.

“Wait for my ambush!” Huang Shaotian replied quickly. Troubling Rain moved swiftly, taking the right road, the roundabout path on the west side. Huang Shaotian’s opening was the same as Lu Hanwen’s.

Tang Rou didn’t make any changes. Her Soft Mist went straight for the center.

Soft Mist arrived first.

As for Troubling Rain?

Huang Shaotian seemed to have copied Lu Hanwen’s pathing. He chose the same direction, the same route, and even the same ambush spot as Flowing Cloud. Then, he began observing Soft Mist.

“This… is he planning on teaching Lu Hanwen?” Pan Lin said.

“He shouldn’t be?” Li Yibo said. This was the playoffs, and Team Blue Rain was on the verge of being eliminated. No matter how important it was to teach a junior, it couldn’t be as important as the team’s playoffs run, no? Unless Huang Shaotian was truly confident that he could beat Tang Rou with ease.

But those familiar with Huang Shaotian knew that no matter how much smack he talked, he was never careless. If even a tiny opening appeared, it didn’t matter if you were a God or a rookie, he would seize it without question.

“He probably just thinks it’s a good opening play too!” Li Yibo said.

The audience members were discussing it amongst each other. Everyone thought Huang Shaotian must be trying to tell Lu Hanwen something.

The two teams, Blue Rain and Happy, were also discussing Huang Shaotian’s actions.

But before they could discuss it for too long, Huang Shaotian made a move.

Troubling Rain rushed out!

Yes, it was similar to what Lu Hanwen had done. While Tang Rou’s line of sight was turned away, he launched a very simple and very crude sneak attack from the back.

But Troubling Rain was faster!

His Silver weapon, Ice Rain, had a much higher attack speed and a much lighter weight than Flowing Cloud’s Flame Shadow. All of these factors determined Troubling Rain’s faster movements. Among these, attack speed was more important, while weight had less of an impact.

How would Tang Rou respond?

She responded the same way to the same attack. Although she was surprised that Huang Shaotian would actually copy Lu Hanwen’s opening, it didn’t affect how fast she reacted to it.

Soft Mist rolled. The moment she got up, her spear slashed upwards in a counterattack.

Pu!

A streak of blood flew into the air. Troubling Rain’s Silver weapon, Ice Rain, struck the rolling Soft Mist.

The sword didn’t pause. Without any extra movements or any wasted inputs, the second slash came…

Pu pu pu pu…

Sword light danced as sword and body collided. As Soft Mist rolled, four attacks had hit her, a mix of skills and normal attacks.

Tang Rou’s counterattack was completely sealed and didn’t come out. After the four attacks, Tang Rou saw a slight opening.

Dragon Tooth!

Soft Mist stabbed towards Troubling Rain with her spear.

But Troubling Rain sidestepped it and attacked in retaliation.

Downwind Sword Slash!

His sword slid across Soft Mist’s spear. The viewers could even heard the whistle from Ice Rain and Dancing Fire Flowing Flame.

The sword light split into two. This Downwind Sword Slash had stopped Dragon Tooth mid-attack. If Tang Rou continued with the attack, she would miss. Cancelling her attack would require an input which would give her too little time to dodge.

The threat of Downwind Sword Slash was frightening. As the sword light flew her way, Soft Mist rolled backwards.

Everyone was dumbstruck.

It was the same attack, but when Lu Hanwen and Tang Rou fought, it had been even. On the other hand, Huang Shaotian immediately suppressed Tang Rou.

What was Huang Shaotian trying to tell Lu Hanwen?

Can’t tell!

It looked as if Huang Shaotian was slapping Lu Hanwen in the face: look, I can do what you can’t.

As for how he did it…

“He’s faster!” This was Pan Lin’s understanding of it.

“Openings. It’s all about finding openings,” Li Yibo emphasized.

“Despite being in a similar situation, Huang Shaotian’s timing was far better than Lu Hanwen’s. That Downwind Sword Slash was the same. Huang Shaotian could have directly followed with this attack previously, but that would have given Tang Rou some space to dodge it. He intentionally created an opening for Tang Rou to take, but he had been waiting for her to attack. Tang Rou was unable to do anything in response. It was a beautiful play.”

“So he really is different…” After Li Yibo’s analysis, Pan Lin sighed. Both Lu Hanwen and Huang Shaotian were Blade Masters, but Huang Shaotian was clearly on a higher level.

After Downwind Sword Slash, Huang Shaotian continued his offense. After a few more exchanges, he no longer seemed as dominant.

“Tang Rou is not bad at defending,” Li Yibo said.

“That’s a huge improvement!” Pan Lin smiled. During the regular season, the two had commented on Tang Rou’s view on defending. Tang Rou followed the belief that offense was the best defense. This belief had its justifications, but these were justifications. The saying never indicated that defense was not important.

Tang Rou’s defense wasn’t bad. Despite Huang Shaotian taking the initiative with his sneak attack, she was defending to limit her opponent’s attack options.

As a result, Huang Shaotian was very generous and promptly gave another opening.

An excellent opening for Tang Rou to counterattack.

Chapter 1453 - Opening

“Chance!” Pan Lin shouted. But as soon as he called it out, he wondered… was this really an opportunity?

The experienced players, who were familiar with Huang Shaotian, like Ye Xiu saw through it immediately.

The cake was a lie! It was a cake filled with poison. If Tang Rou tried to seize this opportunity, Huang Shaotian would most likely retaliate fiercely after just one move. If you saw through it and didn’t take the opportunity, what then? This opening would give Huang Shaotian an opportunity to make adjustments. His previous assault had reached a certain point and then stopped. He left this opening at the perfect time. Whether the opponent attacked or not, Huang Shaotian could re-establish his attack tempo. The advantages were all his.

Amazing!

Everyone sighed inwardly.

Opportunists couldn’t only be good at finding opportunities, creating opportunities was just as important. Huang Shaotian had given away this opening at the perfect time. If he had given away this opening a bit earlier or a bit later, the outcome would not have been as perfect.

If I saw this opening, what would I have done?

The pro players who saw the opening asked themselves this question. As for Tang Rou? She didn’t have time to think so much. Combat was all about timing, and opportunities didn’t last forever.

Counterattack!

For Tang Rou, this bait was too enticing. The moment the opening appeared, she instinctively took action.

Soft Mist turned her wrists. Her actions immediately caught Huang Shaotian’s attention. Tang Rou moved exactly how he predicted she would. This girl’s style was always so intense. Everyone had a clear understanding of it.

Come!

Huang Shaotian had been ready. Troubling Rain also turned his wrists slightly.

But Soft Mist’s turn of the wrist became more and more rapid. It was as if she were squeezing out all the energy she could muster. The spear in her hands seemed to want to fly out of her hands.

This is…

Huang Shaotian suddenly frowned.

He had predicted that Tang Rou would immediately seize the opening and attack, but he didn’t expect her to counterattack so fiercely!

“Beautiful!” Ye Xiu praised from below the stage. Huang Shaotian giving away the opening and Tang Rou seizing it took only an instant. When Ye Xiu said these words, it was hard to tell if he was praising Huang Shaotian or Soft Mist.

Soft Mist rushed out.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

An opening suddenly appeared at such a close distance. A Dragon Tooth would perhaps be the fastest way to seize it. A Falling Flower Palm would give her more momentum. A Tyrant’s Destruction wouldn’t have been a bad choice either.

But… Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Tang Rou unexpectedly used such a high-level skill. No matter how much she liked this move, it didn’t seem logical. High-level skills required more inputs than low-level skills. As a result, high-level skills were almost always preceded by low-level skills as set-ups to ensure the high-level skill would hit. But Tang Rou used a high-level skill to seize such a tiny opening. This was a form of confidence. She wasn’t worried that her hand speed wouldn’t be enough to complete all the inputs in this short window.

And in the end, she completed it.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Dancing Fire Flowing Flame flew out along with Soft Mist, its surging momentum stirring up the surrounding fog.

Dodge!

Huang Shaotian was in a fluster facing this attack.

The hitbox of Dragon Breaks the Ranks wasn’t just the tip of the spear. The powerful force of the strike tore through the air like whirlwinds. These whirling air currents brought along the destructiveness of the strike, turning the attack into an AoE skill.

And in this map, the whirling air currents could clearly be seen because of the fog. The fog was pierced through and blown away.

Shua!

A sword light flashed out, not towards Soft Mist, but to the side.

Triple Slash.

To dodge this Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Huang Shaotian immediately used a skill. Triple Slash was his fastest movement skill. However, the powerful air currents from Dragon Breaks the Ranks made Troubling Rain lose his balance. Huang Shaotian’s control over his character was valiant though. He stabilized himself with the second attack of Triple Slash, but with the second part burned, it was too late to chase after Soft Mist with the third. The movement from Dragon Breaks the Ranks was fast and powerful!

“Ah!” Ye Xiu felt that it was a pity.

“What’s wrong?” Chen Guo asked.

“So close! She almost had him. If she had adjusted it according to the Triple Slash, it would have hit,” Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo stared blankly.

Could a human even do that? Ye Xiu’s criticism was too nitpicky.

“Aren’t you asking for too much?” Wei Chen also thought the same.

“Little Tang wouldn’t care,” Ye Xiu said.

“Okay…”

Everyone could only acknowledge this point helplessly.

“Could you even do it?” Chen Guo suddenly asked.

“I’d try it,” Ye Xiu replied. Even he wasn’t 100% confident either. The window had truly been too short.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks didn’t hit Troubling Rain, but Huang Shaotian’s motive for giving away the opening was ruined by Tang Rou’s boldness.

Was it a coincidence? Or had she seen through it?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo were discussing this issue, but the answer didn’t really matter. Huang Shaotian didn’t care either and typed out a message: “How brave!”

“Doing the same thing twice? Don’t you think that’s a bit much?” Tang Rou replied.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo stopped their discussion.

Tang Rou’s reply said everything.

“Haha, was it too obvious?”

“It looks like I underestimated you.”

“I’ll take it more seriously next!”

“Watch my sword!”

Shua shua shua, four messages came out in the chat. Huang Shaotian had begun his chat spam. But when he shouted “Watch my sword!”, it was Soft Mist’s Dancing Fire Flowing Flame that flying at him.

Tang Rou was truly a representative of someone who took action. How could she stop to appreciate Huang Shaotian’s trash talk? The moment she gave her reply, Soft Mist had already turned around. When Huang Shaotian typed out his four messages, her Soft Mist had started to attack.

Tu tu tu tu.

Four consecutive strikes.

Dragon Tooth, a normal attack, and then a Double Stab. Four strikes at four different positions, all of which were dodged by Troubling Rain.

Huang Shaotian was the first God besides Ye Xiu that Tang Rou had ever met online and offline. At that time, Tang Rou didn’t have much of a concept of the pro scene, and she had still been a beginner. She only knew that the player, Flowing Tree, who she was dungeoning with, was an expert. But she didn’t really know how skilled he truly was. She only remembered that he and Steamed Bun just kept talking and talking, so her initial impression of Huang Shaotian was on the same level as Steamed Bun.

Now, Tang Rou understood clearly just how skilled Huang Shaotian was.

In this 1v1 match so far, her Soft Mist had yet to create a Chaser. Huang Shaotian had always dodged her attacks and never blocked them.

By not blocking them, he wasn’t giving her an opportunity to create Chasers. It sounded very logical. But who could actually completely avoid blocking in practice?

Tang Rou experienced it for herself.

“What’s wrong? Do you feel like you’re missing something?” Huang Shaotian wouldn’t stop talking. He kept typing as he fought.

“Something super important to Battle Mages!”

“Chasers, the answer is Chasers!.”

“You’re a Battle Mage! But where are your Magic Chasers?”

Huang Shaotian kept talking as he played. If you just looked at the actual content of his words, it was difficult to summarize them. He just said whatever came to his mind. There wasn’t any point to it. Sometimes, it sounded like he was making fun of you. Sometimes, he wasn’t. Sometimes, he just sounded like an idiot…

His cocky tone of voice was absolutely loathsome, but he was stating facts. The ridicule wasn’t small.

“So what?” Tang Rou simply replied.

So what?

Yeah! So what?

A Battle Mage without Chasers could still battle, no? Huang Shaotian’s taunting didn’t bother Tang Rou. Her attacks only became more intense.

“You’re so unwavering! How rare!” Huang Shaotian said. He was also unwavering in his trash talk. It was hard to discourage him in this area.

Tang Rou ignored him. She simply continued to attack.

Huang Shaotian continued to go at his own pace. Block? He didn’t completely avoid it. But Battle Mages could only produce Chasers with certain skills, and he always made sure to dodge these skills. He continued to use this method to restrict Soft Mist’s full combat ability. At the same time, he carefully observed Soft Mist’s offense, constantly harrassing, searching for opportunities to establish his offense.

“Coach Li, don’t you feel that Huang Shaotian is playing rather cautiously and conservatively?” Pan Lin said.

“Of course! Just winning isn’t enough. He still has another opponent to beat afterwards!” Li Yibo said.

“Happy’s Tang Rou is an aggressive player. Huang Shaotian retreating is exactly what she wants him to do,” Pan Lin said.

“This… let’s see how it turn outs…” Li Yibo seemed to have his own thoughts.

Chapter 1454 - Annoying

“Tang Rou’s rhythm isn’t good…” After careful observation and thought, Li Yibo finally concluded.

“Oh?”

“Too rushed. It’s a bit out of control,” Li Yibo said.

“This… it’s not anything too surprising,” Pan Lin sighed.

When they talked about Tang Rou, losing control of her rhythm was a point that frequently came up.

For many rookies, the issue was usually because they lacked confidence. They played scared and over cautious, unable to bring out their full potential.

But Tang Rou? She attacked aggressively and fearlessly. Scared? Not at all. No confidence? Also not an issue. Her problems weren’t playing scared or playing too careful, but rather playing too aggressive.

Playing too aggressively didn’t result in her being unable to bring out her full potential. Instead, it pushed her to try for impossible goals, which led to numerous problems.

“It looks like Tang Rou doesn’t have a good solution to this problem!” Pan Lin sighed.

“You can’t really say that,” Li Yibo said, “She actually pays quite a bit of attention to this problem of hers, but Huang Shaotian unwittingly forced her into this trap.”

“Oh?”

“Huang Shaotian is extremely good at controlling the tempo. He’s making Tang Rou feel like if she tries just a bit harder, she’ll be able to break through. But when she ups the tempo by just a little bit, she discovers that it’s still not quite enough. Huang Shaotian has been slowly increasing the tempo to a speed that Tang Rou isn’t able to handle,” Li Yibo said.

Shua shua shua!

Three sword lights, three strikes.

Opening!

Tang Rou finally let out an opening. She had good hand speed. Her awareness, decision-making, and reaction speed weren’t bad either. But in this fast-pace battle, her awareness and her decision-making weren’t enough to ensure she made no mistakes. She didn’t have the experience that Ye Xiu and the others did. Her intuition and instinctive reactions weren’t always the most optimal.

An opening appeared, and Huang Shaotian wasn’t going to let it pass. The cautious Troubling Rain instantly launched a powerful counterattack.

Three streaks of blood flew into the air.

Troubling Rain attacked fast and finished fast. It wasn’t the start of a shift in position. He simply used the opening to deal as much damage as possible to Soft Mist during the short window of time. Tang Rou’s playstyle was forceful, and she quickly found her footing again. Huang Shaotian simply took a step back and let Tang Rou have it.

“This…” Pan Lin didn’t understand, “Huang Shaotian’s counterattack was so short! Was the opening not enough for him to establish an offensive play?”

“He could have, but because his opponent is Tang Rou, he decided to retreat,” Li Yibo said.

“Why?”

“Because Tang Rou is an extremely aggressive player. If Huang Shaotian wants to attack, he can’t avoid forced trades. If this were a normal 1v1, he would have no fear of doing so. But Happy still has another player, so Huang Shaotian wants to minimize the amount of damage taken and go into the next match with as much health as possible.”

“Oh,” Pan Lin understood. This logic was easy to understand. Huang Shaotian chose to play differently because of the situation.

He calmly controlled the pace and carefully observed his opponent. He carefully dodged or blocked her attacks and whenever the slightest of openings appeared, he would mercilessly strike it and deal damage to Soft Mist. He was never persistent. After a few attacks, he would go back to being careful and wait for the next opportunity to appear.

“Huang Shaotian is teaching Tang Rou an important lesson! His meticulous control over the pace of the battle is absolutely brilliant, ” Huang Shaotian sighed.

“But why does it seem like… Tang Rou is speeding up?” Pan Lin questioned.

Li Yibo immediately checked. Soft Mist’s attacks were becoming increasingly fierce.

“This is… if she isn’t able to realize her problems, how can she improve!” Li Yibo grieved, feeling disappointed in her.

How stubborn!

Many of the audience members felt the same way.

Tang Rou winning Best Rookie didn’t help win her much public favor, instead it only increased the hate towards her. Watching her hit a wall was something many people liked to see.

A difference in attitude gave off different opinions.

From a positive point of view, Tang Rou recklessly speeding up was a show of unwavering determination and bravery. From a negative point of view, she was stupidly stubborn; she wouldn’t shed a tear until she saw the coffin.

Go die!

Most people were the latter. They wanted to see Tang Rou fail and feel shame for her loss.

But she kept on speeding up, using 100% of her abilities. However, she kept trying to push her limits, using 101%, 102%, 103% of what she had.

What is this girl thinking?

Huang Shaotian didn’t understand.

Huang Shaotian didn’t think she was that ignorant. He didn’t think that she didn’t know her limits. He didn’t think that she didn’t know she was leaving all these openings in order to increase her tempo.

As for himself?

He was Glory’s number one opportunist. You’re going to give me all these openings. What’s the meaning of this?

Huang Shaotian wondered, but he didn’t relent. If a suitable opportunity appeared, Troubling Rain would take action. In order to seize these opportunities, he had no choice but to increase the tempo to match her.

Is that her aim?

Does she want to wear me down?

If that’s your plan, then you’re too naive!

I’m far more experienced than you. My judgement is more precise than yours. Just you alone won’t be enough to reach a tempo that I can’t control! Before that happens, you’ll be the one to fall! Look, another opening.

Bladestorm!

A storm of blades swept over, a whirl of blue sword light that rushed towards Soft Mist. Suddenly, amidst this dense sea of blue light, red flames burst out.

Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike?

Soft Mist had let out an opening, but she still attacked, abandoning any plans to defend. The Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike collided with Troubling Rain’s Bladestorm. The attack was meant to cover a fan-like range, but Tang Rou condensed it into a small area, focusing its destructive power.

Bang bang bang bang….

Blue and red light clashed, but some of them still went through. Tang Rou didn’t retreat, and it was too late for Huang Shaotian to cancel it. Rather than be the only one to get hit, it was obviously better to make a trade.

Pu pu pu pu…

Both sides were hurt. Blood splattered as the opposing lights clashed and burst forth.

In the end, Huang Shaotian was the one who won the trade, dealing more damage to Tang Rou than she did to him. However, Huang Shaotian couldn’t be happy about it. His goal was to minimize the damage he took. This trade was completely outside of his expectations.

Tang Rou’s offense didn’t stop. After the Hundred Dragon Meteor Strike, her spear continued to strike at Troubling Rain.

Huang Shaotian’s calmness wasn’t shaken by this unexpected exchange.

She’s still speeding up?

He could feel a change in Tang Rou’s tempo. After giving up on defending, she focused all of her effort into attacking.

As a result, more openings appeared so much so that Huang Shaotian wasn’t actually sure which openings to seize because there were simply too many good ones.

It didn’t matter though.

Just one opening was enough. If there were this many good openings laid out, then it didn’t matter which one he took.

Completely reckless. Tang Rou had thrown caution out the window in front of Huang Shaotian. Facing this opportunist, there was no difference between one opening and one hundred openings. Tang Rou didn’t care if she gave away any openings. She continued to speed up the tempo.

Troubling Rain’s sword was about to hit Soft Mist, but facing this reckless offensive, he couldn’t avoid taking damage as well.

Huang Shaotian had the upper hand, but it was again at the sacrifice of his original goal.

Huang Shaotian had no doubt that someone who let out a hundred openings would never beat him. But at what price?

Shit!

Huang Shaotian realized it.

At the beginning, he had been baiting Tang Rou to increase the tempo. Huang Shaotian was very pleased, seeing her fall for it.

But just when he thought that a good tempo had been achieved, Tang Rou didn’t stop. She raised it even higher. And Huang Shaotian had no choice but to keep up with her.

Huang Shaotian hadn’t thought this reckless move would cause him any trouble.

But later, he realized that while Tang Rou left even more openings, she traded it for a more powerful offensive. All of her energy was being put into attacking.

A threat?

Everyone laughed. With so many openings, how could this sort of offensive be a threat?

But Huang Shaotian knew that it was trouble.

He would have no trouble beating Tang Rou.

But the trouble was what came after when he needed to face Happy’s next player.

Tang Rou wasn’t playing to win this 1v1, but rather for Happy’s next player to win.

The damage she could deal couldn’t compare to the damage that Huang Shaotian could deal by taking advantage of her openings. However, she gave Huang Shaotian no choice but to take damage as well.

She wouldn’t beat Huang Shaotian, but she ruined Huang Shaotian’s goal.

The moment that Soft Mist fell, she told everyone her intentions.

“I might lose, but Happy definitely won’t!”

Chapter 1455 - Shut Out

63%.

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had 63% left. Tang Rou’s Soft Mist had traded 69% of her health for 37% of Troubling Rain’s.

It was not an equal trade, but if the fight had followed the pace that Huang Shaotian had set, the trade may have been even worse. In the end, Tang Rou had used her usual style to break through Huang Shaotian’s control.

Tang Rou was the same Tang Rou, strong-minded and refusing to back down.

You want me to increase the tempo? Okay, I’ll do that.

You don’t want me to increase the tempo anymore? Sorry, I’m going to keep doing it.

Rude and stubborn without reason.

From the day Tang Rou stepped into the pro scene, that was her playstyle. Countless people hoped to see her fall, but she never did. She continued to do what she did throughout the entire season. Facing Huang Shaotian, although she lost, she had achieved the outcome she wanted.

Even so, did that mean Happy would definitely win?

Many people questioned Tang Rou’s final words.

Troubling Rain had a little more than half his health left. Huang Shaotian just might be able to win under these condtions.

More importantly, who would Happy send out next?

Su Mucheng? Qiao Yifan? Bao Rongxing (Steamed Bun)? Wei Chen?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo quickly did an overview of Happy’s remaining players.

Su Mucheng seemed to be the most reliable of the four choices. But the problem was that this map was unfavorable for Launchers. Launchers could not display their ultra-long-range advantage.

“If Happy knew that Blue Rain would choose this sort of map, then they definitely would not have put her in the group arena,” Li Yibo said. He implied that he favoured having Su Mucheng as Happy’s anchor. It would indeed be Happy’s most stable arrangement. Unfortunately, the map chosen by Blue Rain erased this stability.

“This is probably one of the reasons Blue Rain chose this map: to make Su Mucheng useless!” Li Yibo said.

Who would it be?

The crowd members and the viewers at home were waiting nervously. It was as if whoever was chosen would dictate the winner of the group arena.

Under everyone’s gaze, someone stood up from Happy’s player seat and headed towards the stage. Her long hair fluttered in the wind.

The Blue Rain fans were wild with joy. For the Happy fans, it was as if a bucket of cold ice had been splashed onto their heads.

Su Mucheng.

In the end, it was Su Mucheng.

The crowd immediately started livening up. Blue Rain’s fans had been on the backfoot the entire time, but at this moment, they could see the dawn of victory.

“So Happy really did pick Su Mucheng!” Pan Lin sounded somewhat gloomy.

“Yeah,” Li Yibo sighed.

The map chosen today by Blue Rain had troubled Happy again and again. Happy had passed through each test, finding themselves in the lead at the final step. However, they were now met with one last obstacle in their path.

Launchers.

Launchers had an attack range of 40 units. The map itself didn’t change the Launcher’s attack range. However, visibility was limited to 20-25 units, thus, having an extremely long range was pointless.

20-25 unit attacks was still quite a distance. However, for Launchers, it was still too close. Launchers had strong AoE and high damage attacks, but their attack speed was very slow. At too close of a distance, before the attack went off, it was very possible that the attack would be interrupted. What’s worse was that her opponent was the opportunist king, Huang Shaotian.

Thinking of all these points, Blue Rain’s fans felt like victory was already theirs. The depression from the previous rounds had been swept away.

“We didn’t know that Happy’s final player was Su Mucheng, but Tang Rou should have! Was it not the right move to entrust the win to Su Mucheng on this map?” Pan Lin said.

“What else could she do?” Li Yibo said, “If she could beat Huang Shaotian, do you think she wouldn’t try? It was exactly because she couldn’t see herself winning that she went through with such a strategy. This map is unfavorable for Su Mucheng, but Su Mucheng is still a pro player. I’m sure Tang Rou’s confidence in her will act as motivation, not pressure.”

“I hope so!” Pan Lin replied.

At this moment, the two female players on Happy, one coming down from the stage, the other heading towards the stage, met midway.

Pa!

The two girls didn’t say anything. When they passed by each other, they gave a high-five as if handing off the torch from one player to another. Neither of them turned back as they continued forward.

Tang Rou went back to her seat.

Su Mucheng went into the player booth.

Chen Guo was extremely worried. Her concern for Su Mucheng was extraordinarily abnormal. She was concerned for her as a friend and as an idol that she worshipped.

“Hey!” She yelled at Ye Xiu.

“Hm?” Ye Xiu turned his head.

“How will it turn out?” Chen Guo said.

Ye Xiu understood what she meant. His expression wasn’t too carefree either: “This map isn’t good for Launchers.”

“Then what can she do?” Chen Guo said.

“Even if it’s not easy to play, she’s still got to do it,” Ye Xiu said.

“Stupid,” Chen Guo rolled her eyes. It might sound stupid, but it was the truth. There were countless times where the matchup was bad or the fight seemed unwinnable, but giving up and getting discouraged was never the solution.

She’ll win!

Chen Guo could only tell herself this. The match began.

“Ah, how unfortunate, to think you’d have to play on this map,” Huang Shaotian started chattering. He chatted, but he also hoped for the other person to talk back. When facing players like Mo Fan, Huang Shaotian felt discouraged at times when he typed madly. As a result, he usually got excited when he met a player he was familiar with because it meant an actual conversation. It wouldn’t be just him talking!

But he immediately started by poking at Su Mucheng’s weak point and didn’t get a reply back.

“Why aren’t you talking? Too much pressure? Hahaha,” Huang Shaotian continued.

“Where are you going to go? With a visibility of 20-25 units, are you going to the left or the right?” Huang Shaotian guessed.

“But I don’t think you’ll be that naive. With only 20-25 units to work with, will you be able to set up a firing line?”

“If you can’t, then I’m sure you know that closing this distance will be too easy for me.”

Huang Shaotian chattered on and on. As for the firing line, everyone knew that the closer the distance, the harder it was to set one up. Launchers had slow attacks, so they needed distance. At 20-25 units away, her attacks would need to be extremely accurate. Only by hitting the opponent would she be able to maintain a safe distance.

But against Huang Shaotian, no one dared to say that they would never miss.

Huang Shaotian was also confident.

Last round, Tang Rou had taken out 37% of Troubling Rain’s health, which was outside of Huang Shaotian’s expectations. He was feeling a bad premonition.

No one could say that they could win 100% of the time, let alone when he wasn’t coming in with 100% of his health. Huang Shaotian felt a bit uneasy about this last round. But he did feel a lot better after seeing that his opponent was Su Mucheng.

Li Yibo’s analysis wasn’t wrong. One of the reasons for choosing this map was to shut out Su Mucheng. Su Mucheng had plenty of experience and her skill was first-class. Her character Dancing Rain was quite powerful too. Compared to Happy’s rookies, she was a much more reliable choice. Happy didn’t know what map Blue Rain chose, so it had been very likely that Happy would choose Su Mucheng.

Su Mucheng really did come out and in the final deciding round too. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain may only have 63% of his health left, but everyone thought that he had a higher chance of winning. He had no qualms about using his map advantage to bully Su Mucheng either. Troubling Rain didn’t take a roundabout route and took the central path. As he made his way to the center while chatting, Troubling Rain and Dancing Rain met.

“You!”

Huang Shaotian was surprised. The viewers had noticed it, but he found out now. At this rate, it would be a face to face fight, and because of this map, Launchers would lose their long-range advantage.

23 units.

The two found each other at this distance. Under normal circumstances, Launchers would feel that the distance was too close and would need to pull away. But in this map, Su Mucheng could only take the fight at this distance.

Huang Shaotian was somewhat startled, but he didn’t think much of it.

The purpose of the map was to shut out Su Mucheng. It could be seen that they had come prepared against Su Mucheng. They didn’t underestimate her just because the map was unfavorable for her. Under these limitations, how would she fight? They had studied this question too. At 23 units apart, Huang Shaotian didn’t think Su Mucheng could give him any trouble. On the other hand, this distance would make her feel uncomfortable.

Launchers feared close combat. The heavy armor and cannon slowed down her movements, plus she didn’t have close combat skills like Sharpshooters did. If the Launcher was closed in on, then the Launcher needed to run.

“Watch my sword!” Huang Shaotian typed. After finding Dancing Rain, Troubling Rain rushed at her. A trace of blue was left in the dense fog wherever the sword swung. The sword light was like a storm as it swept towards Dancing Rain.

Boom boom boom!

Three missiles flew out.

Anti-Tank Missiles. This low-level skill was quite fast. But against Huang Shaotian, how could a few missiles stop him?

Blue light flickered amidst the fog. Troubling Rain turned slightly, avoiding the missiles. He didn’t slow down as he continued forward.

As for Dancing Rain, she used the recoil from the Anti-Tank Missiles to fly backwards. She needed to keep her distance no matter what.

“Can you run?” Huang Shaotian messaged. Suddenly, an explosion sounded from up above.

Chapter 1456 - What Type of Player Is She?

This is!

Huang Shaotian looked up. A Heat-Seeking Missile pierced through the fog from above.

How?

The Heat-Seeking Missile had come, but where was the heat source?

Everyone looked at the scene and fell silent.

Where was the heat source? From their omniscient view, it was clear as day. The heat source was next to Dancing Rain. The surface of the forest wasn’t flat. Dancing Signal had placed the signal in a small pit in the ground behind her. This skill had activated before the Anti-Tank Missiles. When Dancing Rain used the recoil from Anti-Tank Missiles to fly backwards, the signal couldn’t be seen from Huang Shaotian’s point of view.

Boom!

A small mushroom cloud bloomed in the forest. Compared to the thick smoke, the forest fog seemed thin and dreadful.

Huang Shaotian had Troubling Rain run as soon as he heard the explosion. But the missile moved faster than he could. He had noticed the Heat-Seeking Missile too late, and it was no longer possible for him to dodge it. Troubling Rain only had time to take a single step before the missile landed in the pit near Troubling Rain. The rumbling mushroom cloud sent Troubling Rain into the air.

6%!

Troubling Rain’s health instantly dropped by 6%.

Launchers had terrifying firepower. And this had been after Huang Shaotian had Troubling Rain move away from the core of the explosion. If the full impact of the missile had hit him, he would have certainly lost more than 6%.

Even so, just this 6% made Huang Shaotian’s heart ache. Troubling Rain had only started with 63% to begin with. He now only had 57%.

“Dirty! When did you become so dirty!!” Huang Shaotian vented! Before Troubling Rain even landed back onto the ground, he sent a complaint to Su Mucheng.

Bang!

His reply was another explosion from above.

Stinger!

The viewers had noticed it before Huang Shaotian. Dancing Rain hadn’t retreated too far using the Anti-Tank Missiles. Seeing the Heat-Seeking Missile hit, Su Mucheng wasn’t going to let this opportunity pass.

The Stinger borrowed the smoke and dust as cover until it reached just above Troubling Rain’s head. As Troubling Rain fell, the Stinger split apart in the air. Countless stinger missiles descended, surrounding Troubling Rain.

“I already knew!”

A message leapt out. Troubling Rain swung his Ice Rain, and his character shifted horizontally.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh…

The stinger missiles brushed past Troubling Rain.

Boom boom boom boom…

The stingers exploded but only acted as a backdrop for Troubling Rain. Under the light reflecting from the explosions, Troubling Rain walked towards Dancing Rain.

Was Huang Shaotian intentionally slowing down the pace to make it more dramatic? Of course not. After noticing Su Mucheng’s craftiness, he didn’t dare rush forward too hastily. He slowed the pace to more carefully observe his surroundings.

I have the advantage! Huang Shaotian was confident on this point. He stared at Dancing Rain’s weapon and saw a bright sparkle suddenly light up like a star.

Laser Beam!

The speed of light was incomparable, but Huang Shaotian had reacted before the attack came out. Troubling Rain started making irregular movements, swaying left and right as if he were drunk*.

BIU. A Laser Beam tore through the air. Su Mucheng had tried to predict where he would move, but Huang Shaotian was swaying left and right without any logic behind his movements. Su Mucheng could only gamble and see whether she could get lucky enough to hit Huang Shaotian.

Unfortunately, the laser brushed past him and missed.

Seven steps!

The distance between Troubling Rain and Dancing Rain was even steps, a distance that a Launcher needed to retreat from.

Boom!

A missile was fired. It was only a normal attack.

The attack was secondary. Su Mucheng was simply retreating with Aerial Cannon.

Was it enough at seven steps away?

Many couldn’t help but feel worried. Troubling Rain dashed through the explosion from the artillery shell.

Triple Slash!

Huang Shaotian didn’t dodge and instead used Triple Slash. The first slash cut apart the missile. Although his character would take some damage, Huang Shaotian clearly didn’t care about it. He needed to stick close to her and establish his offensive tempo. The instant Su Mucheng chose to retreat, he launched his assault.

All caution flew out the window. He was like a red-eyed gambler who would throw everything he had regardless of anything else.

This was his style. When an opportunity came, he wouldn’t hesitate or hold back. He would do all that he could do to strike at his target.

When it rains, it pours!

Sword light!

With a flicker, he reached Dancing Rain. Troubling Rain’s approach was faster than Dancing Rain’s retreat.

Because he had actually used Triple Slash before Dancing Rain started to retreat. He had calculated the moment that Su Mucheng would have no choice but to run and use Aerial Cannon to do so. Triple Slash had been executed before that missile had been fired. This tiny difference helped Huang Shaotian win this decisive opportunity. He Triple Slashed through the missile directly towards Dancing Rain. Moving with Aerial Cannon was faster than moving along the ground, but there was a flaw. The movement speed wasn’t balanced, going from slow to fast, slow to fast. Triple Slash had closed the distance during the slower portion of Aerial Cannon movement.

But just when the third slash of Triple Slash was used, the final angle wasn’t enough to strike Dancing Rain.

I need another attack!

The attack would need to be fast because Dancing Rain would reach her fastest speed soon, which would pull apart the distance between them. The opportunity to attack would only last an instant.

Opportunity! Instant!

These words always made Huang Shaotian’s blood boil. He loved this feeling.

Fast, he needed to be fast.

Meteor Form!

The Level 75 skill was the fastest Blade Master skill in their kit. The sword carried the user, and the user pushed the sword. A flash of blue light cut through the fog like a meteor.

Pu! The sound could barely be heard as if there was no time for the sound to resound.

Blood wrapped around the trace of blue light as if a long wound had been drawn across the sky.

Swift and accurate!

Dancing Rain spun in the air from the sword’s momentum.

Troubling Rain turned around, ready to follow up. But the instant he turned, he saw Dancing Rain’s weapon in front of him.

Opportunity! Instant!

The same key words, but this time for Su Mucheng. The Meteor Form had knocked her spinning in the air, could she hit him?

Boom!

During her first spin around, Su Mucheng attacked.

The first rotation was the fastest, but also the moment when Huang Shaotian would be most off guard.

Huang Shaotian saw the cannon flash and shoot out a missile at extremely close range. Launcher attacks had strong knockback, forcefully taking the powerful attack was not a good idea. It would destroy his tempo. Huang Shaotian did not take the blow. Having started with less health than her, he chose not to force his way through.

Dodge, he could only dodge.

Huang Shaotian felt that it was a pity, but he maintained his cool. He dared to take risks, but he still knew how to be patient. He only took risks that he could afford to take. And right now, taking the risk would reap him no benefit, so he waited.

Move to the side!

Huang Shaotian had Troubling Rain dodge to the side, but soon afterwards, he felt his heart tighten.

Dancing Rain had used Anti-Tank Missiles. Given her situation, accurately hitting a target from her position was already very difficult, yet the Anti-Tank Missiles fired were even lined up in a formation!

By using the spin from Meteor Form, the three Anti-Tank Missiles were lined up in a row, left, middle, and right, blocking off all of Troublin Rain’s escape options.

Boom!

Troubling Rain was engulfed in a fiery explosion. Huang Shaotian instinctively dodged, not thinking that Su Mucheng could utilize the spin from Meteor Form. By the time he realized it, it was too late.

“Amazing!” Pan Lin sighed.

On the other hand, Li Yibo was dumbfounded.

It had taken him quite a while to figure out how the Anti-Tank Missiles had hit. If the previous Heat-Seeking Missile was a dirty play exploiting the terrain, then this attack was a display of sharp precision and control.

Su Mucheng…

How should she be evaluated?

When she joined the Alliance, she had joined the number one team and stood as the partner of the number one player in Glory. No one started higher than she did.

But afterwards, their team never took home another championship trophy.

Because of her beauty, she always remained a popular player. But because of her beauty, there was always controversy surrounding her.

For a lot of players, if they were surrounded by so much controversy, they would probably want to prove themselves as soon as possible, no?

But she never did. She continued to play as a supporting character in Excellent Era. She was never impatient to make any stunning plays.

Was Su Mucheng reliable or not?

It was difficult to give a clear answer.

You could say she wasn’t reliable, but she always performed solidly.

You could say she was reliable, but it always felt like she was lacking something.

Everything about her seemed to be consistent but never outstanding. When she played, what are her thoughts? Li Yibo was suddenly very curious.

Chapter 1457 - An Aggressive Su Mucheng

Li Yibo had time to think about things carefully, but the players on stage did not.

Su Mucheng’s brilliant technical display led to a successful strike against Troubling Rain, whose body hung suspended in the air due to the explosion from the Anti-Tank Missiles. The recoil from these Anti-Tank Missiles also shifted the tumbling Dancing Rain to the side. Even so, she wasn’t going to let this opportunity go.

Boom!

Another missile flew into the air. Dancing Rain was still spinning, making it look like she had thrown it out. Even if it was a throw, it was an accurate one.

The distance between the two players was too close. Troubling Rain had yet to escape from the Anti-Tank Missile’s hitstun before the new attack struck.

Ka!

The sound of metal cracking could be heard alongside the explosion.

Armor-Piercing Missile!

The skill dealt damage and reduced the target’s defense. The sound of metal cracking indicated that Troubling Rain’s light armor had been damaged, and his defense would temporarily be lowered.

At max rank, Armor-Piercing Missile’s effect lasted 8 seconds and reduced the target’s physical defense by 30%.

30% was a considerable reduction. Launchers didn’t have many attacks with special effects, and this skill was one that allowed them to deal more damage.

The skill usually marked the beginning of a fierce assault. But Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was still spinning in the air!

Both the Anti-Tank Missiles and the Armor-Piercing Missile had been released consecutively in a short time frame. Could Dancing Rain keep up the assault given her situation?

She could!

A bright pillar of light descended from the air just as people were beginning to show doubt.

Not only did she attack, she used a powerful high-level skill, Satellite Beam!

Everyone was shocked, especially the viewers who played Launchers. They knew just how unbelievable it was. Satellite Beam was a skill that was difficult to control and aim accurately. If she landed the Satellite Beam in her current state, then that would be even more astonishing than the previous Anti-Tank Missile and Armor-Piercing Missile.

But she missed!

Huang Shaotian deserved his reputation. He wasn’t able to dodge the previous Armor-Piercing Missile because it had simply come too fast, but this Satellite Beam had a rather long start-up time. Although the previous attack had increased the hitstun duration, it was just a tiny bit too short.

Huang Shaotian grasped that small opening!

Lunge!

It was a low-level skill. The damage was low and the movement it enabled was very short. But this sudden lunge was just enough to let Troubling Rain dodge the first part of the Satellite Beam. After that, he traversed through the smaller beams that split off.

Downwind Sword Slash!

Sword light flew out from Troubling Rain on his third step. A streak of blue crossed through the heaven and earth, but it was too hard to see what it was exactly because it was soon covered in dark red.

Hit!

The airborne Dancing Rain had nowhere to run to. The recoil from her previous attacks had reduced much of her spinning, and her position in the air wasn’t too clear. From a certain perspective, this Downwind Sword Slash removed Dancing Rain’s knock-up status effect, sending her flying towards a tree. Although Su Mucheng hastily had Dancing Rain shoot twice, it wasn’t able to stop the momentum from Troubling Rain’s attack.

The tides of battle instantly shifted again.

No one had expected this Blade Master and Launcher battle to turn out this way.

According to common knowledge, when Blade Masters and Launchers fought, the Launcher ran while the Blade Master gave chase. If the Blade Master caught the Launcher, the Blade Master won. If not, the Launcher won.

Right now, the Blade Master and Launcher were fighting an even battle at such close range. To be able to make such an abnormal situation happen, Su Mucheng was undoubtedly deserving of praise.

Fighting at close range was extremely unfavorable for Launchers, but through impeccable timing, Su Mucheng was able to use this close range to send out attacks that were harder to dodge.

These successive attacks worried Blue Rain’s fans.

They were unexpectedly worried for Huang Shaotian in close combat against a Launcher. When they thought about it again, they found it hard to believe.

Dancing Rain had finally been hit flying by Troubling Rain, giving everyone a little bit of room to relax.

In reality, the previous exchange had been very quick. From beginning to end, it had taken less than ten seconds. But those ten seconds were so filled with content that it would take more than ten minutes to digest.

The match continued.

Sending Dancing Rain flying was just a start. Troubling Rain quickly gave chase.

Shadow Steps!

This time, Huang Shaotian used Shadow Steps to prevent Su Mucheng from tricking him. No matter how familiar Blue Rain’s players were with this map, there was no way they could have anticipated that Su Mucheng would place a signal in that little hole. What’s more, the terrain would undergo changes from the previous battles in the group arena. Who knew if that hole had come with the map or if it had been created.

All sorts of tricks could be employed in this map. As for Su Mucheng… Huang Shaotian admitted that he had taken it too easy at the start probably because his opponent had been a Launcher. He couldn’t help it. That isn’t right! Huang Shaotian scolded himself. He had known Su Mucheng for quite some time. He knew how crafty she could be.

Shadow Steps!

In order to get close to her, Huang Shaotian had used seven shadows to surround Dancing Rain. This time, he wasn’t careless. He blocked off every retreat path. Su Mucheng would most likely send out attacks as she fell to use Aerial Cannon to adjust her positioning.

Boom!

As he expected, Dancing Rain sent out attacks. With seven shadows, Su Mucheng didn’t know which one was real. She could only use these attacks to help push her Dancing Rain away.

These movements had been within Huang Shaotian’s predictions and he quickly reacted.

Sword Draw!

Whether the shadow was real or fake, all seven sent out sword slashes towards Dancing Rain.

Which one was real? Which one was fake?

Su Mucheng had no way of telling. Even if she could, she wasn’t like a bird who could fly nimbly through the air and dodge the attack.

As a result, Su Mucheng abandoned her defense and had Dancing Rain take out a Gatling Gun.

Ta ta ta ta ta…

A string of bullets rapidly fired, practically the moment Dancing Rain was hit.

Su Mucheng immediately deduced where the real body was. As Dancing Rain flew back, she aimed her gun and fired towards the real Troubling Rain before the drops of blood even hit the ground.

Pu pu pu pu pu…

Several bullets struck Troubling Rain. With Gatling Gun’s firing speed and this distance, it wasn’t possible for him to dodge. As Dancing Rain flew back, the bullets were focused on Troubling Rain. The burst of bullets made Troubling Rain look like a ragdoll. It was true that Gatling Gun was a low-leveled skill, but it still did considerable damage when all of the bullets landed.

Everyone was awestruck, including Team Happy and Chen Guo.

She had already forgotten to cheer and become excited. She was completely shocked.

Aggressive!

Su Mucheng fought extremely aggressively.

She didn’t know which shadow was real, so she used herself as a testing stone and then made an aggressive counterattack, making both sides suffer from the exchange.

She had been trying to run the entire time, but running away wasn’t a choice she made because she was sacred. Throughout this entire match, she seemed to have no fear of engaging in close combat, and she didn’t act like a typical Launcher who decisively chose to run as soon as the opponent got near.

In close combat, she tried every way she could think of to display a Launcher’s power. She didn’t yield an inch as she attacked her opponent.

Her aggressiveness had caught Huang Shaotian off guard.

He had never met a Launcher like this before.

He had never seen Su Mucheng play like this before either.

Despite his shock, Huang Shaotian maintained his composure.

Troubling Rain had lost another 9%, but this time, Huang Shaotian didn’t lose the trade. Meteor Form, Downwind Sword Slash, Sword Draw, these three fast skills had taken out 11% of Dancing Rain’s health.

But overall?

Troubling Rain only had 48% health left, while Dancing Rain still had 89%.

There was a 41% health disparity and Su Mucheng was playing abnormally aggressive. Huang Shaotian didn’t dare act blindly.

With less health, he didn’t dare make too many trades, but Su Mucheng’s aggressive playing was showing that she intended on doing so.

In the previous group arena round, he didn’t want to trade to conserve as much health as possible for Happy’s fifth player, but Tang Rou forcefully made trades to make him lose health.

Right now, Su Mucheng was utilizing this point to make things difficult for Huang Shaotian.

Last time, he didn’t want to make trades so he could keep himself healthy.

This time, he didn’t want to make trades so he could keep himself alive.

48% health wasn’t just Troubling Rain’s life, but Team Blue Rain’s last life in the group arena.

Huang Shaotian no longer gave chase. Troubling Rain turned and disappeared into the fog. He had given up on chasing after her relentlessly and decided to be more tactical. He wanted to ambush her, which meant the first thing he needed to do was to go into hiding.

Chapter 1458 - Hurricane Cannon

Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had taken the initiative to retreat, but this time, it was Su Mucheng’s turn to be relentless. Raising her cannon with both hands, Dancing Rain chased after Troubling Rain, following the path that he had taken. Even though Troubling Rain had vanished from her sight in the blink of an eye, her attack was still extremely decisive. Boom!

The forest was filled with bright flashes from the explosions. It was already the last round, so there was no need to conserve mana, and on top of that, the Launcher’s normal attacks also did damage in an area-of-effect. The aggressive Su Mucheng had now turned into the destroyer of the forest, with her artillery barrage engulfing her path as she steadily chased in the direction that Troubling Rain had fled in.

In the end, just as she had just reached the spot where Troubling Rain was hiding behind a tree, sword light flashed towards her.

Huang Shaotian had been called the Demon Blade, and this title was precisely because he was able to seize opportunities that others weren’t able to notice, and could often launch attacks in situations which others deemed to be impossible.

When he seized these impossible opportunities, the things he accomplished were always a little strange, and so after some time, the nickname of Demon Blade was born.

At this moment, if not for the viewers’ omniscient point-of-view, how many people would think that Huang Shaotian, having just decided to escape and seeing Su Mucheng closing in, would instead immediately drop his original decision to quickly lay in ambush along the path that she was taking? Even though this new decision was a very logical one, Huang Shaotian’s reaction was simply too fast, catching everyone off-guard.

Of course, being fast could allow him to catch others unprepared.

When this sword light emerged, Su Mucheng really was somewhat unprepared.

The sword light landed squarely, and Dancing Rain staggered and fell towards the side.

Collapsing Mountain!

Troubling Rain brandished his sword, preparing to continue the assault, but once again, he was met face-first with the mouth of Dancing Rain’s cannon.

Su Mucheng didn’t become any less aggressive after forcing Huang Shaotian to run. In this moment, her split-second reaction was to launch a counterattack.

“What have you been through, why are your attacks so fierce!”

Huang Shaotian blew his top and shouted, as Troubling Rain stopped his attack in mid-air. The Collapsing Mountain was changed into a Falling Light Blade, and with a stroke, he fell towards the side.

Boom!

Of course, the cannon fired an attack. Though this attack was unable to prevent Collapsing Mountain from completing, Huang Shaotian really didn’t want to engage in any trading with Su Mucheng.

“The one who wronged you wasn’t me, right?”

In the midst of the attacks, Huang Shaotian was still sending messages. After dodging the cannon blast, the shockwave from the Falling Light Blade was just enough to reach Dancing Rain.

Dancing Rain was already rolling, using the knockback from the attack earlier along with the Falling Light Blade’s attack to cancel each other out. As she was rolling, a single grenade also rolled outwards.

“…”

Huang Shaotian was speechless, and could only have Troubling Rain jump and dodge the attack. He wouldn’t be able to dodge the attack by moving forwards, so he could only retreat.

“Blocking our road to the championship title, is there any wrong greater than that?” Su Mucheng replied.

“If you look at it this way, you’ve also wronged me considerably!” Huang Shaotian replied.

Troubling Rain jumped nimbly backwards just enough to dodge the explosion from the grenade, and retaliated at the last moment.

Headwind Strike!

Troubling Rain jumped forwards, his body spinning in mid-air and dodging one of Dancing Rain’s artillery shells. Immediately after, sword light condensed into a circle, flying towards Dancing Rain.

This one sword was quite a strong move.

In close-quarters combat, no matter what, the Blade Master would reign supreme, not the Launcher.

Su Mucheng had used her aggressive performance to suppress Huang Shaotian. To be suppressed by a Launcher in close-quarters combat was a disgrace, and even to normal players, it was embarrassing enough. But as for the esteemed Sword Saint, even after being bullied like this, his mental state was still calm.

He had a very clear understanding of what capital Su Mucheng had to rely on.

She was aggressive, but there was a reason that she was aggressive. Su Mucheng didn’t just decide to fight head-on and charge for no reason, taking her Launcher to be a Knight.

The disparity in health between the two was what allowed Su Mucheng to make some decisions in close-quarters combat that would normally be disadvantageous to her. As for Huang Shaotian, because of his health disadvantage, he had no choice but to dodge these “decisions”, and gradually, it looked like he was in a difficult situation.

And now, knowing that Su Mucheng would fight in this manner, he also calmly made his decision. He would avoid playing into Su Mucheng’s intentions, and begin his attack from there.

Headwind Strike connected, and Huang Shaotian had Troubling Rain use Rising Dragon Slash!

This blade didn’t hit Dancing Rain, but as Troubling Rain rose in the air, he narrowly avoided another attack that Su Mucheng had sent towards him whilst she was stumbling.

“Oh oh oh!!!”

The entire crowd saw this thrilling moment and cried out in surprise.

The Rising Dragon Slash brough Troubling Rain behind Dancing Rain, and at that moment in mid-air, his body twisted. Falling Phoenix Slash!

His body didn’t twist completely at all, and this Falling Phoenix Slash was awkward and ugly, but the sword light accurately chopped towards Dancing Rain’s head. On top of that, she still hadn’t regained her balance from the stumbling that the Headwind Strike had caused!

This was the rhythm of a professional player at the apex of Glory.

The difference between them and a normal player was clear as day. If it was an ordinary player, they wouldn’t be able to combine a Rising Dragon Slash and Falling Phoenix Slash so quickly, right after Headwind Strike had completed.

Slash!

The sword light descended, and Dancing Rain was knocked onto the ground.

The stadium was filled with applause.

In the beginning, Huang Shaotian being beaten up by Su Mucheng had made them extremely anxious, but at this moment, it looked like Huang Shaotian had found his rhythm.

As Dancing Rain rolled, offsetting the attack, Troubling Rain’s figure had already begun moving towards the side. Huang Shaotian believed that Su Mucheng would forcefully attack at this moment, so the path that he chose wasn’t the fastest path to get close to Dancing Rain. Instead, he moved to a location that Dancing Rain wouldn’t be able to attack while rolling.

Pressing hard, but not pressing too hard.

To a Launcher, a class bad at close combat, a distance of one, two or three steps could all be considered close-quarters fighting, preventing them from displaying their ranged superiority. So now that Huang Shaotian hadn’t chased as closely, he was a bit further away from Dancing Rain, but Su Mucheng was now unable to make her aggressive counterattacks.

As expected, Huang Shaotian wasn’t such an easy player to take down.

As Su Mucheng rolled and tried to forcefully counterattack, she saw that Huang Shaotian had unexpectedly controlled Troubling Rain to move towards an area that she couldn’t adjust her attack to hit, and also understood what had happened in her mind. She knew that Huang Shaotian had already made adjustments to his attacking rhythm.

As such, after rolling, Dancing Rain rolled once more.

Roll, roll roll, Dancing Rain rolled in an arc on the ground.

“Hahaha, is this some vulgar movement that you’ve learned from Fang Rui?” Huang Shaotian laughed.

When one thought of Su Mucheng’s beautiful figure also rolling on the ground in a vulgar fashion like Fang Rui, it was certainly difficult to bear. Huang Shaotian’s words completely shattered the “female goddess” image in the blink of an eye.

He wasn’t particularly worried about such movement. Fang Rui was an opponent that they had researched for several years. Even if she had learnt Fang Rui’s dirty movements, it wasn’t enough to catch an experienced veteran like Huang Shaotian off-guard.

As he ridiculed her, he was actually carefully watching where Dancing Rain’s rolling silhouette, paying attention to angles from which he could dodge her attacks before continuing to close the distance.

In the end, just as Troubling Rain succeeded in drawing close and was preparing to attack, he heard a “whoosh”.

The sound was a little bit smothered, and a bit long. It also seemed to have some kind of revolving sound, rubbing against the cannon’s walls as it fired out.

This is……

Huang Shaotian’s brain flashed with understanding, but in the end, this skill appeared slightly faster than he was able to react.

As the artillery shell left the cannon, a whooshing sound rang out.

Hurricane Cannon!

A level 75 Launcher skill.

At this time, Huang Shaotian had already reacted. He had Troubling Rain frantically dodge to one side, but it was already too late.

Unexpectedly, Su Mucheng had simply and directly fired this cannon shot at him while rolling. After that whooshing sound rang out, a hurricane swirled up, with Dancing Rain’s body as the center. In an instant, Dancing Rain was sent flying in the air, as the hurricane rapidly expanded. Troubling Rain, who was trying to retreat, was only able to take half a step before caught by the hurricane, and in an instant, he was sucked into it.

That Hurricane Cannon shot was still drilling into the ground, frantically revolving. This intense hurricane seemed to come from the ripples on the body of the artillery shell. But how could Huang Shaotian have the mood to appreciate this at this time? In the instant that Troubling Rain’s body went out of control, he knew it spelt disaster. He already had no way of controlling his character to do anything. The only thing he could do was to forcefully raise his field of view, and what he saw was Dancing Rain, floating in mid-air with the help of a cannon shot. He saw the pitch-dark mouth of the cannon aiming once more towards the hurricane, and aiming towards him.

Boom!

At the same instant that the Hurricane Cannon exploded, Dancing Rain’s cannon sent a charged-up Quantum Bomb towards him. On top of the explosion, there was another layer of energy fluctuating out. The recoil from a Quantum Bomb was uncomparably strong. If a character was standing on flat ground, they would have to take a step back in order to dissipate the recoil, or they would be flipped onto the ground.

At this time, Dancing Rain had already charged up this shot in mid-air. As she reached the highest point, she synchronized with the explosion of Hurricane Cannon, sending out the Quantum Bomb. With the strong recoil, Dancing Rain was just like an artillery shell, rocketing through the sky.

All of this was clearly seen by the crowd. But what about Huang Shaotian? After one round of explosions, his field of view was completely covered with the light and thick smoke from the explosions.

What about Dancing Rain?

After freeing himself from the explosions, he quickly swept all 360 degrees around him, but he couldn’t find her.

On top of you!

The viewers wished they could run up and pull Huang Shaotian’s ear to tell him, and as for Dancing Rain, she had already begun to fall at this point. The pitch-dark mouth of the cannon once more locked on to its target. She wasn’t impatient to fire her shot, instead, she wanted to wait for a certain distance, to wait for a distance in which even Huang Shaotian wouldn’t be able to dodge in time.

It’s already more or less there!

Su Mucheng had already made a precise judgement, and immediately began inputting her skills to attack, but all of a sudden, Troubling Rain, who had been looking in all directions vigilantly, suddenly raised his sword towards the sky.

Piercing Form!

One blade dotted the firmament.

Fine sword qi flew out, and the incomparably strong Piercing Form immediately wrecked Dancing Rain’s figure in mid-air.

Did he really not know that Dancing Rain was above him? Those who thought as much were underestimating Huang Shaotian.

Chapter 1459 - Dangerous Opportunity

To land the hit, Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain fall down to a low height, a height within a Blade Master’s attack range. When Troubling Rain’s Piercing Form came out, the high priority skill disrupted Dancing Rain’s positioning. She wasn’t able to cancel her attack, and the artillery shell completely missed its target.

Huang Shaotian was unphased. Troubling Rain raised his sword and leapt into the air.

Sky-Plunging Blade, Immortal Guides the Way.

Two skills, one after the other. In a normal player’s hands, using these two skills in such quick succession would be unthinkable.

The Sky-Plunging Blade caught Dancing Rain and swung her towards the ground.

By the time Immortal Guides the Way came out, Dancing Rain was positioned below Troubling Rain. The powerful blow-away effect made Dancing Rain fall even faster.

This sudden push made Dancing Rain crash even harder into the ground, messing up her Quick Recovery timing. She tried to adjust it, but she wasn’t able to in time. Dancing Rain hit the ground, her heavy armor crushing the branches beneath her.

Both players lost a good chunk of health in this short instant.

Troubling Rain had been hit by a Level 75 Hurricane Cannon and then a charged Quantum Bomb. These two attacks had taken away 11% of his health.

Dancing Rain took even more damage.

The exchange started with Huang Shaotian’s ambush to Headwind Strike, Falling Phoenix Slash, Piercing Form, Sky-Plunging Blade, and Immortal Guides the Way. All of these skills dealt considerable damage, and all of them had hit. Dancing Rain had lost 18% of her health.

In the end, Troubling Rain had 37% health left, while Dancing Rain had 71% health left.

When the two started the round, it had been 63% to 100%. In total, Troubling Rain had lost 26% of his health, while Dancing Rain had lost 29% of her health.

Huang Shaotian had a slight 3% lead in terms of damage dealt, but that was meaningless.

He had started out behind by 37%. A 3% lead didn’t even make up for 10% of that number.

Now, Troubling Rain had even less health, making it even more unfavorable for Huang Shaotian.

He could not afford to miss any more opportunities. As Troubling Rain fell, his sword swept towards Dancing Rain.

Because Su Mucheng had messed up the Quick Recover, she had no way of dodging this attack. The strike would be from the back as well. Would she be able to avoid the follow-up?

Shua!

Another sword light fell, but all it hit was branches and leaves. Dancing Rain had rolled to the side, her cannon aimed coldly at Troubling Rain.

Boom!

Smoke rolled into the air.

She was firing at nearly point blank range. It wasn’t possible to dodge it at this distance. However, Huang Shaotian swung his sword faster than she could fire her cannon. He wasn’t able to dodge, but his sword was able to strike Dancing Rain.

Blood blossomed into the air. All Su Mucheng could see was red. Glory used these realistic details to let the players know of their condition.

Dancing Rain was covered in blood, but what about Troubling Rain? The artillery shell exploded in his face. The smoke and fire engulfed him as he was sent flying away.

But as he flew backwards, Huang Shaotian sent out another strike. The sword light from Sword Draw split apart the smoke. By the time Su Mucheng noticed it, it was too late. Huang Shaotian had used the smoke as cover for a follow-up.

Su Mucheng had also wanted to follow-up, but it was interrupted by the sword strike. After steadying herself again, the smoke in front of her had dispersed. She saw as Troubling Rain rolled across the ground and rushed back towards her.

Boom boom boom.

Su Mucheng fired three Anti-Tank Missiles, attacking Troubling Rain while retreating.

She had played aggressively, but it had been done with thought. Playing aggressive didn’t meant that she didn’t care about the distance between the two sides. When there was an opportunity to trade with Huang Shaotian, she would engage in close combat with him. But if there was no such opportunity, she would try her best to pull apart the distance and wait for one to come.

“You’re running again?” Huang Shaotian messaged. He had seen through Su Mucheng’s playstyle and strategy. She had retreated because she wasn’t able to see an opportunity to attack. These were the moments that Huang Shaotian needed to grasp.

Triple Slash!

Troubling Rain used it as a movement skill. He didn’t take a straight path towards her, instead taking a curved path. It was a very smart method of dealing with Aerial Cannon. With Aerial Cannon, the Launcher would be moving backwards. If the opponent gave chase from the front, it would be easy for the Launcher to delay him. However, it was hard for the Launcher to change directions while in the air.

Thus, taking a curved path was effective against Aerial Cannon movements. But taking a curved path had its own problems. It required the player to cross a longer distance, so it took more time. Aerial Cannon was fast too, so it made it harder to close the distance.

As a result, taking a curved path could not always be done. It depended on the distance and the timing.

Grasping timings was Huang Shaotian’s specialty. The Triple Slash path was completely beautifully. The viewers could tell that Dancing Rain was trying to adjust her aim to catch Troubling Rain, but she was always behind all the way until Troubling Rain reached her flank.

Upwards Slash.

Troubling Rain made a simple slash upwards, but it was at a spot which the opponent couldn’t dodge. Dancing Rain, who had been moving backwards with Aerial Cannon, was lifted into the sky.

Su Mucheng had Dancing Rain aim towards him. In reality, being in the air wasn’t too bad for Gunner classes because their firing produced recoil, allowing them to move in the air and disrupt their opponent’s aerial control.

However, as a pro player, just trying to escape wasn’t all. They would always be trying to search for opportunities to injure the opponent too. You couldn’t win a match just by running away.

Su Mucheng moved her cursor, but there was no sign of Troubling Rain.

Sua!

Another sword strike, dealing damage and keeping Dancing Rain in the air. Su Mucheng kept searching, but she was unexpectedly unable to find him.

Vanishing Step!

Vanishing Step was considered a peak Glory technique. It required a player’s intuition and technique to reach perfection to perform. Even in the pro scene, there were few players who could execute this technique well. It had always seemed to be a technique that only existed in theory.

At this moment, Huang Shaotian was using Vanishing Step to keep the opponent in the air, and if it continued, it was likely that victory would be his.

“But it’s very difficult, ” Li Yibo said,” Juggling a Gunner class to death is extremely difficult, let alone a top-tier Launcher like Su Mucheng.”

“Let’s keep watching, ” Pan Lin didn’t seem to want to elaborate. This battle was too intense. The two sides were constantly going back and forth with neither side able to hold a dominant advantage. All sorts of brilliant plays were being displayed. Right now, Vanishing Step had finally appeared. Would Huang Shaotian be able to keep this technique going against Su Mucheng? Would he be able to make up for the deficit with this play?

Everyone looked at the sword in Troubling Rain’s hands, at the sword light flying out from it. The sword light weaved across Dancing Rain, keeping her tumbling non-stop.

But Su Mucheng seemed to have no reaction.

As a Gunner class, even just randomly attacking would make it very hard for the opponent to keep the Vanishing Step going. But Su Mucheng didn’t do this. She just seemed to be looking around.

Was she looking for an opening? Was she waiting until she could counterattack?

Shouldn’t her first priority be to get out of Vanishing Step? Wasn’t Su Mucheng being a bit too confident, thinking of directly going for a counterattack?

Dancing Rain’s health continued to drop.

1%.

2.3%.

0.9%.

4%.

Attack after attack dealing different amounts of damage. High, or low, or perhaps just to keep her in the air. All of them left marks on her character. Damage quickly accumulated as Dancing Rain’s health fell rapidly at a visible speed.

60%…

50%…

The difference between their health bars was closing.

Still not going to move?

Happy’s fans were starting to have trouble sitting still. They had no idea what Su Mucheng was thinking.

Huang Shaotian did though. He knew exactly what she was thinking.

They were only paying attention to why Dancing Rain wasn’t attacking. However, they didn’t notice that although she wasn’t attacking, she was constantly adjusting her weapon angle.

Huang Shaotian saw it very clearly because he needed to predict where Dancing Rain would be, which meant that he needed to see where her cannon was aiming towards so he could react and prevent her from escaping. Huang Shaotian was aware of what Gunners could do to escape from the air.

However, Dancing Rain didn’t attack, and it was making Huang Shaotian feel exhausted.

Su Mucheng had anticipated Huang Shaotian being on guard against her aerial movements. As a result, she kept moving her cannon to have Huang Shaotian keep making adjustments. It had only been a few seconds, but the ordinary person had no idea just how focused Huang Shaotian was. Vanishing Step was an extremely difficult technique that required a lot of concentration. And now, Su Mucheng was making it even harder for him.

This isn’t right! When Huang Shaotian realized that the situation wasn’t right, he had already gone too far. He discovered that he wasn’t able to keep up and adjust to Dancing Rain’s tempo. For a keen opportunist like him, he had sniffed out an incredibly dangerous opportunity for him.

Chapter 1460 - Advance Bravely

What an opportunity!

Even though this opportunity didn’t belong to him, Huang Shaotian couldn’t help but feel excited at any opportunity he saw.

Would Su Mucheng be able to grasp an opportunity like this?

While everyone else hadn’t even realized what was going on, Huang Shaotian was already beginning to worry about whether the opponent would miss the opportunity. No matter what, opportunity was always an exceptionally beautiful thing to him.

She didn’t miss it!

Dancing Rain’s swinging cannon opening suddenly steadied, and sparks flew outward.

“Ah!”

For the audience, this attack came too quickly. Even though they had been wondering why Su Mucheng wasn’t firing any attacks to give Huang Shaotian some difficulty, this fire that now came from Dancing Rain still felt off.

It was just this attack, but it caused so much difficulty!

This one shot broke Huang Shaotian’s Vanishing Step. That wasn’t all – after this shot, Dancing Rain gracefully twisted in the air, and where before she had seemed helplessly tossed around in the air, she now very steadily aimed her cannon right at Troubling Rain.

Boom boom boom boom!

The cannonfire was like a pouring rainstorm. Troubling Rain was instantly swallowed whole.

Breaking the Vanishing Step?

Everyone discovered that they had underestimated that first shot that Su Mucheng had fired. It had been the herald of the counterattack. In the blink of an eye, the situation had completely flipped on its head.

How did this happen?

Everyone was speechless. The Blue Rain fans in the stadium who had been cheering had issued a few sighs of regret at that first shot, but now that things were like this, it was as though their necks had been collectively broken. No sound came from them anymore.

Boom boom boom boom!

In their ears there was only the sound of Dancing Rain’s cannonfire, eating away bit by bit at Troubling Rain’s health. And Dancing Rain was using this combo to slowly fall to the ground. The whole offensive was completed while she was in motion – to restrict Huang Shaotian to the point where he was completely helpless, it was clear how perfect Su Mucheng’s control was. Huang Shaotian was the kind of person who only needed the barest hint of an opportunity to pull off a trick.

30%…

20%…

10%…

Once a pro player established an offensive, the opponent’s health could be cut down this quickly.

Blue Rain’s fans in the audience had grown pale. At 10%, the health bar became red, signaling the danger of the situation. But the combo still hadn’t been interrupted, and Su Mucheng still had the initiative. A distance of 21 body lengths could still be fully covered by the cannonfire.

Her Firing Line?

Everyone was in a daze as they watched Dancing Rain attack. Today’s Su Mucheng was so powerful, it had taken everyone aback.

Keep fighting!

Blue Rain’s fans were furiously cheering on Huang Shaotian in their hearts, but they didn’t dare make a sound, as though any sound would distract him.

“You’re trying to take me down in one go?”

But before anyone distracted him, Huang Shaotian was already distracting himself, sending a message in the chat.

This was the talkativeness that so many people hated, but now that this sentence appeared, it instantly reassured everyone.

The fact that Huang Shaotian was still trash-talking meant that he hadn’t given up yet. He was definitely still brimming with fighting spirit.

He would definitely find an opportunity to counterattack!

Blue Rain’s fans were instantly filled with confidence and anticipation.

And Huang Shaotian didn’t disappoint.

Sword’s Divine Judgment!

A ring of sword energy rippled through the cannonfire, slicing through the shots with a series of booms.

Sword’s Divine Judgment, this wasn’t a skill that could be adjusted with minute inputs. The only thing that could be controlled was the timing of the skill’s start. To achieve this effect now, this was an opportunity that could be encountered but not begged for. Yet this was Huang Shaotian, and he instantly seized the chance.

Triple Slash!

With the bonus from Sword’s Divine Judgment, Triple Slash became even faster. With three flashes of swordlight, Troubling Rain finally broke free from the Firing Line that Su Mucheng had established.

But Dancing Rain’s cannon was still locked onto him.

There was nowhere for Huang Shaotian to dodge, and Troubling Rain only had 8% health remaining. For a Launcher, this was low enough that one powerful attack could take him down.

His options were limited. Retreat and then find another chance to ambush? He might not get a better chance than the one he had now. His target was right before his eyes.

Advance!

Huang Shaotian controlled Troubling Rain to charge forward, toward Dancing Rain’s cannon pointed at him.

In his eyes, this wasn’t just the character of an opponent. This was a struggle for the championship, and all obstacles needed to be shattered with his sword. This was the path that could not be avoided.

No turning back. Curving Wind Form!

The skill was released, carrying the boost from the Sword’s Divine Judgment. Faster. Fiercer.

The sword energy retracted, and Dancing Rain had no choice but to crash into the tip of the sword, but the cannon in her hands was steady.

This was the moment that would decide victory!

Everyone stared with eyes open wide, watching the swordlight and cannonfire meld together, shining brilliantly. On this stage, this was everyone’s goal, their dream, their glory.

Everyone.

But only one person could be the last one standing.

Su Mucheng, Dancing Rain.

After a period of calm, she was the one who stood at the very end.

Huang Shaotian lost, Blue Rain lost. In the group arena, the choice of map had demonstrated how much they had prepared, but in the end, Happy had obtained victory.

Was Blue Rain’s performance bad?

No one would think so.

The players of both teams had performed excellently. But there could only be one winner. That was all it was.

Su Mucheng and Huang Shaotian walked out of their competitor booths together, to be met with a quiet stadium.

This battles was undoubtedly the most fierce and exciting of all the group arena battles today. The entire fight had been conducted under extremely dangerous conditions, where one mistake could spell defeat. During the entire battle, the audience felt that they didn’t even have the time to take a breath. Now that it was over, it was clear that Huang Shaotian’s performance was faultless, and there wasn’t really anything to criticize about the performance of Blue Rain as a whole. But, they had lost, and this ending made their hearts heavy.

They had already lost an away game. Now, they were playing their home game, but they had still lost the group arena.

With the new playoffs competition format, losing one point in the group arena wouldn’t affect the team competition that much. But just from the current mood of the fans, it was clear that although it didn’t affect the numbers much, people’s emotions weren’t so robotic.

As the two players walked offstage, the ones who reacted first were Happy’s fans in the west seating area. A thrilling process with victory as the outcome, was there anything more they could ask for in this match? Happy’s fans had full reason to go wild with excitement.

Blue Rain’s fans came to their senses after seeing Happy’s celebrations. The team was already behind, they were already at the critical hour. As fans, how could they be so downtrodden, how could they spread their negative emotions so casually?

They were Blue Rain’s loyal supporters. They sat here today to wait for Team Blue Rain’s victory.

They might not be able to help the players onstage, but offstage, they could at least help the team keep their spirits up!

“Go Blue Rain!” It wasn’t clear who started it, but soon, the sound filled the entire stadium. All of the Blue Rain fans came together. Now wasn’t the time to wallow in melancholy. The situation was serious for them, and so it was more important than ever to boost morale.

“We’re only one point behind, the situation isn’t too bad.”

And so everyone began to think this way. Of course, they hope that Blue Rain’s players would also be able to take this kind of mindset. The fans couldn’t directly change the players’ moods. They could only try and shape the atmosphere of the stadium to motivate the players.

They watched Huang Shaotian, watched him return to Blue Rain’s player area, watched as the other Blue Rain players surrounded him.

“I swear, Su Mucheng was hacking today!” Huang Shaotian said indignantly, standing in the middle.

Everyone laughed.

“In the team competition, we also need to pay attention to her performance,” said Yu Wenzhou.

Blue Rain immediately entered the rhythm of preparing for the upcoming team competition. They didn’t speak a single word more about the situation of the group arena.

“We’re only one point behind, the situation isn’t too disastrous,” was the mantra that the fans were using to reestablish their confidence. But on Blue Rain’s side, there was no mention at all.

Without wasting a single moment, Blue Rain was already beginning to plan for the team competition.

They’d prepared before the match, of course, but in the stadium, there would always be minor adjustments depending on the performance of the opponents during the group arena. Today, for example, Su Mucheng’s condition was exceptionally outstanding, so in team competition they would have to pay attention to her.

Team Blue Rain was already entirely immersed in the rhythm of the team competition.

What about Happy? After all, they had a number of rookies, and so it would be hard for them to match the mature mood of Blue Rain. But Ye Xiu didn’t say anything to dampen their spirits after their victory.

“Keep up this momentum, let’s crush them in the team competition!” Ye Xiu said.

Crush them! Facing Blue Rain, even Samsara wouldn’t dare use this kind of wording. But Ye Xiu used it, and Happy’s members didn’t treat it like a big deal.

“Watch me, Boss!” Steamed Bun said, with unparalleled confidence.

“It’s up to you, Steamed Bun,” said Ye Xiu.

“Of course,” said Steamed Bun. He made all sorts of arrogant faces at Blue Rain’s player area, with the look of a conqueror.

“Good luck, Steamed Bun,” everyone said.

The break between the group arena and the team competition was rapidly drawing to a close. With the judge’s signal, the players of the two teams began to enter. Everyone leaned forward to get a better look at the rosters of both sides.

Blue Rain: Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian, Lu Hanwen, Zheng Xuan, Xu Jingxi, Song Xiao.

Exactly the same as the previous round.

Happy’s side had some adjustments, though. Last round’s Wei Chen, who had ties to Blue Rain, did not appear this time. He and Qiao Yifan had been swapped out with Tang Rou and Steamed Bun this round. Happy’s team competition roster this time was: Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Steamed Bun, An Wenyi, Tang Rou.

Among them, it was unsurprising that the three All-Star level players Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui appeared. So far, these three players made the most consistent appearances. An Wenyi, of course, couldn’t be left out of the team competition. So, when Happy made adjustments, it would be of the other two slots, and this time, Happy switched them both.

Chapter 1461 - Gusty Garden

On stage, the players competing in the team competition lined up and shook hands.

“Still not scared?” Ye Xiu asked Yu Wenzhou as they shook hands.

“Why should we be?” Huang Shaotian interrupted. He looked to be in high spirits, as if the loss hadn’t affected him at all.

“Why do you always have to butt in!” Ye Xiu looked helplessly at Huang Shaotian as he came to shake his hand.

“You’re about to experience our might very soon,” Huang Shaotian said.

“How come I didn’t see any of it a minute ago?” Su Mucheng replied to Huang Shaotian’s remark with a sly smile, as she came up to shake his hand. Her words held a lot of weight considering she had just beaten Huang Shaotian in the group arena, even if they hadn’t started the fight with the same amount of health.

“Looks like the time for me to take revenge is already here!” Huang Shaotian sighed.

“Isn’t it usually like this for you guys? So sensitive. You must take revenge pretty frequently, huh.” Fang Rui shook Huang Shaotian’s hand.

“What’s this? A round robin?” Huang Shaotian said angrily. The guys from Happy were targeting him one after the other! His fellow teammates were laughing on the side. They seemed to have no intentions of helping him in this verbal war.

“You’re so violent! You were like that when we were setting dungeon records together too. No wonder you’re a Leo.” Steamed Bun was Happy’s fourth player. When he had been setting dungeon records with the rest of the crew, he had no clue what the pro scene was, so he didn’t know how incredible of a background that Flowing Tree had. After hearing his teammates talk about it, he finally understood. When he shook hands with Huang Shaotian, he even connected his remark with feelings from the past, causing the others from Blue Rain to raise their eyebrows.

Setting dungeon records? When did that happen? Huang Shaotian’s teammates looked at him with suspicion.

“Fuck, you bastard. Wait for me, I’ll kill you soon!” Huang Shaotian said.

“Then you’ll have to kill me first,” Happy’s fifth player was their healer An Wenyi. His words were too fitting. If the healer didn’t die, it wouldn’t easy to kill off a player.

“Even if dies, there’s still me!” This time, Huang Shaotian didn’t even have time to give a reply when Happy’s sixth player followed up. It was Tang Rou, the girl who loved to play fast and aggressive.

“Fuck you guys!” There was no one after Tang Rou. By the time Huang Shaotian responded, Happy’s six players were already on their way out. Blue Rain’s other players were laughing themselves silly.

“Even I wouldn’t be able to bear it if I were in your position, Huang Shao!” His normally unenthusiastic teammate Zheng Xuan added insult to injury.

Huang Shaotian ground his teeth.

“Let’s get ready!” Yu Wenzhou chuckled. He had been watching but didn’t say anything. He knew they were just joking around. Huang Shaotian wouldn’t actually get irritated from this. In the trash talking world, Huang Shaotian would often shoot himself in the foot, but he would never let it affect his playing. Even if he did act out, it was because he could do it in the passing. When he chose opportunities, he always decided based off what was most appropriate.

“I look forward to your performance!” Just as Team Blue Rain was about to leave, Ye Xiu made one last yell from the side. Huang Shaotian turned around and gave him the middle finger.

The two teams went into their respective player booths. The match soon began and the characters loaded into the map.

Map: Gusty Garden.

This was a comprehensive map shaped like a rhombus. There were a total of nine wind sources spreadly evenly across the map. The wind sources would randomly generate different types of wind, e.g. whirlwinds, gales, icy winds, etc., which would affect characters in different ways and could potentially tip the scales in a battle.

Maps with auxiliary features were more fun for players, but added complexity and difficult for pro players. The maps chosen by home teams usually practiced unique strategies unuseable in other maps, making it more difficult for the away teams to adjust.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo gave a brief analysis going over the features of Gusty Garden. The two teams spawned at the usual northern and southern ends of the map. Happy was on the southern end, while Blue Rain was on the northern end. Team Blue Rain immediately set out, as for Happy? The away team was clearly much more hesitant.

“Blue Rain obviously knows the map well, but Happy doesn’t. The first thing they need to do is figure out the positions of the nine wind sources. If I remember correctly, Gusty Garden should be a map released last year. Even if Ye Xiu has seen a lot of things, he probably doesn’t have any in this map,” Li Yibo said.

“Blue Rain might have chosen this map to get around Ye Xiu’s terrifying knowledge of the game,” Pan Lin said.

“Yes, although Blue Rain lost the group arena, they still fully utilized their map advantage. I’m sure they came prepared with this map as well.” Li Yibo said.

“Blue Rain is taking the central path. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain is still with the team. He’s not moving as a lone unit. Happy is moving towards the northeast. It looks like they’re trying to find the wind sources,” Pan Lin said.

As he said these words, the big screen showed a zoomed out map, indicating the location of the nine wind sources. Then, they added in Team Happy’s position.

“Team Happy seems to be moving… very deliberately!” Pan Lin remarked, seeing their movements.

“It’s as if they know the locations of the nine wind sources. It’s not too surprising. Happy may have looked over it briefly before and noted the key features,” Li Yibo said.

“Happy can’t also be familiar with this map, can they?” Pan Lin said.

“This…” Li Yibo wasn’t sure. If Blue Rain decided to choose this map, they must have known that Happy hadn’t used it before. Could this map have been a map that Happy had once planned on using before? The chance of such a coincidence was extremely low. If it really was the case, then Blue Rain was truly unlucky.

All of Team Happy pushed forward. Not long afterwards, they heard a huge gust of wind up ahead. After the projection technology ascertained the region, the only sound that could be heard was the the sounds of wind.

But despite the loud winds, the characters barely seemed to be affected.

This was one of the nine types of winds, loud wind. The effect was sound. In this environment, trying to use sound to make a decision was impossible.

Since the teams were far from each other, Happy wasn’t worried about the effects of the loud wind. They just seemed to be taking a stroll through the region, though they had changed to a different direction.

From their movements, it was certain that Happy knew exactly where the wind sources were. Now, what they needed to do was figure out what each wind source did because that was random. Blue Rain was the same. At first, they went straight for the center, but not to look for the opponents. They were going towards a wind source too. After figuring out what type of wind that source produced, they immediately headed for a different location.

Both sides had the same goal. Their paths were different, but both teams picked the most efficient routes from their starting points.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo had found quite a bit of information by now. Any player could figure out the most efficient route from the starting points. Happy and Blue Rain weren’t doing anything new and went with the most practical path.

It’s just that if these two continued along their routes…

After figuring out their routes from their starting points, they could see that once both sides found four wind sources, they would meet in the center.

The progress of the match seemed to be heading towards this direction.

After Blue Rain went through the south, southwest, west, and northwest wind sources, they headed for the center. After Happy went through the north east, east, southeast, and south, they headed for the center too.

Because both teams knew the exact locations of the wind sources, as soon as they entered a new region, they would immediately head towards a different one.

“The two teams should have expected this might happen, right?” Pan Lin guessed. Since the teams were using a popular route, they should anticipate that the other team might do the same, no?

Just when Pan Lin said these words, Team Blue Rain made a change. As they approached the wind source in the center, they gradually moved into an attack and defense formation. Happy also made a similar adjustment. From Happy’s formation, it could be seen that they knew where Blue Rain was coming from.

“Although both teams have reached this far, the two teams might not meet,” Li Yibo suddenly said.

“Oh?”

“From their route, it looks as if they’re checking the locations of the wind sources, but in reality, they’re not actually going to the wind source itself. Once they reach the edges of the wind region and figure out what type of wind is there, they head towards a different region. That’s why Happy is going towards the center from the south. It’s faster. After finding out what this region’s wind is, they’ll likely head towards the southwest.”

“Oh oh…” Pan Lin thought for some time before understanding Li Yibo’s words.

“But there could also be a change because of the wind in the central region,” Li Yibo said.

“Oh?” Pan Lin stared blankly for a bit.

At this moment, both teams had scouted out four wind sources with five unknown. However, the viewers had the results from both teams, so they had knowledge of seven of them total. They could deduce the possible winds in the central region by process of elimination. Li Yibo probably guessed what changes there might be based on these two possibilities.

By the time, the two teams had scouted out the wind in the center.

Gale!

Of the nine types of wind, gale was the strongest wind. The characters moving headwind would feel a resistance in their movements, while the characters moving tailwind would feel a pushing force.

From their current positions, Blue Rain was moving tailwind.

Use the wind!

Team Blue Rain didn’t change directions and charged straight into the wind. Taking advantage of the wind, they moved at a speed otherwise impossible under normal conditions.

Chapter 1462 - Downwind Offensive

“So fast!” countless people exclaimed.

Special battles on specific maps with unique traits didn’t occur too often. Strong wind was common, but Gusty Garden was the only map that had wind sources creating gusts strong enough to change a character’s speed so drastically.

As for how much of a speed increase this wind granted, it was unclear. The wind would have a different effect depending on a character’s weight and strength stats. But judging from how rapidly the Blue Rain players were dashing around, the boost seemed to be at least 50%.

And as soon as they entered the wind, the real value of this map to Blue Rain became apparent. The five characters all had different weight, strength, and base speed, but under the complex effects of the gale, they maintained their formation exactly as it was before. It was clear that they had plenty of experience under these conditions and were able to cope with ease.

Meanwhile on Happy’s end, they knew the position of the wind sources and could walk a strategic path, which showed that they weren’t entirely unfamiliar with this map and had a basic understanding of it. But without specific training, an understanding of this situation was already about as much as they could hope for. To fight in this wind? Never mind the fact that they didn’t have training, even if they did, they were currently positioned against the wind, so the wind would be reducing their speed. Compared to Blue Rain, who had a speed boost, the difference between the speed boost and speed reduction could be as much as 100%. Even if they were facing ordinary players, it would not be a good idea to enter the wind zone from this side.

Naturally, Happy didn’t try. After figuring out that there was gale here, the whole team began to head toward the next wind source.

But Blue Rain continued to travel downwind, prepared to cut off the path that Happy was taking.

Blue Rain made a decisive and correct deduction.

Blue Rain, traveling downwind, quickly left behind all of the fallen trees and plant life. In the blink of an eye, they’d traversed half of the wind zone, and right in front of them, the silhouettes of Happy’s five players had already appeared in their view.

Blue Rain didn’t slow down at all, and rushed forward just like this.

Happy’s members of course discovered Blue Rain’s presence. There was no way they would enter the wind zone to fight an opponent that had the advantage of wind direction.

“Continue forward!” Ye Xiu directed.

But Blue Rain was already attacking them.

The attack came from the unmotivated Zheng Xuan. His Spitfire Bullet Rain could be considered Blue Rain’s number one ranged attacker.

Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh.

A number of grenades flew out simultaneously. There was no way this was from multiple skills used in a row. Without a doubt, this was the powerful Level 70 Spitfire skill, Chaotic Grenades.

Implosion, Timed, Poison Gas, Electric…

Countless grenades were thrown by Bullet Rain. They didn’t travel as quickly as bullets, but at this time, they experienced a greater effect from the gusts of wind than bullets would. The sky seemed to fill with shooting stars that were all of a sudden right in front of the whole team. The pressure was upon them.

Boom!

But the sound of this explosion came a bit early, and then within the wind gusts, a wave of energy rippled outward in all directions, carrying a force even stronger than the wind.

The gusts of wind could increase or decrease the speed of a character, but it ultimately wouldn’t send characters flying. Compared to the force of an Implosion Grenade that could blast away a character, the wind was still somewhat inferior.

This Implosion Grenade amidst the Chaotic Grenades exploded before even leaving the wind zone. In Happy’s formation, smoke trailed from the tip of Lord Grim’s Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

Such a fast grenade traveling in the wind was actually shot down in midair?

A coincidence? It didn’t seem like it. Of the grenades, the Implosion Grenade was the most destructive for a team’s formation. How could it be such a coincidence, that among so many grenades, this was the one shot down? It was clearly intentional.

It was too frightening.

Ye Xiu’s extreme accuracy with his controls was incredible. But Lord Grim’s attack didn’t stop there – he quickly fired another shot.

But this shot missed. Chaotic Grenades in the wind weren’t so easy to hit. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim hit one of two shots. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain only had time for one shot, but she missed as well.

After two gunshots and one cannonshot, the grenades had flown into Happy’s midst. Happy’s players didn’t have the time to split up and dodge, because these grenades had simply come too quickly, and the range they covered was simply too large.

And so they didn’t dodge, and instead used this tiny amount of time to contract their formation slightly.

Qi Guard!

In the end, the skill that Happy used to resist was a Qi Guard from Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea.

It wouldn’t be enough, would it?

In this moment, everyone thought this way, because a Qi Guard could only take so much damage; it wasn’t an unbreakable shield. And with so many grenades from the Chaotic Grenades, even though some were primarily effect-based and wouldn’t cause much damage, a Qi Guard would be far from enough to block them all.

Boom!

The Qi Guard hadn’t even completely formed before a grenade crashed against it with an explosion.

A cloud of green gas spewed outward, diffusing along the outer shell of the Qi Guard.

Poison Gas Grenade, represented by the color green in this game to signify its poisonous property.

The Qi Guard couldn’t be Poisoned, but the poison gas still eroded it.

Immediately afterwards, an Electric Grenade exploded, sending currents of electricity sparking along the Qi Guard.

And then a Timed Grenade. If it hadn’t hit its time limit, an impact would not cause it to explode, and so when it hit the Qi Guard, it simply bounced along the top.

And then there were ordinary Impact Grenades, Remote Grenades, and others. It seemed like they all hit at the same time, but they were actually slightly staggered as they hit the Qi Guard.

The sound of explosions was nonstop, and the Qi Guard was quickly shattered. But what about the grenades that hadn’t exploded yet, that could still attack?

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella swung open, and the grenades that broke through the Qi Guard exploded on the surface of the umbrella. An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands also immediately set up a Great Heal, restoring the health Lord Grim had lost while holding up the umbrella shield.

Facing this Chaotic Grenades that had come from the wind, Happy’s members cooperated on all levels without wavering at all.

But Blue Rain’s offensive had only just begun.

Troubling Rain, Flowing Cloud, Blue Rain’s two Blade Masters were already slashing their way forward. They both used a Triple Slash to open the way, and with the effects of the wind, they moved like twin shooting stars. Close behind the Chaotic Grenades, they had already rushed out of the wind zone, but they were still moving incomparably quickly with the wind’s momentum.

Meteor Form!

The two Blade Masters unleashed the same skill, but Flowing Cloud used a greatsword while Troubling Rain wielded a lightsaber, so because of the weapon difference, the two versions of the same skill still showed a slight difference in speed.

Troubling Rain was slightly faster; Flowing Cloud slightly slower.

But this slowness was only relative to Troubling Rain’s quickness. With the lingering momentum from the wind, and the fact that Meteor Form was the fastest skill of a Blade Master, this wasn’t a speed that a human could capture.

Two silhouettes, two arcs of swordlight, swept into Happy’s formation, carrying two trails of scarlet blood. And then in the blink of an eye, coordinating with the teammates that were still in the wind zone, they began to move against Happy from both sides. But at the same time…

“Your face!”

A shout from Steamed Bun flashed in the match channel. Steamed Bun Invasion threw out a Sand Toss, directly toward the faces of Troubling Rain and Flowing Cloud right as they were finishing their Meteor Forms and spinning around.

But both of them reacted extremely quickly. One to the left and one to the right, at the same time as they angled their camera views away, the swords in their hands were already swinging upward.

Upwards Slash.

A skill that couldn’t get any more ordinary. Under normal circumstances, Steamed Bun would have no trouble dodging this attack.

But at this moment, the two Blade Masters were coordinating with two Upwards Slashes, one slightly faster, one slightly slower; one from the left, one from the right; one with a short blade, one with a long blade. With this, all of the space where Steamed Bun could dodge was sealed off.

Fortunately, Steamed Bun wasn’t the only Happy player here.

Sword Draw!

Lord Grim had just used the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella to block the Chaotic Grenades before their formation was invaded and he was hit by the unimaginably quick Meteor Form. But now, with the momentum he’d taken from that attack, he twisted his body, as though chasing the blood that had been sent flying by the slash. A Sword Draw flashed outward, slicing the threads of blood in two as it slashed toward Troubling Rain and Flowing Cloud.

Clang!

A resounding sound.

Lord Grim’s Sword Draw was from a left-handed sword, so it was a slash from right to left. From the point of view of the Blade Masters, Troubling Rain was on the left, while Flowing Cloud was on the right. With this attack from Lord Grim, Troubling Rain suddenly canceled his Upwards Slash, and instead pointed his sword straight upward, using the Blade Master skill Guard just in time to parry Lord Grim’s Sword Draw.

Because this Sword Draw was from right to left, when Troubling Rain blocked it, he had no way to continue slashing rightward. Flowing Cloud continued his Upwards Slash unimpeded. And Steamed Bun hadn’t reacted to this change yet, so that even though Huang Shaotian left this opening for him, it was too late for him to dodge. In the end, he was still lifted into the air by Flowing Cloud’s attack.

And when Troubling Rain blocked this Sword Draw, his body slid backward. Flowing Cloud’s Upwards Slash succeeded, and the sliding Troubling Rain was already using a Sky-Plunging Blade.

When that attack came out, it looked like it was getting farther and farther away from Steamed Bun Invasion, but in the end, the glinting sword energy at the tip of the blade was just enough to hit Steamed Bun Invasion.

Flowing Cloud withdrew his Upwards Slash, and after Troubling Rain’s Sky-Plunging Blade, he used another precisely-timed skill. There was no pause in the offensive of these two players as they continue to land attack after attack on Steamed Bun Invasion. The skilled coordination between the dual Blade Masters was incredible enough to render the entire stadium silent.

On this end was the invasion of two Blade Masters into the formation; on the other end, Swoksaar and Bullet Rain, who were still in the midst of the wind, were using the wind’s momentum for their attacks.

But Swoksaar was a Warlock, and his curses would come out as they were supposed to. They couldn’t borrow the wind’s momentum. But there was nothing to lose from him standing in the wind, and it offered him some defensive protection. When Dancing Rain fired a cannon shot toward him, as soon as it entered the wind zone, it very noticeably slowed down and found it more difficult to fly forward. Facing such a long-ranged attack, dodging was a trivial matter. It was as if Swoksaar were standing in some kind of safe zone where he could calmly and steadily cast his curses. Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain, meanwhile, continued to rely on the wind to greatly boost his own attack rhythm.

Gusty Garden. As expected of a map that Blue Rain chose at their most critical moment. Just using the gusts from the wind source, they were able to play such a thrilling offensive.

Chapter 1463 - Not So Simple

Pan Lin and Li Yibo didn’t spare any effort on the praise, giving them all to Blue Rain’s current assault. The first wave of Chaotic Grenades had perfectly neutralized by Happy’s teamwork, but the pincer attack from the two Blade Masters that followed had Happy struggling to cope.

They had slipped up!

The more observant viewers realized that Happy’s formation had scattered somewhat. If it was just against Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen’s two Blade Masters then, no matter how amazing their teamwork was, a 2v5 was practically impossible to win. However, Blue Rain didn’t just have just those two. Swoksaar, a Warlock with powerful CC abilities, stood in a windy area. Bullet Rain, a Sharpshooter with high DPS AoE attacks, could inflict all sorts of CC too. These two classes weren’t classes whose assaults you could deal with just by relying on a healer for support. The two stood in the windy area, throwing their attacks cheerfully.

Happy was downwind. They wouldn’t be able to get any advantage from charging into and fighting in the windy area. If they sent ranged attacks from outside of the windy area, then the attacks would be hindered by the wind and their power would be decreased. As a result, even though they were charging into a five character formation, the two Blade Masters weren’t feeling too much pressure. Instead, with the support and CC from the ranged characters in the windy area, the assault went smoothly.

“Happy’s in a bit of a mess!” Li Yibo exclaimed.

This was the first time the two sides had really clashed, but Happy seemed to be sliding down a slippery slope already. Their original formation had shattered, their players not cooperating, all of them fighting as individuals… This was a one-sided slaughter!

Was this battle going to be decided so soon?

Swoosh swoosh swoosh….

The sword light from Blue Rain’s Blade Master duo shimmered brightly, their swords becoming one deadly system, striking their enemies down.

“Scared yet? Scared yet!” Huang Shaotian was even spamming the chat. Mockery wouldn’t affect his performance or judgment, but it didn’t mean he didn’t mind it. He minded it very much, but the more he did, the more calm he would be, using his actions to express himself. Once his plans had succeeded, then trash talk was easily within reach. In the blink of an eye, forty-seven “scared yet”s appeared on the screen.

“Not at all.”

Naturally, it was Ye Xiu who was able to reply at such a time. Huang Shaotian glanced towards Lord Grim, but he suppressed the urge to immediately charge over and stab him. He was trying to determine whether going up to teach this guy a lesson was the best choice he had right now.

It seemed like a good idea.

Huang Shaotian swept his gaze over the battlefield. Happy’s five characters were scattered, and Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen didn’t have the ability to pursue them all at once, so they needed to lock onto a target. As for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim? He was right on the edge of the gale wind area. If they pursued, they could force him into the gale and then using their upwind advantage…

Wait a moment!

At this point, Huang Shaotian realized something.

If they pressed Lord Grim into the gale from this position, then the upwind advantage would be something only Swoksaar and Bullet Rain had. On the other hand, Troubling Rain and Flowing Cloud would be downwind just like Lord Grim…

Trying to be clever?

Huang Shaotian immediately reorganized his thought processes, sneering. Ye Xiu was the heart and soul of Happy. If they could wipe him from the game, then it would probably be even more effective than taking out their healer. However, it wasn’t the right opportunity. What about their healer? Huang Shaotian turned to look at Little Cold Hands, but the other was a little too far…

Happy, in the end, understood the importance of healers. Even scattered, they remembered to make sure to protect their healer. An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands had run off. If they went in pursuit, it would take some effort. Plus… Huang Shaotian looked over the battlefield and noticed something else.

Had Happy fallen into chaos? Yes, but there was a method to their chaos.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was bait. If Huang Shaotian and and Lu Hanwen teamed up against him, and pushed him into the windy zone, then using his tailwind advantage, he could suppress them. The others in Happy would probably use this chance to rearrange themselves and take an advantageous position. Thus, they definitely couldn’t go after Lord Grim.

What about Little Cold Hands?

He was a little far, but if Happy really had been thrown into chaos, it wouldn’t be too hard to close in on their healer. However, it might look like Happy was scattered, but they all stayed in range of Little Cold Hands’ position. Little Cold Hands was yet another trap. If Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen attacked him, Happy might surround the two of them.

How crafty!

Huang Shaotian saw through two of their tricks in one go and couldn’t help but be surprised.. At this point, many people probably thought that Happy was done for. Those who thought that way were underestimating Happy too much.

“Steamed Bun!”

That was when, in the Blue Rain party chat, Captain Yu Wenzhou gave them a clear attack target.

From afar, Yu Wenzhou had a better view of the overall situation.

His thoughts matched Huang Shaotian’s. Happy was in chaos, but there was a method to it. They still had tricks up their sleeve. For example, Lord Grim as bait, Little Cold Hands’ trap. For someone who hadn’t noticed anything wrong, they would probably choose one of these two crucial members of Happy as their primary attack target. However, Huang Shaotian noticed, and so did Yu Wenzhou.

These two characters were temporarily off limits. Happy still had three other characters. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was a ranged unit. As soon as the battle erupted, she pulled away as far as possible. Right now, not even Swoksaar nor Bullet Rain could hit her, so what were Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen going to be able to do?

Then there was Fang Rui. He was a slippery, hard to catch fellow, and his Boundless Sea would flee from trouble without hesitation. If Yu Wenzhou and Zheng Xuan wanted to effectively attack him, then they would have to move forwards. The further forwards they moved, the less protection they would get from the windy zone, and the less the windy zone would buff their attacks. Who knew if this Fang Rui was yet another bait?

Then, there only remained Steamed Bun Invasion.

Was this too a trap? Yu Wenzhou had, naturally, considered this. However, he tossed the idea aside after careful consideration. Steamed Bun Invasion was Happy’s most unpredictable and out-of-whack member.

He was, after all, a rookie, and a rookie that would occasionally roll straight off the tracks, Yu Wenzhou thought to himself.

Speaking of which, their team, Blue Rain, could integrate all sorts of strange players, but what about this Steamed Bun? Would they be able to integrate him into their strategic system? This was something Yu Wenzhou had considered before, in his spare time. It was clear that he never underestimated Steamed Bun.

Yet after thinking it over, Yu Wenzhou hadn’t thought of any way to integrate Steamed Bun into Blue Rain’s strategic system.

Like Ye Xiu, Yu Wenzhou had no way of completely understanding and predicting Steamed Bun’s behavior on the field. Blue Rain’s style revolved around making up for one another’s faults to create a stronger whole. For any two members of Blue Rain, they could form a complete whole. However, this Steamed Bun, his crazy moments weren’t something anyone else could get any warning of. How would they form any synergy like that? How would they form a strategic whole with that?

Perhaps, Yu Wenzhou thought, Steamed Bun wasn’t a team competition kind of player. Yet, today, he saw Happy arrange for Steamed Bun in their team competition lineup. To Yu Wenzhou, this was a daring and risky move.

It was hard to say if Steamed Bun’s unpredictability would be more of a hindrance to his enemies or his teammates. In the playoffs, where a single mistake could lose them everything, no team would dare arrange for a ticking time bomb like that to play.

But Happy dared, and it wasn’t as if they had no other choice. That player called Qiao Yifan was much more stable than Steamed Bun, much more reliable. There was also Wei Chen. It wouldn’t be impossible for him to set alight his passions and give another spectacular performance. Or what about that Luo Ji? He wasn’t as skilled, but his style was very detailed and methodical. A player like that would be much safer as a part of the tactical system than Steamed Bun, no? There was also Mo Fan. Though his style was too individualized, but with training and practice, he would be able to adjust and play a solid part of the strategy.

It was only Steamed Bun, whose unpredictability wouldn’t be able to compensated for with tactics. However, it was Steamed Bun who was chosen for this team competition.

Well, since this was how things were, then why not go for it? Yu Wenzhou didn’t think any further. Steamed Bun couldn’t be predicted, so he told everyone to be on their guard and focus, so that they would be able to react appropriately no matter if this guy acted as a god-like opponent, or a pig-like teammate.

So far, Steamed Bun had yet to become godlike, and was out of tune with the rest of Happy, thus he became Blue Rain’s breakthrough point. Yu Wenzhou didn’t hesitate. After he made this judgment, he immediately told the entirety of Blue Rain to target Steamed Bun Invasion.

Collapsing Mountain!

Lu Hanwen charged fearlessly, throwing out a Collapsing Mountain at its longest range. This use of Collapsing Mountain let him leap further and created a greater impact, but it was slow to act and had a longer ending lag. Pro players rarely ever used it to initiate a fight.

But right now, Lu Hanwen had Huang Shaotian cover for him. Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain would be the follow up to this rarely used form of Collapsing Mountain.

No one knew if Steamed Bun had noticed such a deeply thought out cooperative arrangement. Either way, he didn’t receive this Collapsing Mountain. With two consecutive back jumps, he dashed out of range. He could tell that Blue Rain was going to concentrate their fire on him from what he saw of their actions.

“Holy crap, so many people ganging up on me!” Steamed Bun exclaimed in the match chat. The tone that bellied these words, it was almost like he couldn’t comprehend why a team would do something so common to team competitions.

“1v1 me! Do you dare to fight me 1v1?” Steamed Bun yelled.

Blue Rain thought he was trash talking. They naturally ignored him, going in for the kill.

“Where’s that Leo? Come and fight me! Didn’t you cry and scream about wanting to fight me 1v1 back then?” Steamed Bun continued.

Everyone exchanged looks.

What on earth was going on? Leo? That was referring to Huang Shaotian, right? Team Blue Rain’s hardcore fans were naturally familiar with their ace’s star sign.

But… Huang Shaotian screaming and crying about wanting to fight Steamed Bun 1v1?

Everyone was suddenly very interested in this piece of gossip.

“What the hell are you going on about!!” Huang Shaotian immediately bristled. He had wanted to fight, but it wasn’t directed at Steamed Bun! And screaming and crying? Not even in your dreams.

“I’m giving you a chance now.” Steamed Bun was still going on.

“KILL HIM!!!” Huang Shaotian yelled. At this point, the target of his anger and their team’s attack target overlapped perfectly.

This… they could feel real killing intent here! Everyone thought to themselves.

Chapter 1464 - Bomb Disposal Specialist

“Scaredy-cat Leo!” Steamed Bun sternly reprimanded Huang Shaotian in the chat.

Huang Shaotian was pissed!

There was no way anyone would ever agree to a 1v1 duel in the middle of a team battle, right? So why was this guy so seriously insisting on this? That brimming hostility, it was unbearable!

Downwind Sword Slash!

The swift sword light well represented Huang Shaotian’s current mood. He would never lose his cool over the mockery of trash talk, but as it happened, the one who spewed trash talk right now was the optimal attack target, so without any pressure, he could use his official role to satisfy his personal interests. His mood was beautifully expressed, and the timing, angle, and speed of this Downwind Sword Slash reached the peak, completely flawless.

Hit!

No one could have dodged or blocked this kind of attack.

The bladelight scattered fresh blood outward. Steamed Bun Invasion was sent pathetically tumbling onto the ground. But with this, he was really rolling quite far!

“Not bad, kid!” Huang Shaotian sent in the chat. Pro players were very sensitive to distance, because that was how they chose the most suitable skill to use at any given moment. Steamed Bun seemed to be helplessly rolling along the ground as a result of the ferocity of the Downwind Sword Slash, but in reality, he was using the momentum of this strike to put some distance between himself and his attacker. The posture was a but ugly, but he achieved the goal he wanted.

This Downwind Sword Slash on its own was indeed executed impeccably. But a good offensive was like a banquet, composed of many different dishes. It couldn’t rely on just one.

Steamed Bun Invasion used this Downwind Sword Slash to increase the distance. If the close-range Blade Master wanted to close in again, then the Brawler could use mid-range techniques to counter him. From this, it could be seen that even though this Downwind Sword Slash was flawless, it couldn’t become a banquet. The attack landed, but it didn’t consider the follow up.

In the end, had Huang Shaotian been too impulsive?

This Downwind Sword Slash, displaying Huang Shaotian’s annoyance, would lead people to think this way. But those who thought this way were overlooking the fact that this was a team battle, not individual. Huang Shaotian wasn’t the only cook for this banquet. By itself, this Downwind Sword Slash might have left an opening, but in a team battle, there were teammates that could cover this opening. Huang Shaotian used this skill, not because he had lost his judgment in a fit of anger, but because this was a team battle, and he trusted that there were enough people next to him that could cover this opening.

Curse!

Bullets!

When Huang Shaotian’s Blade Master could no longer attack because of the distance, the long-range attackers Yu Wenzhou and Zheng Xuan immediately gave firepower support.

After the Downwind Sword Slash, the two skills of the two characters immediately followed, and there was even cooperation between them as well.

Steamed Bun’s reaction speed and control was good, but the attacks of these two characters cut off all space he had to dodge.

The curses of a Warlock and the firepower of a Spitfire.

Of the two skills, he would have to choose one to be hit by in the end. Steamed Bun was very decisive, and he twisted his body toward the bullets that Bullet Rain fired toward him.

Under typical circumstances, players would want to choose to take the skill that damaged them less, but the problem was that the attacks from these two classes both had more painful effects than just damage.

Swoksaar had used a Binding Curse. It wouldn’t cause any damage at all, but it would imprison the target character.

What about Bullet Rain? He had fired Freezing Bullets, which carried the Freeze effect. It only had a certain chance of activating, but all of the Gunner subclasses, aside from Launchers, could attack with consecutive, continuous shots. The Spitfire’s Freezing Bullet could be considered a buff, and the action to use it was changing the magazine. After changing the magazine, normal fired bullets would become Freezing Bullets. Under the Spitfire Classing skill Ammunition Expansion, this magazine could hold as many as twenty Freezing Bullets.

If one bullet had a certain probability of causing a Freeze, with twenty bullets, it would be very difficult to avoid every single one. When all bullets hit, it was fairly common to become entirely Frozen.

Right now, Steamed Bun Invasion forcefully headed in this direction, and was swiftly hit by a series of bullets. Freeze took effect, and his movements instantly slowed down. But for now, he hadn’t been completely Frozen. This was also the reason to choose this direction instead of going toward Swoksaar’s Binding Curse. Moving more slowly was always a bit better than being unable to move at all.

But this was such a shallow reasoning, so of course, Blue Rain had thought of it as well. When Yu Wenzhou and Zheng Xuan launched their pincer attack, they had already calculated that Steamed Bun Invasion would choose to head toward the area covered by the Freezing Bullets.

sword light flashed.

When Troubling Rain used his Downwind Sword Slash, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud was rushing forward to cooperate. The light of his blade ultimately fell upon the area where Bullet Rain’s bullets pointed. Blue Rain’s offensive wasn’t conducted by one person, it was a combination of four people landing upon Steamed Bun Invasion.

But while Blue Rain had four players, Happy had more than just Steamed Bun Invasion as well. Even while focusing on Steamed Bun Invasion, Yu Wenzhou hadn’t overlooked Happy’s other four players, either. The fire from Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain could cover the whole map, and she immediately began giving support. And her judgment overlapped with Blue Rain’s actions very well – the cannonfire was already covering the position toward which Flowing Cloud was charging.

What an incredibly accurate prediction.

A prediction of Blue Rain’s coordination as a team, a prediction of the awareness of Blue Rain’s players.

Su Mucheng’s attack landed at the same time as Lu Hanwen’s attack, but Su Mucheng’s target was precisely Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud.

Boom!

The explosion sent waves of energy rippling outward, and that sword light from Flowing Cloud wavered. All of this happened so quickly, just in the span of a few seconds, so precisely that it seemed as though everyone had rehearsed it beforehand. Flowing Cloud arrived, the cannonfire arrived, there was no chance at all for Lu Hanwen to dodge.

An opening!

Flowing Cloud’s attack was destroyed by Dancing Rain, and Steamed Bun Invasion immediately had an opening before him. But Yu Wenzhou, who was cool-headedly paying attention to the entire field, had noticed Dancing Rain’s attack and anticipated that Flowing Cloud’s attack would be broken. So, Swoksaar cast another spell, covering this opening in advance.

Claws of Darkness!

From the void, black claws gleaming with demonic power extended forth, snatching toward Steamed Bun Invasion. This attack was also a predictive attack, a prediction of the opponent’s movements.

But, unfortunately, this was Steamed Bun that Yu Wenzhou was trying to predict.

The Claws of Darkness snatched downward, the flowers of the devil were blooming, but where was Steamed Bun Invasion?

With a roll, Steamed Bun Invasion had actually rolled back to where he was before.

The so-called opening was that, using the cover from Dancing Rain’s fire, he could continue in the same direction to break free from Blue Rain’s attacking him. But Steamed Bun didn’t head in that direction, and instead went back toward the position where he had been surrounded and trapped.

Had he also predicted Swoksaar’s attack against him?

Those who liked to overthink situations would of course consider this situation. But even those who were familiar with Steamed Bun, couldn’t determine how he had had that shining eureka moment.

“Maybe that was just convenient for him?” In Happy’s player area, those who weren’t onstage speculated.

But even though this was an unexpected movement, aside from avoiding this Claws of Darkness from Swoksaar, there wasn’t anything particularly shining about this.

The Freeze effect on Steamed Bun Invasion’s body hadn’t worn off yet. If he was hit by another attack with a Freeze effect, the chances of him becoming completely Frozen would greatly increase. Bullet Rain hadn’t finished firing his twenty Freezing Bullets yet, and with Steamed Bun Invasion returning to his former position, it was very easy for Zheng Xuan to fire at him. The Freezing Bullets immediately chased him.

He just acted a bit unexpectedly…

Even Yu Wenzhou thought this way. Someone acting unexpectedly didn’t automatically guarantee that they could win the initiative. If a sword came down on an opponent and that opponent didn’t dodge at all, that would also be very unexpected, but could that cleaved opponent really be said to have the advantage?

Steamed Bun Invasion’s action, aside from dodging the Claws of Darkness, was truly a disastrous movement.

But the bullets that Bullet Rain fired were actually completely blocked in midair.

Prediction. Again, prediction.

And this time, the one who made an accurate prediction was Ye Xiu.

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella blocked all of the Freezing Bullets, and suddenly, a large path was opened before Steamed Bun’s eyes.

This time, Steamed Bun didn’t trip up, and he immediately controlled Steamed Bun Invasion to charge onto this path. The still half-Frozen Steamed Bun Invasion seemed to be moving in slow-motion, and it was very amusing to watch. But the cover of his teammates allowed him to resolutely walk forward. Lord Grim helped blocked the attacks from Bullet Rain, while Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain blasted a Firing Line next to him, causing a great deal of trouble for the two Blade Masters controlled by Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen if they wanted to catch up and attack.

A suicidal trip, ultimately inviting a turnaround. Why?

Yu Wenzhou’s gaze landed upon Lord Grim.

He had never understood why Happy wanted to use Steamed Bun, such an unreliable player, for such a crucial match, but now, he was beginning to see why.

The reason was very simple: it was all because of Ye Xiu’s presence.

Even though he also had no way of predicting Steamed Bun’s actions, his experience and awareness allowed him to maximally cover Steamed Bun’s openings.

This was perhaps a way of turning the rotten into the miraculous, or perhaps he was only barely able to control the situation. But this ticking time bomb that was Steamed Bun – Happy had their bomb disposal expert, but on Blue Rain’s side, which of them could take care of the danger that Steamed Bun posed at any moment?

Ye Xiu’s all-class experience and awareness was not something that everyone had.

Steamed Bun was a player that often exposed vulnerabilities, but Happy purposely took advantage of this fact. Under the unpredictable rhythm of battle that this guy led, which side would ultimately take control?

In Yu Wenzhou’s mind, behind Steamed Bun Invasion appeared, with unparalleled clarity, the figures of Lord Grim and Ye Xiu.

Would they once again be beaten at their own game?

Chapter 1465 - Attack the Core

During the regular season, Blue Rain was one of the few teams that defeated Happy twice in the team round. No, more accurately, it was three times. During their last match in the playoffs, even though Blue Rain had lost in the end, they had defeated Happy in the team round.

Three victories against Happy. Logically, they should be relatively experienced in dealing with them. But, as Blue Rain’s commander, Yu Wenzhou didn’t have that feeling at all.

Two meetings in the regular season, and then their last meeting during the playoffs. Three battles against Happy, and they had all felt different.

This wasn’t just because of Happy’s adjustments in terms of players and tactics. Over the course of these three battles, what was even more clear to see was Happy’s growth.

Ever since entering the pro scene, Happy’s players were recklessly absorbing experience and growing up at a crazy rate. Every year brought new teams, and these new teams, after entering the high-end refinery that was the pro scene, all demonstrated clear improvement. But Happy was the only one that had reached such heights so fast.

Most people looked at Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, and Fang Rui. They felt that because Happy had three All-Star level players, they weren’t a typical new team, and that was why they could have such a strong performance.

But was that the only reason?

Consider Happy’s three All-Star level players.

Ye Xiu had left the pro scene for a year and a half and was now playing a new unspecialized class; Su Mucheng had left the pro scene for a year; Fang Rui had been standing at the pinnacle of Thieves before switching classes.

These three people all had their own problems. In fact, it could be said that they were among Happy’s weaknesses. For Happy to become such an unusual new team, it definitely wasn’t only because of the presence of these three All-Star level players.

Improvement. This was the key word shared by Happy and all other new teams. And the biggest difference between Happy and these other new teams was that Happy was able to completely turn their improvement into capability.

As long as the players became stronger, the team’s capabilities would increase, right?

This logic seemed obvious. But in reality, even though this logic worked in 1v1s, in team battles, this statement wasn’t so certain.

A team needed cooperation, needed understanding, needed mutual adaptation.

When a new team’s players began to grow, quickly or slowly, could the team stay whole and adjust appropriately to this kind of growth?

This wasn’t a simple matter. The biggest difference between Happy and the others was that Happy achieved this point very well. They were adjusting nonstop in response to the improvements made by the individual players.

In the end… it was still because of that guy, the one at Happy’s helm, Ye Xiu. He accurately grasped the fabric of Happy, and he let all the teams that only faced Happy once in the span of months feel the leaping growth of their battle ability. They were able to completely take advantage of that exceptional growth that characterized new teams.

And when they stood on the battlefield?

Countless scenes from Happy’s battles flashed through Yu Wenzhou’s mind.

The immature Happy had many weaknesses, but when opponents tried to charge toward Happy’s so-called weaknesses, how many teams were actually able to use that to crush Happy?

Happy had areas where they had yet to mature; they had areas where they weren’t good enough. But Happy themselves knew all of this, clearer than their opponents did, and so they had ample preparations to counter those who tried to attack their weak areas.

It all came back to Ye Xiu…

In Yu Wenzhou’s mind, the image of Ye Xiu and Lord Grim continued to sharpen, and what he covered was no longer simply Steamed Bun and Steamed Bun Invasion – it was the entirety of Happy!

If we don’t defeat this guy, we have no way of truly defeating Happy!

Those so-called breakthrough points, weaknesses, could all turn into reversals because of the presence of one person.

To defeat Happy, Yu Wenzhou discovered that what he had to do was so simple, yet not at all.

Defeat Ye Xiu.

Yes! That was all.

Beat Ye Xiu, and you can beat Happy.

This goal simply sounded like nonsense. Because this sentence could be applied to any team.

Beat Wang Jiexi, and you can beat Tiny Herb.

Beat Zhou Zekai, and you can beat Samsara.

Beat Han Wenqing, and you can beat Tyranny.

Every team had its core, and if the core was defeated, the chances of victory would greatly increase. But a core was a core because it was the most difficult person to beat in the entire team.

To beat them, you would have to pay an unusual price.

Just like that Happy versus Tiny Herb match, where Happy forcefully took down Wang Jiexi, trading two for one. And in the end, their plan worked, and they beat Tiny Herb.

The battle had been thrilling, but Yu Wenzhou didn’t agree with the reliability of that method. In that battle, it could be said that they won because they defeated Wang Jiexi, but it would be better to say that by defeating Wang Jiexi, they destroyed the confidence of the rest of the Tiny Herb players.

That was the main reason why Tiny Herb had lost. If the other players hadn’t wavered because of this, the fact was that the core player had traded themselves for two players and achieved the advantage of numbers. Many teams probably wouldn’t find that a difficult trade at all.

Happy targeted Wang Jiexi not for a strategic victory, but a psychological victory. That was why they could strive for this without worrying about the cost.

And this had been possible because of the problem with Tiny Herb itself.

If it had been Samsara, and they’d tried to trade two players for Zhou Zekai; or if it had been Tyranny, two for Han Wenqing, the result likely would not have been the same.

Then right now, against Happy, against Ye Xiu, could they use this kind of method?

In Blue Rain’s team channel, the captain’s directions suddenly appeared: Attack Ye Xiu.

They could!

After reflection, this was the conclusion that Yu Wenzhou ultimately drew.

To Tiny Herb, Wang Jiexi was the backbone of their spirit; to Happy, Ye Xiu was the backbone of their strategy.

In those scenes from Happy’s battles that had flashed through his mind, Ye Xiu was like a foundational rock. Wherever he was needed was wherever he was moved.

Without his support, Team Happy wouldn’t be able to tie together into a whole. And on this battlefield, the ticking time bomb that was Steamed Bun Invasion would lose his bomb disposal expert.

Defeat Ye Xiu! That would destroy the structure of Happy’s strategy, and without that linchpin, Happy would show many openings. At that time, it was likely that no one would be able to patch them up well enough.

Yu Wenzhou gave this direction, and Blue Rain immediately began to carry it out.

Troubling Rain, Flowing Cloud, one fast blade and one slow, suddenly flung off Steamed Bun Invasion and pointed toward Lord Grim.

“Damn!” Steamed Bun immediately started mocking them. “You can’t even take care of me and you still want to take care of our boss?”

Steamed Bun’s words were only because he was still alive. To be honest, this powerful offense that Blue Rain had launched against him had rendered him quite helpless.

“Little guys move aside!” Huang Shaotian rudely replied. His lightsaber Ice Rain had already pierced toward Lord Grim’s heart.

Whoosh whoosh, Lord Grim’s silhouette flashed like a ghost, and suddenly he had already moved to Troubling Rain’s side.

Ice Rain hit air, but Troubling Rain immediately turned, and the slightly slower Flowing Cloud bolstered the attack as he continued to stab toward Lord Grim.

Lord Grim tried to move again, but Swoksaar’s curses and Bullet Rain’s firepower together sealed his paths of retreat.

Lord Grim, without anywhere to run, instantly became a crowd of shadows.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Lord Grim left behind a fake body while his real body was taken away. The first phase of Blue Rain’s offensive ultimately missed.

But the whole team adjusted its offensive very quickly and continued to attack. Happy’s scattered formation had yet to restabilize.

Yu Wenzhou continued to carefully watch the whole situation. When they began focusing all their attack on Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim, how would Happy adjust? Yu Wenzhou didn’t dare let down his guard. Especially since they were attacking Ye Xiu, it would be very easy for this guy to lead him into a trap. He had to pay careful attention to the development of the battle as a whole.

Yu Wenzhou’s gaze passed over Happy’s players, one by one.

Someone’s missing!

Yu Wenzhou suddenly discovered.

“Where’s Fang Rui?” Yu Wenzhou asked in the chat.

“Circling around,” said Zheng Xuan.

Yu Wenzhou let out a breath. He’d missed one character, but fortunately, he had his teammates.

Fang Rui circling around, that was almost certainly to take advantage of the wind. The force of the wind didn’t affect a Warlock’s curses or a few other spells, but fire-type magic and a Qi Master’s qi could be strengthened by the wind’s momentum.

Knowing the opponent’s intent, naturally he could counter it. But Blue Rain didn’t do anything for now, because if they defended too early, then Fang Rui would withdraw his plan. Might as well use the opponent’s move against him, let him circle around, wait for him to try and attack before discovering that he was thwarted.

Blue Rain continued to chase Lord Grim, until their heads hurt.

Lord Grim’s movement was simply too fast – it was like he was leading them on a train ride. From afar, Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain showered them in cannonfire.

But all of this was within Yu Wenzhou’s expectations. Swoksaar’s skills now were like a guiding beacon. Under his adjustments, Blue Rain’s chase was not impatient. The two Blade Masters Troubling Rain and Flowing Cloud didn’t attack hand in hand; Troubling Rain chased more tightly, while Flowing Cloud lagged slightly behind. Zheng Xuan and Yu Wenzhou’s characters were still in the wind zone, moving parallel, and their healer was also closely keeping up with the team’s rhythm.

Lord Grim hadn’t been chased down, but inadvertently, Fang Rui’s plot to circle around was already interrupted. Blue Rain, in chasing Lord Grim, had changed their position drastically, so their back was no longer their back. Where Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea entered the wind zone, he was now at a crosswind with Blue Rain’s players, so that neither side had the advantage.

Fang Rui controlled Boundless Sea to move, because he still wanted to pull out the angle to get the wind advantage, but he ended up running this circle in vain.

In the wind zone, Happy’s few players were helping Ye Xiu as much as they could.

It was about time.

Yu Wenzhou coldly assessed the situation.

Another message appeared in the team chat: 1, Ye Xiu, cut Steamed Bun.

The offensive changed again.

Steamed Bun. Blue Rain’s target was still Steamed Bun. But one player was left next to Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim.

Troubling Rain, Huang Shaotian.

The “1” referred to BOX-1. Team Blue Rain was using Huang Shaotian to execute BOX-1 against Ye Xiu.

Because Ye Xiu was the core of Happy’s strategy, then BOX-1 was the perfect strategy to use. But Ye Xiu was a demon, and if they tried to do it directly, there was probably no one who would be able to directly restrict him. And so Blue Rain first used a powerful all-around attack, relying on their numbers to advantage. They let Fang Rui go so that Happy’s side over here would be even weaker, like luring the tiger off the mountain. And when the time was right, Huang Shaotian would hold down Ye Xiu, and the others would attack Steamed Bun.

This time, if Ye Xiu wanted to defuse the bomb, it wouldn’t be so easy.

Chapter 1466 - Qi in the Wind

“Hey! What was that for!” Steamed Bun cried out in the chat. Even though he wasn’t as chatty as Huang Shaotian, he was still far more talkative than most players. Rookies, in particular, would almost always play careful, completely focused on their playing. There were truly very few rookies who trash talked during a match.

Not only was Steamed Bun talkative, his words were good at catching the attention of other people. It was a normal many-against-few situation, yet he was scolding the enemies as if they were in the wrong. Blue Rain’s sudden change in targets cut off Steamed Bun’s connection with Ye Xiu and angered him. It was as if Blue Rain had offended the heavens, and he needed to give them justice.

“What are you guys thinking!” Steamed Bun shouted.

No one in Blue Rain answered back. The three characters focused on Steamed Bun. However, for this BOX-1 strategy to work, the conflict between Ye Xiu and Huang Shaotian was the key point.

“Can you get past me?” Huang Shaotian wasn’t idle. He quickly joined the chat. Although Steamed Bun was a strange one, he couldn’t outshine Huang Shaotian. The disparity in word count was too big.

“Annoying,” Ye Xiu replied back with a single word. Lord Grim twisted his body in an attempt to get past Huang Shaotian.

Huang Shaotian reacted extremely fast. Troubling Rain turned around and lifted his sword, Headwind Strike!

Headwind Strike was originally a circular attack, but under Huang Shaotian’s control, it spun around into a flat ellipse, covering quite a bit of horizontal distance.

Jump back.

Not only did Lord Grim fail to get past Troubling Rain, he was forced back a step.

Boom boom boom.

Artillery fire descended.

Su Mucheng didn’t support Steamed Bun, who was in a more dangerous situation. Instead, she prioritized Troubling Rain.

2v1, 3v1.

Were they planning on making a trade? Or did Su Mucheng want to help Ye Xiu break free from Huang Shaotian.

The viewers weren’t sure, not even Pan Lin or Li Yibo dared to make any conclusions. The fight between the two teams was changing at a rapid pace. What’s more, Blue Rain was playing abnormally aggressive today, unlike their usual defensive counterattack style.

“Could it be because of Happy’s Bao Rongxing? Perhaps it’s easier to take the initiative by playing aggressive.” Pan Lin and Li Yibo could only guess.

The battle was developing on two ends. At this moment, the camera switched over to a character that hadn’t yet entered the fray.

Boundless Sea.

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea.

He had tried to circle around to Blue Rain’s rear, but Blue Rain noticed him and prevented it from happening. Fang Rui wasn’t willing to let the matter go and continued to try different angles. It was as if he had to use the gale to attack Blue Rain no matter w hat.

“Fang Rui… is gambling a bit…” Pan Lin said, seeing Boundless Sea stubbornly try to find a way in.

Li Yibo didn’t say anything.

It was a crucial match. Fang Rui was an incredibly experienced and crafty player, would he really make a gamble?

He probably has something else in mind. Li Yibo carefully observed Fang Rui’s movements.

Even Li Yibo was suspicious, how could Yu Wenzhou not be either?

The situation on one side of the battle was clear. Ye Xiu was being BOX-1ed by Huang Shaotian, while Su Mucheng was helping him break free. Huang Shaotian could be considered as being in a 1v2, so it looked like a BOX-2. However, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain was a Blade Master, a melee class. Dancing Rain was long-ranged, so she could fire from afar. She was taking the initiative to attack him, not Troubling Rain restricting her movements. The BOX-2 was weak. If Su Mucheng wanted to leave, she could leave. Huang Shaotian had no control over her.

He could only stop Ye Xiu, and that was his goal.

It was a 1v2 though, and he was facing the former Best Partners. The difficulty of doing so didn’t need to be said. What Huang Shaotian was doing reminded people of the previous Blue Rain vs Happy match.

In that team competition, Blue Rain’s former captain, Wei Chen, had accomplished a 1v2, no? He stalled Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou and Lu Hanwen by himself.

In the end, Wei Chen sacrificed his character to achieve these goals, but what about Huang Shaotian?

Huang Shaotian was different because he wasn’t focused on dragging down both players, but rather only Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. As long as Dancing Rain’s attacks didn’t affect his end-goal, he wouldn’t care.

He was very focused.

He didn’t care if he was being harassed by Su Mucheng.

Yu Wenzhou was overjoyed at this turn of events. He hadn’t expected the BOX-1 to last this long because after shifting their focus onto Steamed Bun Invasion, Happy’s other characters were free to do what they wanted. It would be easy for Happy to break Huang Shaotian’s BOX-1.

That was the reality. Su Mucheng decided to prioritize breaking the BOX-1.

But who would have thought that Huang Shaotian would be so tenacious?

This sort of opportunity couldn’t be wasted.

The rest of Blue Rain understood this and attacked Steamed Bun Invasion even more fiercely.

Steamed Bun didn’t even have time to type into the chat. Steamed Bun Invasion was beaten up left and right.

Although was in a sorry state, he wasn’t completely trapped.

How troublesome!

Blue Rain looked towards Happy’s other character.

Little Cold Hands, An Wenyi’s Little Cold Hands.

While they were busy with Steamed Bun, Happy’s healer was providing Steamed Bun with as much support as possible.

No one was disturbing him, and he was only focused on a single target. Under these circumstances, An Wenyi, who had exceptional timing, had God-level healing. What’s more, his character Little Cold Hands had the highest heal crit in the game, making it even harder for Steamed Bun Invasion to die.

Blue Rain had no choice but to make some adjustments. Under Yu Wenzhou’s orders, Zheng Xuan took care of Little Cold Hands. Although both were long-ranged classes, Spitfires were faster than Clerics. No one else was more suitable than him to suppress the healer.

But when Zheng Xuan fired at Little Cold Hands, he discovered that his Bullet Rain’s attack range wasn’t quite enough.

With no other choice, Zheng Xuan could only have Bullet Rain move forward. Little Cold Hand’s healing needed to be suppressed. If not, their DPS would be drastically reduced, and Huang Shaotian was dealing with a lot of pressure. His BOX-1 could be broken at any moment, so they needed to hurry.

But when Bullet Rain moved forward, Little Cold Hands moved back.

An Wenyi was aware of the enemy side’s intentions. Thus, he moved back to get out of Zheng Xuan’s attack range.

Zheng Xuan could only continue to speed up Bullet Rain’s pursuit. After Yu Wenzhou noticed the change, he suddenly felt a bad premonition. He hastily turned his head back…

Sky Piercing Strike!

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea finally made his move. Amidst the strong winds, the qi looked hazy. However, its speed was extremely fast. It seemed to meld together with the wind, and in an instant, Bullet Rain was swallowed up by the qi. Bullet Rain was sent flying as if he he had been Blown Away.

Yu Wenzhou wanted to warn him, but he was too late.

He hadn’t been ignoring Fang Rui. It was just that with his original position, Fang Rui was temporarily no threat. He had planned on doing the same as before. He would pretend to ignore him and then neutralize whatever his intentions were at the last moment. As a result, Fang Rui had always seemed invisible.

But An Wenyi suddenly tilted the scales.

Little Cold Hand’s retreat backwards made Zheng Xuan instinctively chase after him.

It wasn’t that Fang Rui had moved Boundless Sea into the correct position, but rather, Bullet Rain had gifted himself to the enemy.

All of this had taken only a split second, and all of it was because of An Wenyi’s bait.

Even Yu Wenzhou reacted to it too late.

Bullet Rain was blasted away by the Sky Piercing Cannon. Along with the momentum of the wind, the blow away effect was even stronger. Bullet Rain was directly thrown outside of the wind zone.

And when he had moved to pursue Little Cold Hands, he had stopped attacking Steamed Bun Invasion. An opening immediately appeared in Blue Rain’s assault on Steamed Bun Invasion as a result of the sudden interruption.

Steamed Bun Invasion immediately rolled and escape through the opening.

Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud attacked with his sword, but Steamed Bun Invasion responded with a Brick.

“Take this brick!”

This guy was still chatting! Who knew if it was because of his early contact with Huang Shaotian, but Steamed Bun liked to call out his moves too. He couldn’t speak in the chat, so his only choice was the chat. It had always annoyed him.

The “Take this brick!” had been sudden, but Lu Hanwen’s reaction speed was astonishing. Flowing Cloud turned his head and dodged it. The sword light continued forth, but after noticing Swoksaar’s movements, he adjusted.

“Haha, scared?” Steamed Bun noticed the change in Flowing Cloud’s attacks. Delighted, Steamed Bun Invasion took the chance to counterattack.

But little did he know, Lu Hanwen had intentionally left an opening. And this opening wasn’t for him, but for Swoksaar.

Hexagram Prison!

Pillars of light descended. Steamed Bun tried to dodge, but it was too late.

“LET ME OUT!!” Steamed Bun cried out in the chat. His Steamed Bun Invasion had been trapped by Hexagram Prison.

Having seen the situation change, Yu Wenzhou decided to stop their assault on Steamed Bun Invasion. But because of the Hexagram Prison, it was as if they pressed pause on their previous offense. First stop, resolve the issues, and then continue…

Boundless Sea!

The invisible Boundless Sea was now a threatening presence because he had finally gotten onto the tailwind of the wind zone. And the strong winds made his qi attacks even faster.

After sending out a Sky Piercing Cannon at Bullet Rain, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea headed towards Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar.

Yu Wenzhou didn’t panic. Swoksaar moved and maintained the same angle with Boundless Sea.

Fang Rui was trying for a certain angle, not just because he wanted to strengthen his attacks with the wind. More importantly, at a certain angle, Qi Masters would be suppressed by the gale. For example, if the wind and his attacks were perpendicular to each other, unless he was right next to his opponent, his qi energy would be blown away by the wind, and he would have trouble aiming his attacks.

Fang Rui probably knew this point too, but Yu Wenzhou knew it better than him.

Blue Rain had chosen this map, and Blue Rain also had a Qi Master.

This was why Yu Wenzhou dared to let Fang Rui’s Qi Master loop around them because he knew exactly how the gale helped or hindered a Qi Master.

Bullet Rain was blown back. It had been too fast for Yu Wenzhou to respond, but if Fang Rui wanted to target hise Swoksaar, then he wasn’t going to let another accident happen.

Chapter 1467 - Breakthrough

The battle was a blur to the viewers.

This team competition had too many changes happening too quickly.

Neither side had a fixed strategy. In other words, when facing each other, there was no single path that could go all the way. It could only go back and forth with both sides constantly adjusting to each other’s reactions.

Who was winning? Who was losing?

In terms of offense, Blue Rain had the greater initiative. Happy’s formation was somewhat in disarray. However, the more attentive viewers may have realized that Blue Rain had started with the tailwind advantage, but now?

Not really.

Swoksaar’s curses wouldn’t be strengthened by the gale. In fact, Swoksaar was positioned more defensively. Their healer, Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker, was also positioned more defensively.

The impact of the wind on Blue Rain’s offense was practically zero. On the other hand, Happy’s Boundless Sea was taking advantage of the wind for his attacks.

Yu Wenzhou had Swoksaar move to not give Fang Rui any opportunities to attack him. But Boundless Sea simply waved his hands in a different direction and shot out a Qi Bullet as fast as a meteor.

Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain dodged in a flurry. After getting sent flying by Boundless Sea, he had paid great attention to his existence! That guy knew how to put on an act. He looked like he was moving to attack Swoksaar, when he suddenly turned and fired at Bullet Rain.

Zheng Xuan wanted revenge. Bullet Rain fired back at Boundless Sea.

But because of the effects of the gale, Bullet Rain’s gunshot…

“Hahahaha,” Fang Rui laughed in the chat. Boundless Sea slid his palms across.

Qi Blade!

Qi Blade was a difficult-to-react-to skill in the first place. The gale only made it even harder. Zheng Xuan didn’t have time to think. Before even seeing it come out, he had Bullet Rain roll.

Did the Qi Blade come?

Zheng Xuan didn’t notice any changes in his surroundings. Suddenly, Swoksaar stumbled and nearly fell to the ground.

What’s going on?

Everyone was dumbstruck. Lord Grim? Dancing Rain? Steamed Bun Invasion? None of them had attacked Swoksaar. That meant it could have only been Boundless Sea.

“Don’t underestimate me!” Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had intentionally kept the same posture as when he had sent out the Qi Blade. His two hands weren’t facing Swoksaar.

But from the wind, they realized what had happened.

Boundless Sea had accounted for the effects of the winds in his calculations. He knew the Qi Blade would fly diagonally from where he was aiming towards Swoksaar.

The strong winds could shift the movements of the Qi Blade, but it could not disperse the qi itself. With the wind, the Qi Blade’s momentum was even stronger.

It was just that this sort of calculative ability… this was clearly the map that Blue Rain had chosen. If their Qi Master, Song Xiao, had been the one to make such an accurate shot, it wouldn’t have been too surprising. But, Fang Rui…

Fang Rui had been completely invisible before. The broadcast had given him very little screen time.

At this moment, the director went back to check Fang Rui’s movements from before. He realized that Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea hadn’t just been moving. He had been sending qi out as he moved.

Fang Rui had been measuring the effects of the wind on his qi. His accuracy wasn’t without reason. However, figuring out the wind in such a short amount of time couldn’t be done without talent.

The invisible Fang Rui and Boundless Sea immediately became the star of the show.

Amidst the winds, Boundless Sea assumed his dirty pose, half-crouching. His hands were raised to his chest, gathering swirling qi from the surroundings. Fang Rui’s incomparably dirty Qi Master suddenly looked to have the air of a great scholar again.

This was…

Qi Master Level 75 skill, a skill that had a cast time. It could be charged. At this point, Blue Rain no longer had time to interrupt it. Even so, they still had to do something. If they couldn’t interrupt it, they couldn’t just let Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea keep charging it, right?

Thousand Chants in Full Bloom!

Before Blue Rain attacked, Boundless Sea released the skill. It was only one palm, but all of the qi that had accumulated burst out, similar to Flash Burst. However, Flash Burst only a single burst of qi, while Thousand Chants in Full Bloom was like a flower.

Numerous bullets sprayed out and then scattered throughout the field because of the wind.

Bullet Rain, Swoksaar, and Soul Speaker were all within this rain of qi. Thousand Chants in Full Bloom originally didn’t cover a large area, but because of the wind, using the word scattered to described these bullets of qi was perfectly appropriate.

Of Blue Rain’s three characters, Swoksaar was in the center of the meteor shower. There was no place for him to dodge. The bullets of qi along with the added force of the wind forced Swoksaar back.

The other two, Xu Jingxi and Zheng Xuan, had to give up what they were doing before to dodge the attack.

For a moment, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had stopped all three alone!

It was only for a short moment, but these opportunities didn’t come by easily.

Boom boom boom!

The sounds of cannonfire suddenly became even more compact.

Bullet Rain and Swoksaar had been pinned down in succession. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had suddenly shifted targets. Her target was no longer Troubling Rain, but Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud.

Lu Hanwen wasn’t too bothered by it. He had noticed the attacks and dodged them.

Steamed Bun Invasion now had room to breathe and immediately became more boisterous.

“Leo, let me fix you up!” Steamed Bun shouted in the chat. He had received Ye Xiu’s orders. Once he found an opening, he would immediately attack Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain.

The crowd booed.

Who are you? You say you’re going to fix up the Sword Saint? Even if the battle had taken a turn, haven’t you heard the phrase “having an unfair advantage”?

The crowd couldn’t admire Steamed Bun’s delight at all. But they could see that with Steamed Bun Invasion move towards Huang Shaotian, the connection between him and Lord Grim had been reestablished.

“He’s all yours, Steamed Bun!” Ye Xiu immediately called out in the chat. Afterwards, Lord Grim tried to retreat.

“Leo, do you dare to fight 300 exchanges with me?” Steamed Bun challenged, while throwing a Brick towards the back of Troubling Rain’s head.

Huang Shaotian had been checking his surroundings. When he saw the Brick, he had Troubling Rain tilt his head. It seemed like he had no intentions of letting Lord Grim go.

But then…

Pai.

Not a brick, but a slap on the face.

If it was a Brawler’s Slap, Lord Grim could do it too. He had pretended to retreat. Taking advantage of Huang Shaotian dodging Steamed Bun Invasion’s Brick, he suddenly came out with a slap.

As soon as the attack hit, the combo began.

With a hook, Troubling Rain was sent flying into the air. As for the follow-up attacks, not even the fastest mouth could narrate every attack.

Unspecialized Blitz!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella kept changing forms, keeping Troubling Rain tumbling in the air.

This combo couldn’t last that long though. After all, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea couldn’t just spam Thousand Chants in Full Bloom. Blue Rain’s three players had been positioned scattered apart. No matter how well Fang Rui took advantage of the wind, he couldn’t keep all three under control.

Bullet Rain’s rescue soon arrived. Huang Shaotian used the opening to escape. But what should they do next? For a moment, Blue Rain didn’t seem to have a direction.

Happy’s broken formation had now been re-formed.

Lord Grim and Steamed Bun Invasion were together alongside each other. Su Mucheng had the long-ranged support. An Wenyi was in the middle as the healer, getting protection from two sides. And although Fang Rui was deep in enemy territory alone, he had the wind on his side and had nothing to fear.

What should they do?

Quite a few viewers were looking at Team Blue Rain’s chat.

At this moment, Blue Rain should have some idea on what to do, right? Their previous plans seemed to have been broken apart one by one.

Some people looked at the health on both teams. After comparing them, they saw which side had won the exchange.

“Coach Li, what are your thoughts?” Pan Lin asked Li Yibo this question.

“It’s still too early to say, but what Blue Rain does next will be crucial to how the rest of the match plays out,” Li Yibo said.

“Of course,” Li Yibo immediately added, “It’s also important to see how Happy is able to take advantage of this situation.”

Sure enough, Happy didn’t disappoint Li Yibo. After breaking apart Blue Rain’s tactics one by one, it was time for their counterattack.

Even though Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain had been rescued from Lord Grim’s combo because of his teammates, Happy had no plans of letting him escape.

Troubling Rain became Happy’s focus point. Lord Grim’s attacks became the lead for the entire team.

“Take my fist, Leo!” Steamed Bun continued to shout. Previously, he had been ridiculing Blue Rain for teaming up on him, but he had no problems teaming up on Huang Shaotian.

Blue Rain’s fans had already started booing. They were worried for Huang Shaotian!

But at this moment, Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud broke through Su Mucheng’s zoning, his greatsword coming to the rescue.

Meteor Form!

Flowing Cloud’s greatsword, Flame Shadow, was fast. Along with the explosions from behind, he blazed across the field into the enemy lines.

“Wow, this kid’s pretty impressive,” Steamed Bun was put in a difficult situation because of the attack.

They couldn’t bother trash talking Steamed Bun. Lu Hanwen could actually be considered a senior. They were amazed that Steamed Bun could actually dodge that sudden attack.

“If he had been wielding a lightsaber…” Li Yibo spoke halfway through before stopping himself. He realized that he seemed to say those words a bit too much. It was like he was criticizing Lu Hanwen for choosing a greatsword over a lightsaber. In reality, Lu Hanwen used his greatsword to great effect, accomplishing things that couldn’t be done by a lightsaber. Li Yibo only felt it was a pity that the attack speed was slow.

“Kid, I admire you! You’ve at least got more guts than that Leo! You’re a worthy opponent!” Steamed Bun continued to chatter.

“Fuck, you bastard, I’ve endured long enough. Come here and let me hack you into pieces!!!!” Insulted without even being in the conversation, Huang Shaotian finally couldn’t bear it anymore.

Chapter 1468 - Double Image

Was he enraged?

Seeing Huang Shaotian rant so angrily that he didn’t even bother to use punctuation, many people thought this way. But just as many weren’t fooled at all. Huang Shaotian’s fighting existed on a completely separate channel from his trash talk. His trash talk didn’t reveal any of his cold, brutal, opportunistic style at all.

So, seeing him yell in the chat that he couldn’t endure Steamed Bun any longer, at least half of the audience didn’t believe him all.

It looked like Steamed Bun didn’t believe him either. He completely ignored Huang Shaotian, and instead focused on controlling Steamed Bun Invasion to fight Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud.

This was simply too normal of an action. The opponent in front of him was strong, how could he simply turn around to go and fight someone else just because they yelled something?

But, everyone who saw this scene couldn’t help but think: Steamed Bun looked down on Huang Shaotian and didn’t want to bother with fighting him anymore.

What was up with that?

Those who thought this didn’t know whether to laugh or cry. This was such an important playoffs match, with such a fast rhythm, so many changes, endlessly wonderful. But as soon as the scene focused in over here, how come it seemed like it was hiding this unseriousness?

Were these two people really treating this match seriously?

Even Blue Rain’s own fans couldn’t help but begin to question their Sword Saint.

And what was the Sword Saint actually doing?

After shouting at Steamed Bun, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain actually dropped the opponent in front of him and prepared to kill his way toward Steamed Bun Invasion.

“He lost his cool?”

Seeing this, countless people began to shout. Shock, disappointment, delight in disaster, all sorts of emotions were pulled forth by this one action of Huang Shaotian’s.

Such a strong retreat was obviously unwise. Even the chaotic Steamed Bun, in these conditions, didn’t lose the opponent in front of him, Lu Hanwen. And Huang Shaotian, who was supposed to be more mature, actually did such a childish action, and the opponent he dropped was Ye Xiu! An opponent even scarier than Lu Hanwen.

As expected, Ye Xiu didn’t miss this opportunity. Lord Grim immediately went for the opening that Troubling Rain exposed as he forcefully retreated.

At that moment, swordlight violently burst forth.

Formless Phantom Blade!

The Level 70 Blade Master skill, the skill that still dealt the highest damage, Formless Phantom Blade. Troubling Rain retreated and went after Steamed Bun Invasion, but before he got there, the skill was already activated.

And then, one step, one turn.

The opening that Troubling Rain had exposed while retreating was suddenly completely covered by swordlight.

Ohhhhh!!!!

Blue Rain’s Xiaochuan Stadium was instantly filled with the cheers and hollers of Blue Rain’s fans.

They were simply too moved, because their core, their ace, their idol, their Sword Saint, hadn’t let them down in the end.

He hadn’t lost his cool. This was a trap, a trap inviting the gentleman to enter the funeral urn.

But Ye Xiu wasn’t without defense.

Facing the sudden turn and explosion of swordlight, Lord Grim swiftly retreated, the sword chasing him.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh… ding… whoosh whoosh…

The interwoven arcs of swordlight flashed through the air, punctuated with the occasional sounds of contact. Huang Shaotian’s Formless Phantom Blade was simply this fast, so fast that no one could see how he was actually attacking. It seemed as though it was just that one moment, swordlight burst forth, dazzling the eyes, drawing attention, and then in the next moment, the light was gone, and all was still…

It looked like it was all over. Troubling Rain, Lord Grim, the two characters stood in their original positions.

What happened?

While too many people were still in a daze, Lord Grim suddenly rushed forward.

And Troubling Rain? Troubling Rain didn’t move. Huang Shaotian actually just stood and watched as Lord Grim came at him with a Double Stab, impaling his body.

And he still maintained that pose.

Formless Phantom Blade, the pose after retracting the final slash…

Huang Shaotian had unleashed the final slash of Formless Phantom Blade, but he hadn’t managed to hit the target.

An opening, this was undoubtedly a huge opening. Many Blade Masters, if they felt they didn’t have full grasp of the situation, would rather give up on the last and most powerful slash of the Formless Phantom Blade.

Huang Shaotian unleashed this slash, but this slash hadn’t managed to hit. Any Glory player could stand up and tell Huang Shaotian what that meant.

So how could Huang Shaotian not know this principle? And with his skill, how could he have let this happen?

This was why everyone was so shocked by this situation. The doubt was so strong that even the televised broadcast decided not to play the currently unfolding battle at full screen. Instead, they split to a small window, and in slow motion replayed the Formless Phantom Blade exchange between Ye Xiu and Huang Shaotian just now.

What kind of exchange had it been?

Even though it was slowed down to a quarter of the speed, everyone could still clearly sense how fast it was.

Formless Phantom Blade was that fast. But Ye Xiu’s responses seemed to be even faster.

Lord Grim, with almost miniscule movements, dodged the slashes that this skill sent at him one after another. The tip of the sword, the blade of the sword, it all seemed to go right past him, without a single one landing. The audience watched as one slash looked like it was about to hit, and they felt their hearts leaping into their throats – and this was watching a slow-motion replay!

Then, they saw that the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in Lord Grim’s hand suddenly elongated, and that slash that seemed undodgeable was parried just like that.

He parried a Formless Phantom Blade?

Aside from dumbstruck, was there any more suitable emotion?

Everyone had only ever seen this kind of thing in performances before. Two pro players, both using Formless Phantom Blade, and then ping-ping-pong-pong clashing again and again, until it looked like there were flowers blooming around them from all of the sparks flying. But that was practiced beforehand, where both sides knew from what angle and with what speed the other player would come at them. Yet now, this was the playoffs battlefield, and the one behind the Formless Phantom Blade was the number one among Blade Masters, the Sword Saint!

And his Formless Phantom Blade had actually been parried by the opponent…

After that, Lord Grim continued to retreat, continued to dodge.

His one parry, of course, couldn’t interrupt the Formless Phantom Blade attack, and the skill steadily reached the end. Just the fact that he’d been able to last this long was already breathtaking. No matter how they looked at it, though, there was no way for him to dodge or block the next slash, and this next slash just happened to be the most powerful, final slash of the Formless Phantom Blade!

The sword lifted!

Carrying an incomparably sharp swordlight. Those sword shadows that had been all scattered earlier now seemed to gather and accumulate upon the blade, and the final gleaming blade of light flashed forth!

What was that?

And then everyone looked at where the swordlight had travelled, and they blinked, or rubbed their eyes.

Had their vision gone fuzzy?

Everyone thought this, because in their view, in that one moment, it looked like there had been a double image of Lord Grim. An instant later, it had vanished.

The scene rewound and replayed in slow motion, this time at one-eighth the speed.

This time, everyone saw clearly.

Shadow Clone Technique!

It was Shadow Clone Technique. Lord Grim’s two hands moved so fast as to be undetectable. He’d completed the seals in the span of time of the already incredibly fast Formless Phantom Blade…

What kind of handspeed was that?

Everyone searched for a number on the screen, hoping it would tell them, but there was none…

No number, they could only rely on their feeling. But for this sort of inhuman thing, how could an ordinary person rely on their feeling?

The Shadow Clone Technique didn’t send the original body far away, so the real and false bodies stood very tightly together. The final slash of the Formless Phantom Blade arrived, and at one-eighth speed, everyone could finally clearly see that the instant this skill had activated, the clone had been broken by this final slash. At one-fourth speed, everyone finally identified this double image that they’d mistaken for their eyes going blurry, because it really had only appeared for an instant.

And even at one-fourth speed, it had only been there for a moment, allowing everyone to realize that that was the only way he would have been able to dodge that slash. Normal movement couldn’t be made faster with faster handspeed. Only the hand seals of a Ninja would, with an increase in handspeed, release a skill faster.

Ultimately, Ye Xiu succeeded.

Using a method that surpassed everyone’s imagination.

And no one could forget that Ye Xiu was an old general of ten years. This sort of unbearably fast handspeed, wasn’t that supposed to be something that only the youth had?

The final slash of Huang Shaotian’s Formless Phantom Blade hadn’t landed, but at this time, no one felt that he had made a mistake.

He had already done very well, using blade after blade to attack the defending Ye Xiu, forcing him back until he had nowhere to dodge and nowhere to block. What happened afterward couldn’t be called Huang Shaotian’s fault. That sort of transcendence of natural human limits, how could that be treated as a miscalculation?

It wasn’t Huang Shaotian’s fault, but no matter what, his Troubling Rain once again fell into an unfavorable situation as Ye Xiu controlled Lord Grim to unleash another flurry of attacks at him. But those who had just been watching the small window reply found that for now, they couldn’t re-immerse themselves back in the normal battle. That moment, that instant, they still weren’t sure if it had even been real. They needed to watch it a few more times.

In comparison, the live audience was better off.

The screens suspended at the center of the stadium were large enough to replay that moment over and over… but in truth, they didn’t replay it for too long. After all, this was Blue Rain’s home stadium, and that wasn’t a thrilling moment that belonged to Blue Rain.

But just once was enough to render the entire audience speechless.

Xiaochuan Stadium, at this moment, was dead silent. This was a moment that belonged to Happy, but even Happy’s diehard fans sitting on the west side were so shocked that they forgot to cheer.

Beyond all belief.

That was perhaps the only way to describe that scene. Pan Lin and Li Yibo, in the broadcast, were reciting those words as well.

But on the battlefield, a Chaotic Rain silently fell at this moment. The initiative that Ye Xiu had gained with his unbelievable controls was immediately broken by this silent Chaotic Rain.

“No matter how exciting, he just dodged one attack.” In Blue Rain’s channel, Captain Yu Wenzhou spoke calmly.

Huang Shaotian’s calm was to help him clearly and accurately seize killing opportunities. But in Blue Rain, the one who was truly as calm as an unmelting glacier of a thousand years was still their captain.

Chapter 1469 - This Is The Strategy

Seeing Yu Wenzhou send this message in the chat, Xiaochuan Stadium was suddenly filled with thunderous applause.

When Huang Shaotian’s valiant Formless Phantom Blade was broken by the opponent like that, never mind the players on the field, even the watching audience couldn’t help but feel unsettled.

But now, one sentence from their captain was enough to reassure everyone.

That was right!

It was nothing more than dodging one attack. No matter how clever the method was, the final result wasn’t anything special. It was simply a dodge.

It was like kicking a goal in soccer. There would always be those super-difficult, inimitable shots, but with regards to the match itself, no matter how exciting, it was only one goal and one point, nothing more.

Don’t pay it too much mind. Keep your spirits up.

Even the Blue Rain fans watching from off the field understood the meaning of their captain’s words.

The Chaotic Rain splashed upon the ground, and even Ye Xiu couldn’t continue to control his character under the Confused state. He could only try to get out of the skill’s range as early as he could.

“Sorry,” Su Mucheng said in Happy’s chat.

Swoksaar didn’t have any close-range opponents covering him, and she was the only one who could have used an attack to disrupt him. But she hadn’t noticed the casting of this Chaotic Rain. From a certain angle, it could be called her mistake.

“Don’t worry,” Ye Xiu replied.

He didn’t have any intent of blaming anyone. The Launcher had the longest attack range of any class, and often had the ability to target any opponent during a battle. But did that mean that every attack interrupt would be left to the responsibility of the Launcher? Of course not.

Even a Warlock, a character that was important to target and interrupt, could not always be interrupted in this kind of chaotic battle.

“Leave him to me!” Fang Rui shouted in the chat.

Blue Rain was avoiding the location occupied by Fang Rui, and by this time, they had spread outside of the gale area, trying to go as far away as possible. Fang Rui felt a bit sad leaving behind his advantage, but right now Boundless Sea didn’t serve any purpose by staying in the wind area, so he also controlled Boundless Sea to travel with the wind and flew like a shooting star toward Swoksaar.

“Huh, how come you’re not crawling anymore?” At this moment, a message from Steamed Bun suddenly appeared in the match chat.

What?

Blue Rain’s players all had a double-take. What was that supposed to mean?

And then, very soon, they saw Fang Rui reply, “Crawl your face!”

Fuck!

Everyone was shocked. Steamed Bun’s mockery didn’t discriminate between friend and foe? He would mock even his own teammate?

But while Happy’s two players bickered, their characters on the battlefield were cooperating. Steamed Bun Invasion, currently fighting Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud, suddenly turned and tried to leave. Lu Hanwen, of course, wouldn’t let him go easily, but Lord Grim, who had managed to escape from the Chaotic Rain, was just passing by. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella waved, and with a clang, it parried Flowing Cloud’s attack.

Guard!

Lord Grim used the Blade Master skill Guard. Flowing Cloud’s Silver weapon Flame Shadow was extremely heavy, so his attacks had much knockback. After Lord Grim blocked, the force of the attack sent him crashing in the direction of Steamed Bun Invasion.

“What a mistake!” Pan Lin shouted, as the two characters slammed into each other.

Players on the same team couldn’t harm each other, but because Lord Grim was sent flying by the force of Flowing Cloud’s attack, this crash was considered an attack. It wouldn’t have been a big deal if the opponent had purposely used knock back to blow the opponent away, but this was Ye Xiu controlling Lord Grim to voluntarily help cover Steamed Bun Invasion. Flowing Cloud had hit two birds with one stone, which was truly somewhat embarrassing.

“No, wait!” But at this moment, Li Yibo suddenly shouted.

After being hit, Steamed Bun Invasion staggered, but because of it, his charge suddenly accelerated. He and Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea were trying to use a pincer strike against Swoksaar, but because their plan was obvious, Blue Rain was already on the defensive. Yu Wenzhou was paying attention to the movement speeds of the two characters, and Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain was already opening fire to block Steamed Bun Invasion.

Zheng Xuan chose to block Steamed Bun because he saw that Boundless Sea was still in the wind zone, and attacks in that direction would be affected. Originally, it had all been calculated very clearly, including Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud catching up from behind to coordinate and close in. but in the end, because Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim passed by, it was all blown to pieces.

Steamed Bun Invasion, with a sudden burst of speed, broke through Bullet Rain’s cover. Yu Wenzhou, who had been controlling Swoksaar to change positions, was clearly unprepared for this abrupt change.

“Prepare your face!” Steamed Bun once again gave a shout before attacking. Steamed Bun Invasion arrived in front of Swoksaar and threw a Sand Toss his way.

What Yu Wenzhou feared the most was such moments of unpreparedness.

His awareness, reaction, judgment, they were all sufficient to respond to whatever happened. But always, in the last moment, when it was time to turn his awareness and reaction into controls, he was too slow.

Yu Wenzhou had long since grown accustomed to this awkwardness. He was unperturbed, and already began calculating for what would happen after he was hit.

But this time…

A gold-colored shield of light suddenly surrounded Swoksaar. Steamed Bun Invasion’s Sand Toss, after hitting this shield, was swallowed into nothing. Swoksaar didn’t take any damage, nor did he lose his sight.

Holy Shield Technique!

The Paladin skill.

When Yu Wenzhou was faced with a situation he couldn’t handle, his teammates knew as well. Xu Jingxi didn’t begrudge using his skill, and Soul Speaker cast Holy Shield Technique to protect Swoksaar within.

Unlike the Qi Master’s Qi Guard, which didn’t move once cast, Holy Shield Technique was a protection centered around a character and would move with the character’s movements.

Yu Wenzhou was already in the process of dodging in the aftermath of the attack, but with this Holy Shield Technique, his controls went more smoothly.

Yu Wenzhou didn’t slow down as a result of this. The Holy Shield Technique was equivalent to giving a character some extra health; it couldn’t completely block all of the opponent’s skills. For example, some of the Grappler’s grab attacks would throw the character along with the Holy Shield Technique; it wasn’t like the golden shield would prevent the grab.

So Swoksaar still had to dodge. Yu Wenzhou couldn’t let his character be controlled by the opponent.

As for where he would go, Yu Wenzhou had already calculated. There was no safe zone in a battle, of course, so he wanted to go in a direction where it was convenient for Blue Rain’s players and characters to support him. As for where Steamed Bun might intercept him, he swiftly calculated those as well.

Here!

Yu Wenzhou chose a direction that was inconvenient for Steamed Bun and was good for cooperation with the Blue Rain players. But Steamed Bun’s view didn’t even glance his way – he just continued charging straight forward.

What was he doing now?

Yu Wenzhou didn’t understand Steamed Bun’s plot, but it also didn’t interfere with his own escape, so even though he didn’t understand, it was better for him to first just get as far away as he could. Swoksaar dodged to the side, and Steamed Bun Invasion really didn’t attack him at all, he just passed right by Swoksaar just like that.

Yu Wenzhou’s heart jumped as he suddenly realized something. Alarmed, Swoksaar turned around, pulling his camera view, and as expected…

Steamed Bun Invasion was charging straight. Over there, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had adjusted his movement direction. The true target of these two’s pincer attack wasn’t Swoksaar, but Soul Speaker, Blue Rain’s healer!

The audience members with the omniscient view didn’t react much faster than Yu Wenzhou. It wasn’t until the thing actually happened that there were shouts of surprise.

Li Yibo’s brain just wasn’t enough.

He had started as a pro player, playing in countless real battles. Later, he became a professional commentator, watching countless battles.

But in Li Yibo’s memory, there had never before been a match where the rhythm was this fast. How long had this battle lasted so far? It had barely been a few minutes, right? But everything was happening so suddenly. It was like being on a speeding train.

For any match, whether the home or the away team, there would always be a general overall strategy they followed. But in this match? Up to now, Li Yibo had yet to figure out what the main goal of either team was.

This match felt like two enemies meeting randomly in the Heavenly Domain, neither side having prepared beforehand, and then breaking out into a fight. All of the responses followed from the immediate, real-time changes. All strategic thoughts were formed spontaneously on the field.

What was going on?

Li Yibo was truly lost, completely lost. In this match, maybe the yelling in the chat was a bit unprofessional, okay, but right now, had the two sides prepared strategy beforehand? What were the methods they’d prepared to win this match?

Especially Team Blue Rain. This is your home match, your map. Did you not think beforehand how you were going to use it?

“The offense and defense is so fast that Blue Rain has no way of using their home field advantage!” At this moment, Pan Lin suddenly exclaimed this sentence, and Li Yibo felt as though he suddenly saw the light.

“What did you say?” Li Yibo cried out.

“Ah?” Pan Lin, alarmed, thought that he had said something wrong.

“The fast offense and defense prevents Blue Rain from using their home field advantage…” Li Yibo repeated the sentence to himself.

“Ah… so far, aside from predicting Happy’s path at the very beginning, and then attacking Happy from the advantageous position in the center wind zone, Blue Rain hasn’t really used the map!” Pan Lin said.

“You’re right!” Li Yibo nodded his head sharply. He figured it out.

The two sides didn’t have any strategy?

How was that possible! This was a playoffs match. If time permitted, no amount of preparation was too much. Who would slack off?

Blue Rain had used the map from the start, attacking downwind and instantly scattering Happy’s formation. Their opening was successful.

Then what about Happy?

Happy’s strategy, Happy’s battle plan for this match, was what everyone saw now!

Play fast, play chaotically! Using a fast and changing rhythm, keep Blue Rain’s hands and feet tied, make it so that they had no way of using wind zones on this map as they had practiced.

Both sides looked like they were lacking in preparation, turning this into a mess.

In reality, Blue Rain had prepared, but they had no chance to display it. Happy? The situation right now was what they had prepared for. Their goal was to chase victory in the midst of chaos.

Chapter 1470 - Wild Happy

After looking over the clues and reviewing the contents of the previous rounds in this match, Li Yibo was even more confident in his views. When the two sides first clashed, it had been extremely unfavorable for Happy. At that time, they could have evaded Blue Rain’s downwind assault, but Happy stubbornly chose to stay and face them.

Li Yibo wanted to say he didn’t understand their choice, but didn’t have time to because the pace of the match had been too fast, especially with one side getting a speed boost from the strong winds.

But then, the situation had unwittingly unfolded into the present state. Along the way, there were simply too many details worth talking about.

“To think Happy would actually use such a strategy… uh… speaking of which, does this count as a strategy?” Pan Lin said after listening to Li Yibo’s analysis.

Li Yibo forced a smile. A strategy usually entailed structure, but Happy’s strategy changed depending on the situation. It was completely chaotic. It couldn’t really be considered as a strategy. But the important part was that Happy succeeded at least for now. Blue Rain wasn’t able to display their home game advantage.

“If they win like this…” Pan Lin didn’t know what to say.

If just randomly fighting could win, then the win wouldn’t just be over Team Blue Rain. It could be considered a slap to the term pro-level playing. Were strategy and tactics actually meaningless in a competition?

“Haha, this isn’t something that can be accomplished just by playing around randomly,” Li Yibo laughed.

“Oh?”

“Think about Team Happy’s background,” Li Yibo said.

The current Happy was no longer an unremarkable grassroots Internet cafe team. They were a top eight team that had made it into the playoffs.

There were no weak teams in the playoffs. Because anyone that could stand here had experienced the test of an entire season. Perhaps winning the Challenger League could be done by a fluke of luck because that was an elimination tournament format. But there was no luck in the regular season. It was 38 rounds of back and forth. How could it be so convenient as to always be lucky?

In a competition of skill, the skilled teams would receive attention, especially for a team like Happy, where there was always something to talk about. As a result, the media had pretty much dug up all there was to know about the members of Team Happy.

“Team Happy’s background?” Pan Lin stared blankly. He had always followed Team Happy closely. With Li Yibo’s reminder, he immediately thought of all the details of Happy’s team roster.

Compared to the teams that went through the Alliance’s investigation to make it into the league, Team Happy didn’t suddenly become known in a single day. Their team had history which could be traced back all the way to the opening of the tenth server.

Yes, the opening of the tenth server.

Too many people remembers how in the first day of the tenth server, the name Lord Grim kept popping up in the world chat, which could be checked. Many of the First Kill records in the tenth server’s Beginner Village were held by Lord Grim.

The opening of the tenth server was the day of Ye Xiu’s retirement.

The story could be easily pieced together. Many tenth server players could describe the terrifying dungeon record wars that followed. And in this war, the name Lord Grim could not be missed. He held countless spots on the leaderboards, a member of one guild one day and then a different guild the next day.

Whether it was Tyrannical Ambition or Blue Brook Guild, there were traces of Lord Grim. The members of these guilds had leaked out that at that time, Lord Grim had already been holding that crazy transforming Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. They also stated with certainty that Ye Xiu had two partners by his side, Soft Mist and Steamed Bun Invasion.

Later, Concealed Light and One Inch Ash joined…

Pro characters were stored in Glory’s in-game servers too. Happy’s characters could be searched and verified as created in the tenth server.

Team Happy was a new team from head to toe. Almost all of their members had come from the tenth server.

And how had they grown throughout this journey?

Pan Lin knew. Li Yibo had wanted him to think of this point.

Happy’s players had grown together through chaotic fights. From a trusted information source, in the tenth server, Lord Grim had become a public enemy of all the top guilds. These top guilds weren’t just random player guilds, but Club guilds, guilds with a powerful background.

Because Ye Xiu’s investment into the tenth server had disrupted the balance between the guilds. When he reached Level 50 and entered the Heavenly Domain, the top guilds had allied together and went on a hunt for him. According to another trusted information source, Deception had appeared besides Lord Grim at that point.

Happy left behind a very clear trail in history. And this trail was made up entirely of the blood and tears of the big guilds.

And Happy’s players had trained and grown in these sorts of fights. 5v5 team battle? Too small scale! In the game, five players was just half a team. A team was ten players, and a group consisted of ten teams, a hundred players!

Even if the skill levels of those 100 players couldn’t compare to a pro-level, it was obvious which one would be more chaotic, no?

Making the fight chaotic wasn’t because Happy had no idea what to do against Blue Rain in the home game, rather it was because it was their best way of facing Blue Rain and the playstyle they were most adept at.

How long had it been since pro players had experienced chaotic fights like those in the game? They were used to logical and structured 5v5 fights. Such wild chaos hadn’t been seen in so long. Perhaps even many of the players who came from the Club training camps didn’t have these types of experiences.

If pro teams were thrown into the game, they could deal with any in-game matter without a problem. But the pros would be relying on their superior intuition and technique to bully in-game players. However, Blue Rain wasn’t playing against normal players. Blue Rain was facing Team Happy, a playoffs team.

Happy had been a mess at the start, and now, Blue Rain was also in a mess.

But Happy was happy being in a mess. Amidst this chaos, there was rhythm and synergy. But Blue Rain was truly a mess. They couldn’t find the appropriate rhythm, or perhaps, it could be said that they weren’t able to establish one.

Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion had feigned a pincer attack on Swoksaar, but then suddenly turned to pincer attack Soul Speaker instead. Team Blue Rain was in disorder. Swoksaar turned to cast a curse, but this time, Su Mucheng locked onto him. She fired a shot at him, forcing Yu Wenzhou to avoid it.

Details such as Ye Xiu using Guard to crash into Steamed Bun Invasion and helping him accelerate were lost by the viewers. The match was developing simply too fast. Right now, Ye Xiu was violently attacking Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud, pushing him back. On the other end, Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain wanted to get past him, but his attempt didn’t escape Ye Xiu’s notice. Lord Grim suddenly swept across the field with a Shining Arc, cutting Troubling Rain off. After two quick swipes, Huang Shaotian had no choice but to have Troubling Rain retreat.

Paladins wore plate armor. Although their defense was much higher than Clerics, their movements were much slower. Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion made his way to him practically unimpeded.

Xu Jingxi saw them clearly. He obviously had no intentions of being a sitting duck. Soul Speaker readied a Halo Smash. Whoever first reached him would receive a hit back, creating an opening for him.

Which one?

Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker retreated two steps, so he could see the attacks from his left and right more clearly.

They’re here!

On his left side, Boundless Sea raised his two hands, letting out a blast of qi. Xu Jingxi immediately acted and readied a Halo Smash, but…

Cloud Grasping Fist!

Boundless Sea had unexpectedly used a Cloud Grasping Fist.

This skill grabbed the target. It dealt no damage, so it wasn’t something Halo Smash could reflect back. Xu Jingxi was depressed! He didn’t know if he should blame luck or if it was because Fang Rui had seen through him. Then, what about Steamed Bun Invasion?

As he moved to make it more difficult for Boundless Sea to grab him, Xu Jingxi looked towards Steamed Bun Invasion and saw something coming towards him. He immediately tilted his head.

Hu!

A Brick whistled by. There wasn’t enough time to activate Halo Smash!

“To think you dodged it,” Steamed Bun was surprised, “Blue Rain’s players really are amazing!”

Steamed Bun finally said a few kind words to Blue Rain, but Blue Rain’s players nor fans could feel excited about these words in any way. From what he was saying, dodging his Brick was an incredible feat.

Blue Rain’s two Blade Masters were blocked by Ye Xiu. Yu Wenzhou was busy dealing with Su Mucheng and didn’t have time to help. Only Zheng Xuan was left.

The spiritless Zheng Xuan didn’t dare be negligent. His Bullet Rain rushed towards Soul Speaker, with his sights locked onto Steamed Bun Invasion and Boundless Sea. Then, Zheng Xuan personally witnessed a kidnapping take place.

Could this even be called a fight?

Zheng Xuan felt his mind go hazy. Steamed Bun Invasion and Boundless Sea, two Fighter classes were surrounding their healer, punching and kicking him! You would expect a few skills to be used, no? But the two enemies were just swinging their arms and legs. You couldn’t even tell whose arm or leg it was! And as Soul Speaker was beaten up, it looked like he was being forcefully dragged towards an area.

An area?

The wind zone!

Those two guys wanted to kidnap Soul Speaker and bring him into the wind zone! If that happened, Blue Rain would have trouble taking advantage of the terrain to rescue him.

How stressful!

Zheng Xuan had become the team’s only hope, and he couldn’t help but mutter his catchphrase. Then, he charged forward resolutely.

“Let go of our healer!” To motivate himself, Zheng Xuan gave a shout in the chat.

“Someone’s here! What do we do!” Steamed Bun said. From the way he phrased it, it really did sound like they had been caught in the middle of a kidnapping.

“Pretend we didn’t see him,” Fang Rui said.

“How smart!” Steamed Bun said.

Zheng Xuan was infuriated. Did he really pose no threat to them?

Chapter 1471 - Can Never Be Overlooked At Any Moment

Bullet Rain.

Bullet Rain.

In this sort of critical moment, Zheng Xuan usually liked to drop a “how stressful” in the chat before acting. But this time, in a rare sight, he didn’t complain at all. Just like that, Bullet Rain, scattering a rain of bullets, rushed forward.

Boom boom boom boom.

A road paved with the fireworks of explosions. When a Spitfire went on full offensive, the sight was as splendid and colorful as a Mage’s attacks. Zhang Jiale, the creator of the Hundred Blossoms style, used this point to the fullest, and those who came after him all learned something from the Hundred Blossoms style. Perhaps they wouldn’t take advantage of the special effects of the attacks to the peak like he did. But for Spitfires, how dazzling the offensive was became an important metric for gauging strength.

Zheng Xuan, this unmotivated guy, was currently playing an unusually dazzling game. He had always been viewed as the best Spitfire player after Zhang Jiale, and he’d even had the opportunity to go to Hundred Blossoms to fill the gap that had been left by Zhang Jiale’s retirement, and become that team’s core.

But Zheng Xuan’s unmotivated personality led him to reject that kind of invitation. And not long after that, another Blue Rain player, Yu Feng, left for Hundred Blossoms. As a Berserker, he lifted up this team. So, these two teams still ended up completing this kind of exchange.

Because of his lack of motivation, Zheng Xuan had suffered more than a bit of criticism. But he never minded the opinions of the outside world.

There was no ambition in his chest. He never cared about how important he was, how much people looked up to him, how much they expected from him.

But now, Zheng Xuan resolutely focused all of his spirit.

Because the situation they faced now was extremely dire. If their healer was really dragged into the wind zone by Fang Rui and Steamed Bun, saving him would become extremely difficult, and they would lose the initiative completely.

But this, by itself, wasn’t enough to force Zheng Xuan to focus. What really caused him to focus was the fact that, in such critical moments, he didn’t want to let his teammates down.

Yes. He was an unmotivated person, but Blue Rain, his Blue Rain teammates, accepted his personality. They allowed him to be lazy sometimes. They allowed him to bring that dull, listless performance sometimes, where others would be grinding their teeth in frustration.

This wasn’t to say that Blue Rain was really that casual. This was all because Blue Rain, Blue Rain’s players, always had faith in Zheng Xuan’s judgment.

Laziness, listlessness…

Whenever Zheng Xuan displayed these traits, it was always during irrelevant moments. But any time things were at a crucial point, this guy would always rush forward with a “how stressful” on his tongue. He had never dropped the ball before.

His teammates accepted him, and Zheng Xuan wasn’t someone who couldn’t tell good from bad. He always repaid everyone’s acceptance.

He understood that, standing on this battlefield, he wasn’t fighting just for himself. Sometimes, he could give up without a care, but the team couldn’t, his teammates couldn’t. And so, he would continue to walk with everyone. In the end, he lived up to the trust everyone had in him.

Unmotivated?

If this was truly a competition where everyone only strove for individual honor, Zheng Xuan probably would have been eliminated from this circle long ago. But Glory was a team project; it wasn’t a single-player game. It wasn’t that Zheng Xuan lacked motivation, it was that his motivation needed to be inspired from different sources. Such as, for his teammates, for the team…

For him, paying enough trust would earn the deepest repayment. And Team Blue Rain had done exactly this.

“Charge!!”

Seeing Zheng Xuan control Bullet Rain, Blue Rain’s fans exploded with cheers.

At crucial moments, no one could slack off. The audience, the players, including Happy’s players.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was forcefully holding back Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen both. Su Mucheng’s Launcher was preventing Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar from casting a single curse. Weren’t Happy’s players putting their all into seizing this opportunity firmly?

Fang Rui told Steamed Bun to ignore the attacks from Bullet Rain.

But, could they be ignored?

Freezing Bullet, Flash Bullet, Electric Grenade, Implosion Grenade…

Spitfires were not a class that only dealt damage; they had great crowd control. And attacks that had controlling effects simply could not be ignored.

When Fang Rui said to ignore them, Happy’s fans were scared to death. They thought, how could they be ignored?

And Steamed Bun’s answer, “how smart,” only frightened them even more.

These two conducting their kidnapping, they were really audacious to the extreme!

They really dared to ignore him?

Bullet Rain poured down, everything was coming to a head, and these two audacious fellows didn’t disappoint – they really dared!

“Go go go go go!!” Steamed Bun shouted in the chat, and as he shouted, he furiously unleashed punches and kicks upon Soul Speaker!

Xu Jingxi understood the current situation. He didn’t have much means of fighting back, but he could put up a resistance.

“Throw here!” Fang Rui suddenly called in the chat.

Steamed Bun, who liked to complain, didn’t bother to say anything this time. He lifted up Soul Speaker and swung.

Fling!

Even though it was a Grappler skill, it was a sub-level 20 skill, so all Fighters could learn it. None of the four Fighter subclasses would completely neglect this kind of forceful grab skill.

Compared to the Grappler, which had its grab-strengthening classing skill, the other three classes couldn’t use the skill to the same effectiveness. But the skill could still throw the target, living up to its name.

Soul Speaker flew.

Plate Armor wasn’t light in weight, added to the fact that Steamed Bun Invasion’s Fling was only so strong. His flight wasn’t long – he’d only just flown out of Steamed Bun Invasion’s hands before it looked like he was about to land.

But Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea was already ready to catch him.

“Fling relay?” Pan Lin exclaimed.

“It’s still not enough!” Li Yibo said. Even if they tried to relay throw him, they were still too far from the wind zone. Boundless Sea’s Fling was even weaker, because the Qi Master’s Strength was a bit less than the Brawler’s.

But at that moment, a grenade landed right behind Boundless Sea as he was grabbing Soul Speaker.

The grenade cracked and split in two, and a powerful force began to draw in the surrounding air.

“Implosion!” Pan Lin once again exclaimed. Instantly, he understood.

They thought that it wasn’t enough because they only saw what was in front of them. Fang Rui thought that it was enough because he saw the whole situation. He saw that Bullet Rain had thrown an Implosion Grenade their way, and he was going to use the momentum brought by this Implosion Grenade.

The airflow drew everything inward, sending the plants scattering. Boundless Sea, right next to the grenade, was instantly sent flying by the grenade, but his two hands were still gripping Soul Speaker. This was a priority that the Implosion Grenade couldn’t break.

Fly out. The two characters flew out together.

Exclamations sounded throughout the crowd of Blue Rain fans, who were all thinking, “it’s over, it’s over.”

“Don’t underestimate me!” But at this moment, Zheng Xuan didn’t say his catchphrase “how stressful,” but instead exploded with this shout.

Bullet Rain changed direction.

Chasing the two characters flying through the air, madly going after them.

Those dazzling explosions upon the ground were now aimed into the air, exploding nonstop next to Boundless Sea and Soul Speaker.

What godly gun technique!

Everyone was shocked.

Because the two characters were stuck together by the grab, they flew a bit more slowly from the explosion than they otherwise would have. But to focus fire completely upon the trajectory they followed, thoroughly bombarding their bodies, how many people could do what Zheng Xuan did?

The applause swallowed the Blue Rain stadium.

Zheng Xuan, this person who never had motivation, now displayed such a thrilling performance at this crucial moment. It surprised everyone, it raised everyone’s spirits.

And were these attacks just to deal damage?

Of course not!

The implosion sent them flying quickly; Zheng Xuan’s attacks chased after them quickly; everything happened in an instant. But the trajectory of the two flying characters, under Bullet Rain’s attacks, was changed. It was clear to see that the two stuck-together characters wouldn’t land in the wind zone. Even if Boundless Sea tried to Fling now, there was no way he could send Soul Speaker into the wind zone.

The applause became even more enthusiastic, so much that no one noticed a gunshot, a gunshot that was separate from Bullet Rain’s midair firing, a gunshot that was different from Dancing Rain’s explosive artillery fire.

With a gunshot, Bullet Rain’s attacks were extinguished, and after that, Zheng Xuan saw a grenade fly past his sight, flying toward those two characters in the air.

The type of the grenade clearly registered in Zheng Xuan’s pupils.

Implosion!

A grenade he was incomparably familiar with. And its trajectory…

No!

Zheng Xuan desperately wanted to stop this grenade, but when he tried to control his character, Bullet Rain couldn’t move. Of course, there was a reason why he couldn’t move.

Stun Bullet. The earlier gunshot had been a Stun Bullet, stopping Bullet Rain’s attacks for good. And after that, this Implosion Grenade flew outward, Zheng Xuan wanted to stop it but couldn’t. Only with great effort could he move again, and he couldn’t be bothered to figure out who had done all this. Bullet Rain lifted his gun, furiously trying to detonate that Implosion Grenade in midair.

But, it was too late…

Perhaps the Implosion Grenade hadn’t managed to fly to its most optimal position, but when it burst, it still accomplished the goal that Happy wanted.

Whoosh…

When the Implosion Grenade blasted open, there was this sharp sound of a twister. The two characters were still stumbling from their landing, one continued to stumble, while the other was picked up into the air again.

Right now there wasn’t a grab in effect, so the the Implosion Grenade only affected the opponent. Soul Speaker was sent flying once again.

And the stumbling Boundless Sea simply rolled into a half-crouch. He didn’t even bother to stand up straight, he chased after Soul Speaker half-rolling, half-crawling. Behind him. Steamed Bun Invasion brandished his brick and aggressively followed.

It’s over…

Zheng Xuan was in despair. At last, he had nothing left to stop this. That damned Stun Bullet, that damned Implosion Grenade, that damned guy.

Zheng Xuan already knew who had orchestrated this whole thing.

It was that person who, at any moment, even if he was being pincered, even if he was being pincered by dual Blade Masters Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen, could never be overlooked. That damned person.

Ye Xiu.

Lord Grim.

Chapter 1472 - New Criminal Partners

If looks could kill, Ye Xiu and his Lord Grim would have been dead by now from the crowd.

Despite pressure from Huang Shaotian’s and Lu Hanwen’s Blade Master duo, he was still able to find an opening at a crucial moment and complete Happy’s plans. Wasn’t that what it meant to be a core player?

If the brilliant escape from Formless Phantom Blade could be considered as just dodging an attack, then this time, Yu Wenzhou wouldn’t be able to wave away the play as just landing an attack.

Anyone could see how fatal it was for Blue Rain to have Soul Speaker flying away at this moment.

Seeing Soul Speaker tumble helplessly towards the wind zone, Blue Rain’s fans hated how they couldn’t reach out with their hands to help him get back his footing.

No one could stop it though.

The stadium was filled with sighs of despair.

For Blue Rain, the outcome wouldn’t just be the end of this match, but the end of Blue Rain’s season. A powerhouse team making it into the playoffs was nothing noteworthy. They only had one goal: to be the champions. A season, where they didn’t win the championships, was a failure for them.

Were they actually going to fall in the quarterfinals of the playoffs?

The match wasn’t over yet, but Blue Rain’s fans were already feeling pessimistic.

Because no one could stop it from happening.

Yes, no one.

But there was the wind.

When Soul Speaker entered the wind zone, he faced against the wind. As a result, the resistive force of the wind slowed his air speed.

Chance!

Countless people cried out in their hearts.

But in reality, they had no idea if this was an opportunity. They suddenly noticed a difference in how they expected things to turn out, so they thought it was an opportunity.

And it really was one.

However, it was different from the surprise the spectators felt. Blue Rain’s players had anticipated this possibility.

Swoksaar raised his staff.

Boom boom boom, Dancing Rain’s artillery shells flew towards Swoksaar. Su Mucheng wasn’t going to mess up at a critical moment.

Boom!

Amidst the rumbling smoke from the explosions, Swoksaar’s staff was still flashing with a dark purple light.

The curse hadn’t been interrupted, meaning Dancing Rain’s attacks hadn’t hit.

As the smoke dispersed, Troubling Rain’s figure gradually appeared.

Using your own body to block an attack was as stupid as it got. Perhaps because of how stupid it was, too many people would forget about this option.

Huang Shaotian did such a stupid-looking action at this crucial moment. He had let Ye Xiu go and reached Swoksaar’s side to help block the incoming attacks.

Ye Xiu didn’t react slowly either. When Troubling Rain suddenly jumped away, he realized something.

He didn’t block Troubling Rain. Instead, he immediately attacked Swoksaar.

But he was too late.

By the time Lord Grim acted, Ye Xiu knew it was too late.

When Huang Shaotian seized an opportunity, he wouldn’t leave any openings behind. By the time Ye Xiu noticed Troubling Rain’s movements and made a decision, it was too late.

Troubling Rain had been hit, and Swoksaar was hit by Lord Grim’s attack. However, the curse went through.

Hexagram Prison!

Swoksaar had unexpectedly cast a Hexagram Prison.

To seal Boundless Sea? To seal Steamed Bun Invasion?

These two characters looked as if they could continue their kidnapping of Soul Speaker because the wind had stopped the kidnapping to reach its completion. Had Yu Wenzhou cast a Hexagram Prison to stop one of them?

No!

When the Hexagram Prison descended, the one locked into place by the six seals was Soul Speaker, Team Blue Rain’s Paladin.

Everyone was startled, but understood soon afterwards.

Anything sealed by Hexagram Prison would take no damage, and the prison could not be broken.

There was only one way to dispel Hexagram Prison: wait until the duration of the curse ended. Even if the caster died, the prison would stay in existence.

This was the difference between a Warlock and a Mage.

Mages used mana and incantations to create magic. When the Mage died, their magic would disappear as well. But Warlocks used their mana to create a sort of contract. Even if the Warlock died, the contract would still exist. Thus, the curse would last until the contract’s conditions were fulfilled.

The Hexagram Prison locked Soul Speaker, but it wasn’t to seal him away, it was to proctect him.

Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion could attack Soul Speaker, but they would have no way to carry Soul Speaker out further into the wind zone. They could only wait on the side for these 10 seconds and wait for Team Blue Rain to rescue their healer.

10 seconds. That was how long Swoksaar’s Hexagram Prison lasted.

“Beautiful!” Zheng Xuan was suddenly reinvigorated, after losing a lot of morale from Ye Xiu stopping his attacks. Bullet Rain raised his gun, but then, he saw that Boundless Sea didn’t dodge or let up. It was as if he couldn’t see the Hexagram Prison as he crashed straight into it.

Crash!

When Boundless Sea touched the Hexagram Prison, the pillars of light entered his body. In the next instant, Boundless Sea was forcefully dragged inside the prison, right next to Soul Speaker.

Without any hesitation, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea threw Soul Speaker to the ground.

Soon afterwards, Steamed Bun Invasion also charged into the Hexagram Prison, locking himself up too. He stomped on Soul Speaker twice.

The audience was dumbfounded.

This… the old Criminal Partners consisted of Fang Rui’s Thief and Lin Jingyan’s Brawler. Their nickname mainly came from their classes. A Thief and a Brawler. If they weren’t committing crimes, what were they doing?

But looking at the two criminals in front of them, Fang Rui had switched to a Qi Master, which had zero relationship with criminal activities. Steamed Bun Invasion was a Brawler, but he was a rookie. However, the two of them together were truly criminal to the core. Soul Speaker had been thrown into the Hexagram Prison, and the two of them threw themselves in as well to continue beating him up. It was too evil, too immoral, too criminal!

That was what the audience thought, but to Blue Rain’s pro players, this was a tactic.

Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion looked as if they were walking right into a trap, but in this way, no matter what Blue Rain did, the instant the Hexagram Prison disappeared, these two would still be the closest to Soul Speaker. When that time came, the two would still hold the initiative. Would Team Blue Rain be able to immediately stop the two as soon as the Hexagram Prison went away? Probably not. Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu, one far one close, wouldn’t make it easy for them!

Team Blue Rain’s players laughed bitterly. Yu Wenzhou even more so. He just couldn’t get a handle on those two.

In any case, Blue Rain still needed to try.

The two locked by Hexagram Prison had better not think about dodging any attacks. Among the three Blue Rain players who could reach them, just Zheng Xuan’s Spitfire alone could cover both at once.

However, just attacks alone wouldn’t be able to split those two away from each other!

Even if an Implosion Grenade was thrown, the two couldn’t be thrown outside of the Hexagram Prison. Their movements would be locked down by Hexagram Prison.

Right now, they couldn’t do anything. The key moment would come the instant Hexagram Prison dissipated.

Blue Rain’s players knew the timing, but Happy probably did too. Data such as the duration of skills couldn’t be hidden.

Ten. Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain attacked. Swoksaar continued to be suppressed by Dancing Rain. Huang Shaotian and Lu Hanwen continued to be blocked by Ye Xiu.

Nine. All of them moved towards the Hexagram Prison at the same time.

Eight. The same.

Seven. The same.

Six. The crowd in the stadium went onto their feet.

Five. Another second passed.

Four. Troubling Rain and Flowing Cloud suddenly switched positions.

Three. Both Blade Masters used Shadow Steps simultaneously, instantly filling the field with nineteen shadows.

Two. All of the scattered shadows rushed towards the Hexagram Prison.

One. Lord Grim chased after them and caught the real Flowing Cloud!

Zero. Hexagram Prison disappeared. In the end, Huang Shaotian was more experienced. His real body was able to escape from Lord Grim’s entanglement.

Meteor Form!

Ice Rain swung forward, sword light flying. To stop a target, a skill with a forced knockdown was the most optimal choice.

Qi Wave Shield!

But Happy’s two players were ready. Don’t look at how much of a bully the two looked like while in prison. In reality, there was a lot of thought going into it. They had been counting the ten seconds too, or at least, Fang Rui was.

A Qi Wave Shield was pushed out the instant the Hexagram Prison went away.

The sword shadows fell onto the Qi Wave Shield. This skill covered a much smaller area, but its defensive capabilities were much higher than Qi Guard. The entirety of Meteor Form was blocked by the Qi Wave Shield.

Huang Shaotian wanted to follow with another attack, but Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had reached behind him. Huang Shaotian had paid too much attention to this end and neglected his back. Just when he was about to attack, Troubling Rain was suddenly launched into the air.

Bang!

With a Falling Flower Palm, Lord Grim sent Troubling Rain flying and then chased after him. Huang Shaotian had been too focused on the main issue at hand and had neglected Ye Xiu. However, Ye Xiu had also neglected Lu Hanwen to deal with Huang Shaotian.

As a result, the moment Huang Shaotian was sent flying, Lu Hanwen also sent Ye Xiu flying.

Troubling Rain flying outwards had interfered with Zheng Xuan though. He had saved up his cooldowns previously. Now, he had fired out all sorts of special bullets with CC effects. Suddenly, a wild Troubling Rain appeared.

Glory had friendly fire off, but attacks couldn’t just magically teleport past an ally! Huang Shaotian was trying to control his character to not interfere with Zheng Xuan’s offense, but many of the attacks still hit Troubling Rain. These attacks suddenly became like faulty goods, snuffed out without any effects coming out.

On the other side, when Lu Hanwen had Flowing Cloud hit Lord Grim flying, he had done it with intention, sending Lord Grim crashing towards Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion. But just as Lord Grim was sent flying away, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella above his head went kakaka into Rotor Wings, and Lord Grim flew away on his own…

Chapter 1473 - Learning from the Opponent

Dadadadadada…

The sound of the Rotor Wing was clearly transmitted to everyone’s ears. To Blue Rain’s people, it sounded like cruel, mocking laughter.

The situation had gotten to this kind of unsaveable point. Soul Speaker was abducted into the wind zone by those two Fighters, and Lord Grim was using Rotor Wing to fly that way as well.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain was a long-range attacker, standing at relatively safe position, and An Wenyi had also long since controlled Little Cold Hands to circle around from afar, preemptively destroying any thought Blue Rain might have had at a healer exchange.

There was no other way.

Only one path was left to Blue Rain – enter the wind zone, against the wind.

But as the ones who had chosen this map, Blue Rain knew better than anyone else how unfavorable fighting upwind in this gale wind zone would be. Would knowing the disadvantages allow them to avoid the risk? Things clearly weren’t that simple.

But facing such a severe situation, Blue Rain didn’t panic. In their chat, message after message from Captain Yu Wenzhou jumped onto the screen.

Crippled hands, that was only relative. Crippled hands in the professional circle would still be at the top among ordinary gamers.

The instructions were methodically issued, and without any hesitation, Blue Rain’s players began following directions.

Fighting directly upwind absolutely could not work. Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan, one left and one right, circled around from the two sides, echoing the hook Fang Rui had taken at the very beginning. They couldn’t leave the center path empty either, though. Lu Hanwen’s greatsword Blade Master Flowing Cloud took charge. But the true main attacker of this arrangement was Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar.

Curses. Only Swoksaar’s curses wouldn’t be affected by the gales. That was to say, he himself suffered no disadvantages from fighting upwind.

And so Swoksaar immediately began to cast. Every second they were slow here, their healer Soul Speaker would take one more second of attack. Doubt, hesitation, consideration, none of that belonged to Blue Rain right now. The guidelines to their actions right now consisted of only one word: fast.

Quickly disrupt them from the front, quickly have two characters circle around from the left and right.

Happy, of course, wouldn’t sit and watch Blue Rain arrange their pincer formation.

Dancing Rain opened fire first, aiming her cannon at Swoksaar. Su Mucheng was always closely paying attention to the movements of the character that Yu Wenzhou controlled.

Boom!

The shell exploded, but Swoksaar continued casting, uninterrupted. Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had stepped up, using his greatsword Flame Shadow to directly knock aside the shell.

The shell exploded upon impact. Swoksaar was perfectly protected, and Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud had only suffered a little bit of damage from the airflow of the explosion.

But this one moment of cover clearly wasn’t enough. What Yu Wenzhou was controlling Swoksaar to cast evidently wasn’t one of the small spells that could be completed in an instant.

It’s all up to me!

Lu Hanwen, this child player who had joined the Alliance at age fourteen and who hadn’t yet reached age sixteen, was already incredibly used to taking up this kind of heavy responsibility on the battlefield.

From day one of Blue Rain lifting him into the first-string roster, they dropped him in this position. And this was what had formerly been Yu Feng’s position, bold and ringing, the head of Blue Rain’s train.

A fledgling child became Team Blue Rain’s attack leader. In the beginning, many people didn’t understand Blue Rain’s arrangement, and even called it insane.

But Lu Hanwen’s performance swiftly silenced those voices. Looking at him, some even saw the Alliance’s shining future.

Lu Hanwen himself never thought that much. In the beginning, he was just excited at being able to stand onstage, a pure and simple excitement.

A burden to shoulder? The expectations of too many people? All that a fourteen-year-old child could feel of these things was haziness.

No one deliberately pointed these out to him, and so, in this haze, Lu Hanwen began his professional career. He won in this haze, he lost in this haze; he cried in this haze, he laughed in this haze. And thus gradually, the haze dissipated, and he began to sense that standing on the battlefield wasn’t merely a proof of ability, but an inheritance of responsibility and obligation.

He needed to inherit all that the Blue Rain players who had stood in this position before him had carried.

The fourteen-year-old child didn’t retreat at all. It was as though he had found a new and intriguing toy, as he began to taste this all.

But this certainly was no toy. This was certainly much heavier than a child’s imagination. And for this, Lu Hanwen had cried the tears of regret.

The tears washed over him, allowing him to grow. Even though he was only in his teens, Lu Hanwen was a true man. Every time he cried, he only became stronger and more determined.

And now, he carried this upon his shoulders, with no turning back. He was no longer in the haziness of before. He had the courage, he had the faith to carry this all.

It’s up to me!

Lu Hanwen firmly told himself. He did not want to again spill tears of regret after playoffs.

Flowing Cloud closely guarded Swoksaar. He didn’t miss any attack angle that could potentially interrupt Swoksaar’s casting. At this moment, there were no seniors to help him. It was all up to him.

Boom boom boom.

In the end, the person most focused on this area was still Su Mucheng.

After the attack that Lu Hanwen had blocked, Dancing Rain unleashed the three shots of an Anti-Tank Missile.

Three shots in a row, it’ll be difficult…

But, I can’t miss a single one!

Lu Hanwen welcomed this challenge. Flowing Cloud stepped forward, and his sword slashed out.

A greatsword wasn’t as nimble as a lightsaber. Flowing Cloud’s slash was heavy, unchanging, but the character’s position, the timing of the attack, the character attacking, were all controlled extremely well.

Boom!

First shot.

Boom!

Second shot.

The blade flashed forward, breaking two of the shots, and then stopped in the air.

Boom! The third shot exploded.

Lu Hanwen had incredible eyesight and reaction speed. This, he had just displayed in the hazy forest of the group arena. But this one slash detonating all three cannon shots still incited a full stadium of applause.

But it wasn’t over yet!

In the wind zone, Fang Rui and Steamed Bun were fighting 2v1 against a healer, how busy could they be? Seeing that Yu Wenzhou was coming to disrupt hem head-on, they prepared for the enemy. And seeing that someone was guarding him, even blocking the cannonfire from Dancing Rain, they of course would cooperate to attack him.

Qi Bullet!

Boundless Sea’s palm pushed forward.

Interrupting a skill didn’t need a lot of damage, as long as the skill was fast enough. For a Qi Master, a Qi Bullet could be sent out with one push, so of course it was the most convenient choice for this.

But this kind of low-damage skill was much appreciated by the one guarding Swoksaar. Lu Hanwen had just finished dealing with Su Mucheng’s attack when he saw Boundless Sea slapping a Qi Bullet in this direction. Without even thinking, Flowing Cloud stepped to Swoksaar’s other side and directly used his body to block the Qi Bullet.

A lowest-level skill, how much damage could there be!

“Damnit!” Fang Rui wasn’t polite as he expressed his frustration in the match chat.

These disruptive attacks were all blocked by Lu Hanwen. But Swoksaar still hadn’t finished casting, so his duty was yet unfinished. Both sides readied more attacks, and on another side, An Wenyi wasn’t idling around either. Little Cold Hands joined as well, lifting her cross, facing Swoksaar, and swinging it left and right like a pendulum.

Hypnosis!

An Wenyi, taking advantage of the fact that no one was disrupting him on his end, actually also began a very intensive spell. He was trying to get Swoksaar to stop his work entirely.

Lu Hanwen saw it, but he really could do nothing about it. A Cleric’s Hypnosis had a long cast time, so if he wanted to stop it, he had to do it now. If the interrupt wasn’t successful, then it would land upon the target with 100% guarantee. But Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud wasn’t any long-ranged attacker, and An Wenyi had quite cunningly positioned Little Cold Hands in a position that wasn’t nearby. Interrupting Little Cold Hands was truly outside the range of Lu Hanwen’s ability.

Was this it?

Was he once again unable to help the team in their most dire moments?

Gunshot!

Little Cold Hands’ swinging of the cross instantly stopped.

The interrupt was successful, and there was only one person on Blue Rain’s side who could use Gunner attacks, Zheng Xuan.

In the team round, you are never alone on the battlefield.

Lu Hanwen thought of his captain’s words, and felt fortunate, felt proud. Their Blue Rain was just this kind of team, accepting the unmotivated Zheng Xuan, accepting the chatterbox Huang Shaotian, accepting the slow-handed captain. And he, this fledgling, inexperienced kid, wasn’t he also accepted by everyone?

Accepting each other, covering each other’s weaknesses, Blue Rain came together into a cohesive whole. When Lu Hanwen lamented that he wasn’t enough, his teammate easily helped him take care of the problem.

Zheng Xuan helped Lu Hanwen deal with this problem, and Lu Hanwen himself was still helping his captain deal with a problem.

Zheng Xuan succeeded, and so, shortly after, he succeeded as well.

The cast was complete.

Purple-black light flashed at the tip of the scepter.

Death’s Door!

With such a long cast time, the audience had guessed early on what this skill probably was. And now that Swoksaar had finally completed the cast, nothing could stop it.

Death’s Door, erected into the void, didn’t suffer any disruption from the wind zone. The Death’s Door and the gale were like two dimensionally-separate objects encountering each other, but each existing in its own world, unable to interact with each other.

It and the wind were on separate dimensions, but with Boundless Sea, with Steamed Bun Invasion, with Lord Grim, it was on the same plane.

And so when a character crashed into the Death’s Door, it immediately unleashed all of its demonic power, attempting to swallow this guy into nothingness.

Of course, it couldn’t actually swallow this character, this was just how the skill would deal its final damage. Under the gazes of the silent and shocked audience, the Death’s Door trembled, and along with the character that had crashed into it, shattered into a mess of purple-black light and shadow.

The Death’s Door vanished. What shocked everyone was that such a fast method of dealing with the Death’s Door was the exact same method that Yu Wenzhou had used in the last team round, against Wei Chen’s Death’s Door.

In this match, Happy had already learned and copied it.

Chapter 1474 - Can’t Waver

Death’s Door disappeared, having quickly fulfilled its destiny. Amidst the light of the disappearing Death’s Door, looking as if it intended to devour everything, the one who fell was Lord Grim.

Ye Xiu had copied what Yu Wenzhou had done, but when everyone thought on it, they couldn’t understand how this had happened.

This was because the situation Happy was facing was different from what Yu Wenzhou had been met with.

When Yu Wenzhou was up against the Death’s Door, there was only one target in range, his Swoksaar. So, when Swoksaar collided with the Death’s Door, the Death’s Door ended.

But now, it wasn’t just Lord Grim within reach of this Death’s Door. There was also Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion. You could even say that the intended target of this attack was Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion.

Under these circumstances, there was no reason for Death’s Door to disappear after catching only one of its targets.

“What’s going on?” Pan Lin questioned, recovering from his shock.

“How strange,” Li Yibo tagged on, not having any intentions to try and explain this. He couldn’t figure it out either.

Never mind those two, even Yu Wenzhou, a god-level Warlock player, was puzzled at the disappearance of the Death’s Door. In fact, due to his familiarity with the skill, it was even weirder for him.

How did this Death’s Door disappear? Was there some unknown characteristic of Death’s Door that all these players didn’t know of?

In this moment Yu Wenzhou suddenly thought of their senior, their old captain, Wei Chen, now a member of Happy.

Wei Chen was definitely one of the very first amongst Warlock players, or even players in general. He had persisted for ten years, an amazing achievement. After all, Wei Chen hadn’t been a pro player for large majority of those years, just a normal player. It was perfectly normal for a normal player to get tired of a class and switch. It was truly rare for a normal player to remain playing the same class for ten years. At that point is was true love.

For their old captain Wei Chen, it really was true love for the Warlock.

So, perhaps, this unknown characteristic of Death’s Door was something he discovered. As for Ye Xiu, he was just using Wei Chen’s discovery and taking advantage of the bug to end the Death’s Door early against the skill’s design.

No… it wasn’t against the skill’s design. They had probably used a detail of the design that no one else knew about.

What was it?

Though Yu Wenzhou was curious, there wasn’t any point in agonizing over it now. Today’s match had given him all too many questions. Yu Wenzhou still hadn’t figured out how Ye Xiu had managed to pinpoint so accurately where to set the shadow trap.

However, he didn’t hesitate due to this confusion. If Death’s Door didn’t accomplish his aims, then he’ll just use another.

Shadow Flames!

An ember of dark purple flames leaped out from Curse of Destruction.

Yu Wenzhou didn’t use anymore large scale spells like Death’s Door. After all, it was unfair to expect Lu Hanwen to cover him all by himself. Thankfully, Zheng Xuan passed by and helped out a bit, but now, Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan were both far away, having gone around the flanks. They couldn’t help out over here anymore. Swoksaar’s casting had to sync with the rhythm Flowing Clouds was setting.

Shadow Flames was successfully cast, the dark purple flames flickering.

When this skill hit, then the target would take damage over time. Each tick of damage would interrupt casting. Thus, this ball of flame was thrown at Boundless Sea. No matter how dirty Fang Rui played his Qi Master, he couldn’t escape the fact that many of the Qi Master’s skills required casting.

If Boundless Sea let it hit, then his attacks would be restricted. If he dodged, then he would give Xu Jingxi an opening and chance. A healer under siege was restricted to just waiting to be saved, he was using his own methods to struggle, trying to find an opportunity.

Now, an opportunity had come!

Fang Rui was unwilling to be CC’ed by Shadow Flame and immediately had Boundless Sea dodge.

Yu Wenzhou’s choice of target was very clear and thought out. He had a clear view of the situation. Making Fang Rui dodge would be able to give an opening. Thus, Shadow Flame flew out, Boundless Sea dodged, and Xu Jingxi immediately understood, his heavily armored Paladin taking one step this way.

One step, just one step.

As Soul Speaker managed this step, his back suddenly tensed before his body was thrown into the air.

Circle Swing!

Lord Grim, who had fallen in the explosion of Death’s Door, had stood up again and returned to crush the hope that Blue Rain just saw.

Crash!

Soul Speaker was slammed into the ground.

“Where do you think you’re running, brat!” Steamed Bun yelled into the chat. His tone, demeanor… it was like he didn’t know he was a rookie.

“I would’ve been fine even without your help,” Fang Rui suddenly said.

“Huh?” Steamed Bun replied.

“Not you, Steamed Bun,” Ye Xiu typed a reply as fast as he could. Though he knew that Fang Rui was talking to him, but if they let Steamed Bun misunderstand, then things would go downhill very fast.

“We’re counting on you, Steamed Bun,” Fang Rui also broke out into cold sweat, hurriedly pitching in and making sure that Steamed Bun was focused and happy.

“You can count on me!” Steamed Bun was delighted, and Steamed Bun Invasion quickly pinned Soul Speaker and gave him a beating. Tyrannical Chain Punch was sent out like some sort of low level skill, very wastefully unleashed onto Soul Speaker.

Ye Xiu and Fang Rui’s hearts calmed. Let him be as wasteful as he wants; it’s better than going completely out of it.

“It’s all up to you!” Ye Xiu once again made sure Steamed Bun focused, but his words had a second meaning. Fang Rui understood, knowing that Ye Xiu was actually talking to him. As for Steamed Bun, the other cheerfully gave an acknowledging reply. Fang Rui didn’t dare tell him the truth of the matter.

Lord Grim was originally in the windy zone, but now he charged out with a tailwind.

Lord Grim didn’t go after Troubling Rain on the right or Bullet Rain on the left, instead charging directly at Swoksaar. Swoksaar, who only had Flowing Clouds protecting him.

Charge, Shining Cut!

Two skills, one change of direction, Swoksaar’s skill was dodged, but Flowing Clouds’ greatsword Flame Shadow was already crashing towards Lord Grim’s head.

Collapsing Mountain!

Without Huang Shaotian there to cover him, Lu Hanwen’s Collapsing Mountain wasn’t executed so wildly, instead more reserved, in a way that gave him the ability to advance and attack or retreat and switch as he needed…

However, there was no switching so quickly!

Lu Hanwen could only keep up with Lord Grim with his view! Just as the Collapsing Mountain was about to hit, Lord Grim turned once again.

Colliding Stab!

With another movement skill, Lord Grim brushed right past the Collapsing Mountain. Lu Hanwen wanted to change the direction of his slash, but he couldn’t make it in time. He had never felt encumbered by Flame Shadow’s slow speed. Though he was just a young teen, Lu Hanwen liked this sturdy weight. Every strike, every hit had him feel content and satisfied.

But now?

When this strike hit the ground heavily, his heart felt exceptionally empty. Seeing Lord Grim’s Colliding Stab dart under his Collapsing Mountain and striking true at Swoksaar, the captain he had been protecting, Lu Hanwen, for the first time, thought to himself: if only this sword was a little bit faster.

He was wavering.

This determined, optimistic and hardworking young man, was helpless in this crucial moment, and finally began to doubt his choice of wielding his greatsword…

“Where’s your mind wandering off to, huh? Focus focus focus…”

That was when Blue Rain’s team chat was suddenly flooded with these words.

Huang Shaotian was the only one who spoke or typed like that.

But… focus?

The audience was thinking to themselves, there wasn’t anyone not focusing. In their eyes, Blue Rain’s players were all very focused and doing their best. Although Lu Hanwen failed to stop Lord Grim and Yu Wenzhou failed to avoid the attack, they were definitely paying attention. They were focused and doing their best.

“Who’s not focused?” Pan Lin was also asking.

Thus, Li Yibo’s attention wavered as he realized he couldn’t answer. It was happening again. Whenever the match was at its most intense, there would be more he didn’t understand…

Lu Hanwen’s face burned.

Everyone else was confused, but he was more than clear on the fact that it was him Huang Shaotian was telling to pay attention.

It wasn’t saying that he failed to stop Lord Grim because he wasn’t paying attention, but after he failed, there was a moment of hesitation, a moment where he wavered and doubted.

It was just an instant, but Huang Shaotian saw, saw right through him…

Lu Hanwen was ashamed of himself.

Protect captain’s Swoksaar. In the past, that was always Huang Shaotian’s responsibility. Thus, Blue Rain used a strategy where Swoksaar was bait and Huang Shaotian executed a sneak attack to deal a crippling blow. This time, taking into consideration that it might be harder to move around in these windy zones, the job of protecting the captain was passed to him.

And what did he do?

After failing to block his opponent’s assault, he had began to waver. And this instant had Huang Shaotian taking notice. This might be because he never wavered. He made mistakes, and failed to protect Swoksaar sometimes, but Huang Shaotian had never, ever wavered. His tendency to ramble had been pointed out again and again over these years, but when had he ever hesitated and decided to change? Okay, that wasn’t the best example, but Lu Hanwen felt Huang Shaotian’s determination through the other noticing his own wavering.

There was no wavering, you can’t waver!

Take your choice with you to the end!

Haaa!

The greatsword switched directions, cutting through the wind with a sound like Lu Hanwen’s inner roar. Flowing Clouds slashed at Lord Grim, determined!

Boom boom boom boom!

Canonfire blocked his way. Dancing Rain had begun to support Lord Grim from afar. Lu Hanwen’s rescue mission had suffered a setback, but now he had readjusted his state of mind. Lu Hanwen never lacked courage. What he lacked was the calm that their captain Yu Wenzhou conducted himself with, the cold determination Huang Shaotian displayed.

And right now, he didn’t rush into things and use up all his energy. He carefully surveyed the the situation, contemplative. Suddenly, his eyes lit up.

Happy’s healer, Little Cold Hands, was really close!

Chapter 1475 - Steady

From realization to decision, Lu Hanwen was resolute. He abandoned his captain, Swoksaar, with no hesitation and rushed towards Little Cold Hands.

Triple Slash!

Shadow Steps!

Two skills were used one after the other. The shining arcs from Triple Slash had yet to disappear, when Flowing Cloud split into several shadows, which spread throughout the field. In an instant, Little Cold Hands was tightly surrounded.

“Oh oh oh!!!” The crowd cheered.

Everyone had been worried about Swoksaar’s safety, but Lu Hanwen decisively gave up on his captain and pounced towards Happy’s healer.

What will the outcome be?

There was no time to think about it carefully. It was just that usually, when a pro player did something unexpected, it would turn out to be a brilliant godly play.

Hua hua hua hua….

Wild applause followed soon afterwards. After getting trapped by Shadow Steps, Little Cold Hands was indeed helpless. Lu Hanwen could perfectly control seven shadows to the extent that not even a Glory senior player could quickly distinguish the real from the fake. How could a rookie like An Wenyi do so?

Even so, Lu Hanwen was completely focused on his playing. He didn’t underestimate or look down on Team Happy’s so-called “weak point”.

The purpose of Shadow Steps was to confuse the opponent, but the true aim of his play was to land an attack.

The course of events from Triple Slash to Shadow Steps to Flowing Cloud attacking took place in the span of merely one or two seconds. When Flowing Cloud’s greatsword, Flame Shadow, cut Little Cold Hands, the afterimages from the sequence could still be seen.

When Little Cold Hands was knocked to the ground from the attack, the applause became even more thunderous.

From the audience’s perspective, Lu Hanwen had successfully accomplished his goal with that strike hitting.

But artillery fire arrived shortly afterwards to rescue An Wenyi.

Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain had been circling around the edges of the area the entire time. Every point on the battlefield was within her range. Lu Hanwen’s decision had been too sudden, and Su Mucheng hadn’t been able to react in time to it, which was why her support only came now.

Lu Hanwen wasn’t surprised. He had expected Su Mucheng’s Launcher to try to stop him. Her Screen Cannon tactic was an important point that Team Blue Rain had emphasized during their match preparations.

However, at this distance…

Lu Hanwen was confident that he could lock down Little Cold Hands while dodging Dancing Rain’s attacks. After all, his target was a Cleric without any combat threat, making it much easier for him to deal with.

Flowing Cloud dodged as he swung his sword at Little Cold Hands. Lu Hanwen was mainly focused on Su Mucheng’s attacks. As long as he wasn’t disrupted by her, he could pin down Happy’s healer without a problem. In that case, Happy should send more people to rescue him, no?

That was Lu Hanwen’s plan.

Their healer, Soul Speaker, was also in Happy’s hands, but Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan were going to rescue him. Even if Happy wanted to trade healers, they would need to make some adjustments to the current situation. The easiest and most effective way was for Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim to change targets to Lu Hanwen.

Lu Hanwen didn’t neglect Lord Grim. Since this was the most likely outcome, he obviously wouldn’t let the opportunity go by. He would use it to give Blue Rain the initiative, which was exactly what they needed.

But…

No movement.

Lord Grim didn’t make any changes and continued to attack Swoksaar.

Swoksaar was a Warlock. His close combat capabilities were better than healers, but it was still very limited. What’s more, Yu Wenzhou’s crippled hand speed against Ye Xiu’s unspecialized blitz… Lu Hanwen didn’t want to think about it. If he thought about it any longer, he felt like he would be disrespecting his captain. But if Ye Xiu wasn’t concerned about Lu Hanwen’s side, did that mean he thought Su Mucheng was enough to resolve the problem?

It looks like I’m not putting on enough pressure! I need to let Happy feel that just Su Mucheng alone won’t be enough to get their healer away from me!

Attack, continue attacking. Compared to before, Lu Hanwen’s offense was bolder. It was as if he wouldn’t let stop even if he died.

But…

Still no movement.

Lord Grim’s attacks were still focused on Swoksaar, not a single attack missing. Lu Hanwen wanted to see if Lord Grim was ever looking towards his side, but… the unspecialized offense was just too fast. His weapon just kept on transforming. Lord Grim’s positioning, posture, and movements would constantly change according to the weapon’s transformations. Whenever he looked towards his side, was it a coincidence or was he actually taking note of the situation there?

Lu Hanwen didn’t know, but he had just learned from first-hand experience. This time, he couldn’t waver. If he let go of Little Cold Hands to rescue his captain, wouldn’t that mean he was just wasting his time with those previous attacks? In a high-level competition, there was no place for wasted actions.

Even if he had made the wrong choice, he had to take it all the way through and pave a path of blood through his mistake!

Slash slash slash!

Flowing Cloud attacked even more ferociously. Because of the greatsword in his hands, it sometimes felt like he was a Berserker instead of a Blade Master.

“Coach Li, what are your thoughts?” Pan Lin couldn’t help but ask Li Yibo for his opinion again.

“This is… there are a lot of different exchanges taking places. It’s hard to make any definite conclusions,” Li Yibo said.

“When you say exchanges, are you referring to Blue Rain’s healer, Happy’s healer, and Yu Wenzhou?” Pan Lin said.

“Yes… at first glance, Blue Rain seems to be trading 2 for 1, but they’re about to go rescue their healer. As for Happy’s side, Su Mucheng is evidently not able to suppress Lu Hanwen alone. As a result, the outcome is depended on Blue Rain’s side. If Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan are able to rescue Soul Speaker, the initiative will fall into Blue Rain’s hands,” Li Yibo analyzed.

“In other words, Huang Shaotian’s and Zheng Xuan’s performances are key,” Pan Lin said.

“Yes, but what gave this opportunity to turn things around was Lu Hanwen’s brave act. If not, even if Blue Rain was able to rescue Xu Jingxi, it would just result in an even playing field. However, now, Blue Rain has a chance to establish the upper hand,” Li Yibo said.

“Got it,” Pan Lin nodded his head. The stream couldn’t focus on the entire battlefield anymore, since the battle had split into different sections. As the two commentators talked, the camera focused on what the two had determined to be the key area: Blue Rain’s rescue operation towards Soul Speaker.

Soul Speaker could persist for a long time.

For one, he wore plate armor, so his defense was incredibly high. In addition, Xu Jingxi was a tenacious player. If even a small opening appeared to heal or to buff his defense, he would immediately do so. Blue Rain was a team proficient at defense. As the healer, he was an expert at rescuing others and surviving in defensive situations.

“This guy’s really annoying to deal with.” Fang Rui let out a sigh, seeing Huang Shaotian’s Troubling Rain and Zhen Xuan’s Bullet Rain coming in from the sides of the wind zone.

“Don’t worry, I’m here!” Steamed Bun was full of confidence, although no one knew if that stemmed from actual confidence or from not knowing how serious the situation was.

“Enemy reinforcement has arrived,” Fang Rui reminded Steamed Bun.

“You’ve got it?” Steamed Bun played it down.

“You really make things sound so simple,” Fang Rui coughed blood. The two weren’t having much trouble bullying a healer, so the two had the time to chat. But the situation would soon turn more serious. Happy currently held the initiative because they had Blue Rain’s healer as their hostage. However, if Blue Rain successfully saved their healer, not only would they lose their hostage, the hostage would turn into a powerful shield for the enemy. That would be bad.

“Pull him over this way,” Fang Rui called out to Steamed Bun.

“I’ll do what you say!” Steamed Bun replied.

“Don’t let the enemies figure out what we’re trying to do!” Fang Rui said.

“Switch channels?” Steamed Bun asked.

“Okay.”

“11111” Steamed Bun made his existence known in Happy’s team chat.

The Blue Rain fans were furious! Those two bastards were bullying their healer as they played around in the public chat. What do you mean don’t let the enemies know our intentions? They were obviously just bluffing. The fans could see Happy’s chat. No one answered Steamed Bun’s “11111”.

But at this moment, Happy’s captain, the terrifying Ye Xiu, suddenly typed a single word: Steady.

Steady?

Steady what? The current situation?

If they could steady the current situation, Happy would make a one for two trade. That would obviously be great, but the question was, could they steady it? Huang Shaotian’s and Zheng Xuan’s invasion would turn the healer situation into a 3v2. That didn’t seem to be something that could easily be stabilized.

It was just one word, but it brought up a lot of speculation. Pan Lin couldn’t avoid asking Li Yibo again for his opinions, which made Li Yibo want to hack his partner to death. Explaining this match was hard enough already. Now, Pan Lin wanted him to explain Ye Xiu’s intentions? It was as if Pan Lin wanted to see him fall into a pit!

Li Yibo cursed inwardly at Pan Lin, but on the stream, he had no choice but to give his view on the matter.

“Ye Xiu probably has some way to help out Fang Rui and Steamed Bun.” Li Yibo basically said nothing.

Some way to help out?

There were a total of five characters on each team.

The possible support could only come from one of them. Fang Rui and Steamed Bun were the ones who needed help, so that was two eliminated. An Wenyi was also someone who desperately needed help, so he could be eliminated too. Ye Xiu had Blue Rain’s Yu Wenzhou in his grasp. He could let go of Yu Wenzhou to help Fang Rui and Steamed Bun, but that would also mean Blue Rain would have more help in their rescue operation too.

Finally, there was Su Mucheng…

Su Mucheng was best at providing support and coordinating with her teammates. What was she doing now?

The broadcast director hastily searched for Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain. When the director found her, the director was startled.

Dancing Rain’s location…

Dancing Rain stood at the far end of the field, and there was no one else near her. As a result, the camera hadn’t placed much focus on her. She was still a part of several battles though. When Lu Hanwen had chosen to attack Little Cold Hands, her attempts to stop him had received some focus. Because she wasn’t able to suppress Flowing Cloud though, Su Mucheng kept on adjusting Dancing Rain’s positioning, attempting to get closer. Now that the camera had switched to her, everyone could see… were Su Mucheng’s adjustments aimed towards Lu Hanwen’s Flowing Cloud?

No! This… she was planning on providing support to the central battle taking place in the wind zone!

Chapter 1476 - Protected Like a King

Troubling Rain and Bullet Rain had made it to the edges of the wind zone. The two characters didn’t enter it and head directly towards the three players in the middle. Instead, they continued to move forward.

The length of distance traveled was according to the research Team Blue Rain had done on this map. If the two players had chosen to directly cut into the wind zone, they would be at a 90 degree angle with the strong winds. Even if they weren’t facing against the wind, their movements would still be hindered. By moving a bit more forward, they could position themselves into a better angle and borrow the wind for support.

The distance and the angle had been chosen by Blue Rain’s players from their understanding of the gale in this wind zone. Troubling Rain and Bullet Rain came in from the left and the right, but they chose different angles of attack and distances. From their choices, it could be determined that the two players were at different distances from the three players inside the wind zone. As a result, they needed to attack from different positions.

But at this moment, Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain appeared on this side of the battle. In theory, it didn’t matter which player she picked to target, but Su Mucheng went for Huang Shaotian. With distance between them, Launchers would obviously be more comfortable fighting against Blade Masters than Spitfires.

The viewers had neglected Su Mucheng’s movements because the camera hadn’t focused on her much, but what about the players on the field? They could control where they wanted to look. This map didn’t have fog either. Had they not noticed Su Mucheng’s movements?

Of course not.

In reality, all of Team Blue Rain had noticed Su Mucheng’s movements.

But what could they do?

Su Mucheng made clear her intentions, but no one on Team Blue Rain could do anything about it.

Yu Wenzhou and Xu Jingxi were trying to survive. Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan were responsible for breaking open the situation and could not slow down. What’s more, if they went after Su Mucheng, they would have to move in the other direction. How could they have time to do that? Then, there was Lu Hanwen. He was the only one on Blue Rain who held the initiative, but he was the foundation for Blue Rain’s comeback. He couldn’t abandon his post either.

Without any good options, Blue Rain could only watch as Su Mucheng effortlessly carry out her plan. In the end, Su Mucheng had targeted Huang Shaotian, making him feel even more helpless.

The battle taking place in the wind zone had become a 3v3. Through their familiarity with fighting in the wind and support from their healer, Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan felt quite confident in themselves. This was also why they didn’t feel too worried about Su Mucheng.

Go in!

Although Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan were on opposite ends of the wind zone, they had always been in coordination. They didn’t enter the wind zone at the same time, but just entering the wind zone wasn’t their end goal. Their goal was to coordinate with each other when it came time to attack.

One in the front, one in the back. One early, one late. The two characters cut into the wind zone, drawing support from the blowing wind to move faster.

Boom boom boom!

On Huang Shaotian’s side, artillery fire started being sent his way.

“So trigger happy.” Huang Shaotian messaged as Troubling Rain rolled.

Boom!

The shockwaves from the explosions made him roll three times. Under the effects form the wind, he almost couldn’t stop.

“Haha :)” Su Mucheng responded with a smiley face to Troubling Rain’s rolling.

The viewers were dumbfounded. Dancing Rain had predicted Huang Shaotian’s actions. The three Anti-Tank Missiles had been fired towards where Troubling Rain rolled to. She had considered the wind into her calculations too. They could even see the three Anti-Tank Missiles curve because of the strong wind. In the end, the missiles had accurately struck Troubling Rain.

Huang Shaotian felt embarrassed at getting hit by the first attack. It couldn’t be said that he had been too careless. He could only blame himself for being too familiar with the map. That roll had been instinctive. Because of the wind, he would naturally roll faster and farther, making it more effective for dodging attacks. But because he made the optimal choice, it had limited the possible mixups that could be made. Su Mucheng had guessed it and predicted that Huang Shaotian would react in this way.

The shockwaves sent Troubling Rain rolling three times. Su Mucheng seized the opportunity and had Dancing Rain move. The viewers saw it clearly. Right now, Dancing Rain had the tailwind advantage, while Troubling Rain had the headwind disadvantage…

Everyone knew what this meant. Su Mucheng had seized the most favorable position. No matter how familiar Huang Shaotian was with this map, he would still have a tough time. Su Mucheng was no noob! Just being able to land that attack in these strong winds showed her knowledge of the winds.

Sure enough, after Su Mucheng got into position, she immediately had Dancing Rain attack. With assistance from the wind, her cannonfire was fast and fierce. The place, where Troubling Rain used to be, instantly became scorched earth. Huang Shaotian had Troubling Rain keep dodging, which he didn’t find too difficult. But after a few steps, he made a realization.

Why didn’t it feel difficult? Because Su Mucheng was intentionally leaving him openings to go towards! If he took those openings, of course he would find it easy. But if he went along with Su Mucheng’s arrangements, Troubling Rain would be pushed out of the wind zone and his time here would have been wasted.

“Don’t count your chickens before they’ve hatched!” Huang Shaotian typed as he moved.

Triple Slash!

Sword light lit up in the wind. Huang Shaotian had planned on using it to initiate the fight with Fang Rui and Steamed Bun, but it looked like he had no choice but to use it now.

The three rays of sword light looked like one due to the wind. Su Mucheng chased after Huang Shaotian, but because of the changes in the wind, Troublin Rain’s movements were difficult to grasp. Su Mucheng had adapted somewhat to the strong wind, but not to the extent that Huang Shaotian had. She wasn’t able to figure out exactly how the wind affected Troubling Rain. As a result, her attacks missed. With just a Triple Slash, Troubling Rain was able to escape from Su Mucheng’s firing line. It looked to be a simple maneuver, but it came from hours of practice on this map.

Unable to catch him, Su Mucheng wasn’t dispirited. She continued to have Dancing Rain move, maintaining her positional advantage over Troubling Rain. Triple Slash had to end eventually. The moment the third slash came out, Dancing Rain began attacking again.

How annoying…

Huang Shaotian couldn’t help but glance at Zheng Xuan’s Bullet Rain. The two needed to hurry and convene. Bullet Rain’s range would allow him to restrict Su Mucheng to a certain extent. Otherwise, if he kept on allowing Su Mucheng to do as she pleased, he would be killed sooner or later, let alone be able to rescue Soul Speaker.

Zheng Xuan noticed Troubling Rain looking towards him. He immediately understood what Huang Shaotian wanted. That side needed help.

But he went along his current route, Bullet Rain would be downwind from Dancing Rain. He would be at a disadvantage too!

He needed to adjust his angle.

Bullet Rain had reached a position which he could attack, but he had to assist Huang Shaotian. As a result, he threw a grenade at Boundless Sea and Steamed Bun Invasion, while searching for a better position to fight Dancing Rain.

“It’s up to you!” Fang Rui suddenly typed into the chat.

What now?

Everyone was puzzled. Then, they saw Boundless Sea grab Soul Speaker and throw him to the side, getting everyone out of the range of Bullet Rain’s grenade. Then, Boundless Sea turned around, assuming that incomparably ugly posture, and start moving in the wind.

This bastard…

Zheng Xuan saw his actions. Fang Rui was planning on disrupting his plans. Whoever struck first would gain the upper hand. As a result, Zheng Xuan used the wind to his advantage and started firing at Boundless Sea.

Qi Guard!

Boundless Sea had been attacking Soul Speaker, so he hadn’t used any defensive skills. The bullets were all blocked by the Qi Guard. Although the shield was quickly broken, Boundless Sea was able to use this time to move forward quite a bit.

Moreover, by crouching low, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea was less affected by the headwind, so he moved faster than he normally did under these circumstances.

“Leave this to me. Take care of him, Steamed Bun!” Fang Rui typed in the chat.

“Heh, I’ve been waiting for those words,” Steamed Bun replied as if they had intentionally been going easy on Soul Speaker. In reality, that wasn’t the case. The two hated Soul Speaker’s full set of plate armor. If Soul Speaker had been a Cleric instead, the two would have had a much easier time.

1v1?

Xu Jingxi’s eyes lit up.

1v1, and he was against Steamed Bun, who would sometimes confuse himself. Xu Jingxi suddenly saw hope of escaping without any help.

Opening!

Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly let out an opening. Xu Jingxi was overjoyed. Just as Soul Speaker was about to rush out, when he took his first step, he was suddenly met with a heavy blow, stopping him from moving.

How?

Xu Jingxi was astonished. No matter how fast Steamed Bun was, he couldn’t have attacked from that angle. This is?

He looked around and saw Boundless Sea finishing up a move.

Qi Blade!

It had come from Boundless Sea’s Qi Blade.

Xu Jingxi felt gloomy again. Steamed Bun might have his weaknesses, but his teammates knew that, so they would look after Steamed Bun very seriously. As soon as Steamed Bun let out an opening, Fang Rui patched it up.

No…

Not just Fang Rui.

Xu Jingxi was a healer and had excellent observational skills. He looked around and discovered that it wasn’t just Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea. Su Mucheng’s Dancing Rain and Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim were all within range to provide assistance to Steamed Bun.

This guy… how lucky…

Xu Jingxi thought to himself. How could he not! A rookie had three All-Stars protecting him as if he were a king just because he would sometimes go off the rails…

Happy was also a team that was good at making up for individual flaws!

Xu Jingxi suddenly felt a sense of deja vu from Happy.

Chapter 1477 - Unable to Break Through

"Blue Rain's situation isn't looking good!" Li Yibo may not be as observant as Xu Jingxi, but if he dared to make such a conclusion, he must be quite confident in it. When the situation was ambiguous, Li Yibo would never say anything definitive.

Pan Lin didn't follow up on the conversation.

Blue Rain's situation isn't looking good? He could somewhat see it, but where should he begin?

How Happy was playing chaotically?　　

But when you looked at them now, the team was coordinating with each other beautifully. Happy's characters were scattered throughout the battlefield, yet they were all interlinked, making it seem like they were a whole.　　

As for Blue Rain?

Yu Wenzhou was being suppressed by Ye Xiu. Xu Jingxi was being beaten up by Steamed Bun. Huang Shaotian was being suppressed by Su Mucheng's cannonfire. And Zheng Xuan? Huang Shaotian and Xu Jingxi both needed his support, but Fang Rui's Boundless Sea was blocking his way. Zheng Xuan had no easy way to help either player.　　

The only person on Blue Rain with the initiative was Lu Hanwen.

He had constantly been paying attention to the changes in the battlefield. He had thought that Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan would quickly turn the tides in their favor, but to his surprise, both of them were stopped.

If this continued, even if he killed Little Cold Hands, Ye Xiu would probably have killed off Yu Wenzhou by then, and Steamed Bun Invasion should have no trouble taking down Soul Speaker too.

What should I do?

Lu Hanwen had kept on reminding himself not to hesitate and to quickly come to a decision, but at this moment, he just didn't know what he should do. 　

If he couldn't even find the right direction, hesitation wasn't something that he would come across.

Perhaps believing that my seniors would be able to resolve the problem might be a better choice than making a proactive play? Lu Hanwen suddenly thought to himself. In that case, his best choice of action should be to kill Happy's healer, Little Cold Hands, as fast as possible.

With this in mind, Lu Hanwen made his decision and focused on attacking Little Cold Hands.

Huang Shaotian, Zheng Xuan.

In the end, these two were the only ones who could break open the situation.　　

Shadow Steps!

Huang Shaotian saw an opportunity and used Shadow Steps.　

He didn't produce a lot of shadows, just five.

However, a smaller number of shadows allowed Huang Shaotian to control them more precisely. If the enemy couldn't tell which one was real or fake, then the enemy could only gamble on a 20% chance.

Artillery fire focused towards one of the five Troubling Rains. For Dancing Rain's attacks to arrive so fast, it could be seen how decisive Su Mucheng was.

Was it because she couldn't determine which one was real, so she might as well use that time to make a wild guess?

The viewers watching at home held these thoughts.

But the live audience? They had Huang Shaotian's point of view on the big screen, and his point of view would be from the real body. As soon as Shadow Steps came out, everyone wanted to know which one was real, so they all looked at Huang Shaotian's point of view to determine it.

Seeing the artillery fire come, all of Blue Rain's fans let out a gasp of surprise.　　

Whether Su Mucheng had guessed or not, in the end, her attacks were aimed accurately at the real Troubling Rain.

But Huang Shaotian seemed to have anticipated this would happen. Troubling Rain suddenly switched up the tempo.　　

He responded predictably, which allowed Troubling Rain to escape from Dancing Rain's pursuit. In the public chat, Huang Shaotian left a smiley face.

"Shadow Steps was a bait!" Seeing Huang Shaotian's smiley face, Li Yibo realized the problem.

"In the wind, there's actually a pretty clear difference between the real and fake bodies." Li Yibo gestured toward the display, which showed Troubling Rain's still-moving bodies. In this kind of gale, the real and false images of Shadow Steps were indeed in vain.

"Huang Shaotian wanted Su Mucheng to figure out the real one. By doing so, he knew how Su Mucheng would respond, and he used that knowledge to react in a way that would make it difficult for Su Mucheng to give chase!" Pan Lin said.

"Exactly," Li Yibo nodded his head.

As for seizing the right opportunity... for the king of opportunists, this wasn't a problem that needed to be worried about. He had grasped it perfectly. While Su Mucheng was unable to do anything, Troubling Rain immediately cut towards Steamed Bun Invasion. Suddenly, six pillars of light descended from the sky and formed a prison.

Troubling Rain was trapped by Hexagram Prison.

Everyone was shocked. Blue Rain's fans felt their hearts shatter.

Hexagram Prison was a Warlock skill. Besides Swoksaar, only Lord Grim could use this skill by attaching it to one of his weapon forms...

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could transform into a ninjato and dual blades, two Night Walker class weapons. As a result, he could add on two Night Walker skills.

In the group arena, he had used a Thief skill, Shadow Trap. And now, he had used a Warlock skill, Hexagram Prison...These two Night Walker skills were put into great effect at extremely crucial moments. The addition of these two skills to his kit were worth their weight in gold.

Lord Grim's Hexagram Prison was only level one, so it would only last four seconds. However, in the current tense situation, these four seconds seemed to last forever. Dancing Rain's artillery fire swept his way. Huang Shaotian turned his head resentfully as his view was instantly covered by the light and smoke from the explosions.

The audience's line of sight shifted towards Lord Grim.

Hexagram Prison had a cast time. How could he have time to cast the curse, while fighting with Yu Wenzhou?

But when they looked...

Fine! Calling it a fight would be too much of a bias towards Yu Wenzhou. It wasn't a fight, it was a one-sided humiliation. When they looked over, they saw Swoksaar in the air. Lord Grim was using his umbrella's dual swords. He didn't even look at Swoksaar as his two arms swung backwards. The dual swords drew a flower in the air, sending Swoksaar back up into the air.

This was the Assassin's knock-up skill: Leaping Blade, and Ye Xiu even had the time to make it look pretty like a flower...

Lord Grim turned around. His umbrella changed shape again, and the attacks continued.

In the group arena, as soon as Ye Xiu was able to get close, Yu Wenzhou was oppressed until his death. And in this team competition, a repeat of the same story was about to happen.

He needs to be rescued! Even a noob could see that, and there were no noobs on the field. However, Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan couldn't help. Lu Hanwen? Although Lu Hanwen was determined to continue attacking Little Cold Hands, he wasn't dead-set on it. As he attacked, he pulled his battle towards there. He hoped to keep Little Cold Hands in his grasp, while also finding an opportunity to help his captain.　

He wasn't dead-set on his objective, and Ye Xiu wasn't either. How could Ye Xiu not notice that Lu Hanwen was trying to move over towards him? As a result, he moved Swoksaar away as well.

There was no change in the situation. Huang Shaotian was trapped by Hexagram Prison and Su Mucheng's artillery fire.

No choice, forcefully break through!

Zheng Xuan went all out. Bullet Rain rushed at Boundless Sea. He was going to charge through!　

Dazzling light covered his path. Zheng Xuan used attacks to protect himself and accompany him out of this pass.

With the wind to his advantage, Zheng Xuan's charge carried even more momentum. Bullet Rain was like a fierce warrior as he rushed forward wildly.

What can a Qi Master do to stop me? Zheng Xuan carefully went over the possibilities in his head. He didn't have a 100% grasp of dealing with them, which why this was a gamble.　　

Zheng Xuan had placed his bets, but he soon realized that his opponent wasn't playing the same game as him. It was like they were playing to see who would roll higher. After he threw down one dice, he unexpectedly saw the opponent throw three instead...

Fang Rui's Qi Master couldn't be thought of as a conventional Qi Master.

Zheng Xuan obviously knew that. When he made his calculations, he had considered the research they had done on Fang Rui, considering him as a dirty Qi Master. At the same time, he didn't ignore the more common Qi Master methods.

Being able to think up all of these possibilities was due to Team Blue Rain having a Qi Master as well, so the team members were rather familiar with the class.

However, the ones who were most familiar with the class were Qi Masters themselves. They thought they had a grasp of Fang Riu's dirtiness, but when the time came, they realized that it wasn't enough.

One dice, two dice, three dice...

It was as if Zheng Xuan could see his opponent throwing dice after dice. By having three dice, he beat out his one dice despicably.

Bullet Rain fell down to the ground...

Another hope was crushed. Blue Rain's fans became even more nervous.

A turnaround? Where was the turnaround?

Blue Rain's players had done what they could, but Happy had crushed them all.　

What should I do?

Lu Hanwen was unable to keep waiting. Their captain, Swoksaar, was already at red health... The thrashing that he was getting was no different than thrashing a healer. In fact, when trying to survive, healers could cast instant heals on themselves occasionally. But Warlocks? Grasping Ghosts? They could heal themselves a bit by dealing damage with that move, but how could Ye Xiu let him cast a spell with such a long duration?

Huang Shaotian? Zheng Xuan? They were too far away. Even if they could break and rescue Xu Jingxi, Soul Speaker might not be able to rush over in time to heal Swoksaar.

I'm the only one who can save our captain!

Three rays of light flashed as Lu Hanwen's Flowing Cloud dashed towards Lord Grim with a Triple Slash.　

Ye Xiu didn't seem to want to give up on killing Swoksaar. He didn't retreat. He swung his umbrella in an attempt to block the attack.

Clang!

Greatswords were rather heavy. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was forced back two steps from the blow. His umbrella stabbed towards the side, hooking onto the tumbling Swoksaar.

Circle Swing!

Swoksaar was thrown towards Flowing Cloud.　

Flowing Cloud leaped back, his greatsword raised behind him ready to attack.

"Behind" Yu Wenzhou didn't bother controlling his character and typed into chat.

Lu Hanwen was startled. There was no time to look. He had Flowing Cloud dodge.

Chi!

A white Sacred Fire erupted. If Yu Wenzhou hadn't remind him, Flowing Cloud would have certainly been hit by it.　　

Paladins were defenders. And Clerics? Clerics played an offensive support role.

Chapter 1478 - Reinforced Iron Bones

With a Cleric supporting from the side, practically everyone thought of the same thing: kill!

Right now, relying on Little Cold Hands’ healing, Ye Xiu was entirely capable of ignoring Flowing Cloud’s attacks and focusing on Swoksaar.

Then what about Lu Hanwen? If he wanted to stop Ye Xiu, he would have to first use some attacks with strong effects. Only then could he interrupt Lord Grim’s offensive.

In this high-level match, the current situation was so simple that any ordinary gamer could understand it. Blue Rain’s fans were all clenching their fists and cheering on Lu Hanwen as hard as they could.

But then Lord Grim used a skill, instantly turning the hearts of Blue Rain’s fans to ash.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

Within the Fighter class, the Striker skill Reinforced Iron Bones. A low-level skill, it granted a Defense boost that wasn’t anything special, but Reinforced Iron Bones had another effect: Super Armor. At this moment, this became the truly deadly killing move.

Super Armor didn’t help a character’s Defense at all, but it blocked the effects of almost any attack. At this moment, the only skills that could interrupt Lord Grim’s actions right now were those with grab priority.

Blade Master? This class itself didn’t have any grab skills, but they would often have one, the low-level Spellblade skill Wave Wheel Slasher.

That was to say, if Lu Hanwen wanted to interrupt Lord Grim’s offensive, he could only use this one attack…

A ray of white light had already enveloped Swoksaar’s body.

Holy Commandment, a skill that increased the damage that the target took. Using it under circumstances where the target wasn’t being attacked from all sides could be considered overkill. And right now, for Blue Rain, this was only pouring oil onto the fire. Swoksaar didn’t have much health to begin with, and with this 30% increase in damage, how long could he last?

Lord Grim began his offensive.

Flowing Cloud began his offensive too.

Formless Phantom Blade!

At this moment, Lu Hanwen boldly controlled Flowing Cloud to release this powerful attack.

Lord Grim didn’t dodge. He faced forward, and continued his attack against Swoksaar. Flowing Cloud’s Formless Phantom Blade landed slash after slash upon his body, sending blood droplets flying everywhere, but he paid it no mind.

His health was plummeting, but no amount of damage would cause any kind of hesitation or interruption of his actions. This was the value of Super Armor. This might not be an equivalent exchange, but Ye Xiu didn’t care. Because, Lord Grim would only lose a relatively large amount of health; what Swoksaar would lose was his life.

There’s no way…

This was what everyone thought. Even though there was the Wave Wheel Slasher, in such a simple, straightforward, choiceless space, there was no way it would pose any effective threat. Lu Hanwen probably had Flowing Cloud use Formless Phantom Blade because he felt helpless, and decided to use this chance to deal Lord Grim as much damage as he could.

Even the heavy greatsword Flame Shadow was fairly fast with the Formless Phantom Blade. When the opponent didn’t defend at all, this Formless Phantom Blade of Lu Hanwen’s landed slash after slash, and in the blink of an eye, it had arrived at the final slash.

The final slash, the most powerful one of the Formless Phantom Blade.

But just as the swordlight of this most powerful slash flared, Ye Xiu suddenly stopped ignoring Lu Hanwen.

The swordlight flashed, and Lord Grim rolled.

Dodged!

This slash, Lord Grim had actually chosen to dodge. He didn’t mind temporarily stopping his offensive against Swoksaar for this.

He still wanted to dodge? He was making his killing less efficient?

The Blue Rain fans all felt depressed. Ye Xiu controlling Lord Grim to dodge this most powerful slash made them all hold him in contempt.

But then, they watched as this swordlight from Flowing Cloud that had missed its target look like it was splitting apart the very air. Something that clearly wasn’t just the slash of a sword cleaved the air and then vanished.

Everyone gasped.

This slash wasn’t the final slash of Formless Phantom Blade. It was a Wave Wheel Slasher.

Lu Hanwen hadn’t given up at all. He had hidden the Wave Wheel Slasher within the Formless Phantom Blade, to try and catch his opponent by surprise.

But, unfortunately, Ye Xiu had detected it.

Why did he want to dodge this slash? Not because he had wanted to avoid the higher damage of this slash. The reason was simply that this slash truly would have interrupted Lord Grim’s offensive.

The only effective attack, missed. With this, hope was completely extinguished, with not an ember remaining.

But everyone was still wishing for a miracle, wishing for a miraculous turnaround. What if Ye Xiu made a mistake?

He didn’t. Not at all.

Swoksaar fell. And in the last moments before he fell, Yu Wenzhou gave his final instruction of this battle: Save the healer.

Save the healer.

Huang Shaotian and Zheng Xuan had already been rushing to save the healer, and Xu Jingxi was the one currently being saved. Then naturally, this instruction was meant for Lu Hanwen.

Flowing Cloud immediately turned his attack. And Ye Xiu, to kill Swoksaar once and for all, didn’t bother to stop him.

Yu Wenzhou’s final message was to subtly make use of a time gap – before Swoksaar fell, Lord Grim couldn’t move.

But from the distance came cannonfire.

Flowing Cloud had shifted targets, and so Dancing Rain shifted targets; and so, Lord Grim shifted targets.

Lord Grim’s attack stuck to Flowing Cloud, and Swoksaar was ultimately killed by Dancing Rain’s long-range attack. Yu Wenzhou’s final instruction, the opening that had been obtained from the time gap, ultimately still fell upon his partner of many years, Huang Shaotian.

And the most outstanding opportunist in the entirety of Glory did not miss this opening, the opening for which his close friend and partner of so many years had traded his life.

From the winds, Troubling Rain rushed forward.

A twister of swordlight swept toward Steamed Bun Invasion.

Save the healer!

Lu Hanwen had been given the instruction, but the one who ultimately came to fulfill it was Huang Shaotian!

Troubling Rain, unstoppable.

Even if it could be stopped, what could be done? As long as Steamed Bun Invasion’s offensive had a single interruption, Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker could be saved.

Fang Rui dropped Bullet Rain, and Boundless Sea spun and rushed back.

He was travelling downwind, but would he arrive in time?

It was too late!

No matter what, it was too late to block Troubling Rain. But Boundless Sea thrust his palm forward, sending a blast of qi toward Soul Speaker.

And Steamed Bun Invasion didn’t have any intentions of dealing with Troubling Rain.

They were really going for the kill?

They would definitely be interrupted, right? Seeing Troubling Rain’s sword energy, this momentum, everyone thought this way.

But then, they watched as Steamed Bun Invasion, Boundless Sea, the two characters’ bodies suddenly shook, as though their very bones had suddenly hardened.

Once again, everyone was dumbstruck.

Steamed Bun Invasion, Boundless Sea, the two characters had activated the same skill, the same one that Lord Grim had just activated.

Reinforced Iron Bones!

The Fighter class’s Reinforced Iron Bones.

Steamed Bun Invasion, Brawler; Boundless Sea, Qi Master.

Of course they were Fighters, of course they could easily learn the low-level Striker skill, Reinforced Iron Bones.

They wanted not the Defense boost, but the Super Armor.

Troubling Rain’s sword could slice the skies, but so what? All he could use to interrupt the offensive was a Wave Wheel Slasher.

Bullet Rain could open fire with all he had, but so what? Those that exploded with knockback would have no effect against Super Armor. Flash Bullet? Freezing Bullet? The effects of these skills weren’t blocked by Super Armor, but they wouldn’t be able to settle the matter.

Reinforced Iron Bones.

Of Team Happy’s characters, three of them had Reinforced Iron Bones. Had anyone noticed this point in the beginning? No.

Had anyone thought, when the battle reached this instant where everything would be decided, that these three low-level skills would explode at once, producing this kind of crude effect? Also no.

Soul Speaker fell.

He had been suffering attack all this time. If not for his plate armor and tenacious self-recovery, he would have fallen even earlier than Swoksaar.

Now, Blue Rain had lost two characters, one of which was their healer…

Victory was already decided.

Only the most loyal of fans would still cling onto hope of a miracle right now.

On the battlefield, Blue Rain’s players didn’t give up, they were still fighting their hardest. This wasn’t simply the victory or loss of a match, this was the victory or loss of an entire season. It wasn’t over yet – who could give up?

But, when nothing changed in the end, their efforts could only be viewed as a futile struggle. Perhaps in the years to come, their hard work here would be handwaved as “trash time.”

They’d lost.

In their home game, they lost the group arena, they lost the team competition.. The points didn’t even need to be counted for this game.

If not for Happy’s fans in the west section, Xiaochuan Stadium would have been dead silent.

They’d lost, just like this?

It had ended right before their eyes. But the stadium of Blue Rain fans couldn’t believe the reality in front of them.

An entire season of effort, just like that, was lost in the first round of the playoffs, in two matches.

This summer had arrived too early, hadn’t it? So early that people weren’t used to it!

The players from both teams walked out of their competitor booths, and the players who hadn’t been playing joined their teammates onstage. Normally, when Wei Chen won at an away game, he loved to applaud and thank the crowd, the majority of which would be fans of the opposing team. Other players that did this might have been genuine in their thanks, but for him, it was a way for him to gloat. But this time, he was quiet as he walked onto the stage with his team.

To him, Blue Rain wasn’t just any team. Even though he was now standing with Happy, he would never be able to mock them. Winning was enough. On this brutal playoffs stage, in front of this team for which he still had many feelings, he restrained himself.

“Congratulations.” Blue Rain’s Captain Yu Wenzhou shook hands with Ye Xiu.

“Thank you.” Ye Xiu smiled and dipped his head, but didn’t say more.

Huang Shaotian came up to him next and shook his hand. “You’d better win the championships!” he said sternly.

“What did you think I was planning to do?” said Ye Xiu, amused.

“Good. If you’d beaten us and then lost to someone else, I’d never forgive you!” said Huang Shaotian.

Congratulate the opponents, thank the audience. Blue Rain may have lost the match, but they didn’t lose their demeanor. However, there was a hint of disappointment in everyone’s expressions.

They would have to taste this bitter fruit for the rest of the summer. But, that didn’t mean this was the end. There was the new season to come; they would have a new beginning. Day after day, year after year, everyone chased after this goal.

There was only one championship – this was cruelty. But, there was a championship every year – this was never-ending hope.

Chapter 1479 - The Emperor’s New Clothes

Blue Rain's Big Defeat! This was the front-page headline of the latest edition of Esports Weekly.

Happy won the battle, but the reports all focused on Blue Rain, as their loss on their home stage was a more interesting topic.

In any battle there was always a victor and a loser; who won and who lost was never something too surprising. When Blue Rain played their away game against Happy, they still won in the team round, and only lost by one point overall. Yet in their home game, they lost so drastically that the points didn't even need to be counted.

Group arena, lost. Team competition, lost again.

The team loss was particularly surprising – it was on a map with which Blue Rain was very familiar, yet they still hadn't been able to take the initiative.

It was true that people now had a pretty good understanding of Happy's playstyle, but battles were never certain. As the saying went, "eight immortals crossing the sea, each with their own unique powers"– everyone was striving to do their absolute best, in their own ways.

But the feeling that people got from this battle was that as soon as Happy pulled out their powers, Blue Rain was abruptly forced down, gradually falling over in the midst of their struggle.

The atmosphere in the stadium during the match wasn't too bad, but afterward, the criticism was overwhelming.

After the final results came out, everyone suddenly became a Glory expert. Any tiny flaw in Blue Rain's playing became a subject of loud criticism, proof of Blue Rain's failure to perform.

As the losing side, Blue Rain of course knew the problems they had to fix. But too much of this deluge of criticism was simply people parroting each other.

If you're determined to condemn someone, you don't need a good reason.

It seemed that everyone who failed had to undergo an intense round of shaming, as though this were necessary to properly reflect their status as the losers.

And this process of denouncement began right after the battle, during the press conference. It was less of an interview session and more of an attack session. The reporters wrote down in their notebooks not questions for Blue Rain, but speeches to express their vehement opinions regarding the reasons for Blue Rain's defeat.

Strategy, tactics, judgment, performance, awareness…

It was as if Team Blue Rain were stripped bare. They sat on the stage and were stabbed with the verbal knives hurled by the audience.

Knife after knife. Everyone was hit.

Huang Shaotian couldn't restrain himself for long. Several times, he wanted to interject, but each time he was stopped by a look from Captain Yu Wenzhou. Yu Wenzhou understood him very well, both on and offstage. He knew exactly which comments from the reporters would set him off, and with his excellent prediction and judgment, cut him off every time.

Other than keeping Huang Shaotian under control, Yu Wenzhou simply sat there and listened silently, still wearing a faint smile.

These endlessly chattering people in front of them, they were all upset at Blue Rain's failure to live up to expectations, hating iron for not becoming steel. Yu Wenzhou recognized many of them. Indeed, many of them had greatly anticipated Blue Rain's performance, had penned beautiful words for them, had fought written wars for them.

They liked Blue Rain, so they had held high hopes for Blue Rain. The greater the hope, the greater the despair.

However…

Yu Wenzhou simply listened, until the crowd finally fell silent. What there was to criticize had all been criticized, and, suddenly, no one stood up to say any more.

The reporters glanced at each other uneasily, in this calm after the raging attack. They were suddenly keenly aware – this was a press conference, they were supposed to ask questions and spend more time listening to what the players had to say, rather than use the time all the time to talk themselves.

Suddenly, no one knew how to continue. But at this moment, Blue Rain's Captain Yu Wenzhou finally opened his mouth.

"Thank you, everyone, for the concern and kindness you have shown Blue Rain."

Everyone listened in silence. The fact that Blue Rain's captain could say this made them feel that their bitter words hadn't entirely been in vain. Even if they didn't manage to get new information out of the players during this press conference, as long as they were able to get Blue Rain to wake up, then wouldn't it be worth it?

"Everyone, you are all anxious for Blue Rain, and you only wish the best for Blue Rain. This, I understand very well," Yu Wenzhou continued.

"However…" He paused, before continuing. "Even if it is for our benefit, forgive us for being unable to accept this sort of nonsense."

"Hahahahahaha!" At that, Huang Shaotian burst out laughing.

A year's worth of effort had come to nothing. Yet in this time of intense unhappiness, Huang Shaotian was actually laughing. But he was only laughing for the sake of it; the sound masked his acute feelings of bitterness and resentment.

He'd been wanting to say this for a while: What do you guys understand? What gives you the right to spout this nonsense at us?

While Huang Shaotian was laughing, the reporters were stunned. They never would have thought after giving such sincere thanks, Yu Wenzhou would directly and mercilessly call their words nonsense.

Some of them stood up, prepared to retaliate, but Yu Wenzhou's voice stopped them.

Beginning from the very first critic in this press conference, Yu Wenzhou began his replies.

One after another.

Fifteen.

In total, there had been fifteen reporters who had stood up and expressed vehemently their personal, disparaging views on Blue Rain's performance. Yu Wenzhou didn't miss a single one, and even followed the correct order in which they had spoken. One by one, he clearly, logically, systematically refuted their observations and opinions.

And thus, one after another.

Fifteen.

Fifteen reporters felt their ears go red.

Yu Wenzhou's rebuttals were so sensible that the reporters were surprised when he suddenly finished. And then, they all had only one feeling: that they truly understood nothing, that they truly were only speaking nonsense.

This was far more complex and high-end than they had imagined. And after listening to Yu Wenzhou's analysis, the problems that they had brought up felt unbelievably shallow.

It was as though they were a crowd of noobs, charging toward someone and yelling "Why didn't you use ten Formless Phantom Blades to make a hundred-combo to kill the opponent?" And that person would laugh, and pat their heads, and kindly reply that Formless Phantom Blade has a cooldown, you can only use it once, you can't chain together ten.

Even after having their arguments torn apart, not a single one of the reporters reacted angrily to being shamed like this. Because Yu Wenzhou's counters were truly too accurate, they simply couldn't find a foothold to reply.

When Yu Wenzhou finished speaking, the scene once again returned to silence.

"Then…" Yu Wenzhou surveyed the crowd one last time. "Thank you, everyone. We will meet next season."

And with that, Team Blue Rain departed.

And about what happened in this post-match press conference, not a single reporter was willing to write. In the end, this match report was simply a collection of outside descriptions, without anything about the emotions and attitudes of the Blue Rain players.

These reporters all shut their mouths, but that wouldn't stop other people from speaking.

The reporters who had undergone this rebuttal, upon seeing the comments made by others, suddenly felt that those critics were as pathetic as they themselves had been earlier.

Those critiques and analysis were just like the vehement statements they had made during the press conference. Not a single one hit the nail on the head.

It was because their skill wasn't high enough. And now, these reporters knew how these critiques were viewed through professional eyes.

It was nonsense.

All this time, there was simply too much of this kind of nonsense.

Because this was a new circle, those who truly had high-end skills were still participating in the League as players. Not many had joined the other aspects of this industry after their retirement. The media workers were mostly just ordinary fans, and some might have even been forced by their job to learn about Glory.

Their so-called specialist eyes simply weren't at the professional level, especially for the playoffs. Too much of the match content here, they just couldn't understand.

To the pro players, their confident assertions were simply laughable. Yet they weren't self aware; they ran about like the emperor wearing his new clothes, cheerfully streaking, until yesterday, Yu Wenzhou quietly nudged a few of them, and told them: You're not wearing any clothes, don't run around, be careful of catching a cold.

They really were catching cold!

And there were quite a number of them!

To these people, the mountains of comments were simply confused and invalid. But they had no way of pointing it out, because they only learned a few principles from Yu Wenzhou's words. That didn't mean that they had put on clothes, it just meant that they would no longer run around on the street naked.

And Team Blue Rain, because of their captain's powerful performance during the press conference, were completely deaf to these comments.

They knew much more clearly than these people where the true problems lay. Did they need to listen to the opinions of these outsiders?

"Break begins today."

After the match, the first sentence that Team Blue Rain heard from their captain was this one.

"As for the rest, we'll speak of it next season," said Yu Wenzhou.

"Yes!" Everyone nodded.

Even if this had been a bit ugly, this wasn't the first time they had failed. As for where the problems lay…

There were no idiots in Blue Rain. The words that Captain had said yesterday at the press conference, they wouldn't treat that as a mere tongue lashing.

He had simply used the most powerful moment to say those things. To review the recordings of their losing match, while still carrying the depression of defeat, only strengthened the effects.

Seizing opportunities was always Blue Rain's specialty, whether on or off the battlefield.

"See you next season!" Everyone bid each other to take care, and Blue Rain's players began their breaks.

But, not everyone left.

"You're not leaving?" Yu Wenzhou looked at Huang Shaotian.

"I want to watch until the very end. As soon as there's a chance, I'm going to go up and roast the hell out of that guy!" Huang Shaotian said firmly.

"Then what if there isn't a chance?" Yu Wenzhou asked, with a laugh.

"If there isn't, then I can only watch him continue to be proud until the end," said Huang Shaotian.

Everyone wanted to be proud until the end.

Blue Rain no longer had this chance. And that night, another team lost their chance as well.

Thunderclap fought their away game against Tiny Herb, and ultimately lost the match. Having lost both games, they too were eliminated in the first round of the playoffs.

Xiao Shiqin and his teammates had played an admirable regular season this year, but they still had yet to ever break past the first round of playoffs.

Thunderclap's individual strength still wasn't high enough!

This was what the outside world said. Their team strength didn't lose to any powerhouse, but Thunderclap's performance in the individual rounds indeed wasn't very reassuring. The playoffs only made this more obvious.

Once upon a time, in order to gain more powerful helpers, Xiao Shiqin had left Thunderclap. But this time, amidst these voices…

"Do you hear that, they're all saying that our individual strength isn't enough! Train well this summer, all of you. Next season, we're going to give them a scare in the individual rounds!" This was what Xiao Shiqin said before break. This time, he wouldn't think that his teammates weren't enough. He would rise together with his teammates, and together they would strive for a victory that belonged to them.

"Break 37 consecutive wins!" Dai Yanqi jumped up and shouted.

Xiao Shiqin's legs shuddered.

"Watch yourself!" He glared at Dai Yanqi. Encouragement was good, but it couldn't be absurd! Was that even something that a human could accomplish?

Chapter 1480 - Information

TLN: Please go back and re-read the previous chapter! It’s been updated with the actual translation.

The quarter-finals of the playoffs had come to a close. All four games ended in two rounds. Samsara, Tyranny, Happy and Tiny Herb advanced to the semi-finals.

Among them, Samsara, Tyranny and Tiny Herb were all members of the top four in the regular season. Happy, at number six, was the only one to have successfully turned the tables, knocking out the regular season’s third place, Blue Rain. This match, especially the second round at Blue Rain’s home stadium, was the match that had the most discussion.

The group arena was alright. It was clear that Blue Rain had made careful arrangements with their map choice. In the end, it was because their plan for Ye Xiu was completely destroyed that they fell behind.

However, the team competition brought Blue Rain a lot of disgruntlement and jeers, to the point where this match was the hottest topic with the end of the first round.

By now, Team Blue Rain’s holiday had already started. Regarding the last round of the playoffs, their captain Yu Wenzhou had said everything there was to say in the press conference already.

Next up was Tyranny versus Happy and Samsara versus Tiny Herb. The playoffs had entered an even more tense atmosphere. None of these four teams dared relax for even a moment.

Club Tyranny.

Blue Rain hadn’t bothered reviewing the heavily criticized team competition at Blue Rain’s home game against Happy. On the other hand, Tyranny began looking over that match ended. The team competition of that match had become the main focus of their pre-match preparations.

As for who it was they were studying, it obviously wasn’t Blue Rain who had been knocked out of the competition already, but Happy. Happy, who they were facing in the next round. Happy, who had wiped the floor with Blue Rain on their home turf, drawing harsh criticism of Blue Rain from all over.

Those criticisms, to them, were unreasonable. However, they didn’t have the time to spare to explain for Blue Rain, and it wasn’t Blue Rain they cared about anyways.

Happy. The discussions and research these three days were all about Happy, because Happy had revealed all too much in this match, too much that had been kept hidden or vague in previous matches.

The entire team was gathered in the conference room, the match VOD playing on the projector. They had lost count of how many times they had watched and analyzed the match, but none of the Tyranny members held any hint of impatience in their expressions, all focused as if they were in a match themselves.

Zhang Xinjie, their vice-captain, Tyranny’s tactician, stood in front of the projector. He faced the projection as well, watching the recording silently with everyone else.

The two teams spawned and headed out. The viewpoint in the VOD was completely focused on Team Happy.

After three consecutive days of studying the match VOD the file they were using was no longer the original. Speaking of which… as Happy’s five characters advanced, a red circle appeared over Dancing Rain, flashing a few times.

They didn’t stop watching because of this. They had studied this part several times already.

Su Mucheng.

Many people thought her performance wasn’t as spectacular after joining Happy. At first they thought that it was because she was in a new team and had to familiarize herself with her new teammates and characters. However, throughout the whole season, Su Mucheng hadn’t made any particularly spectacular improvement.

However, in these three days at Tyranny, Zhang Xinjie had came to a very certain conclusion.

Su Mucheng’s performed spectacularly, but her brilliance was integrated into the details.

The annotations done for Dancing Rain’s positioning at the beginning was emphasis on her choice of position in their formation as well as the adjustments she made. You wouldn’t be able to see anything from just watching one character, you had to look at it from the whole.

The moment the red annotations appeared, Steamed Bun Invasion and Boundless Sea had both deviated from their formation.

This deviation wasn’t a result of the two not being in sync, but it was because the two characters had been met with obstacles they couldn’t leap over in their linear path, so they had to make their own adjustments.

This was a natural, logical move that couldn’t be more ordinary,

However, Su Mucheng adjusted herself with them.

Dancing Rain, with no obstacles in her path, adjusted her position as Steamed Bun Invasion and Boundless Sea swerved around trees.

The scene was paused.

Happy froze with the two characters swerving around trees and Dancing Rain in her now adjusted position.

“A seemingly inconsequential detail, but this maintains the completeness of Happy’s formation,” Zhang Xinjie turned and said to everyone.

“These movements are woven into this match from start to finish, and we’ll come to it again. This is just to make sure you all realize that Su Mucheng can already do this subconsciously, even for something so inconsequential,” Zhang Xinjie explained, “In other words, I think that Su Mucheng is no longer just Ye Xiu’s best partner, but all of Happy’s best partner.”

After three days of analysis, this was the first time Zhang Xinjie had given such a straightforward explanation.

“She’s become more comprehensive, even more of a team player,” Lin Jingyan said. As veterans, none of them were unfamiliar with Su Mucheng, and with this new information, they would immediately compare it to their original understanding of Su Mucheng and notice the difference.

For the Su Mucheng of the past, not only did she often forget everyone but Ye Xiu, but her support was imbalanced. She placed too much importance on Ye Xiu’s decisions, leading to her inability to maximize her impact in the battle.

This was because Ye Xiu wasn’t always the best target for her to support, and giving support to her other teammates would have been better to open up the situation.

Now, she no longer had any of these problems.

Soon enough, the scene arrived at the first clash between the two sides. Blue Rain took advantage of their tailwind to launch an assault. At this point, Zhang Xinjie had switched the shot to Su Mucheng’s perspective.

With this first person perspective, everyone felt as if they were in the tense atmosphere of the match themselves.

Su Mucheng’s camera view was constantly in motion, things appearing repeatedly in the shot, some far, some close.

Then, it suddenly froze.

It was Zhang Xinjie who paused it.

In the scene, Blue Rain’s Blademaster Duo had already charged into their formation with such great coordination that even Ye Xiu couldn’t stop them.

As for Su Mucheng?

All of this occurred under her eyes, and she had the chance to steady the situation for Happy, but she didn’t.

Su Mucheng’s view, instead, kept a close eye on Yu Wenzhou’s Swoksaar.

“What if it was the Su Mucheng of the past? What would she do?” Zhang Xinjie inquired.

The veterans all fell silent.

The old Su Mucheng would most likely coordinate with Ye Xiu to take on Blue Rain’s Blademaster duo.

But what about the Su Mucheng of today?

“Happy’s disarray here was planned, and Su Mucheng’s decisions influenced Happy’s plans for this stage. If she had coordinated with Ye Xiu to defeat Blue Rain’s Blademaster duo, then this situation here would be difficult to achieve,” Zhang Xinjie said.

Tyranny’s members knew the scenario that followed like the backs of their hands after three days of analysis. Happy had an order to their chaos, while Blue Rain, responsible for scattering them, sunk into their chaos like into quicksand. Of course, every member of Happy had contributed their efforts to this, but even after three days of studying, the role Su Mucheng played seemed to have a deeper layer to it.

“Blue Rain wasn’t cautious enough of Su Mucheng.” As Zhang Xinjie talked, the projection cut to a collection of strung together highlights. Scene after scene flashed by. This was a video of the times Su Mucheng used Dancing Rain’s range advantage to disrupt Blue Rain’s plan. As for Blue Rain, they weren’t watching Su Mucheng very closely, so it made Su Mucheng’s job much easier.

This sentence was basically Zhang Xinjie’s criticism on Blue Rain’s performance. This was a criticism that hadn’t appeared in that cacophony of voices. However, Zhang Xinjie, who had managed to catch onto this, didn’t act proud or anything. This was a trail they had only found after three days of intense study. Su Mucheng’s transformation was very fragmented. It would be very hard to notice without combing through the data thoroughly. Zhang Xinjie could only be thankful, thankful that there was this match to provide them with this fragmented information.

“It seems like we had better keep a closer watch on her,” Zhang Jiale said.

“Or obstruct her view!” Zhang Xinjie gazed at Zhang Jiale as he said this.

The veterans didn’t need to say much more. When Zhang Jiale brought this up, it was because he already understood that he was the one in Tyranny who was most appropriate for cutting Su Mucheng off from her allies. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had ranged attacks and the Hundred Blossoms style was doubtlessly the best at disrupting Su Mucheng, no matter if it was used on the field or on Su Mucheng directly.

And so, a strategic choice was decided. Outsiders would probably never guess that the first person Tyranny brought up as a key opponent to keep watch on would be Su Mucheng, who didn’t seem to shine so brightly amongst the rest of Happy.

This wasn’t the only choice Tyranny had settled on in these three days. The recording continued, and soon came to a chaotic free for all between the two sides. Steamed Bun Invasion had been Blue Rain’s attack target for awhile, but after a few exchanges, Steamed Bun worked together with Boundless Sea to kidnap their healer.

What was Happy’s reasoning behind sending out Steamed Bun Invasion?

This was one of the many questions Tyranny was analyzing these three days. The choice of player and character was the best reflection of a team’s intentions. An unpredictable and unstable player like Steamed Bun wasn’t the strict Zhang Xinjie’s style. Compared to Yu Wenzhou, he was interested in why Happy chose a player that might mess up and cost them their victory at such a crucial map.

Ye Xiu was there to compensate; that was something that Yu Wenzhou realized during the match, as well as something Tyranny quickly figured out. However, this only meant that Happy had the ability to neutralize the risk of using Steamed Bun Invasion, but nothing of why Steamed Bun Invasion was important. It wasn’t like they’d send him up to wear at Ye Xiu’s focus.

As the recording arrived to where Blue Rain’s healer Soul Speaker was kidnapped, the projection once again cut to a collection of highlights.

A collection of highlights of Steamed Bun Invasion attacking Soul Speaker.

Conclusion: Steamed Bun was a counter to Xu Jingxi’s Soul Speaker. The Brawler class had many ways to disrupt and interrupt their opponents, and Paladins with their strong defense had many ways to protect themselves, so a class like the Brawler was required to CC them.

The shot paused at a scene where Steamed Bun Invasion launched a Tyrannical Chain Punch and knocked Soul Speaker down.

“It looks overkill, doesn’t it?” Zhang Xinjie said, pointing at the shot. “However, if he didn’t do something so overkill, then a single Guard of Virtues or Angel’s Might would be able to turn the tables.”

“This Steamed Bun Invasion feels really enthusiastic when it comes to things like this…”

Feelings…. Zhang Xinjie would never rely on feelings for something like this, yet even he had to resort to an ambiguous term like this. He just couldn’t understand Steamed Bun.

Chapter 1481 - Focal Point

Su Mucheng, Bao Rongxing…

Tyranny had studied Happy for three days, and now, it was time for them to conclude their findings. They outlined a summary of these two players’ performances in their match against Blue Rain.

This obviously wasn’t all the information that they had obtained. Under Zhang Xinjie’s meticulous guidance, they analyzed every piece of information.

What should we do?

Everyone had the same thought, much like how Zhang Jiale had tacitly understood earlier the role that he would need to play. However, because of Zhang Xinjie’s caution and seriousness, even Han Wenqing, who had known Zhang Xinjie for many years, had to confirm that everyone was on the same page.

Everything was conducted anxiously but orderly.

Tyranny, Samsara, Tiny Herb, and Happy, who had entered the quarterfinals despite this being their first year in the league.

The next step was the finals.

The next step was the championship cup itself.

At this moment, who could relax? Who could give up?

Every year, when it reached this point in time, the atmosphere would turn abnormally heavy. Even the wars between in-game players would turn exceptionally heated.

The teams that made it to the semifinals were all teams with a strong fanbase. When expectations were high, people would often become sensitive and weak. Since four teams had qualified for the quarterfinals, that meant four teams had been eliminated. None of the four eliminated teams were weak teams. How could any of the fans be content with these results?

One day, two days…

Day after day of tension passed.

The first round of the semifinals was about to begin.

The first round would be Happy’s home game against Tyranny. It would take place in Happy’s stadium in City H.

Happy’s home stadium was formerly Excellent Era’s. In the Glory Alliance, there were no two teams with more enmity towards each other than Excellent Era and Tyranny. When Excellent Era was relegated from the league, countless people thought that the Alliance had now lost a piece of history. Afterwards, Excellent Era disbanded and went away… it seemed like this piece of history would never return.

But then, Happy joined the Alliance. Their leader was Excellent Era’s former captain, Ye Xiu. Happy also succeeded Excellent Era’s home stadium in City H. For a moment, Tyranny’s fans took their hostility towards Excellent Era and placed it all onto Ye Xiu alone.

Of course, Ye Xiu played an important part in the the relationship between the two teams.

It was just that Happy was Happy. Say that Happy was the continuation of Excellent Era? How could that be said? In the Challenger League, Happy was the one who eliminated Excellent Era and led to their disbandment.

Fortunately, Excellent Era was rescued in the end, leaving a few key remnants of the organization. The New Excellent Era had won the Challenger League this season and would be returning to the Alliance. Beside them was also a group of loyal fans who would never abandon the team.

But there were many people who felt like Happy was more like the original Excellent Era, even if they were the team that led to Excellent Era’s disbandment.

It was because Happy took over the original Excellent Era’s home stadium. It was because Happy’s captain was Excellent Era’s former captain, Ye Xiu.

The Ye Xiu that had founded Excellent Era’s dynasty.

The Ye Xiu that had earned the title of Battle God for One Autumn Leaf.

No matter what, these were all of the past, things that had already become reality. These achievements would never be separated from Ye Xiu, nor would they ever be forgotten.

As a result, when Happy and Tyranny met in the playoffs, many people brought up the often-talked-about subject of old enemies.

Excellent Era?

It wouldn’t be good to talk more about one person’s name.

Ye Xiu!

Everyone kept on talking about Ye Xiu. Even Su Mucheng, who used to be a core player on Excellent Era, was mentioned less.

After all, when Excellent Era won their three championships, Su Mucheng hadn’t been a part of the team yet, and most of the enmity between Excellent Era and Tyranny had been established during that period of time. Su Mucheng happened to join the season that Tyranny beat Excellent Era. As such, the hostility towards Su Mucheng from Tyranny’s fans was naturally far less than Ye Xiu, who had led the team that had eliminated Tyranny three times in a row.

The match between Happy and Tyranny was discussed heavily by the media, who hyped up the match by flipping through talking point after talking point.

The day of the match was about to arrive.

And the sight of the fans that had assembled at the stadium was astonishing to see.

Although Happy was a popular team nowadays, their home game against Blue Rain was nowhere near as crazy.

As the beginning of the match approached, the number of people gathered at the stadium was so large that not only were there no empty seats, it might even be hard to find space outside the venue.

This sort of scene could only be found before when Excellent Era played against Tyranny.

Had City H’s Glory fans regarded Happy as an alternative to Excellent Era?

It was a reasonable possibility, but it shouldn’t be to this extent. After all, Happy defeating Excellent Era in the Challenger League was a fact that no loyal Excellent Era fan could ever forget.

There were Excellent Era fans that hated Happy. There were Excellent Era fans that were indifferent about Happy. But those who liked Happy could only be ones who liked fads.

Then, where did all of these Glory fans gathered here come from?

The playoffs was a popular topic among the media. There were, of course, special reports about the various histories behind the teams. Just taking a look at a few articles would give a good overview of the situation.

It was true that many of the people gathered here didn’t have any love or Happy, but their hostility towards Tyranny was as strong as ever.

That was why they came. Not to cheer on Happy, but to see Tyranny fall. There was no Excellent Era these days, but many Excellent Era fans continued their tradition of hating on Tyranny. Many of the reporters that were here to conduct interviews sighed at this scene. Although Excellent Era had already been gone from the Alliance for two years, their influence remained. The players could be gone, the characters could be changed, the stadium could be replaced, but the history that they had left behind would always remain.

Excellent Era was a memory, one whose glory would never be forgotten. And their enmity with Tyranny was a part of that memory.

As a result, there was now another point of discussion.

Happy was the one that led to Excellent Era’s downfall, yet now they were going to carry on the tradition? It was a very contradictory situation.

Of course, there were no lack of optimists in the interviews. They cheerfully expressed that they were here today to see the drama. It didn’t matter who won. Either way, they would be able to vent their anger…

All sorts of topics were pushed to the peak of attention because of this match. There were even fans who were certain that they had seen Huang Shaotian in the crowd. Others claimed to see Yu Wenzhou, Yang Cong, Tang Hao…

In short, the pro players who were no longer in contention for the championships all seemed to be somewhere in the crowd.

Who would win? Who would lose?

Everyone had come here to see the answer to this question.

That night at 8 o’clock, at the sold-out Xiaoshan Stadium, many of the Glory fans gathered outside without seats did not leave. They didn’t need to appreciate the course of the match. Just being able to know the results first-hand was enough for the wait to be worth it.

Inside the venue’s prep rooms, the two teams were getting ready for the match.

“It’s really lively today, huh.” Fang Rui was relaxed, talking to everyone as if this were normal. Team Happy had done what they had always done. At around seven, they left the Internet cafe, ready to cross the street to Xiaoshan Stadium. But when they saw the giant crowd outside, they got scared! It’d be a miracle if famous players like them could make it inside without any trouble!

In the end, Chen Guo urgently contacted the stadium employees.

Xiaoshan Stadium had hosted Glory events for many years. They had experienced the rivalry between Excellent Era and Tyranny and were familiar with handling it. As soon as they took Chen Guo’s phone call, they immediately told them that a special passageway had been prepared for them. The stadium even sent out a staff member to guide Happy inside. In fact, they already knew that Team Happy was right across street from them.

When they got inside the venue, the sea of people outside the stadium left a deep impression on them.

Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng weren’t too surprised. They had been a part of Excellent Era and had experienced it before. But even Fang Rui, an All-Star, had never seen such an army before. As a matter of fact, despite having more experience than the rookies, he felt more surprised than them.

“Why aren’t these people leaving? The match is almost about to start,” Chen Guo said. She was too naive. Chen Guo thought that those Glory fans outside were hoping for a ticket, and since the match was about to start, they clearly hadn’t gotten any tickets and should be leaving. How could she have known that their passion was no longer something that could be stopped by a ticket to the match. Just waiting outside, awaiting for the results with everyone else, was a type of joy to these people.

“I just know that the crowd gathered here today probably isn’t here to support us. Don’t feel too pressured by them,” Ye Xiu said solemnly.

Chen Guo stared blankly.

His intentions were good, but how come the logic didn’t seem to make sense?

“Tyranny has this many fans here?” Tang Rou asked. No matter how much of a rookie she was, she knew quite a bit about the scene now. Their opponent was Team Tyranny. And having worked at Happy Internet Cafe in City H, Tang Rou knew about the people of this city’s relationship with Team Tyranny long before she became serious about playing Glory.

“They’re probably here hoping for Tyranny to fall,” Ye Xiu said.

“Then, aren’t they hoping for us to win?” Tang Rou said.

“They’ll probably be happy if we lose too,” Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou was smart. She quickly understood.

“Too bad we won’t!” she said.

“That’s why I’m saying we should just treat them as if they didn’t exist,” Ye Xiu said.

Just as he said this, they heard a knock on their door. The staff were calling the two teams to get ready to go on stage.

Ye Xiu led the way out of the room and came across Team Tyranny’s captain and his old rival, Han Wenqing, who was also leading his team out.

They looked at each other face to face, without any expression. Soon, the two teams lined up next to each other in the passageway.

“When are you going to retire?” Ye Xiu suddenly asked Han Wenqing an especially depressing question.

“It’s still early.” Han Wenqing’s gaze was firm.

“You still want to win a championship?” Ye Xiu smirked. “You’ve got no chance this year.”

“Humph,” Han Wenqing snorted.

Ye Xiu turned his head and gave an upward nod at the third Tyranny player in line. “You’ve got no chance at a fifth second-place finish, either.”

Zhang Jiale wished he could give Ye Xiu ten middle fingers.

Chapter 1482 - Stepping Back

They hadn’t even gone onstage yet and the mockery had already begun. This knife at Zhang Jiale was particularly cruel – even the stadium worker nearby couldn’t keep a straight face.

But these people from Tyranny had interacted with Ye Xiu for far too many years, and understood him very well. And Zhang Jiale was such an easy target, it’d be strange if Ye Xiu didn’t take a few jabs at him. So even though Zhang Jiale expressed his indignation, Tyranny as a whole remained fairly unruffled. They were all so familiar with each other that even if the hostility was high, they just treated it all as insults traded between bad friends. Notably, when Ye Xiu said this, some people in Tyranny almost laughed. Such as Lin Jingyan.

When Lin Jingyan saw Zhang Jiale twist his head to look at him, he hastily turned it into a cough. Adjusting his glasses, he regained his composure.

“When did you become nearsighted?” Fang Rui happened to be standing across from Lin Jingyan. Fang Rui wasn’t as familiar with the others in Tyranny, but he and Lin Jingyan had been partners back in the day, so of course the degree of familiarity wasn’t the same.

Lin Jingyan adjusted his glasses again. “They’re plain glass.”

“Trying to look all intellectual?” Fang Riu said.

“I think they looked quite good!” Lin Jingyan appeared to be quite satisfied with this new accessory. But then, he heard another voice speak up from behind Fang Rui.

“You’re a Brawler, what kind of Brawler wears glasses to look intellectual?”

Steamed Bun. Only Steamed Bun would have such strict views on Brawlers.

“My character’s class is a Brawler, thanks.” Lin Jingyan felt gloomy as he turned and answered Steamed Bun.

“You don’t like Brawlers? Then why’d you pick one,” said Steamed Bun.

“I…” At this point, Lin Jingyan couldn’t explain any further. This Steamed Bun insisted on drawing an equals sign between the in-game Brawler class and a real-life brawler. Alright, the Brawler class did have the aura of a street thug, but this was still a separate matter, okay? Did using this class mean that you had to have the aura of a street thug?

Lin Jingyan looked at Steamed Bun through his plain-glass glasses, and found that he couldn’t say anything. This guy really fit the image! This hairstyle, this attitude, this attire, throw him onto a street and anyone would recognize him as a little brawler! And… quite a handsome brawler at that.

“Haha…” Aside from a weak chuckle, Lin Jingyan really had no idea what to say. In the end, Happy’s trash talk did have some effect, not from the experienced Ye Xiu, but from the rookie Steamed Bun.

Fortunately, they were finally about to walk onto the stage.

Ye Xiu, Han Wenqing…

When the two captains met at the center of the stage and shook hands, the entire stadium erupted with enthusiastic applause.

Ten years!

Both of them had once stood at the peak of Glory, had experienced ups and downs. Now, ten years had passed, and they still stood on this stage, still stood on this battlefield, still faced off against each other.

Whether they loved or hated them, no one could erase the respect held toward these two people. The two of them shook hands and prepared for battle, once more, after so many times throughout the years. Everyone delivered up applause, no matter whether they were Happy fans, Tyranny fans, or old Excellent Era fans looking for excitement.

But soon after the applause…

“Kill him!!”

Such brutal and foul language immediately rose up within Xiaoshan Stadium. Respect had been expressed, so the next step was to establish dominance.

The two of them had faced off for ten years, and the fans behind them had faced off for ten years as well. Even if their team backgrounds were thrown away, these two people’s names were enough to ignite a fiery chaos.

The emotions of the stadium were immediately bursting aflame, and under this ruckus, the players of the two teams continued to shake hands down the line. After that, the players returned to their respective player areas, and Ye Xiu alone remained onstage.

“Ohhhhhhh!!” In Happy’s home stadium, there were naturally many Happy fans. Seeing this, they immediately started cheering. They knew all too well what this meant – this meant that Ye Xiu was still the first up. Starting from the second round of the regular season, up through the second round of layoffs right now, he had always been Happy’s first player, and he had yet to lose a single 1v1.

37?

Loyal fans didn’t even recognize this streak anymore.

It should be 39!

There was no “individual competition” in the playoffs. There was only the group arena, and they couldn’t expect anyone to 1v5, right? So, because Ye Xiu had twice defeated the opponent’s first player, they counted that result into the record. Quite a few people were emphasizing that Ye Xiu’s current win streak was no longer 37, but more accurately 39.

And now, for the 40th time, Ye Xiu was Happy’s first player. There was no more suspense – after the pre-match formalities, he simply remained onstage and aimlessly strolled around.

In the past, this would have been quite a valuable shot, because Ye Xiu never made public appearances before. He’d always hide very well. But now, it had already been a whole season, so that mysterious aura had long since disappeared. By wandering around onstage now, in everyone’s eyes, it looked like he was trying to provoke Tyranny.

I’m right here. Which of you will come to fight me?

“Who’s coming?” Happy’s fans knew how to get hype, and immediately began shouting.

“Han Wenqing, you dare come?” Someone shouted this. In theory, if a Happy fan wasn’t formerly an Excellent Era fan, they shouldn’t have much reason to hate Han Wenqing. But everyone at least knew that there was so much history between Han Wenqing and Ye Xiu, and so at this time, they wouldn’t shy away from helping their own team’s captain provoke the other.

Of course, everyone loved this this kind of topic, and so very quickly, the entire stadium was helping Ye Xiu call out Han Wenqing.

Tyranny’s fans had no way of retaliating.

Because the player order was decided before the match, if they really hadn’t set Han Wenqing as the first player, there was no way that they would decide to change the order just because the whole stadium was shouting for Han Wenqing to come onstage.

But… Happy’s choice to send Ye Xiu first was a very obvious thing, right? Would Tyranny back down from such a challenge?

They wouldn’t!

Of course they wouldn’t.

This was Tyranny, this was their captain Han Wenqing. Knowing that Ye Xiu stood before him, would he retreat?

What a joke.

When they thought to here, Tyranny’s fans immediately gained confidence. Thus, they also began to shout for their captain, as though it was a guarantee that Han Wenqing would come onstage.

All the way until the digital screen flashed with Tyranny’s first player. All the way until, in Tyranny’s player area, the first player stood up.

The stadium quieted down for a moment, and then Happy’s fans exploded with crazy jeering. And Tyranny’s fans? They were silent.

Tyranny’s first player: Qin Muyun. Character, Sharpshooter Negative Nine Degrees.

Han Wenqing actually retreated? He’d clearly known that Happy’s first player would be Ye Xiu, and yet he still didn’t stand forward to fight Ye Xiu, instead leaving this opportunity to Qin Muyun, this most overlooked player of Tyranny’s main roster?

The audience was shocked, as were the commentators Pan Lin and Li Yibo.

This was entirely outside of their expectations. Pan Lin and Li Yibo had just been talking about how Ye Xiu’s position as Happy’s first player had never changed, and so in the confrontations in this round of the playoffs, it was very possible that Ye Xiu would 1v1 Han Wenqing a number of times.

“Best of three. This ten-year conflict might finally see an answer,” Pan Lin had noted, but unexpectedly, Han Wenqing actually hadn’t come up to fight.

“This…” At first, the two wondered whether Han Wenqing had sustained some injury, and wouldn’t be able to fight at all today. But when they thought again, they remembered he had still been playing well last round. Would he suffer such a serious injury in just a few days? Tyranny couldn’t be that unlucky!

The two exchanged glances. They had no idea how they would explain this. The televised broadcast ignored Qin Muyun as he went onstage, instead choosing to show a close-up of Han Wenqing.

Tyranny’s captain merely sat in his seat, his face cold, his attention on their player walking onstage. It didn’t seem like there was anything unusual going on.

The match hadn’t even begun yet, but the player order had already given everyone a big surprise. It was just completely outside of everyone’s expectations, expectations that had been formed over the course of ten years.

Ye Xiu, too, was surprised.

The broadcast didn’t skip over him, and furiously snatched close-ups of his reaction when Tyranny didn’t send up Han Wenqing.

Ye Xiu was indeed somewhat caught off-guard, somewhat surprised. He glanced toward Han Wenqing, still in Tyranny’s player area. But then, he smiled lightly.

Was it mockery?

Those who saw this immediately began analyzing Ye Xiu’s smile.

Not mockery.

This smile looked more like one of understanding, more like one of relief.

When Han Wenqing’s expression was shown next to his onscreen, this feeling became even stronger.

After shaking hands with Qin Muyun, Ye Xiu headed to the player booth to prepare for the upcoming battle. Everyone was still discussing what it meant that Han Wenqing hadn’t come onstage, and poor Qin Muyun was completely overlooked.

“Han Wenqing isn’t going up against Ye Xiu first battle, are you watching this?”

Huang Shaotian had come to watch the match live. With his status, getting the best VIP seats wasn’t difficult, of course. There was no way he could sit with the masses, because after all he was a top star of Glory as well. Right now, seeing Tyranny’s arrangement, Huang Shaotian sent out a text.

“I’m watching.” A reply came – Yu Wenzhou.

“What do you think he’s trying to do?” Huang Shaotian continued to ask.

“Stepping back,” Yu Wenzhou replied.

They were all players at the highest level. With such great mutual understanding, not much needed to be said.

Stepping back.

The one thing that it had always looked like Han Wenqing didn’t know how to do was step back. But now, he made this kind of choice. Was he yielding, was he compromising?

No. There was absolutely no way.

If Han Wenqing knew how to yield, how to compromise, then countless people’s worldviews would be completely shattered.

Han Wenqing was changing. In the twilight years of his professional career, for the sake of that goal, he was adjusting himself. Much of this could be seen, in fact, from his performance over the course of the regular season.

Stepping back wasn’t compromising, even less so yielding.

Stepping back was a wisdom, a wisdom that Han Wenqing understood, but was unwilling to accept. Yet this time, he had done it. And this was just an arrangement of player order. On the actual battlefield, the Han Wenqing who now knew how to step back, what kind of performance would he bring?

Chapter 1483 - High-Level Hide-And-Seek

Happy faced Tyranny in their home game. The first round of the group arena would be Ye Xiu versus Qin Muyun. The match was at the loading screen stage, but the crowd had yet to quiet down. The people didn’t care about the match itself. Happy’s fans were booing loudly at Han Wenqing for not coming out, while Tyranny’s fans felt like they couldn’t hold their heads high. They forgot that although Han Wenqing hadn’t been sent up this round, the player who had, the poor Qin Muyun, wasn’t getting any attention.

Up until the match began.

When Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees appeared on stage through Glory’s projection technology, on the big screen in the stadium, on the TV or computer screens of countless Tyranny fans, they finally realized that though Han Wenqing may not have gone up, their Tyranny was still fighting.

“You can do it!”

Cheers erupted from the away-game seats, Team Tyranny’s fans.

The loud cheers all of a sudden gave Happy’s fans a fright.

Excellent Era fans were experts at competing against Tyranny fans. Although Happy’s fanbase had some crossover with Excellent Era’s fanbase, it wasn’t a majority. Happy’s fans couldn’t beat Tyranny’s fans in a yelling contest, and the regular season had already proved that.

But this was the playoffs, a competition where one side died while the other side lived. Happy was a new team that was creating a miracle. Once this thought came across their minds, Happy’s fans started to feel their blood boil too.

This is our home field. How can we let Tyranny overwhelm us?

The first intense battle of this playoffs round began with the audience.

In the meantime, the two players on stage were calmly making their way forward.

Happy had chosen the map, Thatcher Manor. It was another setting from a map in the Heavenly Domain. The map consisted of a multitude of elements: a lake on the west side, a small forest on the east side, and a two-story tall manor in the center of the map. Apart from that, there were all sorts of small buildings scattered throughout the map such as a mill, a stable, gardens, and so on.

The two characters spawned on the north and south end of the map. Both of them chose a direct route straight to the center. However, because of the obstruction from the manor, neither of them could see the other side.

Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees came from the north side towards the back of the manor. It looked like he wasn’t a complete stranger to this map. After arriving there, he had Negative Nine Degrees move towards a corner and then borrow window sills and pillars as platforms to jump on. Shortly afterwards, Negative Nine Degrees made his way to the roof of the manor, giving him a wide view of the map.

But Qin Muyun immediately had Negative Nine Degrees crouch and search for an appropriate position before carefully looking outwards.

He was looking towards the south, but there were no signs of anyone.

Judging by Lord Grim’s movement speed, if he had taken the middle road, he should be here too.

But he wasn’t.

The left? The right? Or could it be…

Qin Muyun looked downwards.

The manor wasn’t just decoration. It could be entered. If he and Ye Xiu chose to take the middle road, while he had been jumping onto the roof, he could have easily entered the manor without him noticing.

There was a door at the back of the manor too, but Qin Muyun chose not to go in. Sharpshooters held an advantageous position in an open field. Fighting inside the manor would not be a good idea for a Sharpshooter.

Perhaps Ye Xiu had chosen to go in for that very reason?

As Qin Muyun pondered over this question, his Negative Nine Degrees took the next step.

Boom!

He vaguely heard an explosion, seemingly far yet seemingly close at the same time. As the explosions continued to sound, he was able to accurately determine that the explosions were coming from below.

Hua!

Negative Nine Degrees was laying on the rooftop. However, he hadn’t expected Lord Grim to fire shots from the inside and blow a hole in the roof to force Negative Nine Degrees to fall towards him.

Qin Muyun reacted quite fast. He immediately had his character jump to the side and throw a grenade into the hole.

Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was standing there with his umbrella open, looking at the roof and admiring his masterpiece. Then, he noticed a grenade roll out from cloud of black smoke.

Bang, boom!

Ye Xiu fired at the grenade, making it explode. For a normal player, executing this move would make them feel unbelievably cool, but in Ye Xiu’s hands, it just looked like any other day.

The grenade was no threat to him, but it gave Ye Xiu second thoughts. He could have Lord Grim fly through the hole in the roof and give chase using Rotor Wings, but he had to consider the possibility of an ambush from Qin Muyun.

As a result, Lord Grim went towards the window. He jumped up, shattered the glass, and leaped out.

It was the second floor, but Lord Grim didn’t fall. The moment he was outside, his umbrella transformed into a ninjato and stabbed into the wall. He used it as a lever to jump and then stabbed his ninjato into the wall again…

Ye Xiu was very familiar with the Ninja’s Rock Climbing technique. It was difficult for the audience to keep their eyes away from Lord Grim’s fluid movements.

Lord Grim climbed up the wall, his direction clear. After a few rises and falls, he made it onto the roof. He didn’t stop to rest. He rolled towards a bunker to hide, not making a sound the entire way through.

Then, he peeked out his head and looked towards the other end.

Nothing!

Negative Nine Degrees wasn’t there. Qin Muyun hadn’t chosen to mount an ambush.

Ye Xiu didn’t waste time just because it was outside of his expectations. Lord Grim quickly looked around and found a few potential spots on the rooftop.

From Lord Grim blowing a hole in the roof to jumping onto the roof, the entire course of action took only 5 seconds.

5 seconds. Ye Xiu had checked where Qin Muyun could have moved to within those 5 seconds.

There were only two other possibilities.

First, he could have jumped off the roof. But Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had just climbed up the wall and didn’t see him, so it was unlikely.

The second possibility was that Qin Muyun jumped through that hole.

Calm, collected, and exceptional at picking spots. These were the characteristics that Ye Xiu observed from the fifth player who stood beside Tyranny’s Four Heavenly Kings.

Exceptional at picking spots?

Ye Xiu suddenly realized something. Lord Grim immediately rolled to the side.

Bang!

The sound of a gunshot.

A bullet pierced through the roof and shot towards the sky.

“Whoa!!”

Gasps came from the crowd as the bullet flew.

The viewers had an omniscient view and could see everything. Lord Grim had jumped out the window and made his way to the roof, while Negative Nine Degrees did the opposite and fell through the hole in the roof. Then, just like how Ye Xiu had accurately determined Negative Nine Degrees’ position, Qin Muyun accurately determined Lord Grim’s position.

How had they done it?

“Intuition and deduction.” Li Yibo had commented on this point when Ye Xiu had found Negative Nine Degrees’ position. After Lord Grim entered the manor, he immediately moved towards a spot. From that spot, he was able to catch a catch a glimpse of Negative Nine Degrees jumping towards the roof.

This wasn’t a coincidence. Ye Xiu knew that it was possible to jump onto the roof from the back of the manor, so he looked for a spot for which he could see that. Then, once Qin Muyun got to the roof, what hidden observation spots were there?

Ye Xiu knew of a spot, and it was the spot that Qin Muyun had found. As a result, he attacked there.

Vice versa, Qin Muyun had predicted what Ye Xiu would do, so he had Negative Nine Degrees fall through the roof into the manor. If Ye Xiu wanted to catch a Negative Nine Degrees that was laying in wait for an ambush, where would he go? As a result, he attacked there.

A high-level confrontation and high-level deduction. If neither side was exceptional at picking spots and didn’t choose the most optimal position, the two would have predicted incorrectly.

Li Yibo had given them praise for this point.

And this time, Qin Muyun’s sneak attack didn’t need his explanation. Everyone understood it now. But everyone was astonished that Qin Muyun’s sneak attack actually missed. He had used a high-level Snipe, but it missed its mark. Lord Grim suddenly rolling as if he had a premonition was just too miraculous.

“How did he know?” Pan Lin couldn’t help but ask Li Yibo.

“Ye Xiu probably made a prediction one step ahead…” Li Yibo forced out his words. He wasn’t sure if he was completely correct this time. There was some level of prediction for Ye Xiu’s dodge. But to just barely dodge it in such a timely manner, reaction speed had been a part of it, but luck had been very important too.

Two guns, two switches in position, fluid movements, and deep mind games. The level of skill displayed in this match could clearly be seen.

“It looks like this match will be brilliant game of hide-and-seek.” Just when Li Yibo made this statement, he heard a crash.

The rooftop broke apart.

Collapsing Mountain!

After Lord Grim dodged that shot, he didn’t stop to take a break. He immediately jumped up and used Collapsing Mountain towards the roof.

Happy had certainly figured out just how durable the roof was. This Collapsing Mountain split open the roof as Lord Grim crashed down.

One in the air, one on the ground.

Lord Grim and Negative Nine Degrees saw each other.

Hide-and-seek? Li Yibo hadn’t even finished his words, when the two characters found each other. He had spoken too soon and didn’t have time to swallow back his words.

Bang bang bang bang bang!

Qin Muyun stayed calm. His Negative Nine Degrees fired at Lord Grim as he moved.

Hua!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened, blocking the bullets. Collapsing Mountain had ended when the roof broke apart. Right now, Lord Grim was falling freely. If he were hit by bullets, he would certainly be Delivery Gunned away.

But with protection from a shield, everything changed. Sword light flashed, Falling Light Blade!

Lord Grim changed directions in the air. His umbrella retracted, but… Negative Nine Degrees? He was gone.

Chapter 1484 - Faster at Finding Spots

What is he going to do?

Those who understood the change felt more nervous than Ye Xiu. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were even more so. The two wished this wasn’t a live stream. They wanted to press pause and then give a detailed analysis of the change for the audience to hear, but unfortunately, they couldn’t. It was a match where a myriad of changes could happen in an instant.

Hua!

Without any trace of Negative Nine Degrees to be found, for a moment, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim raise his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

Hide-and-seek?

Maybe it looked like that, but it was a hide-and-seek deathmatch. The goal of the game wasn’t to find the opponent, but to kill the opponent.

After losing sight of Negative Nine Degrees, Ye Xiu’s response was to lift his umbrella to be on guard against any sudden ambushes from Negative Nine Degrees. Then, Ye Xiu quickly recalled where Negative Nine Degrees had been when his Lord Grim had fallen to the ground with Collapsing Mountain.

Next, he tried to predict where Negative Nine Degrees could be.

For Negative Nine Degrees to vanish, he obviously had to have moved, which meant that he first had to pick a spot.

Team Happy had chosen this map. How could Ye Xiu not be familiar with this map? He didn’t need to look around. He could deduce the optimal position in his head.

Charge!

Lord Grim held the umbrella shield above his head as he dashed towards a direction.

But at this moment, a pitch-black gun reached out from the other side and aimed towards Lord Grim.

Everyone thought that Lord Grim would be hit from behind by the bullet, but then, he suddenly stopped.

Lord Grim cancelled Charge and turned around. Light flashed.

Bang!

Sparks flew out from that pitch-black gun. Qin Muyun had put in the inputs. It was too late for him to stop. However, between pressing the trigger and Lord Grim turning around, one of them came first. Ye Xiu had somehow known that Negative Nine Degrees would be here before the gunshot rang. Had he looked over here before?

The broadcast director checked a replay, but he found nothing.

Lord Grim had never looked towards Negative Nine Degrees’ position.

How had he known?

Everyone looked at one another. Li Yibo didn’t know, but Pan Lin had thrown the question to him already.

He didn’t answer for now. Lord Grim stopped abruptly, turned around, and then flickered towards Negative Nine Degrees with a Shining Cut.

It was true that Sharpshooters had the strongest close combat capabilities among Gunner classes, but given a choice, very few Sharpshooters would choose to fight at a close range. Gun Fu wasn’t an easy technique to perform. Without this technique, just their few Taijutsu skills alone were nothing worthy of praise.

So when Qin Muyun saw Lord Grim heading towards him, his first thought was to retreat!

Bang bang bang bang!

Gunshots continued to ring. Negative Nine Degrees leaped backwards and open fired. Bullets sprayed out from his dual guns, the recoil helping to push Negative Nine Degrees back. In this enclosed area, even if the bullets missed Lord Grim, they would hit other objects in the room. The wall, tables, and all sorts of ornaments were shattered by the bullets.

Lord Grim was unscathed though.

Lord Grim drew a beautiful arc across where he moved, traversing through the rain of bullets. Although Negative Nine Degrees’ Aerial Gun technique allowed him to move fast, it couldn’t compare to an actual movement skill. The distance between the two characters was slowly erased step by step.

Seven steps.

Six steps.

Five steps.

Four steps.

The bullets suddenly formed a net that flew towards Lord Grim. Negative Nine Degrees had also stopped retreating. His movements seemed to be nothing out of the ordinary, but he would constantly maintain an angle that he could attack from. The distance between the two was subtly kept under control.

Four Step Gun Fu!

Those who knew what was what instantly recognized it. It could be considered a part of the Gun Fu technique. The number of steps was a way to look at a player’s mastery over the technique. Zhou Zekai’s Three Step Gun Fu was something no other player in Glory had achieved. It was a realm that only he had reached. The other pro Sharpshooters hovered around four steps. If they were feeling good, they could reach three and half steps. If they weren’t, four or even four and a half steps could be riddled with mistakes.

Gun Fu wasn’t a survival technique for when opponents got close. It was an offensive technique for Sharpshooters. Qin Muyun’s main role in Team Tyranny wasn’t as an attacker. His main responsibilities were to restrict his opponents. Gun Fu could occasionally be seen from him, but it never drew too much attention.

But right now, Four Step Gun Fu… ah!

The viewers didn’t even have time to appreciate it, when Negative Nine Degrees suddenly stepped forward. Bang bang bang! He continued to exert pressure onto Lord Grim, but the distance between them was… three steps!

Three Step Gun Fu?

Everyone was astonished. Qin Muyun, whose existence in the team seemed so weak, was actually able to perform what up until now only Zhou Zekai could do?

But before the viewers could appreciate this peak Three Step Gun Fu, Negative Nine Degrees jumped back, pulling the distance from three steps to five steps.

This…

Some players might not see anything strange, but the skilled players, especially the Sharpshooters, were very surprised.

Gun Fu was about moving in and out, but that didn’t mean going from three steps to five steps to three steps. Moving in and out was a way to describe a position, which the user could move in to attack or move out to retreat.

The number of steps was defined as how many steps it took to move both in and out. Qin Muyun had just performed a Three Step Gun Fu, but in the blink of an eye, it turned into Five Step Gun Fu… there was nothing inherently wrong with this sort of change, but how long had Ye Xiu and Qin Muyun been fighting for? Four steps to three steps to five steps, wasn’t he changing it too much? Was his Gun Fu not stable?

There were too many questions, and the two most worried people among the audience were Pan Lin and Li Yibo, who needed to explain it to their friends watching. Li Yibo seemed to have a vague idea, but he wasn’t confident in it. Taking advantage of the intensity of the match, he decided not to talk about it. Instead, he and Pan Lin listed out what skills the two players were using.

After five steps was seven steps!

Seven steps was somewhat far. Gun Fu combined gunfire with the Sharpshooter’s several kicking skills. At a distance of seven steps, the majority of a Sharpshooter’s close combat threat was out of the picture. At this point, he was probably planning on breaking away from using Gun Fu and running away, right?

The audience focused their eyes on Lord Grim.

The other side was getting ready to run, what will he do?

Lord Grim made movements, but it was simply to attack. He didn’t give chase. Ye Xiu let Negative Nine Degrees reach seven steps away.

Qin Muyun felt a shiver down his spine.

Was he seen through?

Seven steps was bait to lure Lord Grim forward. However, Ye Xiu didn’t move. Lord Grim aimed his attacks towards a very specific direction. It was to counter what Qin Muyun would have done if the bait had succeeded.

He really did see through me!

Such a specific direction of attack let Qin Muyun make a firm decision.

Bang bang bang, gunfire continued to sound. Lord Grim didn’t give chase, so Qin Muyun followed along and had Negative Nine Degrees begin to retreat. He had already figured out what route he wanted to take. Even though he wasn’t very familiar with this map, he was exceptional at picking spots, which also meant that he was exceptional at adapting to all sorts of maps.

But then, Lord Grim decided to move.

As soon as Qin Muyun gave away his intent, Ye Xiu acted.

Slide Kick!

Lord Grim slid across the ground, the bullets flying past him, as he headed towards Negative Nine Degrees.

Qin Muyun immediately had Negative Nine Degrees adjust by lowering his aim. He predicted where Lord Grim would slide to and attacked.

Bang bang bang bang.

The glossy marble ground became riddled with holes.

Lord Grim had suddenly jumped.

While he had been sliding across the ground, he sprung up into the air just as Negative Nine Degrees adjusted his aim.

Lord Grim had a gun too!

The tip of his Myriad Manifestions Umbrella opened and aimed at Negative Nine Degrees.

Bang bang!

Bullets shot out.

However, the Myriad Manifestation’s gun form was a Rifle, and Lord Grim didn’t have the class advancement skill “Gun Proficiency”. Lord Grim could not fire rapidly like Sharpshooters using normal attacks. Lord Grim only shot out two bullets, seemingly negligible out of all the other bullets flying through the air.

But Qin Muyun didn’t neglect them.

Lord Grim jumped, the muzzle of his gun gleaming in the light. Qin Muyun immediately had Negative Nine Degrees roll, while also adjusting his aim, pointing his gun towards the sky.

A bright fiery radiance flashed where Lord Grim was.

Flying Meteor!

The Exorcist skill was an above Level 20 skill, which meant that Ye Xiu had chosen to put this skill onto his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella.

This skill had probably been used before Lord Grim had fired those two shots. Those two shots were bait to lure Qin Muyun into dodging. Before Negative Nine Degrees could press the trigger, the Flying Meteor had already descended.

Boom!

A sea of fire swallowed the area. This time, Qin Muyun didn’t have time to dodge. The Flying Meteor had been timed too precisely.

“But the attack only landed because of Qin Muyun’s skill in picking the optimal spot and moving there.” Huang Shaotian received a message from Yu Wenzhou.

Yes! These top experts understood this reasoning.

Positioning was originally Qin Muyun’s strongest point. However, Ye Xiu took advantage of that strength.

It was true that Qin Muyun could quickly find the most optimal position and move there precisely, but because he always made the optimal choice, it meant that he lacked mix-ups.

If Ye Xiu could figure out what that optimal choice was, he could accurately predict where Qin Muyun would move to.

That sounded simple, but it wasn’t something anyone could do. Positioning was Qin Muyun’s speciality, which meant that he was better and faster than others at figuring out what the optimal position was at any given moment.

But since Ye Xiu could keep up with his pace, it meant that Ye Xiu was no worse than Qin Muyun in terms of positioning. It could even be said that he could find the right spots faster than Qin Muyun could!

Chapter 1485 - Saving Trouble

The Flying Meteor was about to strike Negative Nine Degrees. For a moment, whirling flames covered Qin Muyun’s view. He could only rely on his experience and intuition to make his next move.

But his every action was within Ye Xiu’s predictions. A figure suddenly appeared inside the sea of fire as if he were born from the fire, Lord Grim!

A distance of three steps!

Qin Muyun had chosen to retreat. The distance between Negative Nine Degrees and Lord Grim was three steps.

Qin Muyun had shown a Three Step Gun Fu previously, and it appeared to be a distance that he could maintain. However, Qin Muyun knew why it seemed like that.

His Three Step Gun Fu wasn’t perfect. He didn’t have complete control over moving in and out within three steps. But because of his outstanding positioning, he occasionally found spots where he could perform Gun Fu within three steps. When those moments came, he would choose to step forward and perform a Three Step Gun Fu like he had done previously in his exchange with Lord Grim. After all, the closer the steps, the higher the threat.

When he was no longer able to maintain it, he would move back.

By relying on his positioning skills, Qin Muyun was able to form his own unique form of Gun Fu, which allowed him to keep the threat of Gun Fu up while staying at a comfortable distance.

However, right now, Qin Muyun wasn’t in a position where he could perform Gun Fu at this distance of three steps.

There may have been an opportunity at one point, but the spot that Lord Grim was in destroyed Qin Muyun’s last hopes.

I’ve been seen through!

Qin Muyun knew that his technique and his intent had been seen through. Every step he took was uncomfortable for him. The first strike had hit his vital point.

As expected of the one who’s fought with Captain for ten years and often had the upper hand.

Qin Muyun felt awe. When he had started his journey, Ye Xiu had already retired. However, his existence was a part of Excellent Era’s history and Tyranny’s history – the villain in Tyranny’s story.

Qin Muyun had heard of the stories and had seen Ye Xiu’s accomplishments. He had fought against him in the team competitions during the regular season. But in this 1v1, he finally experienced for himself just how terrifying Tyranny’s villain was.

Do I still have a chance?

Once Lord Grim closed the distance between them, he tried to fight while retreating. He looked for ways to escape.

The window?

The door?

The corner over there?

There wasn’t much space in the room. Every exit seemed so close, but close did not mean reachable. Lord Grim blocked him from moving towards those exits. Finally, Negative Nine Degrees was forced into a corner.

Without enough space, he couldn’t even execute Gun Fu. At this point, Sharpshooters practically had no options left. Qin Muyun realized that he had made a mistake in the beginning. Choosing to fight in this enclosed space had been a grave mistake.

But if he hadn’t entered the room, if he had waited up on the roof to ambush Lord Grim, he would have been caught by Lord Grim’s sneak attack!

Qin Muyun had already started to review this match, and when he came to this point, he could only stare blankly at his screen.

Throughout this match, Ye Xiu had the initiative every step of the way. It was because Ye Xiu knew that his positioning was outstanding, so he could always make an accurate prediction of where he would move to. When Lord Grim went through the window onto the roof to sneak up on Negative Nine Degrees, he missed. Why? Wasn’t it because Qin Muyun had dropped through the hole in the roof into the room?

Ye Xiu hadn’t covered this option because from a certain perspective, he knew that it wasn’t a smart one. However, Qin Muyun really did choose this unwise option, throwing Ye Xiu’s plans into disarray for a bit.

Qin Muyun felt like he had realized something. When facing against an opponent like Ye Xiu, the optimal option was not always the best option because the opponent knew what that optimal option was…

I lost.

Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees fell. However, he had taken out 43% of Lord Grim’s health too, so it wasn’t too bad. After careful observation and thought, Li Yibo finally noticed the key points in this match and began speaking confidently about the competition of positioning between the two players.

“In the end, the older, the wiser. Ye Xiu is more skilled!” Li Yibo sighed.

“But what about here!” Pan Lin hinted at the broadcast director to show a replay. When Lord Grim broke the rooftop and fell down, he blocked a few shots with his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. But when he retracted his umbrella, he couldn’t see his opponent. However, he quickly deduced Qin Muyun’s position and found him soon afterwards.”

“Qin Muyun wasn’t in the optimal position, so how did Ye Xiu figure out where he was and then fake an attack?” Pan Lin asked.

“Hahaha,” Li Yibo laughed with delight, “It’s true that Qin Muyun didn’t pick the optimal position, but picking the right spot is dependent on the circumstances. At that time, not only did Qin Muyun need to pick a spot, he needed to take advantage of Ye Xiu’s blind spots and move while Ye Xiu couldn’t see him.”

“I see…” Pan Lin understood.

“Under these conditions, Qin Muyun’s position is, in fact, optimal,” Li Yibo said

“But if Ye Xiu had figured out Qin Muyun’s position, why didn’t he drop down and directly attack him? Why bother faking an attack?”

“Because Qin Muyun really had picked a very good spot! Look, if Lord Grim landed on the ground first, he wouldn’t have been in a good position to launch an attack. In fact, Negative Nine Degrees would have had more space. By faking an attack, he was able to move to a better position to attack,” Li Yibo explained.

“Oh.” Pan Lin felt enlightened and felt even more appreciation for Li Yibo. He had been won over by his analysis.

“In other words, the purpose of Ye Xiu’s feint was to paralyze the opponent and to move to a better position,” Pan Lin concluded.

“That’s right,” Li Yibo nodded. He felt proud that he had seen through the issue.

“What an amazing fight,” Pan Lin sighed.

“Qin Muyun was beaten by Ye Xiu at his own game. I hope it won’t affect him later.” That was what Li Yibo said, but it was evidently a way of phrasing what he wanted to say in a nicer way. In reality, he was pointing out that Ye Xiu beating Qin Muyun would be a blow to Tyranny’s morale.

“But despite Ye Xiu having the upper hand, Qin Muyun was still able to take down 43% of Lord Grim’s health. Qin Muyun performed quite well,” Pan Lin said.

“Yes, especially in the latter half of the fight, where he was backed into a corner. Sharpshooters have a very difficult time fighting in those conditions,” Li Yibo said.

“Let’s see who Tyranny will send up next,” Pan Lin said.

By this time, Qin Muyun had left the player booth. The camera had zoomed in onto him for some time. Li Yibo had seen his expressionless face and had said the words “I hope it won’t affect him later” as a response. The two commentators found a few praiseworthy moments for him before discussing the next matchup.

But in the eyes of the experts, the discussion of the match wasn’t finished yet.

“43% seems a bit much,” Huang Shaotian messaged Yu Wenzhou. Ye Xiu had the clear upper hand. Using nearly half his health to take down the opponent was a bit excessive.

“His opponent didn’t make it easy! Qin Muyun’s positioning is truly outstanding,” Yu Wenzhou replied. When the two experts chatted with each other, they didn’t need to explain every detail like the commentators. They just needed to touch upon the main point.

“If he gave himself more space and put more pressure on him, he could have reduced the damage he took.” Huang Shaotian replied.

“But it’s more risky, and it would have increased the amount of inputs he would have needed to make,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“So he’s trying to save his energy!” Huang Shaotian said.

“That’s why we tried to wear him down,” Yu Wenzhou said.

“That bastard,” Huang Shaotian cursed. They had drawn up a strategy, targeting what Ye Xiu had been worried about, but Ye Xiu was able to neutralize it. When Huang Shaotian thought back, he felt even more helpless. On the other hand, Ye Xiu’s simple and crude setups for Blue Rain all hit their target.

For example, take Blue Rain’s Mister Clutch, Song Xiao. His playoffs run was truly depressing. He had gained fame from his plays in the playoffs. It was as if the playoffs was his home. But his performance in Blue Rain’s two rounds against Happy? In the team competition, as the sixth player, he was often the Mister Clutch that helped Blue Rain open up the field, yet before he could even do anything, the match had already been decided.

Mister Clutch wasn’t on the field at the crucial moments. How could he be clutch if he wasn’t there? Happy had crudely placed Song Xiao on the back burner.

“Let’s see who Tyranny will send up next.” It wasn’t clear if it was because Yu Wenzhou had also recalled their loss against Happy, but he now switched topics.

The big screen displayed Tyranny’s next player.

Zhang Jiale, Spitfire, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

The crowd booed.

Zhang Jiale had returned to the scene, abandoning Hundred Blossoms and joining Tyranny. Hundred Blossoms viewed him as a traitor. The fans of other teams, including Tyranny, looked down on his conduct. The current Zhang Jiale was nowhere near as popular as before. There were always people who would criticize his moral character, and Happy’s home stadium was no exception. As soon as Zhang Jiale appeared, boos and curses were immediately thrown his way.

Zhang Jiale was used to it. It had been two years. He could even face Hundred Blossoms calmly now. None of those boos or criticisms counted as anything.

Two years.

Zhang Jiale was counting his days. He knew that, for people like him, every day that passed was one less day. If they failed this year, what about next year? Did they have a next year?

But none of them could have expected that the one blocking their way would be Ye Xiu. As he walked onto the stage, Zhang Jiale couldn’t help but recall those glorious years when the two had once battled.

Chapter 1486 - One Person’s Dream

Ye Xiu, a first generation pro player. Zhang Jiale, a second generation pro player.

There was only a year between them, so there was no need for any courtesies for seniority. Though Ye Xiu would sometimes act the wise, knowing elder, Zhang Jiale clearly had no care for it.

The two’s first real top level face off was in the third season of the Glory Pro League.

That season, Team Hundred Blossoms’ Sun Zheping and Zhang Jiale, their Blood and Blossoms had fully matured, sweeping across the Alliance and taking first place in the regular season. However, in the end, in the finals, they were met with Excellent Era. The story of how One Autumn Leaf cut through their combo with his Evil Annihilation had become a legend in this scene.

In the end, Blood and Blossoms fell into the background.

Zhang Jiale wouldn’t accept that, of course, so they returned anew in the fourth season.

But this season, they didn’t even make it into the finals. The season came to a close with the legendary battle where Tyranny ended Excellent Era’s dynasty. Blood and Blossoms once more became no more than a passerby.

In the fifth season, Hundred Blossoms came back in high spirits, ready for the new season after three seasons of experience. That was when their captain, Sun Zheping, was forced to retire midseason, in his golden years, due to a hand injury. Zhang Jiale took over as captain and Team Hundred Blossoms charged forward amidst their tears, empowered by their sorrow, straight into the finals.

However, the result was that they lost against the one who joined the scene in the third season, known throughout the Glory scene as the Magician. They lost to the one who, as rumor would have it, was the closest to the God of Glory, the closest to erecting a dynasty like Ye Xiu did. They lost to Wang Jiexi.

Wang Jiexi became Hundred Blossom’s worst nightmare. In the seventh season, when they were mere inches away from reaching the championships again, it was Wang Jiexi who shattered their dreams once again.

Seven years and three runners-up, it was almost as if Hundred Blossoms was plagued by some sort of curse. When they fell to Wang Jiexi this time, Blood and Blossoms had been left in the past, and this had become an accomplishment of Zhang Jiale’s efforts alone.

Perhaps it was because he thought that it was already the best he could do alone, one summer later, Zhang Jiale suddenly announced his retirement.

Today, the story of Blood and Blossoms had truly ended. Though Sun Zheping had already retired in the fifth season, Zhang Jiale had always fought for the both of them.

No one could understand what sorrow he felt, what disappointment he lived in.

The people would only sigh: if Sun Zheping didn’t retire from his injuries, if Sun Zheping had been there all along, then would Blood and Blossoms have erected a Hundred Blossoms dynasty after Excellent Era fell?

There were no ifs.

These ifs were nothing but knives to the heart for those involved.

Zhang Jiale had never given up, otherwise, he wouldn’t have carried the responsibility and dream that two were meant to bear and gritted his teeth, charging onwards alone.

Unfortunately, he still fell in the end and gave up.

Blood and Blossoms was a story of two. One person wouldn’t be able to write that perfect ending.

However, for him personally, there was still a dream in his heart, an everlasting dream.

After a season, he returned, abandoning his old home Hundred Blossoms and joining Tyranny, a pandering move he was despised for. Zhang Jiale had doubted his choices, but ultimately, he didn’t regret it. He affirmed his goals. Now, he stood here, still in control of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, but it was Tyranny he was fighting for. As for his opponent? Ye Xiu wasn’t unfamiliar, but his character was the unspecialized Lord Grim, representing the new team Happy.

Familiar scene, familiar characters, but different people?

No, the people were the same people, but everything else was messed up.

However, no matter what happened, his dream of the championship would never change.

Bang!

A sudden gunshot startled everyone. Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had just loaded into the map and suddenly shot a bullet into the air.

Click, click, click, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms switched rapidly through his cartridges before heading off. This was a habit of Zhang Jiale’s.

It was still the same map, and both chose to go the middle path, so they arrived in the manor in the middle of the map one after the other.

Lord Grim went in directly through the front door. And Dazzling Hundred Blossoms? Straight through the back door.

Although Spitfires were a Gunner class, they had many different kinds of attacks and were called the Mages of Gunners. Their battle styles didn’t need a lot of space like Sharpshooters and Launchers. An enclosed speed was equally as convenient. In fact, there were some enclosed terrains that Spitfires excelled in!

The manor had two floors. Ye Xiu and Qin Muyun’s battle happened entirely on the second floor. The map wouldn’t refresh, so the second floor was still in complete disarray from the previous battle. Negative Nine Degrees’s bullets had turned the rooms that the two characters had fought intensely into a complete mess.

However, Lord Grim and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms were still on the first floor. Both characters were wary, each step taken with infinite caution.

Ye Xiu was familiar with the map. Lord Grim first watched the window for a while like he did against Qin Muyun. After not seeing any signs of Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, he was clearly acting on the thought that “he probably came in through the back door.”

As for Zhang Jiale? He had clearly lost the initiative since he didn’t know the map. After entering through the backdoor, he cautiously surveyed his surroundings, the room layout, the doorway. After entering the room, he glanced around several times and randomly went for the doorway that led to the hallway, opening it with a creak.

The audience held their breath.

In the corridor outside the doorway, Lord Grim was carefully walking over. The sudden opening of the door would expose Zhang Jiale’s position.

“Careless! He knows its a corridor…” Pan Lin was saying, but then suddenly shut up.

Knowing that the corridor was here, he should be on guard for the possibility of his opponent to just so happen to be passing by. He was about to say that, but then, he shut up because he saw that after Dazzling Hundred Blossoms opened the door, he didn’t walk out.

Creeeeaaaak…

The door opened, then closed again, creaking all the while.

Lord Grim, in the corridor outside, already had his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella raised. Lord Grim pointed towards the doorway as he silently edged rightwards to give himself a better view of the room.

Creeeeeaaaak….

The door continued to close, with only a sliver of an opening left.

Was he not coming out?

Just as everyone thought this, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms darted out suddenly.

The door was slammed open again. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had the door behind him as cover, his right hand holding his automatic handgun Hunter Seeker out in front of him.

Zhang Jiale saw Lord Grim immediately.

Ye Xiu also saw the charging Dazzling Hundred Blossoms immediately.

Gunshots.

Both guns spat embers simultaneously. However, for normal shots, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was a rifle. Each reload allowed for two shots. Meanwhile, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was using an automatic handgun. On top of that, he had the Spitfire class skill Ammunition Expansion, which affected normal attacks as well. The number of shots they could fire in that moment were on two completely different levels.

So Lord Grim immediately attacked with a skill.

Anti-Tank Missiles!

Three missiles shot out in rapid succession.

Boom boom boom!

In the narrow corridor, the two characters aimed their guns at one another. The shots they fired collided, exploding. A thick smoke billowed out and enveloped the corridor, and the force of the explosion sent both characters backwards.

Ye Xiu didn’t retreat. With a push of his mouse, Lord Grim used Slide Kick, charging straight at the billowing smoke.

“That’s too daring!” Pan Lin cried out in surprise.

It was an unknown situation, but it wouldn’t be hard to guard against Ye Xiu going on the offensive. So long as Zhang Jiale was on guard, he could just throw a few grenades into the smoke. How would Lord Grim dodge that?

However, when he saw the exact direction Lord Grim had aimed his Slide Kick in, he realized something was wrong.

Was he planning to Slide Kick the wall?

In that moment of confusion, Lord Grim had already slid to the wall.

Boom boom boom!

As expected, flashes of explosions bloomed amidst the smoke. Zhang Jiale had been prepared for the possibility of an attack. However, in this moment Lord Grim slid to the wall and then suddenly jumped up. He unsheathed his ninjato from the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, swinging in and stabbing it into the wall. With a leap, he pulled the blade blade and swung again…

He was running along the wall!

Pan Lin stared in shock. The whole audience stared in shock.

The corridor was narrow, so the force of the explosions enveloped the entire area. But with the wall to brace himself on, Lord Grim wouldn’t be thrown back. The force would just press him closer against the wall….

Taking some insignificant damage, Lord Grim had managed to charge out of the smoke with two jumps, falling forward.

This was originally where Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was, but when Lord Grim appeared, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms immediately darted out of the way. He had kept some distance between him and the thick smoke; Zhang Jiale wouldn’t be so stupid as to stand right in front of it. Thus, he could still dodge out of the way even when Lord Grim used such an unexpected method of attack.

With a step, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms stepped back into the room.

Creeeeeaaak, the door continued to close. With the way he was falling, Lord Grim was going to hit the door. If that happened, that would be rather embarrassing.

Lord Grim hurriedly swung his ninjato again.

Bang bang bang bang…

After switching positions, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms immediately began to attack, but Lord Grim dodged the bullets by swinging his ninjato towards the wall behind, ending up stepping on the top of the door accurately.

With a kick, Lord Grim jumped to the other side of the door and the door closed rapidly. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had to retreat swiftly, almost getting hit in the face by the door.

Clank!

Slamming shut, the door separated the two characters, one inside the room, the other outside.

Since the first level of the castle had to take a lot of weight, the walls were very thick. They weren’t something characters could destroy without some effort. Right now, with the two separated like this, they didn’t have to worry about a sneak attack coming through the wall.

Lord Grim didn’t make any moves for now. This was because Ye Xiu knew the map well. The room had a lot of ways out. If he circled around, he probably wouldn’t be able to catch the other, unless Zhang Jiale stayed in the room and didn’t move.

Right now, the quickest way to continue his assault was to charge inside through this door.

However, the door opened outwards, not inwards, which meant that Ye Xiu couldn’t barge inside like Zhang Jiale had barged outside, using the door to cover his back while he faced the other way. If the door had opened inwards, Ye Xiu would be able to charge in, being able to react no slower than the person waiting on the other side.

However, if Ye Xiu charged inside and Zhang Jiale was ready to ambush him, that would not be good.

What should he do?

The two characters pressed themselves against the wall, silent and unmoving.

Chapter 1487 - The True Hundred Blossoms

The two characters each stood against the wall. The distance between them was very small; the tension was thick in the air.

Until messages appeared in the chat.

“You come in!”

“You come out!”

The childish exchange swiftly broke the tense atmosphere. The audience didn’t know whether to laugh or not.

But while this meaningless chat occurred, Ye Xiu was moving. Lord Grim ended up not going through the door, but he didn’t circle around to a different room either. He actually chose to nimbly make his way outside through the window. Then, he swung his ninjato, quickly flipping up to the second-floor window and rolling back inside, having chosen a suitable position.

Everyone was caught off-guard. With this action, was he planning to directly break through the floor of the second level to ambush from above?

It was a complicated task for the fully immersive projection to beautifully display this interior environment, because anything that obstructed the audience view had to be eliminated. Right now, the floor of the second level looked like it was suspended in midair. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim and Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms were displayed like that, one above and one below, still at a very close distance, but the distance was now vertical instead of horizontal.

On the first floor, Zhang Jiale still hadn’t detected anything. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms lifted a gun with one hand and held a grenade in the other. From where he was standing, he could attack every entrance of this room.

But right now, Ye Xiu wasn’t planning to use an entrance!

Hualala!

Ye Xiu very much valued time. He didn’t hesitate at all while he was on the second floor. While many people were still processing his actions, he was already beginning to act.

The cross section of this castle was fragile enough. One more attack was enough to break through, and amidst the shattered pieces, Lord Grim plummeted downward. In the blink of an eye, he had already found Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’ position. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella swung over, fire!

Zhang Jiale’s reaction wasn’t slow. As soon as he heard a noise above him, even as he lifted his camera to check, his automatic pistol, the Silver weapon Hunting Seeker, was already lifted into the air, and the grenade in his left hand was tossed outward. Immediately after, he confirmed the situation above him and continued to toss grenade after grenade, like a weapon master in wuxia, or like a magician with his playing cards. Those grenades flew outward nonstop.

Boom boom boom boom!

The middle height of the room was instantly swallowed by explosions, just like the passageway earlier, splitting the space in two.

Unexpected?

Ye Xiu’s plan was quite unexpected, but this method was a bit too blunt. The attack made a loud noise when it impacted the floor of the second level, and Zhang Jiale was good enough to immediately react and deal with it. What Ye Xiu gained here was similar to the situation Zhang Jiale had been in when he’d rushed outward through the door earlier – the situation wasn’t particularly advantageous for either side, it would come down to whose reaction was faster.

Earlier in the passageway, the two of them had tied after an exchange of blows. This time, with one above and one below, who would win the upper hand?

Roundhouse Kick!

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms suddenly used a low-level Sharpshooter skill, sweeping around 360 degrees.

Miss!

There was actually no one next to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, and Zhang Jiale instantly knew that he had made a mistake in his prediction. He had originally thought that Ye Xiu would take advantage of the cover, using Shadow Clone Technique to swiftly close in. Yet, surprisingly, Ye Xiu hadn’t done this.

One misstep instantly revealed an opening. Amidst the flashing explosions in midair, Lord Grim looked like he was flying with an imperial sword, and he came plummeting down with a Falling Light Blade.

He had actually stayed in midair for that long?

The audience could see clearly that after Lord Grim broke through the floor, he didn’t hurry to the ground. After the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella fired a few shots in gun form, it shifted back to a ninjato and was anchored into the ceiling.

From the start, Ye Xiu didn’t think that his sneak attack from above would directly cause Zhang Jiale any difficulty. He just wanted to create an unusual situation. With this small opening that Zhang Jiale exposed with his mistake, he now attacked.

Zhang Jiale had no time to dodge. The Falling Light Blade came right down upon Dazzling Hundred Blossoms. But then, with a blast, Lord Grim was also thrown aside by a shockwave. There was a hole in the ground, the scar left by the explosion of a landmine.

Ye Xiu had seized an opportunity for attack, but he hadn’t expected that Zhang Jiale also had an ambush ready. In their second clash, the two of them once again reached a stalemate. But this was only speaking about the battle situation. In terms of damage, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had broken through the firing line in the first clash, and suffered bombing in the second before forcefully breaking through the firing line. In doing so, he had taken more than a little bit of damage. After being sent flying by this landmine, Lord Grim’s health had fallen to 42%, having started this round at 57%.

Two times, he had used up his health for the sake of his offensive, but he hadn’t managed to win the initiative. From this exchange perspective, even though Ye Xiu had initiated the attack both times, Zhang Jiale had ultimately ended up better off.

“Defensive fighting!” Blue Rain was a defensive team, so of course they were very sensitive to a defensive playstyle. Seeing this situation, Huang Shaotian immediately sent another text to Yu Wenzhou.

“Yes.” Yu Wenzhou’s reply acknowledged this point. And in the televised broadcast, Pan Lin and Li Yibo were still exclaiming about how the two players’ incredible reaction speeds and responses made them evenly matched. Those two hadn’t even realized the deeper significance of this!

“This is more like you!” In another area of the stadium, an audience member who was keeping a low profile as he watched the match now uttered this exclamation.

Sun Zheping!

A former part of the Blood and Blossom duo, a former god-level player, now contributing the last remnants of his strength to Team Heavenly Swords with the limited time he had. Today, he could no longer be considered a star. The attention he’d garnered when first returning had gradually faded away because of his severely limited appearances in Heavenly Swords.

Heavenly Swords, where he was now, had no no business in the playoffs; for him, the championship dream was already long in the past. He simply remained here as a passerby, all because of that piece of his heart that prevented him from ever giving up on Glory completely.

Yes, a passerby. His kind of return and onstage appearance could only be considered passing by. Because of this, Sun Zheping didn’t have any regrets about not tagging along with the black horse that was Team Happy. Happy was the starting point for his return. And now, this grassroots team with which he wasn’t unfamiliar was actually piercing straight through toward the championship. If he were still in this team, Sun Zheping believed that he would go crazy from his inability to go all-out at such a crucial time.

Heavenly Swords was a wise choice. Sun Zheping never regretted it.

And seeing Happy reach this point, Sun Zheping felt gratified as well.

He looked forward to seeing this team create a miracle, just like when they had defeated Excellent Era in the Challenger League. But now, Happy was actually facing off against Tyranny…

Toward Tyranny itself Sun Zheping didn’t have any particularly strong feelings. He would pay attention to them only because Zhang Jiale was there, because his former partner, his closest friend, was there.

His emotions, his goal, his pursuit, Sun Zheping understood completely. But now, Zhang Jiale collided with Happy.

It was really a difficult situation to watch. But Sun Zheping was a simple and direct person; he didn’t have any conflicts in his heart. Facing each other on the narrow road, the courageous would emerge victorious – his belief was just that simple. For him, his emotions would never become a burden on the battlefield, and as a spectator in the audience, it was the same.

But now, the Zhang Jiale he saw didn’t have the furious, desperate stance of before. In particular, it was a far cry from that struggling ferocity that he’d displayed while leading Hundred Blossoms after Sun Zheping had retired from injury.

Was this a sign that he no longer had that fighting spirit of before?

Of course that wasn’t the case, because this right now was the playstyle that truly suited him the best.

The Hundred Blossoms style was called the most splendid and romantic playstyle in all of Glory. As the inventor of this style, Zhang Jiale certainly wasn’t imitating anyone with his use of skills. His technique simply reflected his personality; this was just the kind of person he was. That sort of furious, desperate hacking and slashing very much went against his character.

But in Hundred Blossoms, after Sun Zheping was forced to retire from his injury, Zhang Jiale could only take up Sun Zheping’s desperate portion of the playstyle as well.

In reality, it didn’t have to be like this.

Sun Zheping had always wanted to say this to Zhang Jiale. But, it was entirely because of his own injury that this burden landed upon Zhang Jiale. When the other was so desperately carrying it, what right did Sun Zheping have to tell him not to do this?

If you’re willing to carry it, then stay strong and advance!

This was just the kind of person that Sun Zheping was. He only knew how to staunchly encourage his old friend like this.

Unfortunately, in the end, all that Zhang Jiale tasted were the bitter fruits of defeat.

It wasn’t until he arrived at Tyranny that he could finally set down his burdens of the past. Zhang Jiale no longer had to carry the responsibility of two people by himself. And so, the Zhang Jiale of the earliest Blood and Blossoms era had returned. This was the condition that suited him best.

Just in this match, Sun Zheping saw it clearly.

The Hundred Blossoms playstyle was protection, was cover; it filled the openings left by teammates; it augmented the teammates’ offensives. This was an extremely careful and thorough playstyle. It wasn’t something that could be accomplished just by throwing around complicated controls – that kind of Hundred Blossoms wasn’t a true Hundred Blossoms.

In the time that Zhang Jiale had led Hundred Blossoms alone, his technique had grown more refined, but his Hundred Blossoms had drifted away somewhat from its essential spirit.

But now, it had all returned.

In fact, because of his growth from experience, Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms playstyle of today was even more careful and precise. Every thread was tightly interwoven, leaking not a single drop.

People thought that the Hundred Blossoms playstyle still hadn’t emerged in this match?

That was a big mistake.

In the passageway, in midair, those bursting explosions were all the Hundred Blossoms style. And in this kind of space, when the Hundred Blossoms bloomed, there was nowhere to hide. The charging Lord Grim could only suffer the damage he was supposed to.

There were those who thought that the Hundred Blossoms playstyle was supposed to consist of nonstop lights and shadows, flashing until no one could see anything. But this kind of view was too simplistic.

The true Hundred Blossoms wasn’t placed everywhere, it just

Take as an example using lights to block the opponent’s vision. Did that require 360 degrees of surrounding?

It didn’t.

What it truly required was nothing more than, in that most critical moment, a sudden expanse of flashes appearing in the opponent’s vision.

Boom boom boom boom…

In such a small space, the explosions were nonstop. For the moment, Lord Grim had no way of closing in.

It seemed like the explosions weren’t being continuously strung together, but every time that Ye Xiu prepared to control Lord Grim to rush forward, a series of explosions would make his vision go blurry.

Ye Xiu completely understood that this was intentional. Given that the opponent was able to accomplish this to this extent, he didn’t dare blindly charge forward.

The space he had was shrinking, and his exits were already cut off. Lord Grim was right in the middle of the Hundred Blossoms.

Chapter 1488 - Borrow

No holes!

Lord Grim had been trapped, but Ye Xiu's intuition told him that he could only evaluate Zhang Jiale's performance as such.

Ye Xiu had been around throughout Zhang Jiale's professional career. He had watched Hundred Blossom's Berserker and Spitfire rise to fame to Blood and Blossoms dominance in the Glory scene to Sun Zheping's retirement to Zhang Jiale's bitter walk alone. Ye Xiu had been there the entire time, crossing hands with Zhang Jiale at every step.

His thoughts were the same as Sun Zheping's: the current Zhang Jiale was the best that he had ever been because Zhang Jiale had re-found his footing. The years of potential that had been bottled up the entire time were finally being put on display.

Ye Xiu couldn't find any openings, but that didn't mean he could just keeping waiting for one to come.

Zhang Jiale wasn't letting out fireworks for Ye Xiu to enjoy. The bullets fired by Dazzling Hundred Blossoms might not be heavy, but all of them dealt damage. The space that Lord Grim could maneuver around in was getting smaller and smaller, and his injuries were getting heavier and heavier.

Charge!

Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella suddenly opened. It seemed like he was planning on tanking the hits to escape from this predicament, but how could Zhang Jiale not have considered such a simple method like tanking the hits with a shield? As soon as Zhang Jiale saw the umbrella open, he immediately responded.

A grenade was thrown at the edges of the umbrella's canvas. Then, with a bullet, the grenade was knocked over the umbrella, directly into Lord Grim's line of sight.

There was no time for Ye Xiu to react. The grenade exploded.

Remote Control Grenade.

It had less power than the low-level Impact Grenade, but the user could blow up the grenade manually, naturally making it much easier to set off the explosion at a precise timing. The grenade had leapt over the umbrella shield and exploded. Although the damage dealt was low, it had been a direct hit. The knockback sent Lord Grim sliding back.

With Lord Grim swaying from the blow, the umbrella shield no longer fully covered him. Zhang Jiale seized the openings and fired all sorts of bullets.　

Boom boom boom!

Light and smoke intertwined, forming a dazzling picture of a hundred flowers blossoming.

Lord Grim had been swallowed by the brilliant light. All that could be seen was a blurry figure. Zhang Jiale didn't relax and continued to throw out attacks at Lord Grim up until even that blur could no longer be seen.

The attacks suddenly stopped.

Zhang Jiale realized that Lord Grim's health wasn't going down.

How is that possible?

There had been no place for him to dodge or block. Lord Grim had been cornered.

The artillery barrage stopped. The light dissipated. All that remained were remnant flames and smoke. In this enclosed space, the thick smoke would take awhile to disperse, but he was able to see what he needed to see. A hole had appeared in that corner of the room.

Zhang Jiale instantly understood what had transpired.

The walls were sturdy, but no indestructible. It just needed enough attacks. Ye Xiu had made a feint, baiting Zhang Jiale to launch a fierce counterattack. By borrowing the artillery barrage and the cover of the dazzling light, he broke through the sturdy wall and escaped.

Lord Grim had taken a considerable amount of damage to pull this off; only 19% of his health remained. However, in what seemed to be an inescapable position, Ye Xiu had been able to force an opening.　

He really is hard to deal with!

Zhang Jiale couldn't remember just how many times he had thought this in the past.

Zhi!

A door from the other end opened.

The other side of the wall was the neighboring room. Ye Xiu acted decisively, immediately launching a counterattack. Zhang Jiale had Dazzling Hundred Blossoms turn towards that entrance and started attacking wildly. As soon as a figure could be seen, the light engulfed him. However, the figure appeared shorter than usual was knocked down a lot faster. More importantly, Lord Grim's health hadn't gone down.

Zhang Jiale realized that the situation wasn't good. He quickly turned back, but Lord Grim had already closed the distance. Lord Grim had dashed out from that broken hole. As for what had pushed open the door, it was a Goblin. The Goblin had distracted Zhang Jiale for just an instant.

But an instant was enough. Lord Grim had left behind a shadow as he came through the hole in the wall. He had used Shadow Clone Technique, his fastest movement option, to instantly close the distance.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms was knocked into the air. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed in a blur as the Unspecialized Blitz began.　

Blood splattered into the air.

Close combat resulted in this sort of bloody fight.　

Dazzling Hundred Blossom's health slid downwards rapidly. He hadn't taken any damage previously, so everyone thought that Zhang Jiale would be able to end this match without losing much health, evening up the disadvantage left by Qin Muyun's defeat.

But in the end, he hadn't been able to take care of Ye Xiu in one wave.

19%. The remaining health on Lord Grim came back to bite him.

Would he be swept away by Lord Grim's combo?

Everyone started worrying for Zhang Jiale.

Ye Xiu's unspecialized had done this too many times in the regular season. Just one bite, and he would never let go.　　

Zhang Jiale obviously understood this point. Ye Xiu had undoubtedly been their main focus point in their research on Happy. He was an old rival that Team Tyranny was incomparably familiar with, but he just had to switch classes. It had truly been a headache for them.　　

A class change meant a change in playstyle. However, a person's experience, intuition, knowledge, habits, etc. wouldn't change.　　

Team Tyranny's Han Wenqin had fought with Ye Xiu for ten years.

Zhang Jiale and Lin Jinyan were the Alliance's second generation of players.

The players, who were most familiar with Ye Xiu and had fought against Ye Xiu the most times, were coincidentally all from Team Tyranny.

The complexity of the unspecialized class put them in a bind just the same as everyone else, but in terms of grasping Ye Xiu's thoughts, no one else had more of an advantage than them.

Time would take away things, but also leave them with things.　　

Take me out in one combo?

Zhang Jiale was the only one, apart from Ye Xiu, who had experienced four finals. No one had as much experience at the apex of Glory as much as these two had. Zhang Jiale had gotten second place all four times. The experience had tempered his heart even further.

He had experienced the greatest setback four times. It was just a single up-and-down in one small part of a match. For him, it was insignificant.

The second he had been launched into the air, he began resisting. While in the air, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms kept throwing down grenades as if Lord Grim was a piggy bank.

No one had expected Zhang Jiale to actually launch such a powerful counterattack from a disadvantaged airborne state. There were a few grenades that Ye Xiu had no choice but to deal with, but most of them couldn't be dealt with if he wanted to keep his offense going.

Grenades poured from the sky.　　

Amidst the blooming light, Lord Grim tenaciously moved.　　

This sort of powerful counterattack didn't force him back. To think that he would insist on continuing his attacks.

Everyone was astonished.

Tyranny's Han Wenqing, who had never known the word "retreat", had backed down in front of Ye Xiu today. But now, it was Ye Xiu who bravely stood his ground in this situation like Han Wenqing would.

A trade!

The pro players watching the match such as Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian, Sun Zheping all saw through it.　　

Apart from the grenades that would disrupt his offense, Ye Xiu would do his best to dodge the grenades while dealing as much damage as possible to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

A trade was a standard group arena method.

What Ye Xiu seeked wasn't a victory this round, but to pave the road to victory for his next teammate.

"Isn't he just trying to make things easier for himself?" Huang Shaotian messaged Yu Wenzhou.

"Maybe..." Yu Wenzhou replied.

Some of the viewers watching were hoping to see Zhang Jiale break open the situation. Others were hoping to see Ye Xiu end the fight in one wave. However, the experts all knew that this round would end in a trade.

Finally, Lord Grim fell. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had 61% of his health left.

Victory?

In the group arena, it was a bit difficult to say who truly won.

Ye Xiu had lost, but he had taken out 39% of his opponent's health, keeping Happy in the lead.

Zhang Jiale had won, but compared to the expectations towards him when he had cornered Lord Grim, the outcome was somewhat disappointing.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo usually gave a summary or a few comments after a round ended, but right now, the two were sidetracking the main topic.

This individual round seemed brilliant and straightforward. Everything had been directly observed by them, but just talking about those points made the two feel they weren't being thorough enough for some reason. What were they missing? The two were puzzled.

As Ye Xiu walked down from the stage, the crowd clapped in approval. This outcome was acceptable, especially that last comeback. It was a bit unfortunate that he wasn't able to take down Zhang Jiale in one wave, but facing these tyrants, hoping for a 1v2 was too much!　　

Who would Happy field next?

The audience applauded as they fixed their gaze on the big screen. They wanted to know who Happy's next player was.　

Mo Fan!

The name appeared.　　

Mo Fan, known as the Godslayer, had a stable position in Happy's group arena line-up. And his style was recognized by many as very suitable for the group arena.

After his name appeared on the big screen, Mo Fan got up and headed towards the stage. Along the way, he walked past Ye Xiu, but none of them said anything. They just nodded to express "I see you".

Pan Lin and Li yibo wasn't sure how to summarize the previous round, so they shifted the subject to the next round.　　

"The Godslayer facing the 61% health Zhang Jiale." Pan Lin said thoughtfully. Though their starting health wasn't even, if Mo Fan won, another name would be added to the Godslayer's list of kills.

Chapter 1489 - Crazy Hundred Blossoms

When Mo Fan came onto the stage, everyone’s first thought was his title Godslayer. Their second thought was the cold and cheerless chat.

For Mo Fan, it wasn’t even a question of not speaking much, he didn’t speak at all. Even Ye Xiu felt astonished because when he first met Mo Fan in the game, it was true that Mo Fan didn’t speak much, but he wasn’t completely silent like he was in real life. It seemed like he was the type who could communicate in virtual worlds, but when it came to real life, he wouldn’t say a word. After he became a pro, he would practically never speak in the game either. Was it because he was so invested into the game that he couldn’t differentiate between fantasy and reality? Ye Xiu didn’t know, and he had no way to ask. Communicating with him was hard!

Soon afterwards, the match began.

Zhang Jiale was the type of player who would occasionally say a few words. In the fight with Ye Xiu, apart from “You come in!”, “You come out!” when the two were stuck, there were no other interactions between the two players. Relatively few words had been spoken that round. This round, facing the taciturn Mo Fan, Zhang Jiale also became quiet.

“There’s surprisingly little talking between the players today!” Li Yibo sighed. He had thought that because Ye Xiu and Tyranny’s old generals had known each other for a long time, there would be quite a bit of trash talking between them. As it turned out, Ye Xiu and Zhang Jiale bickered childishly for a bit and then, that was it.

“There probably won’t be a lot of talking this round,” Pan Lin followed up. Mo Fan never speaking was common knowledge.

The two players remained silent. Both players chose to take the middle road, moving towards the manor, one from the front, one from the back.

“Are all of today’s fights going to be decided in this manor?” Pan Lin joked.

Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms took the same route as the previous round. He went in from the manor’s back door and walked through the rooms in the first floor. Compared to last round, he had a better understanding of the layout of the rooms, so he walked more confidently.

As for Mo Fan? Deception didn’t enter through the main entrance. This time, a real Ninja had taken the field. With skillful ninjato technique, Deception climbed onto the roof.

The further Dazzling Hundred Blossoms went in, the more careful he became. He needed to be ready for the opponent to appear at any moment. Meanwhile, Deception moved along the rooftop swiftly. Just when everyone thought that he would go through the hole in the roof from the Ye Xiu and Qin Muyun battle, he went directly towards the back of the manor. After cautiously peering downwards, he jumped off the roof soundlessly.

Deception had made his way across the manor to where Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had been initially. Then, he went in.

Tyranny’s fans in Xiaoshan Stadium went into an uproar. Going all the way across the manor to circle to the back of the opponent was truly too despicable. Tyranny’s fans looked down on such an action.

Even if they looked down on it, they couldn’t help but worry for Zhang Jiale because Zhang Jiale clearly didn’t realize what had happened. His vision was focused on where Mo Fan might be if he came through the front door.

Mo Fan’s Deception entered the manor and started his search, quickly checking room after room. Deception was slowly getting closer to Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Happy’s fans were excited.

Sneak attacks! It wasn’t possible to kill the opponent in one strike, but the important part was that when the sneak attack came, the opponent would be flustered. To the viewers, it was an enjoyable sight.

Deception was getting closer and closer. Zhang Jiale hadn’t noticed yet. He was on the lookout for Mo Fan, but he had completely ignored his backside.

The doors were opened gently. To avoid startling the snake by beating the grass, the two were careful with their every action. Although the two hadn’t come across each other yet, the two acted like their opponent was in the next room. But this time, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’ opening and closer of the door was caught by Mo Fan.

With a stride forward, Deception had arrived at the door that Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had just closed and gently opened it.

Mo Fan was familiar with the layout of the manor. Once Dazzling Hundred Blossoms entered this room, he probably wouldn’t look back. This room had only one other exit, and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms could only move in that direction.

Deception had activated the Disappearing Body Technique as he rolled into the room. He got up and sprinted soundlessly towards Dazzling Hundred Blossoms as his two hands quickly formed seals.

Ninjutsu – Flickering Pursuit!

Deception became a blur. It was only then did Zhang Jiale notice, but it was too late. Deception struck Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

“Ohhhhhh!!”

The anxiousness, excitement, and suspense that had been pent up when Deception crossed the manor was let out all at once!

This was the thrill of an ambush. This sort of excitement couldn’t be found in any other way.

Empty Cicada Double Kill, Flame Cut, Annihilation!

Deception followed with three consecutive skills, all of them landing and launching Dazzling Hundred Blossom into the air.

But getting hit into the air had actually given Zhang Jiale an opportunity to respond. He immediately dropped a grenade.

Grenades were AoE attacks. As long as Zhang Jiale had a general idea of Deception’s position, it was enough for him to attack.

As for Deception? He dashed and jumped. Then, he borrowed the wall to jump back. This series of fast and fluid movements allowed Deception to dodge Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s grenade.

Damn!

Surprise flashed through Zhang Jiale’s mind. He had been surprised again and again by Ye Xiu. One round later, he was surprised again by another opponent, Happy’s Mo Fan.

Countless flashes of light accompanied his surprise.

Pu pu pu pu!

As Dazzling Hundred Blossoms fell, Deception jumped and stomped on him.

After Storm Shuriken, he followed with a Bird Fall.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms crashed to the ground. The entire room seemed to tremble. After Deception’s BIrd Fall, he wanted to borrow the momentum to run. For him, the combo had been long enough. It was time for him to stop and adjust the tempo.

But the momentum was unexpectedly too much.

Boom!

Deception crashed into the ceiling, but he didn’t immediately start free-falling down. Instead, it was like he was stuck to the ceiling.

To be more precise, he was pushed.

Deception wasn’t the only one pushed. The furnishings in the room were pushed askew. The more fragile objects shattered into pieces.

Implosion Grenade!

The Implosion Grenade had set off at the perfect timing. It had exploded the instant Dazzling Hundred Blossoms fell to the ground. In this room, apart from Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, nothing else was left untouched.

Deception wanted to escape, but because of the push from Implosion Grenade, he was pushed to the ceiling. Because of the limited space, the force from the Implosion Grenade wasn’t able to completely proliferate outwards, which was why Deception was stuck to the ceiling, unable to get down.

It was just for a short instant, but it was enough for Dazzling Hundred Blossoms to shoot who knew how many bullets.

As the bullets flew, a grenade was thrown. In the blink of an eye, Deception was swallowed by the light. Soon afterwards, he was back onto the ground.

But Dazzling Hundred Blossom followed him down. The bullets continued to barrage him. On the ceiling, a charred strawman could be seen. No one gave it another glance, only the broadcast gave it a close-up.

Substitution Technique!

Although Deception was able to get to the ground, he wasn’t able to escape from Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’ pursuit.

The room had two exits. Mo Fan could only look on helplessly at them; his Deception had no way of reaching them. Not only could he not reach them, to reduce the damage he took, he had to retreat away from them.

Similar to what Ye Xiu had experienced last round, the blooming net of gunfire would force the target to the corner. Then, amidst the beautiful blossoms, the target would be killed.

At the end, Ye Xiu was able to borrow Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’ firepower to break a hole through the wall. But Mo Fan? What could Mo Fan do? Ye Xiu’s previous method of escaping wouldn’t work a second time. Zhang Jiale wasn’t stupid.

Mo Fan could only rely on his own methods.

Deception suddenly retreated back all the way. He hadn’t been forced to do so, it was a display of attitude.

Zhang Jiale promptly adjusted his aim. This short window was an opening for Mo Fan.

An opening that let Deception finish several hand seals.

Ninjutsu – Shadow Dance!

Mo Fan was able to complete the hand seals for a Level 70 skill in just an instant. One Deception turned into ten. The one that had been in the corner was instantly swallowed by the blinding light.

It wasn’t a big room. For claustrophobic viewers, these ten identical clones made them feel nauseous.

“He’s going to use the chaos to run!” Pan Lin shouted.

“Using a high-level skill just to escape, Mo Fan is quite wasteful,” Li Yibo sighed. For a scrap picker, safety was number one. It didn’t matter what had to be used to guarantee his safety, it would be worth it.

Ten Deceptions. Which one was real? There was no way to tell because the Heart of Shadow Dance could be switched around at any time. Zhang Jiale ‘s only choice seemed to be to guard those two exits. But the other side wasn’t just going to line up and rush towards those two exits to die! If Deception used a few attacks to harass Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, wouldn’t that make it easier for him to escape?

How difficult! The Tyranny fans acted as if they were in Zhang Jiale’s position. Their brows were furrowed, and they looked as if they were at wit’s end. But then, they saw the entire room blossom with light…

If it was said that in the previous round, no one was able to see that crazy Hundred Blossoms style, then in this round, everyone saw a Hundred Blossoms that was even crazier than in their imaginations.

The entire room filled with light. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms? Ten Deceptions? All that remained were blurry silhouettes.

The projection technology could intelligently remove objects blocking the viewers’ sights, but it did not obstruct the visual effects from the characters’ attacks…

Who cared if there were ten Deceptions? Who cared if there were two exits? Who cared about enemy harass?

He would simply strike at every corner of the room, leaving Deception no place to hide.

Even though he had returned to his roots, that didn’t mean he had forgotten that wildness from those two and a half seasons.

A hundred blossoms to burn away everything in his path. At that time, he had believed in it!

And now, when he needed it, he wouldn’t give up on trying it.

The three summers of wild blossoms, which had once attempted to burn everything down, bloomed again in this little room.

Chapter 1490 - Escape Isn't the Goal

It was as if a flash grenade had been thrown at the audience. Trying to figure out what those blurry figures were doing amidst the dazzling light required rich experience.

Zhang Jiale’s experience at doing so was second to none. If the Hundred Blossoms Style blinded even him, then that would be heaven’s biggest joke.

Several blurry figures instantly vanished. It just looked like random flashes, but there was purpose behind each flash. No matter how skilled Zhang Jiale was, there was no way for him to use a single skill to cover all four corners simultaneously. The light that enshrouded the room, whether real, fake, attacks, or feints, was carefully arranged by Zhang Jiale.

Unable to differentiate between what was real and what was fake, how could Mo Fan’s Deception escape?

Practically no one believed he could. They couldn’t even see what was happening inside as spectators. How could Mo Fan fare any better?

They were gravely mistaken.

Mo Fan was completely different from them, and the one who felt it most clearly was Mo Fan’s opponent, Zhang Jiale.

The hundred blossoms had only just bloomed, when he noticed that Mo Fan had started making adjustments towards his shadow clones.

The viewers had vaguely observed that several shadows had vanished in an instant.

It was four!

Zhang Jiale knew the exact number.

Then, another four.

Mo Fan was trying to break apart Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s offense. He didn’t get confused by the blinding light, quickly figuring out what was real and what was not.

For most viewers, everything was a blur to them.

But to Mo Fan, this chaos wasn’t nearly enough to confuse him.

He had faced countless chaotic situations before. This chaos was never from just one or two people, but a group of them.

When he had searched for a way to escape from predicaments as a scrap picker, the obstructions weren’t from just one or two classes, but rather a variety of classes.

Chaotic?

Not at all!

Mo Fan’s life as a scrap picker had been chaotic. Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms style had structure.

Four shadows split apart, and then another four.

“Damn!” Mo Fan had surprised Zhang Jiale again.

His Hundred Blossoms encirclement had been broken through, and the reason was because his attacks had structure to them.

And the structure had been grasped by Mo Fan.

If Ye Xiu had done it, perhaps Zhang Jiale wouldn’t have been so surprised, but he was currently facing a young rookie.

“The kid’s got talent in this area!” Sun Zheping smiled from the audience. He was no longer teammates with Zhang Jiale. Otherwise, he would have certainly warned Zhang Jiale. Mo Fan’s skill at escaping was far greater than anyone could imagine. Even with the Hundred Blossoms style, trying to trap him would require even more focus. Mo Fan had grown in chaos.

Scrap picker…

Sun Zheping also felt interested, thinking of Mo Fan’s background. There had never been any pro players now or in the past who had that sort of background.

It was the result of a person training what they were best at in the most suitable environment for them. The outcome was superb and didn’t lack individuality. It wasn’t something that could be molded from the pipeline-like training camps of the pro Clubs.

He possessed godlike skill in his expertise. When Sun Zheping had been at Happy, he and Ye Xiu had privately acknowledged it. And at that time, Mo Fan couldn’t even fit in with the team!

Now, he was expanding his expertise. Not only would it be used for scrap picking, but for PvP on the pro stage.

If he became more all-rounded and flexible, not like how rigid his playstyle was right now, a God of a new generation would certainly appear.

But… with his personality, would he be able to round out his playstyle? When Sun Zheping had been in Happy, Ye Xiu had already been worried about this issue.

But even if it didn’t turn out to be successful, Mo Fan would still be a formidable player.

Godslayer?

That wasn’t a coincidence or a joke.

When the battle shifted towards his domain, he could crush even Gods.

“If he doesn’t notice this, he’ll definitely be eaten!” Sun Zheping thought in his heart.

On stage.

Ka.

The sound of a door opening.

Inside and outside were two different worlds.

One side was chaotic, the other side was calm.

Deception had reached the outside. He had escaped to the calm side.

The crowd cheered loudly.

“Godslayer!!” Happy’s fans shouted excitedly. It was as if Mo Fan wasn’t escaping from a predicament, but rather that he had killed his opponent in one hit. Their cheers also showed just how nervous Happy’s fans had been.

Tyranny’s fans sighed, seeing his astonishing escape.

To think he could escape, and to think it would be so normal, opening the door and running out.

Was Zhang Jiale too old? He couldn’t even suppress a rookie? Quite a few people had these sort of thoughts. Even Pan Lin and Li Yibo wanted to say it, but in the end, they only said that Zhang Jiale was a bit slower than Mo Fan.

Why was he slower? Because he was getting old… the two didn’t say these words.

But Sun Zheping laughed.

He didn’t care who won or lost this match, but when he saw his former teammate performing well, he couldn’t help but smile.

“How steady.” Sun Zheping’s gaze was focused on Dazzling Hundred Blossoms and the light that hadn’t yet dissipated.

Mo Fan was able to find an opening in the hundred blossoms through his scrap-picking skills.

But he was no longer a scrap picker. He was a pro player, and he was constantly fixing his habits.

As a result, besides escaping, he had another choice.

Attack the opponent.

Escape didn’t mean he won. The only way to win was to kill the opponent. Mo Fan knew this point clearly. Gradually, killing the opponent became a higher priority than escaping.

When he had broken through the chaos, Mo Fan’s first thought was no longer to escape, but to use the opening he saw to attack his opponent!

But this time, he had chosen Deception to escape because he couldn’t find an opportunity to attack. After the disturbances from the eight shadows, a huge adjustment was made to the hundred blossoms.

It still covered the room and alternated between real and fake.

However, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had erected an impenetrable defense.

As a result, Mo Fan could not choose to attack. He could only run away.

The two players knew of this detail and so did the pro players watching. But besides them, the rest were discussing how Zhang Jiale was slower.

Zhang Jiale, who they had just commented on being slow, suddenly sped up. The light and shadow from the Hundred Blossoms style seemed to flow out of that door to the next room.

Kakakaka…

The shockwaves kept pushing the door. It wanted to close but it could never close, constantly making an uncomfortable noise.

Deception was hastily running away. Mo Fan hadn’t thought that Zhang Jiale would chase after him so quickly.

But a few steps later, he realized that not only was his opponent pursuing him quickly, his opponent was pursuing him closely.

Bullets, grenades, explosions, smoke, light, all of these seemed to be following him as if they were stuck to Deception’s feet.

In countless hero movies, there was always a hero who ran around freely amidst a field of explosions, but the explosions would never hit.

Deception was running madly, but the explosions kept following him. If this were a movie, the audience would have probably left their seats by now, seeing these narrow escapes again and again.

I can’t get him off of me!

Mo Fan was surprised.

This was what he was best at, but right now, he couldn’t get away from the pursuit.

The dazzling light was like a wave that swept away everything behind Deception.

Mo Fan’s Deception couldn’t stop. He even felt like there wasn’t enough time to look back.

On the pro stage, there were at most 5v5 team battles, which couldn’t compare to the chaos that a scrap picker experienced in the game.

However, he had never experienced such a crazed pursuit in the game.

He couldn’t stop even for a second. If he stopped, the light would swallow him. Although Mo Fan had successfully escaped from that encirclement, that didn’t mean he could replicate that success. Both sides were people, not NPCs. Just because it worked once didn’t mean it would work again.

I need to get away…

Mo Fan seemed to have returned to the former days, where he would have countless people chasing after him. But he was sure that even in those situations, he had never felt such pressure before.

Mo Fan’s Deception had been able to escape from those situations again and again.

But this time, facing this one person’s pursuit, Mo Fan’s Deception fell.

“Escape isn’t the goal. The only goal is to beat the opponent…” Sun Zheping sighed in his heart. He was happy about Zhang Jiale’s outstanding plays. But he also felt regret seeing Mo Fan’s defeat.

Zhang Jiale, 1v2! He had beaten a half-health Ye Xiu and the “Godslayer” Mo Fan. The advantage that Ye Xiu had established was wiped away. Now, Team Tyranny had a 27% health advantage in this group arena.

The stadium was silent. Happy’s fans hadn’t expected this outcome. In the end, Zhang Jiale was able to chase Mo Fan down to his death. This was their home field, yet they were lagging behind.

At this moment, Happy’s third player stood up.

“It looks like it’s my time to shine!” Fang Rui said.

Chapter 1491 - Cloud Wind Body

Lost?

It wasn’t Mo Fan’s first time losing, but the loss this time stunned him. He had been chased to death by his opponent for 2 minutes 34 seconds. He had everything he could think of, yet he had still failed to escape.

He went out of the player booth slowly and walked down from the stage slowly. As he passed Fang Rui, he made no reaction towards Fang Rui’s “I’ll take revenge for you”.

When he returned to his seats and passed by Ye Xiu, he heard Ye Xiu say: “Your thoughts are still too single minded.”

Some people’s play styles were too single minded. Some people’s techniques were too single minded. As for Mo Fan, Ye Xiu criticized him for his thoughts being too single minded.

Mo Fan didn’t reply back. He sat down at his seat in the corner and reflected on these words.

Fang Rui received a warm welcome from Happy’s fans. As they cheered, he strutted around as if Happy wasn’t the team falling behind right now.

He walked onto the stage, waving his hands towards the crowd as if he had won. It was only until the referee rushed over and berated him did he go into the player booth dejectedly.

The crowd laughed.

The tense atmosphere from Zhang Jiale’s 1v2 had lightened considerably.

The match began.

The public chat had been very calm previously, but Fang Rui’s presence changed that.

“How mighty! 1v2!” Fang Rui gave praise towards Zhang Jiale.

“It’s not over yet!” Zhang Jiale replied.

“It pretty much is,” Fang Rui said.

As the two chatted, their characters moved.

The middle road again. There was plenty of content spread throughout the map, but up until now, all of them had taken place inside the central manor.

Every fight had been spectacular though, so there were no complaints from the viewers. On the other hand, Pan Lin and Li Yibo were analyzing Happy’s reasons for choosing this map. So far, it looked like Happy’s players were more comfortable because of their familiarity with the map, but it hadn’t given them any definite advantage yet. Of course, there were a lot of factors in winning a match. Relying on the home game advantage was just one factor.

Boundless Sea and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms quickly reached the front and back of the manor, respectively.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms didn’t hesitate and went through the rear door. Zhang Jiale had made the same choice in all three of his fights.

As for Boundless Sea? Fang Rui looked to have a plan in mind. He opened the front door and strolled leisurely into the manor as if he were here to tour the place.

But the more attentive viewers had noticed that Boundless Sea’s mana was dropping steadily.

He had evidently activated a skill that continuously drained his mana.

What was it?

“Cloud Wind Body!” Pan Lin shouted out.

Cloud Wind Body was a Qi Master high-level scouting skill. In the game, there would be a radar-like map in his view. When a character entered its range, the user would receive a notification.

But if that was all it did, the skill’s value was too worthless compared to the mana it consumed. Cloud Wind Body increased the user’s perception and also gave the user more precise control over their qi. “More precise control” meant auto targeting.

This effect seemed too amazing, but in reality, very few Qi Masters chose to use Cloud Wind Body. Sure, auto targeting was nice, but that didn’t mean the user attacked any faster. Their attacks could still be interrupted. In the majority of Qi Masters’ eyes, the low-level Reinforced Iron Bones was more practical.

In the team competition against Blue Rain, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had relied on Reinforced Iron Bones at a crucial moment to great success. But in today’s match, he had chosen to use a high mana consumption skill like Cloud Wind Body, but the effects weren’t anything impressive.

“Fang Rui isn’t hesitating to use Cloud Wind Body to quickly locate Dazzling Hundred Blossoms… it doesn’t seem necessary?” Pan Lin had his doubts. It was a 1v1 group arena. There was no need to quickly kill the opponent. Fang Rui didn’t need to be so impatient.

Li Yibo didn’t say anything. Although he had the same doubts as Pan Lin, he decided that it would be better to wait and observe some more before further analysis.

Boundless Sea still looked like he was touring around the manor leisurely with Cloud Wind Body activated, but his movement speed had clearly increased. He wanted to minimize the mana consumption.

The viewers with their omniscient view watched as the two characters gradually drew nearer, but because of the walls, neither side could see each other. However, with Cloud Wind Body activated, he could use qi to sense his surroundings. On his radar, a little blip had appeared representing Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Fang Rui didn’t immediately launch an attack like the everyone had thought he would. Instead, his movements made everyone confused.

“Does he want to ambush Zhang Jiale?” Pan Lin guessed. Fang Rui’s signature style was being dirty. An ambush was nothing surprising for him.

Li Yibo remained silent. He looked at Boundless Sea’s movements but couldn’t see any places for him to set up an ambush. But if he wasn’t going for an ambush, what else could he be doing?

Just when he asked this question to himself, Boundless Sea suddenly stopped. On his radar, Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’ little dot was clearly moving. Boundless Sea raised his hands and gathered qi.

“This is… Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow?” Pan Lin noted.

The Qi Master’s Awakening skill, Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, gathered qi and circulated it throughout the body. Boundless Sea’s clothes looked to be fluttering violently in the wind as his entire body seemed to ignite into flames.

“What is he doing? He wants to attack from there?” Pan Lin was utterly confused. Boundless Sea and Dazzling Hundred Blossoms were separated by a wall. There was no door on this wall. There was no way for him to launch a sneak attack!

Li Yibo’s heart trembled.

“Zoom in!” He called out to the broadcast director.

The camera zoomed in, but Li Yibo’s gaze wasn’t on Boundless Sea, but the wall in front.

The large section of the wall paper was peeling off. The bricks that could be seen were covered with cracks.

This was damage left over from the previous two battles. Attacks from Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Lord Grim, or Deception might have landed here. Li Yibo couldn’t remember right now, but he knew that this wall had already been damaged heavily. Fang Rui’s ambush would succeed because Boundless Sea’s attack would pierce through this wall, and Zhang Jiale probably wasn’t aware of it.

The dot on the radar continued to move towards this area.

Boundless Sea’s clothes continued to flutter wildly even making some sound, but this sound wasn’t loud enough to pass through the wall for Zhang Jiale to hear.

Closer…

Everyone knew what was about to happen. They could already picture it in their heads. The broadcast had already found the most suitable viewing angle.

The dot flashed again.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms and Boundless Sea were now as close as possible.

Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow!

Fang Rui didn’t disappoint and attacked. The qi gathered in his body poured out. With a boom, the wall collapsed.

Zhang Jiale was startled. Boundless Sea’s Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow tore through the wall, the glaring light flying towards him.

Roll!

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms rolled to the side.

It was a conditioned reflex for an experienced pro player to roll facing a dangerous situation where there was no time to think.

However, no matter how fast he moved, he couldn’t escape from the system’s auto-targeting.

The Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow adjusted in the air according to Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s movements and crashed into him. The focused qi instantly exploded. It wasn’t just beautiful, it also dealt frightening damage. The nearby ornaments instantly shattered.

Up until Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow hit the target, Fang Rui didn’t deactivate his Cloud Wind Body, so the skill would automatically lock onto the target. Zhang Jiale’s instinctive reaction was no match for the system’s auto-targeting.

But because of the wall, the damage from the attack had lessened. The attack only took away 6% of Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s health.

But this was just the start of Boundless Sea’s attacks.

After a Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, he instantly closed the distance. Once the qi scattered from the explosion, silence didn’t follow. Before the qi completely scattered, a new wave of qi shot out from Boundless Sea’s palms.

Time seemed to have frozen. All people could see was Boundless Sea’s surging qi raging thunderously in this little room. Finally, when everything became peaceful again, the system announced: Glory!

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had won!

The audience was dumbfounded.

A full health Fang Rui bringing down a 27% health Zhang Jiale wasn’t surprising. The surprise was from the way he did it.

Ambush to death in one combo.

Was this dirty or tyrannical? No one was sure.

You could say it was dirty, but that explosive burst of qi was very heroic. You could say that it was tyrannical, but hiding behind a wall and gathering qi was very dirty…

In any case, Happy had won this round. It was a clean victory, chasing back the advantage that Zhang Jiale had gained. If Fang Rui’s previous interactions with the crowd had eased the crowd’s tension, then his dominating performance this round was a tranquilizer to Happy’s fans. After the shock from such a clean victory, Happy’s fans recovered. Their excited cheers resonated throughout the entire Xiaoshan Stadium.

Chapter 1492 - Harmony

Zhang Jiale left the player booth. Despite the cheers for his defeat, he was calm. This loss was too insignificant for him. There was no loser in Glory more pitiful than him.

Zhang Jiale walked down slowly from the stage. The cheers from the crowd continued, accompanied with quite a few boos towards him as well. After his return, his popularity had dropped considerably.

Team Tyranny’s third player stood up from his seat. The display on the big screen amptly switched to an image of the player and character.

Lin Jingyan, Brawler, Dark Thunder.

He had been a part of Tyranny for two whole years, but even now, whenever Lin Jingyan saw his name alongside his character Dark Thunder, he would always feel a sense of unfamiliarity.

Three Hits. In the end, he couldn’t forget the name of the Brawler that he had traveled through wind and rain with for seven years. Even though the two of them had never obtained any glorious achievements, he would always feel at peace controlling that character.

Two years ago, that peace was finally broken.

At the end of his career, Lin Jingyan became a drifting leaf, finally settling at Tyranny.

Lin Jingyan was grateful for Tyranny. During his most bitter moments, the team had looked highly upon him. He had decided that he would give the final light of his career to Tyranny. But in the end, what was different was different.

Lin Jingyan, Dark Thunder.

As Lin Jingyan walked, he looked at the name on the screen and then, at his opponent, Fang Rui, Qi Master, Boundless Sea.

Lin Jingyan suddenly laughed.

The fate of these two brothers were so similar! A different name accompanied Fang Rui too. Fang Rui had even switched classes. Lin Jingyan didn’t only feel uncomfortable looking at the name Dark Thunder. He also felt uncomfortable looking at the name Boundless Sea.

Fang Rui, Thief, Doubtful Demon.

It was almost like he could see these names in front of him.

Lin Jingyan shook his head. Am I getting too nostalgic?

“Take revenge for me.” Zhang Jiale said as he passed by him.

“I’ll do my best!” Lin Jingyan smiled.

“Good luck!” Zhang Jiale didn’t say anything else.

Lin Jingyan walked onto the stage and entered the player booth. He swiped his card and loaded into the match. He had repeated these motions who knew how many times in these nine years, seven years with Three Hits, two years with Dark Thunder.

Dark Thunder…

Lin Jingyan repeated the name of his character again. He loaded into the map, and the match officially began.

Both characters took the middle road again.

The audience was getting a little restless. Wasn’t this the sixth round of the group arena already? Up until now, no player had taken a roundabout route. All of them went straight towards the center. The manor wasn’t a manor anymore, but an arena.

Then, one player at the front of the manor, while the other player at the back of the manor. Except, this time, the two players finally chose to do something new!

Not through the door, or onto the walls!

Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder went counterclockwise from the back of the manor, while Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea went counterclockwise from the front of the manor.

Dark Thunder arrived at the front of the manor. Boundless Sea arrived at the back of the manor. Then, the two went in cautiously through the door.

Everyone was speechless.

These two former partners had become opponents, yet the two were still in harmony? You’re circling around? I’ll circle around. You’re going counterclockwise? I’ll go counterclockwise. You’re going through the door? I’ll go through the door…

The two characters tiptoed their way through the manor as if they were mirrors of each other.

The audience was helpless. They could only wait for the two to run into each other.

But it was as if these two guys had made an agreement not to meet. The two had wandered through the first floor of the manor for a minute, yet neither side saw even a glimpse of the other.

Afterwards, the two seemed to be tired. The crouched down at a corner and took a breather.

At this moment, the public chat was put to use.

“Hey, are you in the manor?” Fang Rui asked.

“Yeah!” Lin Jingyan replied. He didn’t ask the same question back. The way Fang Rui asked the question made it clear that he was in the manor too.

“How did you start the match?” Fang Rui went straight to the point.

“I circled around to the front.” Lin Jingyan went straight to the point.

The playoffs was a death match, yet the two were chatting so nonchalantly. It was as if this was normal day-to-day practice.

“Fuck.” Fang Rui cursed. The referee immediately jumped out, giving him a yellow card. Swear words were not permitted.

Lin Jingyan immediately understood. He didn’t need to ask. Fang Rui had definitely circled around to the back. Their actions were equivalent to swapping positions. They had the same thought: avoid getting caught and carefully scout the surroundings. I avoid you, you avoid me, and so the two went in circles, unable to find each other.

“Keep going!” Lin jingyan was determined to resolve this predicament. Both sides were incomparably familiar with each other’s habits and thoughts. To out-predict the other, just predicting one step ahead wouldn’t be enough because the other side would also predict one step ahead. As a result, neither of them would be able to get the right prediction.

Dark Thunder stood up from the corner, taking the lead. Lin Jingyan switched perspectives imagining what Fang Rui would do next. Then, he would formulate a plan through deeper reads.

The two characters started going in circles again.

Another minute passed. This time, the two didn’t disappoint them. The two players met at the spiraling staircase. The encounter wasn’t sudden, instead seeming very natural, as if the two had agreed to rendezvous here at a certain time. The two took their own paths and finally met.

Finally, some fighting. The viewers thoughts to themselves.

But the two just stared at each other.

To think they would bump into each other here.

What did that mean? It meant the two were still in harmony. They had a deep understanding of each other, so they tried to out-predict each other. But in the end, their predictions were at the same depth.

“XX!” Fang Rui cursed, typing XX.

The corner of the referee’s mouth twitched. XX wasn’t a violation of the rules, but it was obvious that the XX had the same meaning as “fuck”. Fang Rui didn’t say any profanities, but he got the idea across.

The two stared at each other for a good three seconds. Besides Fang Rui’s “XX”, neither said anything. Suddenly, the two acted simultaneously.

Qi Bullet!

Sand Toss!

Each player used a long-ranged skill. They launched their attacks at the same time and dodged at the same time. In the end, neither side was hit by the other’s attack.

Again!

Brawler and Qi Master went back and forth, putting up an intense fight.

Everyone watching could feel their jaws drop.

Was this a fight? Or was this a synchronized show?

Attack, dodge, the two mirrored each other perfectly. You missed, I missed. They went back and forth, appearing more like a dance than a battle.

“Ahem!” After half a minute, Lin Jingyan typed a word into the chat. Dark Thunder’s offense suddenly halted. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea also stopped.

They realized where the issue lay.

Even though they were good friends, this was the playoffs. They had a responsibility as pro players to help their team win, so they used their familiarity with their opponent, hoping to turn it into a weapon. But since the two had a similar level of understanding of each other, the decision that they made were pretty much the same. Their familiarity didn’t become a weapon, instead neutralizing any threat between them.

The deep understanding between the two of them obstructed their fight.

This wasn’t a good feeling.

They were proud of their deep understanding of each other, but in this match, it became their obstacle. To win this fight, they needed to see who could get rid of this connection, the connection of their past.

Another three second pause and then, attack!

The Brawler’s tricks and the Qi Master’s qi collided.

The two started getting hit.

You punched me, I’ll brick you.

The fight was intense, but to the more skilled players, it was unbearably rough.

This was a match that required understanding of their background. The roughness was because of their familiarity, because both sides knew each other too well, making what methods they had unusable.

Instead, attacking without any skill would achieve better results.

They weren’t supporting each other anymore. Instead, they schemed, plotted, and set up traps…

Many players with partners couldn’t bear to keep watching.

What a cruel competition. To win, the two turned their former understanding and complete trust in one another into all sorts of sinister schemes.

Huang Shaotian, who had been communicating with Yu Wenzhou throughout the match through text, fell silent.

Sun Zheping, Zhang Jiale, Han Wenqing, Zhang Xinjie, Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng… all of these people knew what it meant to be “partners”, but these former partners were destroying everything they had established before.

For victory.

For glory.

Every player had many restraints, but for their dreams, they had no choice but to ruthlessly cut off these restraints.

As time passed, their health bars dropped. The people who understood the match didn’t want to analyze the details. Only people who didn’t understand cheered according to the ups and downs of the player that they supported.

No matter how cruel it was, all things came to an end.

No matter how unwilling you were, in the end, there would only ever be one standing in the end.

Fang Rui, Qi Master, Boundless Sea.

In the end, the screen left only a single name. Lin Jingyan, Brawler, Dark Thunder turned dim as his time was over.

The crowd cheered for Fang Rui and for Happy’s win.

The pro players, watching in the stadium, stood up and applauded. They applauded for a match that didn’t have any impressive or brilliant plays.

They applauded for the mutual understanding between the two players, for their determination to win.

They applauded for their everlasting ambition to be the champions, an ambition that would always be worthy of pride.

Chapter 1493 - Referee Assistance

In the end, I still lost!

Lin Jingyan sighed as he walked out from the player booth.

Although it was a pity, he didn’t feel upset. Losing to Fang Rui was an acceptable outcome.

After all, he was in his declining years, while Fang Rui was at his peak.

In terms of getting rid of the past, it had been two years, yet he still could not forget his Demon Subduer. As for Fang Rui? He had even switched classes. Fang Rui had evidently been more decisive than him in this matter.

I really have turned old, while Fang Rui has a long road ahead of him left!

Looking towards Happy’s seats on the other side, Lin Jingyan felt it was a pity that this was a group arena. Fang Rui was not allowed to leave his seat until his role was over. Lin Jingyan wanted to use this opportunity to give Fang Rui his well wishes; he didn’t know if the two of them would ever have another chance to face against each other again on this stage.

After gazing in silence at that side for awhile, Lin Jingyan walked down from the stage. His well wishes could only remain in his heart.

Good luck, my friend!

With the end of this fight, the group arena was at the halfway mark. Happy had three players left, including Fang Rui. Tyranny only had two players left.

As Lin Jingyan walked down from the stage, Tyranny’s fourth player stood up.

Tyranny’s Song Qiying, a Striker rookie. He had joined this season, steadily maturing. It seemed that he would be Desert Smoke’s successor. And in this important playoffs stage, Tyranny had the confidence to send him onto the stage. Tyranny was not Happy. They had other options besides a rookie. Even so, Song Qiying had been fielded as Tyranny’s important fourth player in the group arena; the team’s intent to raise him could clearly be seen.

However, placing him in this position didn’t mean he was the anchor of this group arena. From a certain perspective, fielding him as the fourth player showed Tyranny’s attitude towards this group arena.

“Tyranny’s fourth player is Song Qiying! It seems that Tyranny had no plans of ending this group arena with their fourth player!” Pan Lin immediately started to analyze this arrangement. In the playoffs, the fourth player was oftentimes the team’s core player, trying to win the group arena 4-5 to take a two point lead into the team competition. The more aggressive teams would even place their core player third to take a three point lead.

But Tyranny had placed Song Qiying fourth. It was likely that their fifth player would be their core, captain Han Wenqing. That would be the most appropriate arrangement.

Li Yibo had come from Tyranny, and Tyranny’s captain and core player had been Han Wenqing for all ten years. The team’s captain hadn’t changed, and the team’s core hadn’t changed. As a result, it was hard for the team’s temperament to change. Even though Li Yibo had left Tyranny many years ago, he still had a good grasp of the team. But today, Han Wenqing avoided Ye Xiu and didn’t even take the fourth position, instead fielding Song Qiying.

The more familiar one was with the team, the more strange it felt encountering something unexpected. When Pan Lin raised the discussion, Li Yibo stared blankly for a long time before replying: “Away teams will often play more conservatively!”

It was a standard response. Li Yibo had lost confidence in analyzing Tyranny as former Tyranny player. The Tyranny today felt too different.

“Well, let’s see how Song Qiying performs! It’s also quite a coincidental matchup. When Song Qiying first appeared this season, he had to face Happy’s Fang Rui,” Pan Lin said, “But… Fang Rui shouldn’t last much longer.”

It could be said that Fang Rui had achieved a 1v2. He took down Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, using quite a bit of mana. After that, even though he won against Lin Jingyan, it had been a bloody fight. Boundless Sea only had 14% of his health and 11% of his mana left. He was an arrow at the end of his flight.

“Winning for Fang Rui will be difficult, but with Fang Rui’s methods, if Song Qiying is too careless, he’ll suffer the consequences,” Li Yibo said.

“It’s unlikely that he’ll be careless, no?” Pan Lin chuckled.

Li Yibo laughed as well.

The current Song Qiying was no longer the same Song Qiying as when he first fought Fang Rui. It had been an entire season. As one of the favorites to win the title Best Rookie, Song Qiying had received much attention. Although he looked to be Desert Smoke’s successor, his personality was quite similar to Tyranny’s vice captain, Zhang Xinjie. He was careful and meticulous. He was young, but with his personality, how could he be careless?

The match began as the two commentators discussed this issue. Song Qiying met their expectations. The match had just started, and his attitude towards the upcoming fight could already be seen.

As he traveled, it didn’t matter whether the battle would reach these areas, he would still carefully observe them. His line of sight constantly shifted left and right.

However, the route he chose was still the middle road. The viewers had given up on seeing a battle in water or a forest in this map because the manor at the center of the map had indoor rooms, which meant protection to a certain extent. Taking a roundabout route towards the manor had no meaning in this map, which was why neither of the two teams made that sort of choice.

One player towards the front of the manor, one player towards the back of the manor. The two players met again in the manor for the seventh time.

For someone with a cautious and strict personality like Zhang Xinjie, Song Qiying had probably thought out his plan for this fight before he even got onto the stage. When Song Qiying made it to the back of the manor, he didn’t go through the back door nor did he jump onto the roof. Instead, he adeptly searched for a window and went in.

The two teams had fought several rounds all inside the manor. Tyranny had a good idea of the structure of the manor by now.

When he jumped through the window, he immediately turned up, left, right, checking his surroundings. Song Qiying quickly grasped his present situation.

He didn’t see Boundless Sea. Afterwards, it looked like he already knew what to do as River Sunset walked towards the right corridor. When he reached the second door along the corridor, he went in. He moved step by step as if he were following steps in a guide.

Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea was inside the manor too. He didn’t have much health nor mana, how could he openly welcome his opponent? Last round, he took a roundabout route to the back of the manor, but he was too in harmony with Lin Jingyan. He didn’t want to use the same method twice though, so he had Boundless Sea climb onto the walls of the manor. He didn’t climb to the roof, instead climbing onto a balcony and entering the manor through the second floor.

The second floor was much more intact than the first floor. Only two battles had taken place here. Ye Xiu and Qin Muyun had fought here. Ye Xiu had launched a surprise attack onto Zhang Jiale here too, but the aftermath of it was just a hole in the floor.

Fang Rui had Boundless Sea move towards that hole. When he reached the hole, he took a look at the surroundings. After picking a spot, his Boundless Sea crouched down.

Crouch…

Guarding a tree-stump and waiting for rabbits. In vast open maps, this sort of ambush tactic rarely worked. It only had value if you knew the target’s pathing. But Fang Rui hadn’t done any investigation, yet he still went straight for this hole and crouched there…

Everyone started wondering when a system notification would come.

If someone just sat there patiently not caring if the opponent actually came or not, how long would the match take? As a result, the Glory had rules to prevent it. The referee could judge according to the circumstances whether the player was complying with the rules and then interfere if necessary.

Of course, there needed to be some concrete rules too. The referee couldn’t just start interfering as soon as a character hid behind a corner. The referee could interfere after no target was seen for 18 seconds.

The players familiar with Glory’s rules started helping Fang Rui count.

They were familiar with the rules. How could the master of playing dirty Fang Rui not be either? When it became 17 seconds, Boundless Sea switched postures.

Glory’s referees weren’t machines. This sort of clever loophole in the rules could be denied based on their own subjective views. However, it looked like the referee was okay with Fang Rui’s cleverness and didn’t interfere after 18 seconds.

Boos started coming from the crowd, from Tyranny’s fans. Tyranny’s loyal fans were familiar with the rules. They started booing at the referee because they felt that the referee was being biased towards the home team.

The referee ignored them because the boos were quickly suppressed by the applause. Tyranny’s fans wouldn’t be able to affect a referee’s decision. This was Happy’s home stadium.

“Fang Rui only switched postures. His goal hasn’t changed. Isn’t this violating the 18 second rule for sitting and waiting?” Pan Lin called the referee’s decision into question.

“The referee can make decisions based on his own discretion. First, the two characters are inside the manor, greatly reducing the search area and increasing the chances that Fang Rui’s patience will pay off. Second, Song Qiying’s River Sunset is very close by. It’s very likely that he’ll walk into Fang Rui’s range. My guess is that the referee acknowledged the increased success rate, so he judged that it was fair and didn’t interfere. If Song Qiying chooses to break away from his current route, my guess is that the referee will probably interfere,” Li Yibo was quite knowledgeable about the referee’s thought process.

“I see… but from a certain perspective, by not interfering, isn’t the referee leaking information to the player?” Pan Lin said.

Li Yibo stared blankly. When he looked at the match again, Boundless Sea was no longer crouching, but standing up. Qi was gathering in his palms. However, he couldn’t actually see any traces of River Sunset, yet he was already preparing his ambush as if he knew River Sunset was coming.

Silly referee, his decision seemed very rational, based on the circumstances of the match, but Fang Rui exploited it.

This master of playing dirty took advantage of the rules. Seeing that the referee didn’t interfere, he judged that Song Qiying must be nearing his ambush location.

Chapter 1494 - Heroes Come From the Young

“What guts!” Pan Lin cried out.

The dirty style gave people a feeling of despicableness without any sense of heroism. Fang Rui crouching and waiting there was quite despicable, but exploiting the referee was extremely daring. He already had a yellow card, yet he still dared to challenge the referee.

“That’s why he made a movement after 17 seconds,” Li Yibo said, “He was giving himself a buffer for the punishment. If he was punished, because of this movement, he would only receive a warning and not a yellow card.

“But what if Song Qiying doesn’t end up coming over? Then, would the referee directly give him a yellow card?” Pan Lin asked.

“We’ll know soon.” Li Yibo was wise. Why would he guess when the answer would be known soon?

On stage…

Qi gathered around the palms of Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea, but this time, he wasn’t charging a Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow. With Spirit Reaches to the Rainbow, he would crash into his opponent alongside the qi. He had been facing Zhang Jiale’s Spitfire previously, so he was not afraid. But now, he was facing a Striker, the number one close combat class, throwing himself at the opponent was risky; it could turn into a situation similar to throwing a steamed bun at a hungry dog.

Boundless Sea didn’t have much health or mana. Fang Rui was extremely cautious. He didn’t want to make any risky moves. As a result, he gathered qi in his palms and prepared to shoot a Sky-Piercing Cannon.

Fang Rui couldn’t see Song Qiying’s River Sunset yet, but the viewers watching could could see him. Sure enough, River Sunset was making his way over step by step.

“Careful!” Tyranny’s fans couldn’t help but be anxious. Even though Boundless Sea was an arrow at the end of its flight, a successful ambush could result in heavy injuries to River Sunset.

One step a time. Fang Rui’s perspective was displayed on the big screen in the stadium. A small window showing Fang Rui’s perspective, could be seen in the broadcast as well.

But at this moment, Song Qiying’s line of sight suddenly shifted.

His gaze was fixed on that hole in the ceiling.

Tyranny’s fans felt excited upon seeing this sight, while Happy’s fans were feeling gloomy.

Had Fang Rui been discovered?

The fans on both sides sighed, but for different reasons.

No, not yet!” Li Yibo stated with certainty.

“Song Qiying is only aware that it’s a possibility,” Pan Lin shouted.

How could the careful Song Qiying neglect such an important detail? Even though he didn’t know that Fang Rui really was lying in wait there, he was completely prepared for the possibility of it.

Qi Bullet!

River Sunset sent out a probing attack.

Qi Bullet was a low-level Qi Master skill and could be used by all Fighter classes. River Sunset had learned it, but it clearly hadn’t been leveled very high. There didn’t seem to be much qi swirling inside the Qi Bullet.

Even so, it shot accurately towards the hole in the ceiling and crashed into the edges of the hole. It didn’t make much of a sound before dissipating.

Boundless Sea didn’t move.

Fang Rui wasn’t fooled by this probing attack. The qi gathered around Boundless Sea’s hands didn’t even tremble.

The crowd erupted into cheers in praise of Fang Rui’s calm.

Not only had Song Qiying failed to scout out Fang Rui, this attack was equivalent to telling Fang Rui: he’s here, get ready!

Pan Lin and Li Yibo sighed. A rookie was a rookie. Song Qiying was too naive! Running into someone as crafty as Fang Rui was truly a rookie’s greatest misfortune.

But soon afterwards, everyone was stunned.

After Song Qiying’s River Sunset fired a Qi Bullet at the ceiling and didn’t discover anything, he turned around and left.

He didn’t keep going?

Happy’s fans weren’t laughing, but Tyranny’s fans weren’t laughing either.

Song Qiying probably wasn’t sure, so he decided not to pursue it. But this sort of evasion was not a style that Tyranny’s fans appreciated.

Even if you had your suspicions, why not just keep probing? Why run away?

They were too used to seeing the boldness of Han Wenqing’s Striker. They weren’t used to seeing Song Qiying’s extreme caution.

As a result, when they saw him avoid Fang Rui’s ambush, they weren’t too happy either. They weren’t just looking forward to seeing the ambush fail. They were hoping to see their own player smash apart Fang Rui’s ambush and let him know that traps and schemes were nothing but paper tigers.

However, Song Qiying chose to retreat.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo praised him for his caution and calm, but Tyranny’s fans weren’t feeling too pleased.

River Sunset reached the door. It looked like he was about to push the door open to leave, but who would have expected him to do it in such a manner? He punched the door and sent it flying.

What is he doing?

Everyone was stunned.

River Sunset went through the doorway. Then, after a few steps, he turned around and looked to be gauging the distance before making a sprint.

River Sunset sprinted through the doorway and jumped!

Running allowed his character to jump higher. River Sunset jumped onto the wall on the opposite side and pushed off it to jump again. At the same time, he swung his fist, Through the Back Fist!

Its name said fist, but in reality, it was a palm.

River Sunset pushed his palm against the ceiling, letting out a muffled sound.

But then, crack!!

River Sunset hit the ceiling, breaking it as if it were a dried-up branch. A hole appeared in the ceiling. River Sunset’s head went through first. He quickly checked his surroundings and saw Boundless Sea hastily turning around and pushing out his palm.

River Sunset’s arms trembled.

Reinforced Iron Bones to welcome the Sky-Piercing Cannon!

Qi thundered. Although River Sunset had Super Armor, he had no foothold, so there was no avoiding the knockback from the charged Sky-Piercing Cannon.

Thousand Ton Drop!

River Sunset had shrunk into a ball after using the Through the Back Fist, so he could get onto the second floor faster. He had made it through the hole, so he immediately used Thousand Ton Drop. His two feet stepped onto the edges of the hole, using Thousand Ton Drop to eliminate the knockback from Sky Piercing Cannon.

But a new wave of qi from Boundless Sea had arrived. River Sunset jumped practically parallel to the floor, avoiding the attack. He rolled and got up. Boundless Sea sent out another palm, but with the Super Armor from Reinforce Iron Bones, River Sunset didn’t dodge. He tanked the damage and counterattacked!

Boom!

The crowd erupted.

There were a few unhappy Tyranny fans before, but now, their excitement had reached a peak so high that tears were about to come out.

Yes! This was what they wanted to see. Tough and fierce, not sparing anything to destroy the opponent.

They had completely misunderstood Song Qiying.

This kid was no doubt a young hero of Tyranny. He was cautious and calm, but at the same time, he hid the hot-blooded bravery to charge forward. He wasn’t like what they had previously thought, a spineless coward who shrunk back at the slightest uncertainty.

“Good job, Little Song!!!” Tyranny’s fans shouted. Happy’s fans quickly cheered on Happy, smothering Tyranny’s shouts. But so what if Happy’s fans had a numbers advantage, would they shrink back? Of course not! Even though they weren’t on the stage, they were supporters of Tyranny. If they didn’t even have the energy to persevere, how could they ask the player on stage to?

Roar!

Tyranny’s fans roared with all their might. The outcome of the fight was quickly decided. Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea didn’t have that much health left, after all.

Song Qiying won. Of course, he won.

There was no way he wouldn’t win. However, the cheers from Tyranny’s fans weren’t just for the outcome, but more importantly, for how he did it.

From Song Qiying, they could see the future for which they hoped.

Fang Rui went out from the player booth, shaking his head. He didn’t seem to be happy with the match. Even so, the audience still gave him applause.

Beating Zhang Jiale and Lin Jingyan, chasing back Happy’s lead, his performance was without fault. His ambush didn’t succeed, but through Song Qiying’s unyielding attitude, Fang Rui was able to take away 12% of River Sunset’s health. This meant that Happy had a slight lead.

“Good job!”

Tyranny was praising their Song Qiying, while Happy was praising their Fang Rui. As he walked back to his seat, his teammates praised his performance.

But Fang Rui was unsatisfied.

“That little brat, playing with me like that,” Fang Rui said.

“It’s fine, you take down some of his health, too,” Ye Xiu said.

Fang Rui shook his head. “It was too far from my predictions!”

“How much were you thinking you could get him down to?” Chen Guo was curious.

“Obviously until I got his severed head,” Fang Rui said.

Suddenly, everyone ignored him.

Did you think this was a 1v1 in the online game? With that little health and that little mana, you think you can beat a pro player in the playoffs who came in with full health and full mana?

Even if Song Qiying was a rookie, it wasn’t possible for him to be bullied to that extent.

“Next, next.” Ye Xiu completely ignored Fang Rui, urging the next player to go onto the stage.

Who was Happy’s next player?

Everyone had been guessing as soon as Fang Rui went down from the stage. If it wasn’t Su Mucheng, it was Tang Rou. However, when they saw the name on the screen, everyone was surprised.

Qiao Yifan, Ghostblade, One Inch Ash.

“They’re sending out Qiao Yifan?” Pan Lin expressed his astonishment.

Li Yibo thought about it. Feeling that his reasoning made sense, he replied: “Considering what has happened throughout this group arena, Su Mucheng wouldn’t be a suitable player to pick.”

Pan Lin immediately understood.

Su Mucheng was a Launcher. Her greatest weapon was her long range. However, all of the fights so far had taken place in an enclosed space, which was very unfavorable for Launchers. Happy had chosen this map for the group arena and knew this might happen. Was that why they hadn’t sent Su Mucheng out for the group arena?

Chapter 1495 - Cautious Bravery

“Qiao Yifan versus Song Qiying. This could be considered a battle between rookies, no?” Pan Lin remarked as he watched Qiao Yifan walk onto the stage.

“Pretty much!” Li Yibo nodded his head.

Qiao Yifan was no longer an invisible nobody. As Happy moved towards the spotlight as a dark horse, he became recognized as one of their outstanding players. His past had been dug out long ago. Thus, people with certain amounts of authority in the scene like Zuo Chenrui, who disliked Tiny Herb, often used Qiao Yifan as an example to criticize Tiny Herb for being so blind as to letting go of an incredible talent.

Qiao Yifan’s plays had caught the attention of many. Some even felt sorry for him: this was his first time standing on the professional stage, but because he had been registered with Tiny Herb previously, he could not be considered as a first year rookie and could not contend for the Best Rookie title.

If not…

People like to talk about what ifs. Qiao Yifan himself never cared about these what ifs though. He was extremely happy with his place in the team.

He had switched classes to a Phantom Demon, but he had ample opportunities to go onto the stage. He was often given opportunities even in the 1v1 competitions, which weren’t too suitable for Phantom Demons. This feeling of being valued was something he had never experienced before at Tiny Herb.

He had received quite the attention. Several teams had even privately contacted him, attempting to recruit him.

Qiao Yifan refused all of them without any hesitation. No team or promises could move him because he would always remember, in his time of greatest need, who the person who had extended a hand to him was.

Qiao Yifan didn’t have any resentment towards being ignored, but he attached great importance to being valued.

He hoped that he could stay with Happy to realize his dreams.

The problem was that his dreams were being realized too fast.

Because of Qiao Yifan’s past experiences, he didn’t have high aspirations and was extremely cautious. His initial thoughts were to start over with Happy and become a pro player, one small step at a time.

Yes, his initial goal had been set very low. He didn’t want to give up Glory, and he wanted to continue being a pro player; that was it.

But now, he stood on the playoffs stage, and his team had even smoothly made it past the first round.

His dreams were coming about too too fast to the extent that he was caught unprepared. What was his new goal now? Champion?

Was it really not a joke?

When reality hit him, Qiao Yifan had truly felt a bit dizzy. The seniors at Happy had kept on blabbering about being the champions, but Qiao Yifan always just felt like they were just trying to encourage the team, even if this sort of encouragement was ridiculous! But were the seniors at Happy really the type to keep repeating the same joke?

It turns out that it wasn’t a joke.

It turns out that I just didn’t have enough confidence in myself!

It turns out that we really do have the ability to fight for the championship trophy!

As the playoffs grew nearer and nearer, Qiao Yifan adjusted his frame of mind.

Because he realized that Happy truly did intend on walking the difficult path to become the champions.

Apart from feeling bewildered, he also felt excited.

I need to work even harder, so I don’t become a burden to the team in our path to become the champions. He kept on reminding himself these words.

And now, he was about to stand on the stage alone to pave the way to Happy’s victory.

Qiao Yifan took in a deep breath. He walked onto the stage and couldn’t help but look back towards his team. His captain, Ye Xiu, had his arm raised, giving him a big thumbs up.

“You’re far better than you think you are!”

Ye Xiu had said these words to him before he went up.

This wasn’t the first time Ye Xiu had said these words to him. The way Ye Xiu said it would always fill Qiao Yifan with energy and confidence.

He couldn’t let down his seniors or the team’s hopes.

Qiao Yifan turned back and went into the player booth. He swiped his card, and his character loaded into the map. The opening was the same as all the other ones, the two characters headed towards the manor, one towards the front, one towards the back.

Song Qiying chose the exact same route as the previous fight, which made his scouting much more efficient, quickly filtering through room after room.

Qiao Yifan went in through the front door of the manor. He didn’t make any unexpected moves and started moving through room after room too.

One Inch Ash moved much faster than Song Qiying’s River Sunset, though. It seemed that he had a target location that he wanted to reach as fast as possible.

After going through the front door of the manor, One Inch Ash entered the main lobby. Past that, there were numerous hallways interspersed with rooms, 17 in total, serving various purposes.

Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash went past two hallways and four rooms. When he reached a spot that he was satisfied with, One Inch Ash stopped.

Then, he slashed apart the door that he had just went through.

Then, the door in front and on the right…

All three doors in the room were cut apart by One Inch Ash. Afterwards, he leaned against the wall, his sword raised.

“Is he… waiting?” Pan Lin asked.

Li Yibo frowned.

It could be considered as waiting, but it was a bit different from how it was usually done. By cutting down those doors, QIao Yifan was giving himself away, especially since the rooms in the manor weren’t cut-off from each other. Song Qiying, who was scouting around, clearly heard the noise, and three times at that.

Qiao Yifan was lying in wait, but it gave off the smell of bait.

Wasn’t the bait too obvious? With Song Qiying’s cautious nature, he wouldn’t rashly charge towards that area.

Song Qiying wouldn’t be rash, but he wouldn’t ignore it either, shrinking back and cowering wasn’t Team Tyranny’s style. River Sunset headed towards there.

Boom!

River Sunset also broke apart the doors as he rushed into the room to the right of One Inch Ash’s room. The splintered wood from the door flew everywhere as Song Qiying observed his surroundings, quickly getting a picture of the room’s interior. He didn’t see anyone, but he could see the door that had been cut apart.

His gaze immediately shifted towards that room. Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash was quietly moving towards that door, but after a few steps, he stopped moving. He had his sword raised in front of him, ready to attack at any moment.

The sword’s name was Snow Stripe, a streak of white hidden amidst a dark purple light.

River Sunset’s footsteps slowed the closer he got. When he was almost at the door, his footsteps had practically stopped.

The two players were clearly young rookies, but in this match, they seemed to have the caution of old generals. The tension in the crowd could almost be felt. This situation, where the two sides were separated by just one wall, had taken place before in the fight between Ye Xiu and Zhang Jiale. It was just that this time, the door was already destroyed. The two sides were just one step apart from seeing each other.

One Inch Ash raised his tachi, Snow Stripe, slightly. He could already feel that Song Qiying’s River Sunset was right in front of the door. Light started to swirl around his blade. The contrast between the light and that streak of white appeared even more distinct.

One Inch Ash started casting, preparing to set down a ghost boundary.

As for River Sunset? He seemed to hesitate when he reached the door and then suddenly retreated.

The audience couldn’t understand. But because of the previous round, Tyranny’s fans weren’t going to question Song Qiying anymore. They believed that Song Qiying was a true Tyranny hero. No matter what move he made, they wouldn’t think it was because he was timid. Tyranny’s heroes never cowered.

He retreated two steps and then moved horizontally, swinging his fists.

Pai!

His fist smashed into the wall. Everyone cried out in surprise. They thought that a repeat of the match between Fang Rui and Zhang Jiale would happen again, the wall breaking with a single punch.

The camera zoomed in onto the wall, a bit of the wallpaper could be seen coming off.

As for the wall itself? Not even a tremble…

Immediately afterwards, a second punch came out.

Punch after punch.

River Sunset kept on punching the wall. These were all normal attacks, which didn’t consume mana. But at the same time, the attack power was pitifully low. Trying to breaking through the wall like this would require who knew how many punches. But Song Qiying didn’t care. He just kept on punching.

After several punches, he moved to a different position and then continued his barrage.

People were beginning to see his intent.

Hadn’t Qiao Yifan broken down the three doors? Now, Song Qiying wanted to bring down the entire wall.

It was quite a bold idea, but the execution was a bit brutish, just using normal attacks to punch the wall until it broke.

The two sides were only separated by this wall. How could Qiao Yifan not hear what was going on? Song Qiying didn’t care though. He had made his decision, and he would go through with it.

The ghost magic swirling around One Inch Ash’s tachi, Snow Stripe, gradually dimmed.

Pa, pa, pa, pa…

He could hear the sound of the punches hitting the wall.

Qiao Yifan quickly realized Song Qiying’s intentions. For a moment, he was in a daze.

The other side unexpectedly wanted to break down the wall. This sort of cautious yet bold move was completely outside of Qiao Yifan’s expectations.

Should I go around, or should I stay and wait?

There were only two choices. One Inch Ash leaned against the wall, feeling the tremors from the punches.

Stay!

Qiao Yifan made his decision.

Even if his opponent dispelled this trap with such a brutish method, Qiao Yifan felt like waiting would still be advantageous to him.

Happy’s players knew how much damage the walls could take because this was the map that they had chosen.

They had a certain level of understanding of their opponents. They had a rough idea of Song Qiying’s attack power.

In that case, how many punches would it take for River Sunset to break down this wall?

It was better to have a conservative estimate. That way, he could make plans beforehand. If it was necessary, he could finish off the wall himself and take the initiative.

One Inch Ash stopped leaning against the wall. He retreated back a few steps, his sword directed towards the wall.

I’ll wait! I’ll decide the winner of this fight here! Everyone could see his plans.

Pa, pa, pa, pa…

The sound of punches hitting a wall echoed throughout the stadium.

Chapter 1496 - Fighting Blind

How many punches?

Not many people had the patience to count, but Song Qiying did.

164!

River Sunset had punched the wall 164 times so far. Facing normal attacks, this wall appeared extremely sturdy.

But after 164 punches, the wall was filled with cracks. Many parts of the wall weren’t flat anymore.

Song Qiying drew in a deep breath of air.

Almost.

He didn’t know how sturdy the wall was exactly, but just based on the fights today, their vice-captain, Zhang Xinjie, was able to figure out a rough estimate.

Walls had a health value. Although it was an estimated range, if it came from Zhang Xinjie, then it must be accurate.

165, 166, 167…

After three punches, River Sunset temporarily stopped.

The next punches would be would enter within that range. Song Qiying had no plans of testing what the exact value was one punch at a time. He planned on using a powerful attack to break apart the wall in one strike.

He didn’t know whether Happy’s Qiao Yifan was still on the other side of the wall, but if he was, he would be ready. He pretended that Qiao Yifan was there, waiting for him with a field of ghost formations.

He had used around 160 punches to weaken the wall even though he didn’t know if the opponent was even on the other side.

This method was a bit crude, but it was effective.

This way, he didn’t need to worry about falling into a trap.

Song Qiying knew what class his opponent was. Phantom Demons could completely fill the room with ghost boundaries, which was clearly why Qiao Yifan had chosen this room to begin with.

Severals fights had already taken place in this manor. How could Tyranny not have a good grasp of it by now?

Then, the final hit!

He could attack as he moved past the wall!

Song Qiying drew in a deep breath of air.

Attack!

Ferocious Tiger Flurry! He decided on the Level 70 skill, Ferocious Tiger Flurry.

In an instant, countless punches landed on the wall. In an instant, the wall crumbled. In an instant, River Sunset charged through.

After breaking through the wall, Song Qiying could see One Inch Ash standing on the other side with his sword held in front of him.

Ghost Boundary?

With one glance, Song Qiying confirmed One Inch Ash’s position. With a second glance, he confirmed that there were no ghost boundaries nearby.

None?

Even if there were ghost boundaries, Song Qiying’s River Sunset would charge forward anyways, but he felt that it was strange not seeing any.

However, once a young hero of Tyranny made his decision, there was no retreating.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry didn’t stop. River Sunset continued to charge forward, stepping on the broken ruins.

Everyone’s eyes went wide at this scene, but their eyes weren’t on River Sunset. Even the camera wasn’t focused on this ferocious character.

The camera was focused on the ceiling above him.

Right when River Sunset broke apart the wall and rushed forward, the ceiling suddenly began to fall.

The viewers had known about this possibility. They had been observing Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash through their omniscient view.

But at this moment, someone suddenly let out a cry.

The ceiling was much less sturdy than the wall. While Sunset River had been punching the wall, Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash had jumped, leaving three deep cuts in the ceiling.

As a result, when the wall collapsed, the ceiling, which had been on the verge of collapse, lost its final support.

The wall crumbled, the ceiling collapsed.

But the noise sounded the same, so Song Qiying hadn’t noticed this point. He didn’t realize it until he saw that a shadow in front of him was getting larger and larger.

Song Qiying immediately figured out what had happened.

Ferocious Tiger Flurry.

River Sunset continued to attack, breaking apart the falling ceiling.

“Yes!!” Tyranny’s fans cheered, seeing Song Qiying’s fierceness.

But at this moment, One Inch Ash’s Snow Stripe flashed with light, and a ghost boundary formed.

Qiao Yifan had probably deduced that Song Qiying’s River Sunset could break apart the falling ceiling, but he didn’t place down a ghost boundary ahead of time.

Because a ghost boundary wasn’t a wall, it wasn’t something that could not be entered. Song Qiying’s aggression showed that even if he had placed down a ghost boundary, he definitely would have entered anyways.

If he had revealed the ghost boundary ahead of time, he would have let his opponent know when to advance and when to retreat, which would not have been good.

As a result, Qiao Yifan did not show his hand ahead of time. He waited until the battle began, and acted when his opponent had nowhere to run to!

This was the air of a pro player. It was the biggest difference between a pro player and a normal player.

Having the ceiling collapse was to scatter Song Qiying’s attention and make it so that he could not move.

Song Qiying’s method was simple and direct.

Qiao Yifan was not polite. He carefully set up a trap to face this simple and direct method.

Indeed, not many people had thought of breaking the ceiling.

Dark Boundary!

One Inch Ash started with a Dark Boundary, which inflicted Blind onto enemies.

After breaking free from the ceiling, River Sunset had lost the opportunity to interrupt the cast. The ghost boundary fell. Apart from hastily getting out of its range, there was nothing he could do.

Charge!

River Sunset continued to charge.

But after two steps, he had lost his sight because of the Dark Boundary.

Song Qiying’s screen was black, but he didn’t stop because of that. River Sunset continued forward, throwing a punch towards where he remembered One Inch Ash being.

Collapsing Fist!

A loud whistle accompanied the fist, but how could Qiao Yifan not be able to dodge a punch that the opponent had blindly threw out? One Inch Ash had quietly taken a step back a while ago.

Qiao Yifan was no longer in the position that Song Qiying remembered. He only knew that his punch had missed. Where was One Inch Ash? Left? Right? Behind? Behind to the left? Behind to the right?

Without any hesitation, River Sunset punched again. He stepped forward, Double Tiger Palm!

“AH!!” The audience cried out.

Song Qiying’s screen was pitch-black, but his step forward and his Double Tiger Palm made it seem like he knew exactly where One Inch Ash was. His positioning and his attack were completely on point.

The two palms covered a wide area. One Inch Ash could not dodge to the left nor the right.

His only choice was to keep retreating backwards!

Pa!

The two palms missed their target. Just the force of the strike alone was able to produce a clear sound.

Neither attack hit.

But these two attacks had been let out while blind. If a normal player were blinded by Dark Boundary, they would fall into a disadvantaged state. However, Song Qiying’s River Sunset continued pushing forward, forcing Qiao Yifan into defensive position.

Qiao Yifan felt a bit annoyed. He regretted not moving far away enough in the beginning and escaping cleanly from Song Qiying.

Song Qiying had guessed his position correctly both times. The first time was from memory. The second time? It was probably only because he wanted to continue pushing forward.

In the darkness, there was no way to know which way was out, so Tyranny’s players would always choose to move forward.

Qiao Yifan should have considered this point from the beginning. Even if he hadn’t escaped cleanly at the start, he shouldn’t have retreated backwards. Retreating was the same as cooperating with Tyranny’s fondness for advancing.

The Double Tiger Palm had forced Qiao Yifan to retreat backwards, but with this retreat, he was finally able to launch a counterattack. Even though he knew this counterattack would reveal his position, if he continued to let Song Qiying pressure him, not only would he be wasting his Dark Boundary, it was likely that Song Qiying would seize the initiative from him despite being blinded.

Moonlight Slash!

Sword light flashed alongside the sound of the wind.

Song Qiying couldn’t see, but he could hear.

It was the sound of a slash.

One Inch Ash was a Phantom Demon. He only had three low-level slash skills in his kit.

Ghost Slash, Moonlight Slash, Full Moonlight Slash.

Three skills. His opponent was directly in front of him. What angle would he attack from?

Song Qiying instantly made these deductions. River Sunset leaned to the side.

The audience cried out in surprise.

River Sunset had actually dodged this Moonlight Slash. He was able to dodge it despite not being able to see.

Whirlwind Kick!

River Sunset jumped, his legs sweeping through the air towards One Inch Ash.

Not only did he dodge the attack, he was able to counterattack too. The audience didn’t know what to say.

Hit!

One Inch Ash was unable to dodge and could only take the blow. He raised his tachi in front of him and hastily used the Blade Master’s Guard to reduce the damage.

One Inch Ash was kicked back. Right when River Sunset touched the ground, he jumped up again.

Soaring Tiger!

River Sunset jumped, chasing after One Inch Ash. It looked as if he wasn’t blind at all.

Again and again, the audience couldn’t help but cry out in surprise, let alone the two commentators.

Song Qiying played brilliantly, but Qiao Yifan didn’t let his spirits drop. One Inch Ash put himself in a steady position, ready to counterattack at any moment because this attack should not hit!

It missed!

Just as Qiao YIfan expected, the Soaring Tiger missed.

Song Qiying’s timing and thought process were precise and accurate, but if he couldn’t see, he couldn’t see. When Qiao Yifan put his his guard, Song Qiying wasn’t able to notice his slight change in position from just the feel of his attack connecting.

As a result, there was a slight error in his judgement.

Song Qiying was calm, but his opponent didn’t panic and stayed calm despite the cheers and shouts from the crowd. In the end, Qiao Yifan was able to make use of the Blind on Song Qiying. He didn’t waste this Dark Boundary.

Full Moonlight Slash!

He attacked the airborne River Sunset, striking him in the back and sending him flying towards a corner in the room. The Phantom Ghost’s power residing in his blade began to flicker. Ice Soul, Ice Boundary.

And then Ash Boundary.

And then Plague Boundary.

Qiao Yifan calmly began his offense.

Chapter 1497 - The Ten Year Captain

Glory!

The large word flashed across the screen.

No matter the process, the match would progress toward only one conclusion: victory and defeat.

In this round, victory belonged to Happy’s Qiao Yifan. Thunderous applause instantly rose up within Xiaoshan Stadium.

Filled with regret, Song Qiying walked out of the competitor booth. The stadium full of applause wasn’t for him, but he didn’t lower his head. The opponent had played excellently, but he hadn’t had any embarrassing moments himself.

Perhaps, from the beginning, his thinking hadn’t been meticulous enough.

Even as Song Qiying walked offstage, he was already reviewing his own performance. Again and again, his mind replayed the scene of the ceiling collapsing and River Sunset losing his chance.

If it had been the vice-captain, he definitely wouldn’t have overlooked this point. Song Qiying looked at one particular person sitting in Tyranny’s player area.

He was a Striker, the one in Tyranny who would inherit Desert Dust after Han Wenqing’s retirement. The team had never hidden this point. Tyranny was just this kind of open and direct team, from top to bottom.

Song Qiying wouldn’t refuse this kind of arrangement, and he was proud of this, but he wouldn’t hide his own views. Even though he very much liked his Striker class, in terms of player personality, he more greatly appreciated that of Tyranny’s vice-captain, Zhang Xinjie.

Cautious, thorough, flawless.

In many people’s eyes, perhaps this sort of steady style wasn’t thrilling enough. But Song Qiying felt that this was very cool. Maybe it was just because of his natural personality.

Tyranny didn’t make any specific demands of him, nor had he purposely tried to imitate Zhang Xinjie’s style. But even as he followed and developed the style that he personally liked, everyone in Tyranny looked at him like a little Zhang Xinjie.

Song Qiying didn’t object. He hadn’t purposely tried to mimic it; this was just the style that belonged to him.

But it still wasn’t enough!

Song Qiying reviewed the match, searching for where he hadn’t been good enough. And at this moment, Tyranny’s group arena anchor had already stood up.

Han Wenqing. It could only be Han Wenqing. It had to be Han Wenqing.

He could step back when appropriate, but if he didn’t appear in the group arena in this crucial playoffs match, then Tyranny’s fans would definitely be disappointed, and Tyranny’s players might also be very uneasy.

Ten year captain, ten year pillar.

In terms of the influence had over the team, Han Wenqing was absolutely the number one. Even his long enemy Ye Xiu had met an unhappy end at the hands of Excellent Era. Among the later players, Wang Jiexi came the closest; the influence he had at Tiny Herb was similarly significant. But compared to Han WEnqing, he was still just a bit lacking.

Han Wenqing used his personal spirit and charisma to affect the whole team. Tyranny’s style today was because their captain and core from the very beginning was a player with this kind of style, and it continued within this team to this day.

But what about Wang Jiexi and Tiny Herb? He had changed his own style, assimilated into the team, and ultimately they had won two championships together. In terms of results, his two championships beat out Han Wenqing’s one, but in terms of influence on the team, he clearly couldn’t compete with Han Wenqing.

And now, this ten year captain stood up from his seat. Like so many times before, he was ready to defend that most crucial point for Tyranny.

The Tyranny fans who had traveled far to come here began to roar, as though they had suddenly ignited. In the face of the hopes of his fans, Han Wenqing didn’t play humble. To the away team fans, he extended a fist.

The roars grew louder. At this time, Song Qiying had walked off the stage, and arrived in front of Han Wenqing.

Han Wenqing’s fist lowered, and pointed toward him. Song Qiying immediately reciprocated, extending his arm toward him as well.

Fist-bump!

“Good luck Captain!” Song Qiying shouted.

Han Wenqing nodded, and strode toward the stage.

Tyranny was currently at a disadvantage. Qiao Yifan had used 61% of his health to defeat Song Qiying, leaving him with 39% right now.

This advantage was relatively significant, but now as Han Wenqing walked onstage, there wasn’t a hint of worry in the eyes of those dedicated Tyranny fans. There was only resolve.

A match always ended in victory or defeat. Everyone understood this.

But what was revealed in the eyes of the Tyranny’s fans wasn’t belief in a sure-fire victory or anything. Han Wenqing brought them a steady confidence. They believed that, as long as he was here, then even if they lost, they wouldn’t lose that fighting spirit or confidence. As long as he was here, they would only lose people, but not their determination!

Tyranny had never been a team that feared failure. In the early days of the Alliance, they had been eliminated by Excellent Era three times. Excellent Era and Ye Qiu had been called their weakness, their perfect counter. But, so what? In the Season 4 finals, on the highest stage of Glory, they ferociously defeated Excellent Era and proved themselves. The older Tyranny fans would never forget that day. That day had been the most beautiful demonstration of Tyranny’s strength of character.

Unafraid of failure, always scaling new heights. Under this man’s leadership, Tyranny had walked these ten years. Now, the Tyranny that he led once again advanced toward that highest peak, and he once again stood onstage.

In the televised broadcast, Pan Lin was currently describing all of this in the most poetic way possible. His partner Li Yibo had come from Tyranny and experienced that era, and even if he could no longer see all the strategies clearly, he would never forget Tyranny’s spirit. Because, he was also a member of Tyranny, someone who had gone wild with all of them during that season. Hearing Pan Lin’s passionate description, Li Yibo too felt his heart racing. He even had the urge to rush onstage, grip that mouse and keyboard once more, and battle!

“Alright, the battle’s about to begin. Tyranny’s captain of ten years, Han Wenqing, against Happy’s rookie Qiao Yifan,” said Pan Lin.

Even though Qiao Yifan had registered as a pro in Season 8, he had only appeared in official matches starting from this season, so when talking about him, he was still called a rookie.

The opening didn’t change, they still charged toward the manor at the center of the map. Han Wenqing’s fierce bravery and decisiveness could be seen just from the way he moved his character. Desert Dust’s path was completely straight as he charged forward.

In front of and behind the manor, the same rhythm.

Qiao Yifan, like before, controlled One Inch Ash to take the front door, and then he quickly arrived at the location of the previous battle.

“Qiao Yifan still wants to fight here?” Pan Lin said. After watching the previous match, everyone very much understood how advantageous this whole area was for a Ghostblade. The room’s size, the arrangement of the surrounding rooms, it had all been thoroughly used by One Inch Ash.

What was a home field advantage?

This was it.

Using the map to the maximum extent.

Watching from offstage, Tyranny’s players, including Han Wenqing, all recognized this level of skill. But right now, Qiao Yifan still wanted to make this the battlefield. Wasn’t that too wishful thinking? After seeing how well he’d used this area, would Han Wenqing simply go along with his desires and fight him here?

Uh…

Han Wenqing?

Doubt, after encountering this name, caused the logic to grind to a halt.

It seemed like an illogical move, but if Han Wenqing did it, it suddenly felt more acceptable.

Because he was always like this. Even if he knew there was a tiger in the mountain, he would still head toward the mountain with the tiger. For anyone else, it would be an illogical move, but he could flip the situation in one burst of determination.

Qiao Yifan once again opened the battle here. A typical opponent probably wouldn’t come, but Han Wenqing might actually just burst in. Maybe Qiao Yifan had anticipated this opponent’s personality to make this kind of wishful plan?

And so, everyone looked at Han Wenqing’s side. Desert Dust had entered the manor from the back, and he made a clean sweep of the area. He would arrive here shortly. This time, Qiao Yifan didn’t need to split any doors, so there wasn’t any sound to to notify Han Wenqing. One Inch Ash just set up his ambush in this room, making his preparations for battle.

Because a wall had collapsed, the two rooms were now connected and seemed much more spacious than before. Qiao Yifan wasn’t sure from which end Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust would charge in, so he hid One Inch Ash in a corner, and prepared ambushes for the various possible angles.

He didn’t have to wait too long before he heard footsteps.

The sound of moving footsteps wasn’t hidden at all. Whatever was stepped upon made a sound, closer and closer.

Pa!

Suddenly, there was another sound, and One Inch Ash, pressed against a wall, felt a tremor.

There was no way that Qiao Yifan couldn’t recognize this sound. Just last battle, Song Qiying controlled his character and made this sound over 160 times.

Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was also hitting the wall?

Just as Qiao Yifan reached this realization, pa! The second punch already resounded.

Qiao Yifan had already roughly judged where the sound had come from. As he looked over, he heard a boom, and the wall he turned to look at now had a hole in it.

Three punches to make a hole?

This of course wasn’t because Desert Dust’s attack power was so unbelievable, but because the wall he was punching was already fairly weakened.

There had been so many battles back and forth, all occurring within the manor, and most on the first floor. The room furnishings had already become so wrecked that there wasn’t much more to wreck, and the walls had also suffered much damage during this process. Han Wenqing evidently had found a particularly weak point, and broke through in only three punches.

Was he working out his anger?

At the beginning, this was what everyone had thought!

But very soon, they saw Desert Dust and One Inch Ash meet eyes through the hole.

Seeing One Inch Ash’s position, Han Wenqing of course immediately understood his line of thinking. Would he just boldly go forward and fight with Qiao Yifan in an area where the Ghostblade was most comfortable?

The Snow Stripe in One Inch Ash’s hands was already beginning to flicker with light. But Desert Dust, after meeting One Inch Ash’s eyes through that hole, actually walked past.

Pa pa pa pa, another number of punches, and another hole was opened in the weakened wall. And then, change position, hit again…

The sounds came wave after wave, progressing around in a circle. Qiao Yifan listened and listened, and gradually, he paled.

Song Qiying had only wanted to tear down a wall. Was Han Wenqing preparing to tear down this entire manor?

Chapter 1498 - Dismantle

“What’s Han Wenqing trying to do?” The audience had a clear view of Desert Dust’s actions, and they weren’t so dumb that they couldn’t figure out his intentions. This question was a rhetorical one, expressing their surprise. Even Pan Lin was wondering too, in the live broadcast.

Boom boom boom!

Weak spots in the wall were blasted apart, and soon enough, the two walls were full of holes.

Was the manor trembling?

A constant rumble could be heard now and Qiao Yifan wasn’t sure if he was imagining it, but it felt like the walls themselves were moving, unable to support the weight. The ceiling seemed to be sinking bit by bit, as it had lost it’s support.

If this continued, the manor really would collapse!

Qiao Yifan didn’t care if it was just his imagination or not, he made a resolute decision.

He couldn’t lie here in wait any longer. Tyranny’s old Striker was much more ruthless than their new Striker.

Qiao Yifan had no choice but to act. He was extremely familiar with the structure of this room. Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was destroying the wall in this area.

Using the sound of the attacks to locate an enemy’s position.

With a approximation of Desert Dust’s location, Qiao Yifan had One Inch Ash rush over.

Because he was familiar with the area, he predicted the area of the wall Desert Dust was going to hit next and decided to lie in wait there.

Crouching, One Inch Ash successfully arrived at the base of the wall, carefully poised for action as Qiao Yifan listened carefully to the sounds.

The sounds got closer and closer, and dust began falling from the ceiling above. Qiao Yifan raised his character’s view to look. This time he was certain; the ceiling really was trembling, unable to properly support its own weight.

Qiao Yifan stayed motionless.

Desert Dust was near. If he moved, he’d expose himself.

Thwack, thwack!

Two punches, clear, solid hits. The sound didn’t just come from the air, but the wall itself. Desert Dust had finally struck at the wall One Inch Ash was concealed near.

Boom!

The third punch went through the wall. One Inch Ash remained motionless against the wall. He could see Desert Dust’s fist retracting back through the wall from his angle.

Thwack, thwack, thwack, he was still hitting this wall. Han Wenqing was aiming to find weak spots in the wall, the walls he had punched through hadn’t completely collapsed yet, but once he punched out areas all across the wall, it was clearly unable to take much more.

Boom!

Another hole was punched into the wall, practically right next to One Inch Ash. Qiao Yifan could even see the outline of Desert Dust’s knuckles within his famous silver weapon, the gauntlets Flame Fist.

The color of fire, Qiao Yifan could practically feel the heat radiating off of his fist, the blaze of battle lust and determination.

Thwack!

Another punch and Desert Dust broke through the wall a third time.

It wasn’t at where One Inch Ash was hiding. Qiao Yifan had a clear, precise judgement, and would naturally choose a place where the wall was sturdy, a place Han Wenqing wouldn’t choose.

The strikes sounded next to him and One Inch Ash slowly unsheathed his sword, wisps of light surfacing around him.

Boom!

Another hole appeared. Qiao Yifan didn’t move, his view locked forwards towards the doorway Desert Dust was approaching.

That was when the wall behind him started to quake harshly and began to bend.

No way!

Qiao Yifan raised his head. Areas of the ceiling above were already starting to collapse.

Had it reached its limit?

The answer was yes, and Han Wenqing knew it as well.

Thwack!

Another punch struck the wall. This time, he was no longer picking weak spots, just hitting the wall, using attacks to cause it to quake and bend further. He was trying to hasten the collapse.

Just one punch and that half of the wall caved in. This punch was no longer a normal attack, but a more powerful skill in order to accelerate the manor’s destruction. With the state the manor was in, it caused massive damage.

With this half of the wall collapsed, One Inch Ash was exposed, and the room reached its limits. Without needing for Desert Dust’s further help, the ceiling crumbled with a thunderous rumble.

Qiao Yifan hastily tried to get One Inch Ash out of the way, but Desert Dust lunged forth, right under the collapsing ceiling.

Boom!

The ceiling smashed against the floor, sending dust everywhere. With one last roll, Desert Dust left the fallen ceiling behind him using his low position. When he jumped up, he threw a fist, meeting One Inch Ash’s blade head on.

Collapsing Fist!

The Ghostblade’s slash skills had nothing on the priority of a Striker’s punch. This punch sent One Inch Ash flying, blade and all.

There was no pause in his steps as he flew into pursuit.

The walls were collapsing, the ceiling was falling, but Han Wenqing ignored it all. Desert Dust charged amidst the tremors.

Crash! Crash! Crash!

The sound of rubble falling erupted all around, sending dust flying, devouring their surroundings. Two silhouettes fought in this catastrophic scene.

The entire area, all around them, had collapsed, even the areas that Desert Dust hadn’t struck, were brought down by neighboring areas like dominos, having weakened from the battle prior.

Ruins, ruins everywhere.

The walls collapsed, the ceiling fell, the second floor’s structures, and even walls, fell with it. The audience had long since forgotten about the battle occuring between the two, just watching the ancient manor and wondering if the entire thing would just go down.

It didn’t. In the end, it didn’t.

From the outside, the manor didn’t seem like it had changed at all, but the interior had been completely overturned. The second floor, after a chain of reactions, no longer existed. The first floor was just rubble from the second floor, having turned into ruins.

Boom!

With a thunderous bang, the ruins exploded and a character was thrown out.

Who was it?

Everyone’s gazes followed the figure.

One Inch Ash. It was Qiao Yifan’s One Inch Ash! Soon enough, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust appeared as well. He ignored everything happening around them, and all that existed in his eyes was the target he had to fell. One last punch, the final blow.

Glory!

The system announced Desert Dust victory with the catastrophic scene playing background, the ruins, some areas still falling, crumbling.

The audience didn’t know what to say anymore. A map advantage? Han Wenqing had demolished it. That was… pretty wild.

The Happy fans in the venue were all silent while the guest fans from Tyranny roared and cheered.

What style!

What a Tyranny victory!

Demolished the map with the enemy, destroyed it all, spectacular!

Qiao Yifan walked out of the player booth amidst the cacophony. The crazed Tyranny fans naturally weren’t very friendly to him. Last round, he had Song Qiying completely suppressed. And this round? Han Wenqing had given the Tyranny fans a victory to feel good about, one that gave them the satisfaction of revenge.

Nothing was more satisfying!

The Tyranny fans couldn’t be more excited, almost seeming to forget that this wasn’t over yet. There was still one more member for Happy.

Thus, amidst their excitement, the big screen silently displayed Happy’s fifth player, announcing the identity of their anchor.

Wei Chen, Warlock, Windward Formation

“It’s Wei Chen!” Pan Lin’s shout was one full of surprise. This really was a completely unexpected arrangement.

Wei Chen, Blue Rain’s ex-captain, Wei Chen. In the first team competition against Blue Rain, he used his determination to help Happy build the foundations of their strategy.

He had struggled to the bitter end, but this was exactly why he was deserving of respect. Everyone could tell that this player still had his awareness and judgement, but his reaction and mechanics couldn’t keep up anymore.

Wei Chen wasn’t fighting Blue Rain, he was fighting the cruel passing of time.

His performance last time was practically miraculous. Perhaps it was because they had a home field advantage or he was familiar with Blue Rain’s strategy, that Wei Chen could perform well enough to rival his youth.

When the match against Blue Rain ended, everyone thought that was where his contribution ended. He was their ace against Blue Rain.

However, now, against Tyranny, in the first match, the group arena, Wei Chen was the anchor?

How surprising, but Wei Chen was already getting up, waving at the fans energetically as he walked towards the stage.

He met Qiao Yifan halfway.

“You must’ve been scared!” Wei Chen grinned at Qiao Yifan.

Qiao Yifan paused, unsure how to react. What did that mean? How was he meant to reply to that?

“Watch and learn, youngster,” Wei Chen ruffled Qiao Yifan’s hair. After he completely messed up the other’s hairstyle, he headed for the stage, satisfied.

“Happy’s last player… is Wei Chen. What… is this about?” Pan Lin asked Li Yibo.

“Probably… Wei Chen… has a great grasp over this map…” Li Yibo answered weakly.

His random guess had, actually, hit the mark.

Wei Chen had thought that his playoffs journey would be done at Blue Rain, but when Happy ended up choosing this map for their fight against Tyranny, Wei Chen realized there might be more in store for him.

He was very familiar with this map and even more familiar with the manor in the middle of this map. Indoors battles wouldn’t be able to get fast either due to the switches in small scenes. For a slower paced veteran like him, it was a match made in heaven.

He could fight on this map!

When Wei Chen volunteered, he saw Ye Xiu gazing at him.

He didn’t need to speak to get the idea across, and so Wei Chen got another chance.

However, now… Wei Chen gave a self-mocking smile.

The one thing he was depending on had been obliterated by Han Wenqing. While sitting offstage, he had already cursed Han Wenqing to hell and back over one-hundred and eighty times.

Happy’s group arena was all up to him, yet he had lost his one advantage.

Fighting Han Wenqing head on?

Wei Chen’s heart was trembling. How could the current him take on that raging tiger? Though that tiger had grown old, he was practically old enough to be buried, yet he still crawled out to struggle this one last time.

They had gotten to this point yet the universe was still making things hard for him! Wei Chen couldn’t help but grumble under his breath until the referee waved at him to hurry.

Then let’s do this!

Wei Chen gritted his teeth and entered the player booth.

Han Wenqing? Let me experience your fearsome, tiger-like determination again after all these years!

Chapter 1499 - A Ruined Map

Group arena, final round.

Although Han Wenqing was able to cleanly take down Qiao Yifan last round, it wasn’t possible for his Desert Dust not to have taken any damage under those circumstances. His Desert Dust had 81% health left.

Wei Chen’s Windward Formation was in high spirits, but with that small of a lead, how could anyone favor this old general? Let alone Tyranny or neutral fans, even the Happy fans felt uneasy. Some had trouble understanding Happy’s arrangements for the group arena. Happy had sent a Phantom Demon, who wasn’t suited for 1v1s, as their fourth player. Their fifth player was Wei Chen. Didn’t that mean Happy hadn’t planned on placing a fierce hero as the final checkpoint?

Or could it be that their third player Fang Rui was supposed to be their great general? Had their intention be to end the group arena in a 3v5?

But none of these possibilities were logical.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo discussed this issue as the round officially began.

How would Wei Chen face this deciding round? Everyone was curious about Wei Chen. Then, they saw Wei Chen act.

His character hadn’t moved yet, but the trash talking had started.

“I say, Little Han, how outrageous. How could you tear apart the map like this?” Wei Chen typed.

Little Han…

A cold chill could be felt in the air.

In terms of careers, both of them had started in Season 1. Neither was more senior than the other in that sense. But in terms of age, Wei Chen’s words held true. The problem was Han Wenqing, Little Han… it didn’t feel right! Addressing him like that gave a sense of amiability and care. It didn’t fit this captain of Tyranny at all.

How would Han Wenqing respond?

Everyone’s attention shifted to the player chat.

Han Wenqing didn’t reply. It seemed like he didn’t want to bother with such uncouth trash talking. Desert Dust rushed forward.

Wei Chen’s Windward Formation was on his way over too, but his movements seemed so sluggish. It was completely different from Desert Dust’s lofty advance.

“Is there even a point in playing out this round?” Countless people felt that victory had already been decided just from the energy of the players.

Soon, the players reached the manor.

The inside had torn apart into ruins, but the outside looked pristine. The front door and rear door were still intact. Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust went through the rear door and marched through the broken ruins in front of him.

Because of the destruction, he could see much more inside the manor compared to before. Even so, Han Wenqing didn’t find any traces of Windward Formation.

“He didn’t take the middle road?” Han Wenqing thought about what his opponent might do. The home team advantage for this map came from an understanding of the manor’s layout. Now that the manor had been torn apart, the advantage had disappeared. Wei Chen abandoning this area wasn’t too surprising.

After Desert Dust went in from the back, he moved across the first floor to the entrance at the front and surveyed the surroundings calmly.

But Tyranny’s fans felt their hearts leap to their throats seeing his calmness.

Windward Formation didn’t go elsewhere!

He had come to the manor. It was just that he had circled around to the back and was standing beside a window like a withered up plant.

The view on the first floor had opened up considerably, but it wasn’t as empty as a grass plains. The broken walls and collapsed ceilings were still significant obstructions.

Windward Formation couldn’t see Desert Dust from his position.

As a result, he switched positions and continued to peep like a pervert. Tyranny’s fans wanted to rush onto the stage and tell Han Wenqing that Wei Chen was sneaking around behind him!

After moving to a different position, Wei Chen was finally able to see Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust, who was standing outside, checking his surroundings. Was he planning on leaving?

Knock knock knock!

Wei Chen had Windward Formation swing his staff, knocking on the window sill with all his might. Even if he was a Warlock, he could still swing his staff like a melee weapon!

No one knew what material Death’s Hand was made of, but whatever it was, it made an unpleasant sound when it hit against the stone window sill.

Wei Chen thought Han Wenqing wasn’t able to hear him, so he swung his staff again.

“I’m here, I’m here!” He shouted in the chat.

Desert Dust turned around and looked towards him.

Wei Chen was very satisfied: “You saw me, right?”

Han Wenqing didn’t reply. However, Desert Dust was marching over.

Windward Formation immediately shrunk back. Left? Right? The audience would know, but Han Wenqing wouldn’t. Windward Formation moved around and found another observation spot. He took a furtive glance into the manor.

Han Wenqing was moving fast. Desert Dust was almost about to reach that window. It looked like he was planning on breaking it apart to move past it.

“He’s really got a gift for breaking things!” Wei Chen mumbled. Windward Formation raised his Death’s Hand. Dark energy began flickering. He had started casting a curse.

He was planning on mounting a sneak attack, but anyone could predict that. How could an experienced player like Han Wenqing not be able to?

Bang! The window broke. Windward Formation instinctively raised his Death’s Hand, but… no one jumped through it.

Desert Dust smashed the window to pieces and then moved a few steps over to another window.

Bang! Broken again, but still no one.

“Being so clever. How boring. I won’t play with you,” Wei Chen typed. Windward Formation turned around and left.

Bang! Bang!

Han Wenqing had become a dismantler today. Desert Dust smashed two more windows. On the fourth one, his character rushed out.

Left! Right!

He turned to look at those ends.

No one…

After Wei Chen had said those words, his Windward Formation really did leave. He had made such a big commotion, and after saying he gave up, he really did give up.

As a result, Desert Dust seemed to break those two windows for no reason before charging out ferociously. It all looked somewhat comical.

To think the word comical would one day be used to describe Han Wenqing.

“Are you tired of living!!” Tyranny’s loyal fans roared. They were not happy with how Wei Chen had played with their captain.

As for Wei Chen? His Windward Formation was puffing and wheezing as he climbed up the side of the manor. As he climbed, he would look downwards from time to time to see if Desert Dust had made his way over. It made him look quite flustered.

Sure enough, Desert Dust quickly came!

Not seeing anyone to the left or right, Han Wenqing didn’t hesitate. He chose a direction and started giving chase.

Tyranny’s fans had been worried that their captain would forget to look up. Reality proved that Han Wenqing wasn’t nearly as careless as they thought. The moment he turned around, he looked up and down.

The flustered Windward Formation was immediately caught by him. Wei Chen, who was constantly looking downwards, noticed Desert Dust too.

Windward Formation hastened his movements, making him appear even more flustered.

Han Wenqing saw that his opponent was in front of him, but he had no way of attacking him. No one had a shorter attack range than Strikers. Blade Masters, Berserkers, the other melee classes could use the reach of their sword to extend their range, but Strikers only had their arms and legs.

Chase!

Han Wenqing was decisive. He looked at the side of the manor and quickly found a foothold. Desert Dust jumped, stepped, jumped, stepped, jumped…

Han Wenqing hadn’t deliberately practiced climbing on this sort of terrain before, but with ten years of Glory experience, how could his ability to adapt be normal? The speed at which he climbed seemed quite a bit faster than the flustered Windward Formation.

“Hehe,” Wei Chen suddenly laughed. Windward Formation didn’t keep jumping. He pointed his Death’s Hand down and started casting.

Although Desert Dust was fast, there was still some distance between them. It wouldn’t be possible for him to rush over in time to interrupt the cast.

But seeing Windward Formation casting a curse, the instant Desert Dust paused to jump off a foothold, he waved his hands.

Qi Bullet!

A low-level Qi Master skill flew out.

Strikers didn’t have any long-ranged attacks. It was certainly a huge weak spot, so almost all Strikers would learn mid-ranged skills like Qi Bullet. Even though it wouldn’t deal much damage, the purpose was to interrupt casts. For example, if Windward Formation dodged the Qi Bullet, he would have to cancel his cast.

But Windward Formation didn’t move.

“Hehe.” Wei Chen laughed again.

Pa.

Qi bloomed around his body, but the curse from Death’s Hand was released simultaneously.

Was it really simultaneous?

Of course not.

Since he could cast the skill, it meant that the Qi Bullet had been a bit too late. It was a small detail that was hard to notice, but the system had no trouble making this decision.

The curse had been cast!

Wei Chen didn’t have time to dodge the attack though. Fortunately, it was just a Qi Bullet, so the damage wasn’t high. The knockback wasn’t anything noteworthy either. Windward Formation seemed to be unfazed.

His skill was able to come out in the end.

Chaotic Rain!

Using this skill in this situation was truly too disgusting. Desert Dust, who was climbing up the manor, had no place to maneuver around.

He couldn’t escape, but he could still dodge it.

Han Wenqing saw a place with cover. He temporarily gave up on chasing and had Desert Dust jump towards there.

Chaotic Rain fell, but Desert Dust was able to find cover in time and avoid the attack.

“Beautiful!” Wei Chen praised his opponent. Windward Formation didn’t keep jumping up, instead dropping down.

After dropping down, Desert Dust was now in his line of sight.

A dark energy began swirling around his Death’s Hand again.

Grasping Ghosts!

Desert Dust had nowhere to run. If he jumped out, he would be caught in Chaotic Rain, which would probably be even more disastrous for him.

The fierce tiger… was trapped. Caught between a rock and a hard place, the curse flew out and struck.

Chapter 1500 - I Need to Complete It

Several shadow spectres coiled around Desert Dust.

Grasping Ghosts. It dealt damage over time and amplified the damage dealt by the Warlock. When the skill ended, the Warlock would be healed 33% of the total damage dealt to the target during the duration of the skill.

It was a skill that dealt damage, debuffed the target, and healed the user. When it first came out, everyone thought it was a completely broken skill. However, after some time, people figured out that while the skill wasn’t bad. It wasn’t broken because the effects of the skill were rather weak.

Even so, it was a must-have skill for Warlocks. Wei Chen knew that he was guaranteed to land a hit, so he started with this skill before continuing his assault.

Chaotic Rain continued. Han Wenqing looked completely helpless.

Was he going to keep getting played like a trapped animal?

Tyranny’s fans burst out in fury. When had their captain ever suffered such humiliation?

Jump!

Everyone thought to themselves.

So what if you became Confused? The outcome is going to be bad anyways, but being trapped like this and getting trampled on was too stifling. From their understanding of Han Wenqing, they didn’t think Han Wenqing would be willing to resign himself to this kind of fate.

However, Desert Dust didn’t move…

Shadow Flames!

Windward Formation cast another spell. Dark purple flames began to whirl around Desert Dust. These 6 seconds of flames didn’t only burn down Desert Dust’s health, but the hearts of every Tyranny fan as well.

Why isn’t he jumping?

They couldn’t understand.

The Desert Dust in front of them was slowly drifting away from the Desert Dust in their hearts.

“What self-control!” Fang Rui sighed.

“Yeah,” Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Not only had Han Wenqing learned the word “retreat”, he became even more unyielding. His style had changed to the extent that those familiar with him couldn’t recognize it anymore. On the playoffs stage, these changes only became more apparent.

“How surprising! I thought you’d jump!” Wei Chen poked at his weak spot.

Han Wenqing didn’t reply. In the meantime, Windward Formation started casting his third spell.

With the duration of Chaotic Rain, he knew that his third skill would land. Darkness ripped apart the air.

Windward Formation had summoned Death’s Door!

How shameless!

Countless people cursed in their hearts.

In terms of ruthlessness, there was nothing to pick at. Wei Chen’s methods didn’t carry a shred of restraint. He wanted to annihilate his opponent.

The tear appeared in the sky, revealing an imposing Death’s Door. The Chaotic Rain stopped.

Whoosh!

A figure jumped from a window sill.

Who else could it be but Desert Dust? He had been forced into a location that would provide cover from Chaotic Rain and then forcefully tanked two skills. He had looked completely helpless at the time. But when the last drop of rain fell, he immediately jumped.

The Death’s Door next to him? It was as if Han Wenqing couldn’t see it. Desert Dust went straight for Windward Formation.

Determined and decisive without any hesitation. In this instant, the Han Wenqing that everyone was familiar with had returned. Tyranny’s fans didn’t have time to adjust their emotions, involuntarily letting out a cheer.

Tendrils of darkness extended out from Death’s Door, its target even bumping into it as it scurried away. The darkness immediately gave chase.

Han Wenqing ignored it. Desert Dust used the wall as a foothold and continued jumping. Keep charging forward even if the darkness behind him was in pursuit.

The fans of Tyranny stood up from their seats. They had completely forgotten about their indignation a few seconds ago from seeing Desert Dust cowering under that window.

Punch!

Desert Dust had swung his fist.

And Windward Formation?

Windward Formation wasn’t able to escape in time. To attack Desert Dust, he had dropped down from his original position, moving closer to where his target was. This change in position became Han Wenqing’s opportunity to attack. This decisiveness and ferocity had been outside of Wei Chen’s expectations. He had calculated that Death’s Door would be cast the moment Chaotic Rain ended. He had thought that there was enough time but now, he discovered that what he thought was enough was far from it in front of Han Wenqing’s valor.

Just a bit more, and the tendrils of darkness would catch Desert Dust, but it was too late. Desert Dust’s fist had already reached Windward Formation.

Bang!

Hit.

A solid punch had landed.

However, the slight pause from the punch was enough for the darkness to catch Desert Dust. The tendrils quickly coiled around him.

Was this punch just to vent his anger?

Everyone thought to themselves. But for Tyranny’s fans, even if it was just that, it felt incredibly satisfying. To them, the journey was more important than the destination.

But Han Wenqing’s thoughts weren’t so simple.

After the punch landed, Desert Dust grabbed with his two hands.

Back Throw!

Windward Formation had been grabbed by him, and Desert Dust had been grabbed by Death’s Door. Both of them were dragged away.

The two were dragged together towards the Death’s Door, which then burst into a cloud of darkness.

Death’s Door had accomplished its mission and disappeared. The two dropped from the sky.

One on top, one below.

One slow, one fast.

The faster one was Windward Formation. Although he wasn’t affected by Death’s Door, the Back Throw wasn’t something the Death’s Door could interrupt.

Desert Dust was able to complete the Back Throw, flinging Windward Formation crashing down. As a result, Windward Formation fell faster.

On the other hand, Desert Dust took the damage from Death’s Door before free-falling down.

While in the air, Desert Dust assumed an offensive posture.

Wei Chen was helpless though.

Windward Formation wasn’t free-falling. He had been tossed by Back Throw. Before he hit the ground, he would be in a Stunned state.

He could only watch as Desert Dust raise his foot, Eagle Stamp! Desert Dust dove down as if he were an eagle catching its prey. However, Windward Formation could do nothing.

Sigh…

Wei Chen let out a gentle sigh.

I was too slow.

If he had reacted faster or put in the inputs faster, perhaps that punch wouldn’t have landed or he might have been able to dodge the Back Throw. In either case, he wouldn’t be in his current predicament!

While Stunned, he could only watch as the Eagle Stamp came towards him. The instant the skill effect ended, would he be able to dodge in time?

Wei Chen felt a tremble in his heart. His fingers were starting to go stiff.

It was another contest of reaction speed and hand speed! That was what he was most afraid of and what he was weakest at.

But that’s the only way to get out of this predicament!

If he was hit by the Eagle Stamp and let Han Wenqing close in onto him, his fate would be sealed.

Focus!

Wei Chen grit his teeth. He was no longer looking at Desert Dust, but carefully feeling Windward Formation’s condition. The instant the Stun ended, he would immediately act.

I can move!

All of these thoughts happened in an instant. Wei Chen felt that the Stun had worn off. In that instant, his mind was blank. He had forgotten about the match, he had forgotten what he was doing. He only had one thought: complete it, complete this input.

Windward Formation raised his two hands in front of him…

Bang!

Desert Dust’s Eagle Stamp was kicked Windward Formation’s chest.

“OHhh!!…” Tyranny’s fans cheered for a moment before abruptly stopping.

Windward Formation poofed into smoke and dispersed into the air as Desert Dust continued to fall…

Han Wenqing turned around.

Windward Formation was back on the wall on the side of the manor.

Shadow Clone Technique!

I did it!

Wei Chen’s heart was beating intensely. The lingering fear from the narrow escape from death made his whole body turn soft. It was just a low-level skill, but because of the focus he had put in, he felt like collapsing from exhaustion.

But it’s not over yet! The battle had only just begun.

Wei Chen immediately continued. Windward Formation started casting another spell from the wall.

Soul Slice!

A blade of darkness cut through the air.

In this situation, at this distance, Wei Chen didn’t think of using a high-level skill for a set-up. He simply wanted to take advantage of the fact that Desert Dust was in the air and could not dodge, so he could deal some damage.

He predicted where Desert Dust would land and aimed his Soul Slice. However, Eagle Stamp wasn’t as simple as just a stomp.

Han Wenqing saw Windward Formation casting a spell and immediately finshed his Eagle Stamp.

Pa pa pa!

Desert Dust stepped in the air three times. He didn’t hit his target, but he used these steps to slow his speed down a little bit.

But… it still hit in the end.

Wei Chen was a crafty old fox! This little trick wasn’t going to mess him up.

But apart from damage, the Soul Slice didn’t do anything else. Desert Dust landed on the ground and darted towards the manor in pursuit. As for Windward Formation? He was once again climbing towards the roof in a fluster.

We’re not going to see a repeat of what we just saw, right?

Many of the viewers started to worry.

“No.” Li Yibo dispelled these doubts from the audience.

“His skills aren’t off cooldown yet. How could we get a repeat so soon?” Li Yibo said.

“Of course, he can’t use the same skills, but does he have the tools to do something similar as before?” Pan Lin said.

“Uh…” Li Yibo thought carefully about the Warlock’s kit. It shouldn’t be possible, right? He wasn’t certain though, so he didn’t say it.

Chapter 1501 - Sneaky Acting

Jump jump jump!

The two characters were both jumping nonstop on the manor wall. Windward Formation didn’t use any skills to disrupt him, nor did Desert Dust use any techniques to harass him.

But just this kind of jumping and climbing was already enough to render the watching players dumbstruck.

The map came from an in-game environment, and the online Arena also had this map. With the vast number of Glory players, there were players who had visited this manor in-universe, and of course there were also those who liked to play on this map in the Arena.

But, to so easily leap and scale the side of this manor, this was evidently outside of the experience of ordinary players.

After this match, those Glory players who liked this map would probably once again begin to pay attention to this kind of technique of scaling the manor wall. It was in this manner that professional matches were at the forefront of Glory trends.

And of the two people on the field right now, Wei Chen was more familiar with the map, while Han Wenqing, having played so many battles, was extremely adaptive. Neither player’s controls revealed any flaws.

But Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was still slightly faster. This wasn’t because of any difference in skill, it was a result of the differences between their characters. Strikers were simply more nimble than Warlocks, and had superior movement and jumping ability.

But, he probably couldn’t catch up, right?

Looking at the distance between the two characters, if they set the roof as the target, it didn’t seem like Desert Dust had enough time to catch up to Windward Formation. Then, once Windward Formation reached the roof, he definitely wouldn’t hold back in unleashing a harsh attack down upon Desert Dust, right?

Wei Chen didn’t disappoint. Tossing stones at someone who had fallen into a well, that sort of thing was something he loved to do.

“Little Han, catch!”

As soon as he successfully reached the roof, the panic he’d shown earlier completely disappeared. Trash talk was joyfully resurrected in the match chat.

Nothing had even happened to Han Wenqing yet, but Tyranny’s diehard fans were already getting nervous.

This Wei Chen clearly was limited in his ability, but as soon as he achieved a slight advantage, he simply made people extremely uncomfortable. That sort of completely unconcealed dirty and shameless play, it really made people both annoyed and fearful.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh whoosh…

Standing on the high ground, Windward Formation waved his Death’s Hand, letting loose Curse Arrows, and he sent them scattering in various directions, making them fall like Chaotic Rain. They pattered down, taking advantage of the fact that there were limited footholds on the wall, and very little space to dodge.

But Desert Dust’s arms trembled – Reinforced Iron Bones!

Super Armor was activated, and then Han Wenqing directly ignored the damage he took from Curse Arrows, and continued to use his fastest speed to travel the shortest path.

Wei Chen smiled slightly, and Windward Formation continued to sway his scepter.

Hexagram Prison!

Suddenly, six beams of light appeared in the air, falling straight down!

And the prediction involved in casting this skill wasn’t cheap at all. Wei Chen correctly calculated the path Han Wenqing would take, and predicted where Desert Dust would step. But the skill didn’t target the footholds, it targeted the midair path Desert Dust took as he jumped.

This was naturally harder than locking in on the footholds, but it was harder for the opponent to dodge, as well.

Wei Chen’s reaction speed and hand speed weren’t fast enough, but he was very confident in his accuracy when he stood up here and could calmly cast skills.

The pillars of light came down, and it looked like the midair Desert Dust had no way of dodging. But just when it looked like he was about to hit, Desert Dust’s body suddenly plunged.

Thousand Ton Drop!

Han Wenqing controlled his character to use this skill. Desert Dust plummeted, even faster than the pillars of light were coming down. Just like that, he instantly put some distance between himself and the attack, and his foot landed on another foothold.

Hua!

Thousand Ton Drop was an attacking skill. When his foot hit this foothold, it was instantly crushed by this stomp, and rubble skittered down. But it was enough for Desert Dust to get some force, and he leapt to the side.

The six pillars of light brushed right past him. Desert Dust successfully dodged this attack, and continued upward without hesitation.

“Tsk tsk tsk, starting to wreck this place again? Careful not to wreck yourself!” Wei Chen reproached him in the chat. For Han Wenqing, who still hadn’t successfully made it to the top, breaking a foothold really wasn’t good news for him at all.

Death’s Hand waved once again.

Soul Strike!

Black light flashed outward.

Warlock skills carried many annoying side effects, and this skill was no exception. Soul Strike, as the name implied, directly attacked the target’s soul, causing the target to enter a Trance state. In game, this meant that the target’s controls had no effect.

Even though the effects of this skill lasted only for a very short amount of time, this was undoubtedly a powerful interrupt skill, and it could interrupt not only casts, but any sort of movement.

Take the current situation for example. Leaping up the wall required extremely precise controls. Jumping a distance of three body-lengths versus four body-lengths certainly required different amounts of jumping force. And this was all dependent upon the player to control and react.

At this moment, if someone was about to initiate a four body-length jump and was currently adjusting the amount of power to put into the jump, and was suddenly hit by a Soul Strike, then the jump power might only reach that of a two body-length jump, and the rest of the power would be lost. With that… trying to jump a four body-length gap with only a two body-length jump, wouldn’t he just fall?

And Wei Chen had seized upon this moment exactly. The black light flashed in front of Desert Dust, who was just landing. But his body swung…

The black light just barely flashed past Desert Dust. This Soul Strike, Han Wenqing had actually managed to dodge it.

“Ohhh!” The Tyranny fans, letting out a breath in relief, were very happy. This time, Wei Chen didn’t feel like spitting any words in the chat; his mood grew very serious.

If this Soul Strike hadn’t successfully interrupted Desert Dust’s jump power, then that could just be attributed to luck. But, it had missed altogether. How?

Wei Chen was very confident in the accuracy of his judgment and control. This attack he had calculated very well. But, he had still been too slow?

Wei Chen hurriedly began casting another skill.

Binding Curse!

Another flash of light, but, it missed again!

In such an advantageous condition, he had actually missed two times in a row?

The Happy fans lamented his bad luck, but Wei Chen knew that that definitely wasn’t the case.

After one miss, the second time, his prediction and controls had been even more careful. This second miss shouldn’t be because of any problem on his end.

“Han Wenqing adjusted the rhythm.” Watching the match, Ye Xiu had already seen what the problem was.

“The adjustment is very subtle…” Fang Rui said.

It seemed like a very normal adjustment, but coming from Han Wenqing, suddenly it seemed rather abnormal. Han Wenqing, who had always been a very open and direct player, would actually use this kind of fine-tuning on his rhythm, so slight that it was extremely difficult to detect.

“Has this guy really become so interesting now?” Ye Xiu mused.

Windward Formation continued to cast.

Another curse, another miss.

“Hahahaha!” The Tyranny fans in the stadium had begun to jeer and shout. This dirty-playing guy, he tried to play dirty but his attacks missed, it was extremely rewarding to watch.

“Old Wei still hasn’t noticed?” Fang Rui furrowed his brow.

Even though Wei Chen might not compare to them in terms of pro experience, he had never left Glory after so many years, so his eyes were sharp. Han Wenqing’s adjustment might be slight, but not so slight that Wei Chen wouldn’t be able to detect it, right?

Just as he said this, the fourth spell missed as well.

“This is bad!” Fang Rui shouted, slapping his leg.

A curse missing wasn’t a big deal, but the key was that this fourth curse, compared to the others, was clearly a bit more rushed. Instead of patiently waiting for the best opportunity, Wei Chen had cast it immediately after the third one missed, and hurriedly released it as soon as it was ready.

The panic of climbing the wall was resurfacing. Missing all of these skills in a row made Wei Chen very anxious. After the fourth curse missed, he again hurriedly began casting a fifth.

But by this time, Desert Dust was already almost at the roof. This skill was probably Wei Chen’s last chance at a merciless attack. If he missed again, Wei Chen would lose his positional advantage.

And this time Wei Chen seemed even more panicked, because he used an even faster skill.

Soul Slice!

A blade of black light flashed outward toward Desert Dust.

But just by looking at the moment he released the skill, the experienced players were already sighing.

“He released it early…”

Huang Shaotian had already texted such a lament to Yu WEnzhou, and he was already in the process of writing a new one, too: “Boss Wei’s a bit too nervous…”

But just as he was burying his head in the text, an unexpected situation suddenly emerged onstage.

The Soul Slice didn’t hit. Desert Dust stepped on the final foothold, but just when he was about to reach the roof, but his character suddenly started falling.

How?

Everyone was shocked. The broadcast director reacted swiftly, splitting the screen to show a replay.

That moment that Desert Dust landed on that last foothold, it shattered from the impact, and he fell with it…

“Little Han, catch!”

High-spirited trash talk once again floated into the chat.

Everyone was dumbfounded, including Wei Chen’s teammates.

“Fuck!” Fang Rui was slapping his leg again. As expected of the master of dirty playing, as soon as he saw this result, he instantly understood what Wei Chen had done.

He’d been pretending. It was all an act!

This guy had also probably detected the slight adjustments Han Wenqing had made to his rhythm, but these adjustments were changing often, so even if he could tell the rhythm was changing, it would be very difficult for him to grasp it.

And so, Wei Chen pretended that he couldn’t grasp it at all, he missed skill after skill, and he even adjusted his own rhythm to give off the impression that he was panicked and rushed.

Even Fang Rui, this master of dirty play, had been fooled. Did it even have to be said, how superb this acting was?

And so, the final killing blow simply came from landing on the final foothold.

How come it didn’t hold? Wei Chen had messed with it, of course!

Even as Desert Dust fell, Han Wenqing was still resolute. He pulled his view downward, and could already see another foothold below him, but…

Whoosh…

Black light flashed past.

The Soul Slice cut that foothold.

The missed Soul Slice had never been targeting Desert Dust. Wei Chen put on a good show.

And at this moment, Death’s Hand flashed with magic energy, gathering into a raincloud – Chaotic Rain.

The skill’s cooldown had finally ended, and it was once again cast by Windward Formation. And this time, Desert Dust had absolutely no way of dodging.

The Chaotic Rain poured down, bringing the Confusion, and Desert Dust continued to plummet.

There might have been more footholds further down, but under the Confusion status, how could he possibly find them…

And at the very bottom, on the ground, unnatural wind blew.

The powerful skill, Winding Wraiths, was already ready to welcome Desert Dust…

Huang Shaotian, who had still been in the middle of expressing his emotions to Yu Wenzhou in a text, stared with his mouth hanging open. He put his phone down.

The battle was decided. A target controlled by a Warlock to this extent had no possibility of escape.

In the deciding battle of the group arena, Wei Chen won.

In the group arena, Happy won!

Chapter 1502 - Rivals of Ten Years Meet Once More

“Heh, Little Han, you’re still too green.”

This was the last message Wei Chen left in the group arena chat, something that was enough to make all Glory players spit blood.

If even Han Wenqing was still too green, then was there even anyone who could be considered a veteran? That boast was just completely illogical.

However, this was Happy’s home stadium. As Happy fans, this was something they could totally laugh about.

However, for Tyranny fans it was frustrating. They wouldn’t fear losing, but losing to a guy like this was absolutely disgusting, especially when the one who lost was their most respected captain, Han Wenqing.

No one would blame Han Wenqing for this loss. They had seen his usual courage and determination. It was this opponent; he was too sly, too tricky, too shameless…

Perhaps, on some level, this kind of opponent was the bane of Han Wenqing’s straightforward style!

The group arena had ended, and the two players walked out of their booths simultaneously. Wei Chen, of course, wore a face full of joy, waving at the crowd while shamelessly making a whole lap around the stadium. Even the wild jeers when he passed by the stands for the guest team fans didn’t dampen his smile. In fact, his smile just grew and he was even more enthusiastic in his waving.

The security were restless, as if prepared to face a monster. These were Tyranny fans they were talking about. Was this guy looking to get killed, provoking the Tyranny fans like that? They hurriedly arranged for more people over here while they sent people to try and talk Wei Chen down from his celebrating.

Wei Chen didn’t give them any trouble, finishing his rounds and returning to the Happy player bench. Happy’s members had stood to welcome their hero back.

“Sit, sit, please, sit,” Wei Chen energetically waved his hands at them.

Everyone laughed. None of them said anything about the way he was behaving because they all knew how important this victory was to Wei Chen, how hard he worked for it.

“It’s all up to you guys now,” Wei Chen then said. Next up was the team competition and he wasn’t in the lineup.

“Don’t worry,” Ye Xiu nodded at him.

“Huff…” Wei Chen exhaled heavily and looked back at the screen.

Everything he had accomplished, the victory he had earned, it was all clearly recorded there. This might not be the most spectacular victory he had claimed, but it was definitely the most satisfying. Time wouldn’t let him remain in this moment, but he knew he would never forget any of this.

With the group arena at an end, Happy had a one point lead. The effect of their victory on their morale was significant though realistically speaking, a lead of one point was negligible in the team competition.

Neither team returned to their battle prep rooms, making their arrangements for the team competition right then and there.

The match was only just beginning!

The two teams made surprisingly synchronized pep talks. For Happy, it was mostly reminding everyone that they shouldn’t drop their guard due to their lead from the group arena. For Tyranny, it was about not letting the group arena results get them down. However, the gist of both was the same: a one point lead was nothing.

Both teams were solemn. After boasting for a while, Wei Chen tactfully quietened down, analysing their path of action in the team competition seriously with the others.

Time flew by, and the referee was already on the outskirts of the stage, staring at his watch and getting ready to call the teams to the stage.

Team Tyranny, with a one point disadvantage, rose from their seats first and headed for the stage without needing prompting from the referee.

Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, Zhang Jiale, Qin Muyun, Zhang Xinjie, and sixth player Bai Yanfei.

This was the formation that Tyranny used last season to charge into the championships, as well as what people viewed as their core formation. It was just that Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan and Zhang Jiale were on rotation this season and with the addition of their new little general Song Qiying, this formation rarely appeared. It didn’t even appear in the first round of the playoffs.

Yet now, against Happy, in their first away game, Tyranny used the formation they had used to aim for the championships last season.

Tyranny’s fans started clapping, screaming, cheering their team on.

And on Happy’s side? Captain Ye Xiu merely glanced over nonchalantly when the cheering started before turning back and continuing to speak.

However, the match was about to start, so Ye Xiu finished his pep talk with a few last sentences.

“Let’s go!” With that, Team Happy’s players also stood.

Ye Xiu, Su Mucheng, Fang Rui, Tang Rou, An Wenyi, none of them were unexpected, but the last player…

“Who is this?” Pan Lin inquired in the broadcast, hesitant.

“Luo Ji? Happy is putting Luo Ji?” Pan Lin said, shocked.

Luo Ji… The name felt foreign on his tongue because he rarely ever had to say this name in the broadcast.

In the regular season, Happy rarely sent Luo Ji up. It was only near the end of the season that he saw more match time.

However, Luo Ji was different from Wei Chen. Wei Chen’s sudden participation at the end of the regular season was clearly to help him adjust his state in preparation for the playoffs. But what about Luo Ji? Luo Ji was a rookie, a young player. His participation was, everyone guessed, a form of acquiring battle experience while the circumstances allowed it.

From these few few matches, everyone could see that Luo Ji was special, but he wasn’t particularly skilled yet.

Perhaps he was a player with potential, with a future ahead of him, but right now, he needed more time to grow.

That’s what everyone thought.

However, Luo Ji had appeared in the second round of the playoffs, in the roster for Happy and Tyranny’s team competition.

“Is there some mistake?” Pan Lin wasn’t sure if he should believe his eyes. What if Luo Ji just so happened to stand up?

But it wasn’t so.

The team lineups were already being displayed on the big screen. Not only was Luo Ji’s name among them, it was in the starting five as well. Happy had arranged for Tang Rou to be the sixth player.

It wasn’t possible that this was just a chance for a rookie to acquire battle experience, not here in the playoffs. On this battlefield, there was no holding back.

Then, could it be that Luo Ji was a weapon that Happy planned on using against Tyranny?

Discussions erupted in the venue and online. Pan Lin once again asked for Li Yibo to give his professional analysis. In the end, Li Yibo managed to avoid a proper explanation by explaining Luo Ji’s playstyle.

The two sides lined up, facing each other on the stage.

The first to shake hands were, naturally, the two captains.

Rivals of ten years. The two had faced each other in all four finals of the first four seasons. It was also on this stage that their paths became intimately entwined, pitted against one another.

In the next seasons, the fifth, the sixth, the seventh, the two teams didn’t clash. Excellent Era began their fall from grace, and Han Wenqing, too, began to fall. Everything spoke to them, telling them that their era had ended. Professional Glory had entered a new era of those that came after.

Then, in season eight, Ye Xiu retired, bidding this stage farewell, and Han Wenqing became the only first generation player that was still struggling through this battlefield.

That season, Team Tyranny was quickly eliminated from the playoffs. The people sighed wistfully,witnessing the end of an era.

Who would’ve thought that in the ninth season Team Tyranny would invite a bunch of veterans and stand once more at the highest stage of Glory.

Then, in the tenth season, Ye Xiu led his very own team back into the league.

Now, these two once again were shaking hands on this very stage where their rivalry grew.

Had that era returned?

Seeing this scene, some older fans of Glory found their minds wandering. The battles between these two, it was the memories of that past era! Everyone thought that era had ended, but how come these two were meeting here once more?

“You’ve improved!” Ye Xiu said, shaking Han Wenqing’s hand. They were rivals, but perhaps it was he that understood the one standing in front of him the most. Once upon a time, Ye Xiu had put his everything into defeating this man. He was familiar with Han Wenqing’s awareness, mechanics, methods, and he would be the first to notice the slightest change.

“Your unspecialized isn’t bad either,” Han Wenqing replied. He had changed, but he definitely hadn’t changed nearly as much as this guy. In the resolution of his pro career, he had given up on his best and most familiar Battle Mage for the strange class known as the unspecialized. However, Han Wenqing understood more than anyone how the unspecialized might suit Ye Xiu so, because like Ye Xiu knew him, he also knew Ye Xiu.

Glory Textbook, this title was no exaggeration, he was more knowledgeable than one could imagine.

“It’s not too late to surrender,” Ye Xiu said.

“Are you talking to me?” Han Wenqing’s reply was cold. Surrender? That word didn’t exist in his dictionary.

Ye Xiu chuckled, but said no more, shaking hands with each of Tyranny’s members one by one. Zhang Xinjie, Zhang Jiale, Lin Jingyan… these were old opponents that he couldn’t be more familiar with. The so-called “that era” wasn’t something created by just the two of them. Countless people had already left this battlefield, but who knew if they were watching the ones who were still fighting for Glory from whatever corner of the world they were in.

The players of the two teams headed towards their booths, their characters loading into the map. Some of these characters were more than familiar to the public, but some had only appeared beginning this season. Perhaps, compared to the players, these characters would be better at preserving the legacy of Glory. When the day came that Ye Xiu, Han Wenqing, Zhang Jiale and the others left this battlefield for good, the characters that they once used would continue to carry everything they had left behind.

The second round of the playoffs, Happy’s home game against Tyranny, let the team competition, begin!

Chapter 1503 - A Shift in Style

Team competition map: Full Moon Forest.

As soon as the name of the map came out, Pan Lin and Li Yibo immediately started introducing the characteristics of the map.

Full Moon Forest had the name “forest” in it, but in reality, the forest set the boundaries for the map. The scenario for the setting was a little village inside a forest. The village had a lot of content, but the layout of the map was relatively simple, it didn’t have complicated intertwining alleyways like the larger city maps. The entire village only had four buildings.

The southwest corner had a blacksmith’s shop. The northeast corner had a grocery market. The southeast corner had a storehouse and a watchtower. The northwest corner was the residential area. The houses were built on top of trees with drawbridges connecting the trees together.

Directly to the south of the village was a small pond. To the north was an altar, which was the most open area in the map. There were several large trees providing shade scattered throughout the village. Although it couldn’t be considered a forest, it provided a good amount of cover.

In general, the map was not a place for a direct confrontation. Very few teams chose simple maps in the playoffs. Every team wanted to utilize their home game advantage to the fullest and pick a map that best suited their team.

After introducing the map, Pan Lin and Li Yibo began analyzing what advantages Happy would have as the home team. This topic was much more complicated than an introduction of the map. Pan Lin mainly became a question-asker, giving Li Yibo the main spotlight. Li Yibo could only force himself to analyze the issue at hand. Every few sentences, he would chuckle an awkward “haha” to cover up his lack of confidence.

As the two discussed the topic, the match officially began.

Happy spawned at the southwest corner, surrounded on three sides by trees. From afar, they could see the blacksmith’s shop to the northeast. Tyranny spawned at the opposite end of the map at the northeast corner. Their spawn point was the exact same as Happy’s spawn point, surrounded on three sides by trees. From afar, they could see a grocery market to the southwest.

The two teams went along the only path available. Not long afterwards, a brilliant blue pond appeared to the east of Happy, while an altar appeared to the west of Tyranny.

Team Happy was the home team. They naturally had a plan in mind. Once the pond became visible, they had more directions to choose from. In the end, Happy moved towards the northwest towards the residential area.

On the other hand, once Tyranny had more directions to choose from, they immediately slowed down.

As the away team, they weren’t as familiar with the map compared to the home team, so slowing down the pace was normal. However, as Team Tyranny, slowing down out of caution was very rare.

On one hand, it could be seen how highly Tyranny looked upon Happy. On another hand, it could be seen that it wasn’t just Han Wenqing adjusting, but rather the entire team. All of them were changing their usual pace under their captain’s lead.

Li Yibo had once been a part of Tyranny, so he was very acute to these changes and started confidently discussing this topic. As for the home team advantages that Happy had with this map and the logic behind choosing this map, he put them aside for now…

The two teams moved on their own accord. Neither of them saw each other. It felt like the calm before a storm. Team Happy’s movements were decisive. When they reached the residential area, they began hiding. In the end, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was the only one who hadn’t hidden himself in a residence. Instead, he went along the road, cutting across towards the altar.

Everyone was stunned.

Because the careful Tyranny just happened to be moving towards the altar as well. Li Yibo was talking about this area too. There was no pressure from the map disadvantage for Tyranny because of the openness of the altar area.

But just when Li Yibo was talking about Tyranny’s choice, Ye Xiu moved towards the altar a step ahead of them.

As a result, Lord Grim soon came into Tyranny’s line of sight.

Kakaka!

Gunfire immediately came from Team Tyranny’s side. Zhang Jiale took the initiative and had Dazzling Hundred Blossoms start their offensive.

Han Wenqing was always the first to rush out, but when facing his long-time rival, he remained calm and collected. Not only did he not immediately charge forward, he stopped.

It was a 5v1 confrontation, but Tyranny unexpectedly didn’t immediately pounce on the opportunity.

“Tyranny is playing quite cautiously,” Pan Lin emphasized the word “quite”.

“What? No one’s coming?” Seeing how Tyranny wasn’t coming, Ye Xiu immediately started taunting them.

Tyranny’s players were old generals, plus with their familiarity with Ye Xiu’s personality, no one was bothered by this bit of taunting. Tyranny’s five players ignored him. Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun, the two Gunners, split to the left and right, expanding their team’s field of vision while forming a pincer towards Lord Grim. Han Wenqing, Lin Jingyan, and Zhang Xinjie formed a triangle. Desert Dust and Dark Thunder at the front, while Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock stood at the back. The three slowly advanced.

Tyranny wasn’t like before. In the past, the team would have charged forward as if they were trying to cut open a mountain. Now, they were gently carrying out their offense as if they were droplets of water grinding down stone. The current Tyranny was almost unrecognizable.

Ye Xiu didn’t continue with his trash talk. He had lord Grim retreat back.

He had no choice but to retreat.

Tyranny’s formation looked to be very simple, but Ye Xiu was able to tell that their formation could cover a large area. At the same time, they could shrink and extend freely, instantly converging into Tyranny’s specialty, a frontal assault.

“Looks like they’ve got a few new tricks up their sleeves.”

It seemed to be just a few simple adjustments, but it left a deep impression in Ye Xiu. He could see that this formation was finally bringing out Zhang Xinjie’s talents to the fullest. Zhang Xinjie’s style conflicted with Tyranny’s. After a series of adjustments from the team, they were beginning to assimilate together perfectly.

One of the four Master Tacticians, Zhang Xinjie.

The Zhang Xinjie who won the championships as a starter in the main roster in his first year.

His potential was still far from being cleanly realized!

Ye Xiu retreated.

He chose to retreat without even attempting anything.

He was clear and decisive, leaving the hesitation for Tyranny.

Lord Grim came alone. He obviously couldn’t 1v5, and it was obvious what Happy was planning.

Tyranny wasn’t familiar with the map, so they didn’t know what sort of ambushes Happy could set up. Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun scouted their two sides and confirmed that there was no possibility of a pincer. Tyranny had just come from the back. From how much time had passed, it wasn’t possible for Happy to have circled around them.

In that case, Ye Xiu had come alone to bait them into an ambush. Now that he had retreated, if Tyranny advanced forward, they would certainly be caught in an ambush. However, if they did not advance and stalled for time, they would give an opportunity for Happy to circle around them.

Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun had confirmed that their left and right sides were safe. The altar itself was a flat area, but there were numerous ambush spots in the surroundings. The altar wasn’t that large either, so using the surroundings as cover to set up an ambush was a big threat.

If Tyranny didn’t move, would Happy seize the opportunity to surround them?

No one could tell what plans the two teams had in mind. Everyone could only wait and see.

Tyranny didn’t move. Happy didn’t move.

Tyranny didn’t give chase. As a result, Ye Xiu didn’t have Lord Grim continue retreating. Happy’s four characters, who were hiding in the residential area, stayed still too.

The ten years of rivalry didn’t immediately set off blazing sparks, instead, the two sides were carefully probing each other’s actions. It had to be known that with their understanding of each other, neither side originally needed to do any probing to know the other side’s thoughts.

However, Ye Xiu had a new team behind him, and Han Wenqing’s unyielding fierceness that had been a part of him for ten years had begun to become more flexible.

The two pro players at the ends of their career, the two rivals of ten years were still as diligent as ever, looking for ways to break through.

It was because of this that the two sides were more careful. They wanted to be the first to see through their changed opponent, while not letting themselves be seen through.

Ye Xiu didn’t retreat. Han Wenqing didn’t advance. The confrontation lasted nearly 30 seconds, when suddenly, Tyranny headed diagonally in the 10 o’clock direction.

This movement had been as swift as the wind. Tyranny’s original style was instantly displayed. When the team had been making adjustments, they didn’t let go of their strongest and most reliable weapon.

However, Ye Xiu had seen this weapon many times and didn’t even raise an eyebrow towards it. Instead, when he saw the fierce charge, he smirked.

“What are you charging blindly for? You guys aren’t surrounded.” Ye Xiu typed into the chat.

How could he not see through Tyranny’s intent? The standoff was to let Happy make their setup. Then, before Happy could complete their encirclement, they would suddenly burst out and break through it.

“Yes, how could you not see it?” Zhang Xinjie replied.

“Then, what are you planning?” Ye Xiu asked.

“Positioning.” Zhang Xinjie replied.

Ye Xiu was surprised. When he took a look at Tyranny’s position right now, Tyranny was outside of the altar. Behind them was a flat path, which they could either advance or retreat from. To their left and right was the forest. Compared to their previous position at the center of the altar, they were much less in the open and in a far better position than before.

Li Yibo had analyzed as such. After listeners heard his analysis, they couldn’t help but question it.

Is that all?

Everyone thought to themselves.

All they did was move from one place to another, had Tyranny really needed to be so careful? If Tyranny had just strolled over, what would happen? Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim would rush at them and try to stop them?

That was what everyone else thought, but not Ye Xiu.

It was a very simple movement, but this simple movement showed Tyranny’s spirit.

The Tyranny of before had centered around their captain, Han Wenqing. The Tyranny of today had finally begun shifting their center towards their vice-captain, Zhang Xinjie.

Chapter 1504 - A Lot of Familiar Things

No openings.

Zhang Xinjie made the least amount of mistakes out of any player in the Glory Alliance, and this characteristic was one of his most notable strengths. Now, it was being realized in Team Tyranny’s tactics.

In the past, Tyranny’s bold and aggressive playstyle made it impossible not to make mistakes. As a result, they relied on overwhelming force to push their way through. But now, things were different.

By waiting for half a minute, not only did they not walk into a trap, they promptly interrupted a potential play from Happy before positioning themselves into a more open space, which allowed for them to retreat or advance as they wished. The hidden danger was silently resolved in this way.

Perhaps only someone like Ye Xiu, who had a deep understanding of Tyranny, could these sort of changes clearly.

After moving to the wide open street, Tyranny finally began scouting ahead.

Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust and Lin Jingyan’s Dark Forest at the front, Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms and Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees at the back on the left and right, respectively, and Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock at the center.

The team maintained this formation as they approached Lord Grim. With every step, they seemed to be finding new information.

Retreat?

With how calm and collected Tyranny was moving, retreating would not bait them into action.

Advance?

What good would that do? It wasn’t like he could charge in and 1v5!

However, Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim really did advance forward, matching their every step.

Before Tyranny’s fans could react to Ye Xiu’s insane decision, two players dashed out from Tyranny’s formation.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Negative Nine Degrees.

The two long-ranged gunners unexpectedly took the lead, while Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust and Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder continued to move forward at their original pace.

Gunfire burst forth. The two gunners focused their fire towards Lord Grim.

Retreat?

No, the two Gunners had blocked off the area behind Lord Grim. The two were sealing off his retreat path. Retreating would be exactly what they wanted.

Don’t retreat?

The moment the gunfire stopped Lord Grim from escaping, Desert Dust and Dark Thunder suddenly sped up, dashing towards Lord Grim.

An assault from all sides was completed in an instant!

“Beautiful!” Pan Lin cried out.

Ye Xiu’s response to this beautiful offensive was extremely simple. He opened up his umbrella as a shield and pointed it in Negative Nine Degrees’ direction.

Peng peng peng peng…

The bullets bouncing off of his umbrella sounded quite peculiar. With the bullets blocked, Lord Grim was about to stroll his way out of danger, when white flames suddenly burst from the ground.

Sacred Fire!

Taking advantage of the fact that Ye Xiu’s vision was blocked from his own umbrella shield, Zhang Xinjie cast a Sacred Fire, surrounding Lord Grim in white flames.

Three seconds of Silence, three seconds of opportunity!

In an instant, dazzling light swallowed the area. Lord Grim’s figure became blurry as Desert Dust and Dark Thunder dashed into the light.

The crowd let out a cry of surprise.

Tyranny’s sudden burst of speed from their initial slow and methodical manner was truly shocking.

Tyranny’s tactics had become more varied. Not only did it not weaken their offense, it upped their explosiveness by another level through an abrupt change in tempo. In addition, their change in tactics didn’t leave behind a single opening.

To allow for a sudden increase in tempo, every step need to be carefully thought out for there to be not opening.

Sharpshooter attacks were single-target attacks and were very easy to block with a shield. So what if you blocked them? There’s a Sacred Fire laying in wait!

Facing such a watertight arrangement, even if the experienced Ye Xiu could see through it, what could he do? There was simply no way to break out.

“Ye Xiu got careless!” Even Li Yibo, who had become even more careful for this match, dared to criticize Ye Xiu.

That was what everyone else was thinking too.

Going alone to challenge an entire team was brave, but challenging the team and then getting killed for it was embarrassing.

Ye Xiu was in an extremely dangerous and embarrassing situation, yet… there were still no signs of movement from the rest of Happy.

The broadcast had split the screen to show the perspectives of the four players on Happy, and they could definitely see Lord Grim’s predicament. However, to everyone’s surprise, they stuck to their original plan and didn’t go over to help.

They can’t be that inflexible, can they? It was hard to avoid asking this question.

It was true that pre-match preparations were important, but the other 70% of the match depended on the team’s response to the circumstances of the match. There was no team who would do nothing seeing this situation.

Unless… they were confident that they needed to make any moves.

The camera once again locked onto Lord Grim.

Lord Grim had already been swallowed by the Hundred Blossoms style, and Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan needed only a few more steps to reach him. During these 3 seconds, Lord Grim wouldn’t be able to use any skills. Inside the light, a blurry shape could be seen spinning round and round in a circle.

How long could 3 seconds be?

After a few circles, the blurry figure in the light suddenly sped up. In the next instant, Lord Grim could be seen clear as day in front of everyone.

Lord Grim had escaped from the Hundred Blossoms besiegement, while under the three seconds of Silence from Sacred Fire.

The crowd was silent in shock.

A replay quickly appeared on the big screen. This time, the camera zoomed in, paying close attention to Lord Grim.

All sorts of bullets and grenades had been thrown at Lord Grim. Lord Grim couldn’t use any skills. He could only wave around the umbrella in his hands, blocking what he could as he moved. Three seconds later, through a skill that increased his movement speed, he broke out from the Hundred Blossoms style.

The viewers continued to be at a loss. Despite seeing the slow-motion replay, they still couldn’t understand. How could he escape by just blocking a few attacks?

Only Zhang Jiale understood. Only the person who created the Hundred Blossoms style could.

Only he knew that Lord Grim’s spinning umbrella wasn’t just to block some damage, it was to block the attacks that the Hundred Blossoms style used to restrict the opponent.

It was because he blocked those few skills that the light of the Hundred Blossoms style still existed, yet did little to obstruct its target. After the Sacred Fire wore off, Ye Xiu immediately rushed out with a movement skill, leaving Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan in the dust.

In other words, even though Tyranny’s tactics had no openings, Zhang Jiale’s Hundred Blossoms style had been seen through by Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu’s understanding of Zhang Jiale was not much worse than his understanding of his long-time rival Han Wenqing.

The Hundred Blossoms style? Not just this season, just counting the past, it had been around for a whole six years.

As Zhang Jiale’s attitude changed, the Hundred Blossoms style had also changed, but no matter how much the style changed, there were only so many Spitfire skills. By understanding the purpose of each skill, it was often possible to counter the style.

The theory sounded simple, but there were only a handful who could do it in practice.

Ye Xiu had done it because of his understanding of the style and his experience. After seeing the role of each player in Tyranny’s formation, he was able to immediately deduce Zhang Jiale’s aim during this period of time.

As for how Zhang Jiale would use his skills, with how diverse the Hundred Blossoms style was, there was no way for Ye Xiu to predict it 100%, but he could at least make the mental preparations to defend against the most important attacks. The other part was that Lord Grim had a very big shield.

Lord Grim rushed out from the encirclement and swiftly retreated. Tyranny’s two long-ranged characters chased after him, but the tempo of the two Fighters immediately slowed.

They didn’t pursue him relentlessly because they didn’t forget that the other four members of Happy were very likely lying in wait for them here.

As a result, once Lord Grim escaped from Tyranny’s attack range, Tyranny slowed down as a whole. They went back into a stable formation and slowly approached one step at a time.

Patience. They were playing very patiently.

They had been dreaming of winning the championships for so many years. What was a few seconds of patience to them?

Tyranny steadily pushed forward, making Ye Xiu’s challenge towards them seem childish. Even if had escaped from what Li Yibo thought as impossible to escape from, in terms of energy, Tyranny had the upper hand.

Li Yibo had just been slapped in the face. His mood wasn’t good, and he didn’t want to speak anymore. The majority of people in the stadium were Happy fans. They had been worried seeing that scene. They couldn’t understand why no one in Happy did anything to help. What was Happy’s plan?

No instructions had been typed into Happy’s team chat, which meant that everything so far had been a part of Happy’s pre-match plans. Their strategy seemed to be to lure the opponents deep into their territory, but seeing Tyranny now, they definitely weren’t going to fall into that sort of trap. Even so, Happy was insistent on following with their plans.

“What are they doing?” Even Huang Shaotian couldn’t understand. He messaged Yu Wenzhou.

“Maybe they wanted to have a better feel for Tyranny’s tactical structure?” Yu Wenzhou wasn’t certain either.

“In that case, did they need to do that?”

“If they didn’t do it that way, who else besides Ye Xiu could escape from that sort of predicament?” Yu Wenzhou replied.

Huang Shaotian held his cellphone in his hands for a long time, but he didn’t reply.

Everyone would always ask this question to themselves subconsciously.

Escape from the Hundred Blossoms style the way Ye Xiu did?

Extremely difficult.

Huang Shaotian had a certain level of understanding of the Hundred Blossoms style, but not to the same level of depth as Ye Xiu.

Troubling Rain didn’t have a shield either, so it would be much harder for him to block attacks.

Break through the Hundred Blossoms style while Silenced, only by dodging and blocking?

Extremely difficult was one way to put it, but that was because there was no such thing as impossible!

If he had been in Ye Xiu’s position, he would most likely have died…

Chapter 1505 - Waiting at the Ambush Area

Was Ye Xiu trying to get a feel for the new Tyranny?

After the discussion with Yu Wenzhou, Huang Shaotian began observing Lord Grim more closely.

Tyranny did not react in the slightest towards his provocation, playing extremely patiently. As a result, Ye Xiu had also slowed down.

Retreat. Lord Grim retreated. The pace of his retreat just happened to match the pace of Tyranny’s advance. Not everyone could see this point, or at least, when Pan Lin and Li Yibo talked about this topic, they simply said that Ye Xiu was starting to become more cautious.

Yes, he was being cautious, but for what reason?

To continue getting a feel for Tyranny.

He had been getting a feel for their offense. Now, he was getting a feel for their defense.

“He’s getting a feel for Tyranny’s tempo switch.” This time, Yu Wenzhou messaged Huang Shaotian.

Tempo switch.

Normal players might only have an idea of what it was, but pro players would immediately understand if they heard this phrase.

To put it simply, it was referring to the switch in tempo between attack and defense. It couldn’t be too flat or too exaggerated. It had to be just right.

Ye Xiu was constantly adjusting his own tempo to produce a change in Tyranny’s tempo. From this, he could grasp new information on Tyranny.

“This isn’t to win the match, but to win the set.” Yu Wenzhou typed again.

Huang Shaotian understood this point. Tyranny had constantly been rotating their roster throughout the regular season. It was only until the end of the season did the old generals of Tyranny start coming out together. However, everyone knew that those games were just as a warm-up. Their full capabilities would only be revealed in the playoffs. How had Tyranny changed over the course of this season? The only way to find out was to personally experience it, which was why Ye Xiu didn’t hesitate to take these risks alone. In terms of tactics, it was very risky. But from a strategic standpoint, it would likely prove to be useful in the future.

But would Tyranny let Ye Xiu see everything so easily?

The two Gunners in Tyranny suddenly rushed out again.

Bang bang bang!

The gunfire criss crossed towards Lord Grim. This time, Ye Xiu was ready. As soon as he saw the two dash out, he swiftly retreated.

The broadcast rotated through the four players on Happy lying in wait.

Happy’s ambush area was not far now. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim was retreating towards this area. Would Tyranny walk in to the ambush?

No?

The two Gunners forced Lord Grim to retreat to show that he was not welcome. Tyranny had no intentions of relentlessly pursuing him. As a result, when Lord Grim retreated into the ambush area, Tyranny was still a fair distance away!

Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan didn’t move forward. Only Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun, the two long-ranged characters, attacked from afar. The team didn’t enter into the ambush, instead using their long range to harass Lord Grim.

Even though Lord Grim had long-ranged attacks too, how could he compare to two genuine Gunners? There was no way he could compete with them. He could only continue retreating.

Team Tyranny was unexpectedly using long-ranged classes to open their path forward, while the melee classes stayed at the back to provide support. Even so, this unconventional formation worked perfectly in this situation. Even if the long-ranged characters fell for an ambush, they wouldn’t be as deep into it as the melee characters.

Lord Grim had retreated deep into the ambush.

The houses in the residential area were established on verdant and lush trees. Many of the houses on the trees were covered by leaves and were well-hidden. With one glance, it was obvious that this place was perfect for setting up ambushes. After Zhang Xinjie gave a warning in the chat, even Zhang Jiale and Qin Muyun stopped chasing after Lord Grim.

“You’re not going to heal?” Zhang Jiale asked Ye Xiu in the public chat.

“Not rush,” Ye Xiu replied. Don’t look at how he had never directly engaged in a prolonged fight with Tyranny. He had lost a considerable amount of health during his retreat. He only had 47% of his health left, not even half.

He was half-dead, yet Tyranny still didn’t push forward to kill him. Their patience and perseverance were terrifying.

Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock moved to the front. He looked around. Just like this, he stood outside of Happy’s ambush range and calmly observed his surroundings.

“Happy’s overreaching themselves!” Pan Lin said.

Even if this was a team competition map, it wasn’t so large that it couldn’t be explored. If Tyranny continued to slowly take in their surroundings, they would quickly see what areas to look out for. The person making the observations was the Master Tactician, Zhang Xinjie, the Zhang Xinjie who never let out an opening and never missed details.

Immovable Rock suddenly raised his hands, pointing towards a direction.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms raised his arms and tossed a grenade in that direction.

Boom!

The grenade flew in a beautiful arc, but halfway through, the grenade suddenly exploded. Fire rained down. Dazzling Hundred Blossoms had tossed a Burst Grenade.

“Haha, sorry!” Ye Xiu apologized in the public chat. On the other end of the forest, smoke rose from the tip of Lord Grim’s umbrella. He had shot down the grenade.

Suddenly, Lin Jingyan raised his arm. What appeared to be a wine bottle flew in that direction.

“Are you testing me?” Ye Xiu even had the time to type out a message. Lord Grim lifted his umbrella and with a bang, the wine bottle shattered into pieces. Flames rained down and spread onto the ground.

“Are you trying to set the forest on fire? That’s a bit difficult,” Ye Xiu typed.

The broadcast coordinated with the conversation between the players. As Ye Xiu said these words, the camera zoomed in on the fire on the ground. Sure enough, the fire produced by these skills didn’t last for long before dissipating.

“A better idea would be to learn from Huang Shaotian and cut down these trees instead.” Ye Xiu suggested.

“That motherfucker!” Huang Shaotian was just watching the match, and shots were being fired at him. He quickly expressed his inner resentment in the form of a message for Yu Wenzhou.

Tyranny remained indifferent towards Ye Xiu’s words. Not a single person in the team replied back. Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock continued to observe his surroundings, while communicating the information he got into Tyranny’s team chat.

Ye Xiu didn’t know, but the viewers could see it.

Not only did the viewers know what Tyranny was discussing, they even knew where the other four members of Happy were hiding. Tyranny was discussing where the other members of Happy were likely hiding at. Usually, they would analyze it based off their classes to see what locations would be most advantageous for them.

The likely hiding spots of Happy’s four characters were being deduced. The viewers checked, all correct! Happy’s current hiding spots were within Tyranny’s analysis.

From there, they took the analysis a step further and eliminated the less probable hiding spots.

They did this step by looking at the habits and styles of each player. The player’s style would also decide what type of position best suited them.

After eliminating half of the possibilities, the viewers checked again, all correct!

Terrifying!

Too terrifying!

The stadium was completely silent. Let alone fighting, there was almost no movement whatsoever. Four little squares were sectioned off on the screen, showing each of Happy’s four characters. Whenever Tyranny mentioned the location of these Happy members, the camera would immediately zoom in on the square. The broadcast seemed to be coordinating with Tyranny’s team chat, drawing a diagram for the viewers to see.

However, by doing this, the viewers felt an even stronger sense of chilliness. Tyranny’s strong logic had unraveled Happy’s ambush.

After filtering out the hiding spots by player style and class, they filtered it even further by their offensive and defensive coordination, formation, etc.

In the end, they concluded six possibilities for the four hiding spots. They couldn’t be certain about the two extra, but this was already incredible because Happy’s true hiding spots were all within these six possibilities. As Tyranny narrowed down the search, the audience members in the away team seats were clapping wildly. Every time the analysis was spot on, the applause would reach a new high. As for Happy’s fans? They were dead silent.

Happy’s opponents stood right in front of them, unraveling Happy’s plans bit by bit, yet not a single sign of movement could be seen coming from Happy.

Was this a contest of patience?

But the other side isn’t competing with you in terms of patience! You guys are waiting patiently, but the other side has already completely seen through everything!

If the ambush was seen through, then it was no longer an ambush. Tyranny quickly formulated an attack plan based off of their deductions.

Bang bang bang!

The sounds of gunfire.

The two Gunners led the attack. They ignored Lord Grim, who was directly facing them. Instead, they aimed at trees that appeared to have noone there.

Dancing Rain!

Tyranny just happened to attack where Dancing Rain was. They didn’t attack the important healer, nor the average-skilled rookie Luo Ji, who was coming out onto the playoffs stage for the first time. Tyranny’s first target was the experienced Su Mucheng, the Launcher who held the range advantage.

It seemed to be a stupid choice, but the viewers understood the reason clearly.

Because they had seen the analysis by Tyranny.

There was only one reason for picking Dancing Rain as their first target: Dancing Rain’s position was the position that they were most certain of!

Reliable and never making mistakes, the style of Zhang Xinjie!

Chapter 1506 - The Possibility of Mistake

The dusky forest brightened, illuminating a path from Tyranny’s formation.

Zhang Jiale!

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms!

Hundred Blossoms Style! Offense and defense together. By the time the viewers regained their composure, Desert Dust and Dark Thunder had vanished. Only their shadows could be seen flickering in the light.

The two had charged forward alongside Dazzling Hundred Blossom’s attacks.

Tyranny’s fans instantly became excited.

“Holy Trinity!” The Tyranny fans cheered.

Holy Trinity.

Han Wenqing, Zhang Jiale, and Lin Jingyan. These three old generals of Tyranny had been fighting each other all the way from season two to season nine. At the end of their careers, the three unexpectedly became teammates, gathering together under Tyranny. They were even able to create their own unique offensive formation, which Tyranny nicknamed the Holy Trinity. The name showed just how much synergy there was between them.

The people who understood you the best were your own enemies.

These words suited these three perfectly. From enemies to teammates, being able to create their own set of tactics so quickly was because of their many years of experience as opponents.

At this moment, Tyranny officially began their offensive. The Holy Trinity that had the Tyranny fans go wild last season had reappeared. As for this season, because of their frequent rotations, the three old generals rarely appeared together on stage. The Tyranny fans had been waiting to see this scene for too too long.

现在他们终于等到了,三位一体的攻势,看不出有任何生疏.

Their hopes had finally been realized. The Holy Trinity didn’t seem to be out of practice at all.

Just as the fans were getting excited, another shadow flickered into their view.

Negative Nine Degrees, Qin Muyun. Tyranny’s fifth player, the fifth player who was overshadowed by the Gods around him, had intruded into this picturesque scene. He didn’t match the pace of the other three. His pace seemed completely out of place in comparison.

However, the true experts immediately could immediately feel the improvement in Team Tyranny as a whole.

The Holy Trinity, it still comprised of the same three players. However, there was now a new helper alongside them.

Qin Muyun was outstanding at positioning. He kept weaving in and out between the Holy Trinity, his gaze and gun aimed at spots that could potentially mean trouble for the formation.

It was just that no trouble had occurred yet, so Negative Nine Degrees looked somewhat comical as if he were delusional. But this was Zhang Xinjie’s style: it was better to be safe than sorry. His every move blocked any potential areas that could disrupt their plans.

Shortly afterwards, the Holy Trinity had reached their destination. Cannonfire could already be heard in the forest. Tyranny’s guess had been correct. Su Mucheng obviously wasn’t going to sit there and wait for her death to come. Dancing Rain fired a few shots at the light cover, borrowing the recoil to move.

Aerial Cannon. It was difficult to change directions while using Aerial Cannon, so it wasn’t too suitable for this map. However, with this being Happy’s home map, Su Mucheng was evidently very familiar with this area of the map. As Dancing Rain used Aerial cannon, she accurately calculated the glide distance and direction every time, intentionally bumping into trees to change directions.

After a few shots, Dancing Rain pulled away from Tyranny’s formation.

Bang bang bang bang!

Gunshots suddenly rang in the air.

Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees suddenly fired towards a direction.

Enemy attack?

No!

The slower viewers weren’t sure what was happening. On the other hand, the more attentive viewers quickly realized that Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees was firing at one of the six potential hiding spots that Tyranny had conjectured.

There’s no one there!

The viewers could see where Happy’s members were located and knew the answer. Even so, by checking with his attacks, he helped Tyranny eliminate this possibility.

As a result, apart from the already exposed Dancing Rain, there were only four guesses and three characters left.

Tyranny was in no hurry though.

Tyranny had already reached this far in, was Happy still going to do nothing? If they made some adjustments, they might make Tyranny to predict wrongly. Thus, Tyranny didn’t make any rash movements and focused on Dancing Rain.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms’ offensive kept her under control. The bright lights kept interfering with Dancing Rain’s sight, making it difficult for her to see Tyranny’s pathing. Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan quickly closed in under this light cover.

“Be careful of Ye Xiu!” Zhang Xinjie reminded everyone.

Ye Xiu moved!

He saw that Su Mucheng’s situation wasn’t looking too good. Lord Grim went over to provide support.

Bang bang bang bang!

Another round of gunfire.

It was Qin Muyun’s job to stop Ye Xiu from helping her out. He didn’t need Zhang Xinjie’s warning. He had taken note of Ye Xiu. As soon as he saw Lord Grim move, he didn’t hesitate to attack.

Lord Grim fled behind a tree. Under such heavy gunfire, he couldn’t easily expose himself. He could use his shield to tank the hits, but Lord Grim didn’t have that much health right now. His shield only reduced the damage too. It didn’t negate it.

“Beautiful!” Zhang Jiale praised in the chat as Dazzling Hundred Blossoms attacked even more fiercely.

Zhang Xinjie wasn’t moved by the current situation. He continued to be cautious, paying close attention to those calm areas.

It was too calm.

The battle had already developed to this stage, yet Happy still wasn’t going to act? Were they really going to test Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng and hope for the two to escape on their own?

If Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng failed to escape and died here, the match would be over!

Could I have missed something?

Zhang Xinjie never made mistakes?

That was what people thought of Zhang Xinjie, but Zhang Xinjie himself never felt like he never made mistakes. He simply did his best to think of all aspects before making a decision… others might not see any mistakes, but that was because he was constantly thinking of what could go wrong.

He never let down his guard at any moment.

He always thought of what could go wrong at any moment.

The calmness from Happy gave him that sort of feeling.

Zhang Xinjie wasn’t someone who made decisions based purely off of intuition. This feeling was based on logic: if Happy didn’t make any changes, they would certainly lose, so it didn’t make sense that Happy would make no changes.

Where?

Zhang Xinjie made sure to keep up with the team’s tempo, while continuing to observe his surroundings.

Over there!

Just when Zhang Xinjie turned to look over there, he immediately turned back and had Immovable Rock perform a roll.

There was no sound, no light, but did that mean nothing had happened?

The moment Immovable Rock left that spot, the branches and leaves on the ground were suddenly swept up by the wind.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

The Qi Master’s Cloud Grasping Fist!

Happy’s Fang Rui, the master of playing dirty, had begun his own individual operation as soon as Tyranny entered their ambush area. He was very patient. Even when Tyranny had nearly cornered Su Mucheng, even when Ye Xiu had been prevented from helping her, he hadn’t made his move.

Because what he wanted wasn’t just to give Tyranny a bit of an inconvenience. He wanted to completely disrupt the entire Tyranny with a single move.

He had fixed his sights on Zhang Xinjie, on the important healer.

He had been waiting, waiting for an opportunity to act. From the very beginning, he had planned on stealthily grabbing Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock with a Cloud Grasping Fist.

That was why he ignored Su Mucheng’s and Ye Xiu’s predicament.

Only those sorts of predicaments could catch Tyranny’s attention and lower their guard towards their healer.

These types of ambushes were Fang Rui’s specialty. His judgement was correct. When Qin Muyun began targeting Ye Xiu to stop him from helping Su Mucheng, Tyranny’s attention was almost entirely fixed on the fight over there.

As a result, Fang Rui made his move. Following Immovable Rock, Boundless Sea found a perfect position.

Then, he casted, prayed for good luck, and acted…

However, in the final moments, Fang Rui hadn’t expected Zhang Xinjie to sense it.

The Cloud Grasping Fist missed, exposing his position. Even though he was facing a Cleric, who posed no offensive threat, Fang Rui felt like he had been stripped naked. It was as if nothing could escape from Zhang Xinjie’s notice.

Fine, if an ambush isn’t going to work, then I’ll just go to you!

Boundless Sea unexpectedly rushed forward. The Cloud Grasping Fist had missed, so his new plan was to kidnap Immovable Rock directly.

Zhang Xinjie immediately had Immovable Rock retreat. Tyranny’s other players obviously received the signal. In an instant, the Hundred Blossom style enveloped Immovable Rock. Then, the light and Immovable Rock vanished.

“What! Is this a magic trick? Are you sure you aren’t a Magician?” Fang Rui spat out. He immediately changed his plans. He couldn’t catch Immovable Rock, so he began attacking Qin Muyun’s Negative Nine Degrees. The guy had firepower though. Fang Rui couldn’t fight him out in the open, so he relied on his familiarity with the terrain to begin playing dirty.

Qi Bullet!

Boundless Sea suddenly reached out with his hands and fired a Qi Bullet from behind a tree.

Qin Muyun didn’t dodge and let the Qi Bullet hit Negative Nine Degrees.

He was ready to guard against a follow-up from behind that tree, when a storm of qi came from the other direction.

Sky Piercing Cannon!

The wave of qi sent branches and leaves flying. It was obvious where it was coming from. The attack seemed to be saying to him: you little punk, let’s see you tank this one…

Chapter 1507 - Neither Side Willing to Take a Step

Sky Piercing Cannon!

You could ignore the damage dealt by the skill, but you could not ignore its knockback. If you tanked the skill without Super Armor, you would certainly be sent flying.

Qin Muyun had Negative Nine Degrees dodge and counterattack simultaneously. But when he glanced behind him, his heart tightened.

He had dodged Sky-Piercing Cannon, but the surging qi was now heading towards one of his allies.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms!

Zhang Jiale’s Dazzling Hundred Blossoms.

Sure enough, Fang Rui’s harassment was shameless and dirty. If the attack onto Negative Nine Degrees missed, there was a fallback. It was very clear why he picked those two targets too.

If he hit Negative Nine Degrees, he would reduce the pressure on Ye Xiu.

Hitting Dazzling Hundred Blossoms would be even better. The Hundred Blossoms style was a hindrance towards both Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng.

“!” Qin Muyun didn’t know whether Zhang Jiale noticed it or not and quickly warned him. He didn’t have time to type any words.

Zhang Jiale hadn’t noticed it, but Qin Muyun’s warning was prompt enough. Not just Zhang JIale, but Han Wenqing and Lin Jingyan dodged as soon as they saw the warning.

Dazzling Hundred Blossoms flopped like a fish and rolled, dodging the Sky-Piercing Cannon.

Qin Muyun let out a sigh of relief. However, Fang Rui’s Boundless Sea had disappeared. He didn’t know where he would come out from next time. Qin Muyun started feeling nervous. This was his responsibility, but Fang Rui’s dirtiness was difficult for him to deal with.

It took a long time for talents to grow. Compared to other rookies, he was more mature and rational. From the day he became part of Tyranny’s main roster, he knew that he would not be the lead role on stage. At that time, Team Tyranny had shined the brightest in all of Glory. Legendary names that would go down in Glory history had gathered togther in this team.

Qin Muyun became the fifth player alongside them.

Other rookies might feel pressured under these circumstances, but Qin Muyun did not. He figured out his own role in the team. In this group filled with stars, he didn’t need to shine any brighter. Perhaps being put out of the spotlight would allow him to bring out more of his potential.

As a result, Qin Muyun began his career as an invisible existence. For the rookies of this day and age, perhaps none of them would be happy about such a situation. They wanted to hurry and show everyone their talent, so that everyone would recognize their worth.

Qin Muyun was different.

Just like this, he finished an entire season in the dark. His numbers weren’t spectacular, and he never made any highlight plays in the regular season. However, he was still a part of the main roster. No matter how invisible he may seem, Qin Muyun was confident in his own contributions to the team. His own value would not be neglected. Team Tyranny had Zhang Xinjie, who would never overlook anything. With this vice-captain, Qin Muyun could safely compete with his own style. He didn’t need to worry about whether the team would forget about him.

Qin Muyun succeeded.

Even if he hadn’t received any attention for a long time, as part of the main roster for a season, just that fact alone was enough for people to no longer ignore him.

Qin Muyun continued to hide under the radiance of the Gods around him, but his existence was no longer ignored.

As a result, his playstyle was no longer as suitable this season because their opponents were taking note of him. A player with a steady position in Tyranny’s main roster could not be neglected.

The space that he had due to being ignored was gone. Qin Muyun had no choice but to adapt to the new circumstances.

He could no longer hide. He needed to use his own abilities to make the Gods shine even brighter.

His role was to patch up the gaps in the Holy Trinity.

But facing Fang Rui, Qin Muyun was worried whether he would be able to complete this task. This master of playing dirty was too crafty. Although Lin Jingyan, whose used to be old partners with Fang Rui, had told him much of Fang Rui’s methods and habits, hihs class change made it difficult to rely on just these to keep up with Fang Rui. Tyranny’s heroes were incompatible with his dirtiness. They couldn’t keep up with Fang Rui’s thoughts.

Where is he?

Negative Nine Degrees kept looking. He had outstanding positioning and was good at finding potential trouble spots, but after his misplaced judgement of Fang Rui’s previous move, his confidence was starting to falter.

“Don’t panic!” Zhang Xinjie’s message popped out in the chat. He could tell that Qin Muyun was nervous. Tyranny mainly consisted of experienced veterans. However, their one inexperienced player’s spirit had been disrupted by Fang Rui’s sneak attack.

“I’m coming.” Another person typed.

Lin Jingyan’s Dark Thunder ran towards that area. The Holy Trinity formation had been temporarily disbanded. Han Wenqing and Zhang Jiale were enough to pressure Su Mucheng. When he saw that Qin Muyun was having trouble dealing with Ye Xiu and Fang Rui, he chose to stop what he was doing and help him. Fang Rui was undoubtedly a target that he was familiar with. Dark Thunder turned towards a certain direction.

Sure enough, Boundless Sea was in that direction. Fang Rui was helpless. His old partner knew him too well. Boundless Sea suppressed the rising qi that he had gathered and examined the situation again.

Fang Rui was observing the situation. It was the same for Zhang Xinjie.

Three of Happy’s players were visible. Su Mucheng had been isolated. Ye Xiu was trying to re-establish contact with her, while Fang Rui was trying to disrupt Tyranny’s tempo.

There was no tactical coordination between any of them. Su Mucheng, Ye Xiu, and Fang Rui were doing their own thing. This clearly wasn’t the purpose for setting up an ambush.

Had the ambush already been resolved?

In that case, what about Luo Ji? An Wenyi?

Zhang Xinjie didn’t neglect the potential hiding spots that they had ascertained, but there were no movements from there. The battle on this end had fully developed. There was no extra manpower to check those spots.

Should we continue with our offensive?

Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock had shifted towards this end. No large changes had occurred yet. However, Ye Xiu’s and Su Mucheng’s abilities weren’t just this. With Lin Jingyan shifting his attention to Fang Rui, the pressure onto them should have been greatly reduced. The deadlock should have been broken.

It was true that Lin Jingyan was an effective answer for Fang Rui, but at the same time, Zhang Xinjie took another look at Happy.

Happy still had two players who had not yet showed their faces, so the hidden dangers had not been completely eliminated. Fang Rui’s harassment gave Happy some space. He wanted to use this time to observe Happy’s movements and hopefully reveal all of Happy’s cards.

With support from Dazzling Hundred Blossoms, Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was getting closer and closer to Dancing Rain. Even though he hadn’t launched any attacks yet, his push forward was far more threatening to Su Mucheng than Zhang Jiale’s attacks.

If Han Wenqing’s Desert Dust was able to get close to her, the only outcome for her Launcher was death.

Retreat, keep retreating.

Su Mucheng didn’t seem to have found a way to escape. She could only keep on retreating and maintaining a distance between them.

As she retreated, Han Wenqing and Zhang Jiale advanced. Zhang Xinjie’s Immovable Rock also had to follow his team.

The entirety of Tyranny was being pulled deeper into the residential area. The players could already see numerous treehouses on top of the trees.

They weren’t just following Dancing Rain blindly. The team maintained their formation. As Dancing Rain retreated deeper into the area, they had tried to surround Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim. But in the end, Ye Xiu was able to see through their intentions. Tyranny’s formation was still intact though. Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim failed to reach Dancing Rain, but his presence made it such that Tyranny could not let out any openings. Lin Jingyan and Fang Rui were following along with the paces of their respective teams, keeping their opponent in check and moving.

The atmosphere in the stadium was very strange.

The two sides could take a step and change the situation, but neither of them did so.

In the end, Tyranny didn’t open up their offensive, while Happy didn’t do everything they could to save Su Mucheng. Both sides seemed to be using 70% of their strength. The remaining 30% made the viewers feel extremely anxious.

“The match is still in the observation stage!” Yu Wenzhou messaged Huang Shaotian.

Previously, he had felt that Ye Xiu wanted to get a feel for Tyranny for the sake of the set win. But now, from the looks of it, Tyranny’s Zhang Xinjie also wanted to get a solid grasp on Happy before making his move.

What is Happy planning?

Yu Wenzhou was also puzzled. Unfortunately, even having an omniscient view of the battle didn’t help. The commentators could not see the problem either.

Who would be the first to break the balance?

This was the crucial question. Both sides wanted to react to their opponent’s actions. It depended on who would be more patient.

However, from the current situation, even if Happy wanted to be patient, the situation might not let them.

This was the terrifying part about Zhang Xinjie. His tactics were never dirty. He used oppressive strength to pressure the opponent to force the opponents into doing what he wanted. This tactical style had grown relying on Tyranny’s powerful offensive capabilities.

“Is Happy not able to think of a solution?” Pan Lin cried out. For the people who weren’t able to see deep enough, Happy was at a disadvantage. Tyranny was forcing them back step by step. If Happy could not find a way to break through the situation, they would be forced into action.

Come! Show me your cards!

Happy’s plan couldn’t just be an ambush, right? Why bring a Summoner in this map?

Zhang Xinjie was looking forward to what awaited him.